{
    "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYSBzdGFuZGFyZCBzZXQgb2YgcGxheWluZyBjYXJkcywgd2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkga2luZyB3aXRob3V0IGEgbW91c3RhY2hlPw==",
            "answer": "SGVhcnRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcml2ZXIgZmxvd3MgdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgU2NvdHRpc2ggY2l0eSBvZiBHbGFzZ293Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2x5ZGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvLWdhbWUgZnJhbmNoaXNlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzLCB0aGUgbWFpbiBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCwgY2FycmllcyBhIHdlYXBvbiB3aXRoIHdoYXQgc2hhcGU/",
            "answer": "S2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmaW5pbmcgY2hhcmFjdGVyaXN0aWMgb2Ygc29tZW9uZSB3aG8gaXMgZGVzY3JpYmVkIGFzIGhpcnN1dGU/",
            "answer": "SGFpcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgZnVuYW1idWxpc3Qgd2FsayBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QSBUaWdodCBSb3Bl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlR5cGV3cml0ZXIiIGlzIHRoZSBsb25nZXN0IHdvcmQgdGhhdCBjYW4gYmUgdHlwZWQgdXNpbmcgb25seSB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgcm93IG9uIGEgUVdFUlRZIGtleWJvYXJkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBkb2N0b3Igd2l0aCBhIFBoRCBpcyBhIGRvY3RvciBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UGhpbG9zb3BoeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBvcmdhbiBvZiB0aGUgaHVtYW4gYm9keT8=",
            "answer": "U2tpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gcHJlc2lkZW50IGFwcGVhcnMgb24gYSBvbmUgZG9sbGFyIGJpbGw/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyAiZGFiYmluZyI/",
            "answer": "QSBkYW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgcmh5dGhtIGdhbWVzIHdhcyBtYWRlIGJ5IEhhcm1vbml4Pw==",
            "answer": "Um9jayBCYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RnVyYnkgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDE5OTgu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhICJkYWtpbWFrdXJhIj8=",
            "answer": "QSBib2R5IHBpbGxvdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxMyBob3cgbXVjaCBtb25leSB3YXMgbG9zdCBieSBOaWdlcmlhbiBzY2Ftcz8=",
            "answer": "JDEyLjcgQmlsbGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgIm5ld3MiIG9yaWdpbmF0ZXMgZnJvbSB0aGUgZmlyc3QgbGV0dGVycyBvZiB0aGUgNCBtYWluIGRpcmVjdGlvbnMgb24gYSBjb21wYXNzIChOb3J0aCwgRWFzdCwgV2VzdCwgU291dGgpLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhbiBleGlzdGluZyBmYW1pbHkgaW4gIlRoZSBTaW1zIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdvdGggRmFtaWx5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbGNvaG9saWMgZHJpbmsgaXMgbWFpbmx5IG1hZGUgZnJvbSBqdW5pcGVyIGJlcnJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2lu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBvbiBkaXNwbGF5IGluIHRoZSBNYWRhbWUgVHVzc2F1ZCdzIG11c2V1bSBpbiBMb25kb24/",
            "answer": "V2F4IHNjdWxwdHVyZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgU3dlZGlzaCB3b3JkIGZvciAid2luZG93Ij8=",
            "answer": "RsO2bnN0ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbXVzaWNpYW4gaGFzIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRlZCB3aXRoIEFtZXJpY2FuIHByb2R1Y2VyIFBvcnRlciBSb2JpbnNvbiBhbmQgcmVsZWFzZWQgdGhlIDIwMTYgc29uZyAiU2hlbHRlciI/",
            "answer": "TWFkZW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T24gYXZlcmFnZSwgYXQgbGVhc3QgMSBwZXJzb24gaXMga2lsbGVkIGJ5IGEgZHJ1bmsgZHJpdmVyIGluIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIGV2ZXJ5IGhvdXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S2lzc2luZyBzb21lb25lIGZvciBvbmUgbWludXRlIGJ1cm5zIGFib3V0IDIgY2Fsb3JpZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCB3b3JkIHRvIHRyYXZlbCBpcyAiVHJhdmFpbCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBsZXR0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIEdyZWVrIGFscGhhYmV0Pw==",
            "answer": "T21lZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIGluIEF1c3RyYWxpYS4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIFN3ZWRpc2ggY29tcGFuaWVzIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIDE5NDM/",
            "answer": "SUtFQQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGUgRWVtaG9mLCBQb3J0IFplbGFuZGUgYW5kIEhldCBIZWlqZGVyYm9zIGFyZSBob2xpZGF5IHZpbGxhcyBvd25lZCBieSB3aGF0IGNvbXBhbnk/",
            "answer": "Q2VudGVyIFBhcmNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmVzdGF1cmFudCdzIG1hc2NvdCBpcyBhIGNsb3duPw==",
            "answer": "TWNEb25hbGQncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaWNvbmljIERpc25leWxhbmQgYXR0cmFjdGlvbiB3YXMgY2xvc2VkIGluIDIwMTcgdG8gYmUgcmVtb2RlbGVkIGFzIGEgIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5IiB0aGVtZWQgcmlkZT8=",
            "answer": "VHdpbGlnaHQgWm9uZSBUb3dlciBvZiBUZXJyb3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBMYXRpbiBwaHJhc2UgIlZlbmksIHZpZGksIHZpY2kiIHRyYW5zbGF0ZSBpbnRvIEVuZ2xpc2g/",
            "answer": "SSBjYW1lLCBJIHNhdywgSSBjb25xdWVyZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3RhZ2Vjb2FjaCBvd25lZCAiU291dGggV2VzdCBUcmFpbnMiIGJlZm9yZSBsb3NpbmcgdGhlIHJpZ2h0cyB0byBGaXJzdEdyb3VwIGFuZCBNVFIgaW4gTWFyY2ggb2YgMjAxNy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmlydHVhbCByZWFsaXR5IGNvbXBhbnkgT2N1bHVzIFZSIGxvc3Qgd2hpY2ggb2YgaXQncyBjby1mb3VuZGVycyBpbiBhIGZyZWFrIGNhciBhY2NpZGVudCBpbiAyMDEzPw==",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IFNjb3R0IFJlaXNzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlNhbnRhIENsYXVzIiBpcyBhIHZhcmlldHkgb2YgbWVsb24u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IjI3IENsdWIiIGlzIGEgdGVybSB1c2VkIHRvIHJlZmVyIHRvIGEgbGlzdCBvZiBmYW1vdXMgYWN0b3JzLCBtdXNpY2lhbnMsIGFuZCBhcnRpc3RzIHdobyBkaWVkIGF0IHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgMjcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWFybCBHcmV5IHRlYSBpcyBibGFjayB0ZWEgZmxhdm91cmVkIHdpdGggd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QmVyZ2Ftb3Qgb2ls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3JpZ2luYWxseSBhbm90aGVyIHdvcmQgZm9yIHBvcHB5LCBjb3F1ZWxpY290IGlzIGEgc2hhZGUgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "UmVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5hdGlvbmFsIEFuaW1hbCBvZiBTY290bGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgVW5pY29ybi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY3VycmVuY3kgb2YgUG9sYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "WsWCb3R5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBudXJzZXJ5IHJoeW1lLCB3aGF0IGZydWl0IGRpZCBMaXR0bGUgSmFjayBIb3JuZXIgcHVsbCBvdXQgb2YgaGlzIENocmlzdG1hcyBwaWU/",
            "answer": "UGx1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYW5jaWVudCBHcmVlY2UsIGlmIHlvdXIgam9iIHdlcmUgYSAiaGlwcGV1cyIgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd291bGQgeW91IG93bj8=",
            "answer": "SG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBzb21lb25lIGlzIGluZXhwZXJpZW5jZWQgdGhleSBhcmUgc2FpZCB0byBiZSB3aGF0IGNvbG9yPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2h1cmNoJ3MgaW50ZXJpb3IgaW4gVmF0aWNhbiBDaXR5IHdhcyBkZXNpZ25lZCBpbiAxNTAzIGJ5IHJlbmFpc3NhbmNlIGFyY2hpdGVjdHMgaW5jbHVkaW5nIEJyYW1hbnRlLCBNaWNoZWxhbmdlbG8gYW5kIEJlcm5pbmk/",
            "answer": "U3QuIFBldGVyJ3MgQmFzaWxpY2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzdGF0dWUgb2YgQ2hhcmxlcyBEYXJ3aW4gc2l0cyBpbiB3aGF0IExvbmRvbiBtdXNldW0/",
            "answer": "TmF0dXJhbCBIaXN0b3J5IE11c2V1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBpY2tsZWQgZ2hlcmtpbiB3YXMgZmlyc3QgYWRkZWQgdG8gaGFtYnVyZ2VycyBiZWNhdXNlIGEgVVMgaGVhbHRoIGxhdyByZXF1aXJlZCBhbGwgZmFzdC1mb29kIHRvIGluY2x1ZGUgYSBzb3VyY2Ugb2YgVml0YW1pbiBDLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBwYXNvZG9ibGUgaXMgYSB0eXBlIG9mIEl0YWxpYW4gcGFzdGEgc2F1Y2Uu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW5zdGFudCBtYXNoZWQgcG90YXRvZXMgd2VyZSBpbnZlbnRlZCBieSBDYW5hZGlhbiBFZHdhcmQgQXNzZWxiZXJncyBpbiAxOTYyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9pZSBncmFzIGlzIGEgRnJlbmNoIGRlbGljYWN5IHR5cGljYWxseSBtYWRlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGEgZHVjayBvciBnb29zZT8=",
            "answer": "TGl2ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIE1leGljYW4gQmVlciAiQ29yb25hIiBpcyB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgYmVlcj8=",
            "answer": "UGFsZSBMYWdlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYW4gSXZ5IExlYWd1ZSBVbml2ZXJzaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RhbmZvcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGRydWcgY2FydGVsIHJ1biBieSBQYWJsbyBFc2NvYmFyIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggU291dGggQW1lcmljYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVkZWxsw61u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGRvZyBpcyAnSGFuZHNvbWUgRGFuJywgdGhlIG1hc2NvdCBvZiBZYWxlIFVuaXZlcnNpdHk/",
            "answer": "QnVsbGRvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJlYSA1MSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV2YWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAnUycgc3RhbmQgZm9yIGluIHRoZSBhYmJyZXZpYXRpb24gU0lNLCBhcyBpbiBTSU0gY2FyZD8g",
            "answer": "U3Vic2NyaWJlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbGNvaG9saWMgZHJpbmsgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIG1vbGFzc2VzPw==",
            "answer": "UnVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHZhcG9yIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IGUtY2lnYXJldHRlcyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSB3YXRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmRzICJidW5nYWxvdyIgYW5kICJzaGFtcG9vIiBvcmlnaW5hdGUgZnJvbSB0aGUgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2hhcGUgb2YgdGhlIHRveSBpbnZlbnRlZCBieSBIdW5nYXJpYW4gcHJvZmVzc29yIEVybsWRIFJ1YmlrPw==",
            "answer": "Q3ViZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbGwgdGhlIG51bWJlcnMgb24gYSByb3VsZXR0ZSB3aGVlbCBpcyA2NjYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdmVyeSBmaXJzdCB2aWRlbyB1cGxvYWRlZCB0byBZb3VUdWJlPw==",
            "answer": "TWUgYXQgdGhlIHpvbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBRdWVlbiBFbGl6YWJldGggSUkgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "MTkyNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYW5vdGhlciBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgZWdncGxhbnQ/",
            "answer": "UG90aW1hcnJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIGF1dG9tb2JpbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "RHVjYXRp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgY28tZm91bmRlciBvZiBtdXNpYyBzdHJlYW1pbmcgc2VydmljZSBTcG90aWZ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIEVr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnVsbHMgYXJlIGF0dHJhY3RlZCB0byB0aGUgY29sb3IgcmVkLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSXRhbGlhbiBhdXRvbW9iaWxlIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBnYWluZWQgbWFqb3JpdHkgY29udHJvbCBvZiBVLlMuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIENocnlzbGVyIGluIDIwMTE/",
            "answer": "RmlhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIlNwYW0iIGNhbWUgYmVmb3JlIHRoZSBmb29kIHByb2R1Y3QgIlNwYW0iLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBQb2xhbmQgaW4gUG9saXNoPw==",
            "answer": "UG9sc2th"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaXJlY3Rpb24gZG9lcyB0aGUgU3RhdHVlIG9mIExpYmVydHkgZmFjZT8=",
            "answer": "U291dGhlYXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RmFzdCBmb29kIHJlc3RhdXJhbnQgY2hhaW5zIENhcmwncyBKci4gYW5kIEhhcmRlZSdzIGFyZSBvd25lZCBieSB0aGUgc2FtZSBjb21wYW55Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgbGV0dGVycyBvZiB0aGUgZmFzdCBmb29kIGNoYWluIEtGQyBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "S2VudHVja3kgRnJpZWQgQ2hpY2tlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9ib1NhcGllbiB0b3kgcm9ib3QgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUG9ydHVndWVzZSB3b3JkIGZvciAiQnJhemlsIj8=",
            "answer": "QnJhc2ls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEZhaXIgV29ya3MgQXVzdHJhbGlhLCBob3cgbG9uZyBkbyB5b3UgaGF2ZSB0byB3b3JrIHRvIGdldCBMb25nIFNlcnZpY2UgTGVhdmU/",
            "answer": "NyB5ZWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXJkIGdhbWVzIHJldm9sdmVzIGFyb3VuZCBudW1iZXJzIGFuZCBiYXNpYyBtYXRoPw==",
            "answer": "VW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNlYXJjaCBlbmdpbmUgIkdvb2dsZSI/",
            "answer": "QmFja1J1Yg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGZvdW5kZWQgdGhlIEtoYW4gQWNhZGVteT8=",
            "answer": "U2FsIEtoYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21wYW55IGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgdm9jYWxvaWQgSGF0c3VuZSBNaWt1Pw==",
            "answer": "Q3J5cHRvbiBGdXR1cmUgTWVkaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd29yZHMgbWVhbnMgImlkbGUgc3BlY3RhdG9yIj8=",
            "answer": "R29uZ29vemxlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RnJhbmNpcyBCYWNvbiBkaWVkIGZyb20gYSBmYXRhbCBjYXNlIG9mIHBuZXVtb25pYSB3aGlsZSBoZSB3YXMgYXR0ZW1wdGluZyB0byBwcmVzZXJ2ZSBtZWF0IGJ5IHN0dWZmaW5nIGEgY2hpY2tlbiB3aXRoIHNub3cu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UG9wY29ybiB3YXMgaW52ZW50ZWQgaW4gMTg3MSBieSBGcmVkZXJpY2sgVy4gUnVlY2toZWltIGluIHRoZSBVU0Egd2hlcmUgaGUgc29sZCB0aGUgc25hY2sgb24gdGhlIHN0cmVldHMgb2YgQ2hpY2Fnby4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggb3JnYW5pc2F0aW9uIENBTVJBIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgVGhlIENhbXBhaWduIGZvciBSZWFsIEFsZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmlldG5hbSdzIG5hdGlvbmFsIGZsYWcgaXMgYSByZWQgc3RhciBpbiBmcm9udCBvZiBhIHllbGxvdyBiYWNrZ3JvdW5kLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbm90ZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIG9uIGEgc3RhbmRhcmQgZ3JhbmQgcGlhbm8/",
            "answer": "ODg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1NTyBSUEcgIlJlYWxtIG9mIHRoZSBNYWQgR29kIiwgd2hhdCBkdW5nZW9uIGlzIHdpZGVseSBjb25zaWRlcmVkIHRvIGJlIHRoZSBtb3N0IGRpZmZpY3VsdD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNoYXR0ZXIncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgUGFuYW1hIGhhdHMgbWFkZSBvdXQgb2Y/",
            "answer": "U3RyYXc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgImFwcm9zZXhpYSIgbWVhbnMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIGluYWJpbGl0eSB0byBjb25jZW50cmF0ZSBvbiBhbnl0aGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhdXRob3Igb2YgSnVycmFzaWMgUGFyaz8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgdGhlIGhvc3Qgb2YgYSBwcm9ncmFtIG9uIE5QUj8=",
            "answer": "QmVuIFNoYXBpcm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEZpZWxkcyBNZWRhbCwgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBtb3N0IHNvdWdodCBhZnRlciBhd2FyZHMgaW4gbWF0aGVtYXRpY3MsIGlzIGF3YXJkZWQgZXZlcnkgaG93IG1hbnkgeWVhcnM/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBibG9vZCBjb21wb25lbnQgZm9ybXMgYSBwbHVnIGF0IHRoZSBzaXRlIG9mIGluanVyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGxhdGVsZXRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIHVuaW9uIGphY2sgaW4gaXRzIGZsYWc/",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlIHRyYWluIHN0YXRpb24gIkxsYW5mYWlywq1wd2xsZ3d5bmd5bGzCrWdvZ2VyecKtY2h3eXJuwq1kcm9id2xswq1sbGFuwq10eXNpbGlvwq1nb2dvwq1nb2NoIj8=",
            "answer": "V2FsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFdXRiBwcm9mZXNzaW9uYWwgd3Jlc3RsaW5nIHRhZyB0ZWFtIG1hZGUgdXAgb2YgdGhlIHdyZXN0bGVycyBBeCBhbmQgU21hc2g/",
            "answer": "RGVtb2xpdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmVzdCBzZWxsaW5nIHRveSBvZiAxOTgzIGNhdXNlZCBoeXN0ZXJpYSwgcmVzdWx0aW5nIGluIHJpb3RzIGJyZWFraW5nIG91dCBpbiBzdG9yZXM/",
            "answer": "Q2FiYmFnZSBQYXRjaCBLaWRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAiRyIgbWVhbiBpbiAiRy1NYW4iPw==",
            "answer": "R292ZXJubWVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZXNzZW50aWFsIGNvbmRpbWVudCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIGFzIEphcGFuZXNlIGhvcnNlcmFkaXNoPw==",
            "answer": "V2FzYWJpIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gZWdncGxhbnQgaXMgYSB2ZWdldGFibGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpa2luaSBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgIkJpa2luaSBBdG9sbCIsIGFuIGlzbGFuZCB3aGVyZSB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBjb25kdWN0ZWQgdGVzdHMgb24gYXRvbWljIGJvbWJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGRlc3RpbmF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBtaXNzaW5nIGZsaWdodCBNSDM3MD8=",
            "answer": "QmVpamluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdW5pdCBvZiBjdXJyZW5jeSBpbiBMYW9zPw==",
            "answer": "S2lw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIFNwYW5pc2ggYXV0b25vbW91cyBjb21tdW5pdHkgb2YgQ2F0YWxvbmlhIGJhbiBpbiAyMDEwLCB0aGF0IHRvb2sgZWZmZWN0IGluIDIwMTI/",
            "answer": "QnVsbGZpZ2h0aW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5pY2tuYW1lIGdpdmVuIHRvIHRoZSBIdWdoZXMgSC00IEhlcmN1bGVzLCBhIGhlYXZ5IHRyYW5zcG9ydCBmbHlpbmcgYm9hdCB3aGljaCBhY2hpZXZlZCBmbGlnaHQgaW4gMTk0Nz8=",
            "answer": "U3BydWNlIEdvb3Nl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29sb3VycyBpcyBOT1QgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gdGhlIGxvZ28gZm9yIEdvb2dsZT8=",
            "answer": "UGluaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgU3BhbmlzaCB3b3JkIGZvciAiZG9ua2V5Ij8=",
            "answer": "QnVycm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIHdvcmQgZm9yICJoYXQiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hhcGVhdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFN1biByaXNlcyBmcm9tIHRoZSBOb3J0aC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbG9yIG9yYW5nZSBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgZnJ1aXQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gInNjaWVudGlzdCIgd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBpbiB3aGljaCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTgzMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzJyBDREMsIG9uZSBpbiBob3cgbWFueSBBbWVyaWNhbnMgZGllIGFubnVhbGx5IGR1ZSB0byBzbW9raW5nPw==",
            "answer": "Rml2ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHR5cGljYWwgRXVyb3BlYW4gc3dvcmQgZGVzaWduPw==",
            "answer": "U2NpbWl0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcywgIklmIHlvdSBlbGltaW5hdGUgdGhlIGltcG9zc2libGUsIHdoYXRldmVyIHJlbWFpbnMsIGhvd2V2ZXIgaW1wcm9iYWJsZSwgbXVzdCBiZSB0aGUuLi4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1dGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Um9tYW5pYW4gYmVsb25ncyB0byB0aGUgUm9tYW5jZSBsYW5ndWFnZSBmYW1pbHksIHNoYXJlZCB3aXRoIEZyZW5jaCwgU3BhbmlzaCwgUG9ydHVndWVzZSBhbmQgSXRhbGlhbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgSHViYmEgQnViYmEgZmlyc3QgaW50cm9kdWNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGludmVudGVkIFBhc3RhZmFyaWFuaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgSGVuZGVyc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyByZWFsIGhhZ2dpcyBtYWRlIG9mPw==",
            "answer": "U2hlZXAncyBIZWFydCwgTGl2ZXIgYW5kIEx1bmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdlYnNpdGUgIlNodXQgVXAgJiBTaXQgRG93biIgcmV2aWV3cyB3aGljaCBmb3JtIG9mIG1lZGlhPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9hcmQgR2FtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgZ3JleXNjYWxlIGZhY2UgaXMgb24gdGhlIGthcHBhIGVtb3RpY29uIG9uIFR3aXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9zaCBEZVNlbm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2hhcnRyZXVzZSBpcyBhIGNvbG9yIGJldHdlZW4geWVsbG93IGFuZCB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGFnZ2lzIGlzIHRyYWRpdGlvbmFsbHkgYXRlIG9uIEJ1cm5zIE5pZ2h0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSwgbm90IGluY2x1ZGluZyBKYXBhbiwgaGFzIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBlb3BsZSBvZiBqYXBhbmVzZSBkZWNlbnQ/",
            "answer": "QnJhemls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgWm9kaWFjIHN5bWJvbCBmb3IgR2VtaW5pPw==",
            "answer": "VHdpbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGVycnkgR2lsbGlhbSB3YXMgYW4gYW5pbWF0b3IgdGhhdCB3b3JrZWQgd2l0aCB3aGljaCBCcml0aXNoIGNvbWVkeSBncm91cD8=",
            "answer": "TW9udHkgUHl0aG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TG9jYXRlZCBpbiBDaGlsZSwgRWwgVGVuaWVudGUgaXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgbGFyZ2VzdCB1bmRlcmdyb3VuZCBtaW5lIGZvciB3aGF0IG1ldGFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q29wcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBudW1iZXIgb2YgTWljaGVsaW4gc3RhcnMgYSByZXN0YXVyYW50IGNhbiByZWNlaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhyZWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBvbmUgaXMgImVudmlvdXMiLCB0aGV5IGFyZSBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIHdoYXQgY29sb3I/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOQVNB4oCZcyBtb3N0IGZhbW91cyBzcGFjZSB0ZWxlc2NvcGU/",
            "answer": "SHViYmxlIFNwYWNlIFRlbGVzY29wZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCB0aXRsZSBvZiB0aGUgUHJpbWUgTWluaXN0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIFVLPw==",
            "answer": "Rmlyc3QgTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgVHJlYXN1cnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgVmFsdmUgY29vcGVyYXRlIHdpdGggaW4gdGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBWaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "SFRD"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcGFzdCB0aW1lcywgd2hhdCB3b3VsZCBhIGdlbnRsZW1hbiBrZWVwIGluIGhpcyBmb2IgcG9ja2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "V2F0Y2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVTIGVtZXJnZW5jeSBob3RsaW5lIGlzIDkxMSBiZWNhdXNlIG9mIHRoZSBTZXB0ZW1iZXIgMTF0aCB0ZXJyb3Jpc3QgYXR0YWNrcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RnJlbmNoIGlzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGxhbmd1YWdlIGluIENhbmFkYS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1vcnNlIGNvZGUsIHdoaWNoIGxldHRlciBpcyBpbmRpY2F0ZWQgYnkgMyBkb3RzPyA=",
            "answer": "Uw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBJdnkgTGVhZ3VlIHVuaXZlcnNpdGllcyBoYXMgaXRzIG9mZmljaWFsIG1vdHRvIGluIEhlYnJldyBhcyB3ZWxsIGFzIGluIExhdGluPw==",
            "answer": "WWFsZSBVbml2ZXJzaXR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHRoZSAxOXRoIENlbnR1cnksIHRoZSAiTGl2aW5nIFJvb20iIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGNhbGxlZCB0aGUuLi4=",
            "answer": "UGFybG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgaG93IG1hbnkgeWVhcnMgd291bGQgeW91IGNlbGVicmF0ZSB5b3VyIGNyeXN0YWwgYW5uaXZlcnNhcnk/",
            "answer": "MTU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmVkIFZpbmVzIGlzIGEgYnJhbmQgb2Ygd2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNhbmR5Pw==",
            "answer": "TGljb3JpY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik51bWJlciAxNiBCdXMgU2hlbHRlciIgd2FzIGEgY2hpbGQncyBuYW1lIHRoYXQgd2FzIGFwcHJvdmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZCBnb3Zlcm5tZW50Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR2VybWFuIHdvcmQgZm9yICJzcG9vbiI/",
            "answer": "TMO2ZmZlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcm9tYW5pemVkIEphcGFuZXNlIHdvcmQgZm9yICJ1bml2ZXJzaXR5Ij8=",
            "answer": "RGFpZ2FrdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcm9tYW5pemVkIFJ1c3NpYW4gd29yZCBmb3IgIndpbnRlciI/",
            "answer": "WmltYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBhbmltYXRyb25pYyBzaW5naW5nIGZpc2ggcHJvcCwgc2luZ2luZyBzdWNoIGhpdHMgc3VjaCBhcyAiRG9uJ3QgV29ycnksIEJlIEhhcHB5Ij8=",
            "answer": "QmlnIE1vdXRoIEJpbGx5IEJhc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGlzbmV5J3MgSGF1bnRlZCBNYW5zaW9uIGlzIGhvbWUgdG8gYSB0cmlvIG9mIEhpdGNoaGlraW5nIEdob3N0cy4gV2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVtPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTW91bnRhaW4gRGV3J3Mgb3JpZ2luYWwgc2xvZ2FuPw==",
            "answer": "WWFob28hIE1vdW50YWluIERldy4uLiBJdCdsbCB0aWNrbGUgeW91ciBpbm5hcmRzIQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSAyMDE0LTIwMTUgQXVzdHJhbGlhbiBCdXJlYXUgb2YgU3RhdGlzdGljcywgd2hhdCBwZXJjZW50YWdlIG9mIEF1c3RyYWxpYW5zIHdlcmUgYm9ybiBvdmVyc2Vhcz8=",
            "answer": "Mjgl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhIEJ1cmdlZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBmbGFn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIG1hbGxvdyBmbG93ZXIsIG1hdXZlIGlzIGEgc2hhZGUgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZmFzdCBmb29kIGNoYWluIGNhbiB5b3Ugb3JkZXIgYSBKYW1vY2hhIFNoYWtlPw==",
            "answer": "QXJieSdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IHBsYW50ZWQgdGhlIHNlZWRzIG9mIFF1ZXJjdXMgcm9idXIsIHdoYXQgd291bGQgZ3Jvdz8=",
            "answer": "VHJlZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIHN1Ym1hY2hpbmUgZ3VuIHdhcyBpbmZvcm1hbGx5IGtub3duIGJ5IHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiBzb2xkaWVycyB0aGF0IHVzZWQgaXQgYXMgIkdyZWFzZSBHdW4iPw==",
            "answer": "TTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2xvc2VzdCBwbGFuZXQgdG8gb3VyIHNvbGFyIHN5c3RlbSdzIHN1bj8=",
            "answer": "TWVyY3VyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb21tb25seSB1c2VkIG5vdW4gaW4gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggbGFuZ3VhZ2U/",
            "answer": "VGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgImFzdGFzaWEiIG1lYW5zIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIGluYWJpbGl0eSB0byBzdGFuZCB1cA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhaXJsaW5lIHdhcyB0aGUgb3duZXIgb2YgdGhlIHBsYW5lIHRoYXQgY3Jhc2hlZCBvZmYgdGhlIGNvYXN0IG9mIE5vdmEgU2NvdGlhIGluIDE5OTg/",
            "answer": "U3dpc3MgQWly"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1pdG9jaG9uZHJpYSBpcyB0aGUgcG93ZXJob3VzZSBvZiB0aGUgY2VsbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBCQlBBLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiBwdWIgbmFtZSBpbiB0aGUgVUs/",
            "answer": "UmVkIExpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIGxldHRlciAiTSIgaW4gdGhlIE5BVE8gcGhvbmV0aWMgYWxwaGFiZXQ/",
            "answer": "TWlrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgYm9vayBvZiB0aGUgT2xkIFRlc3RhbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "R2VuZXNpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2NvdGNoIHdoaXNreSBhbmQgRHJhbWJ1aWUgbWFrZSB1cCB3aGljaCBjb2NrdGFpbD8=",
            "answer": "UnVzdHkgTmFpbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlsbSBzdGFyIGhhcyBoaXMgc3RhdHVlIGluIExlaWNlc3RlciBTcXVhcmU/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBDaGFwbGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2Npb3Bob2JpYSBpcyB0aGUgZmVhciBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "U2hhZG93cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFVTIHN0YXRlIG9mIENhbGlmb3JuaWE/",
            "answer": "R29sZGVuIFN0YXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcm9tYW5pemVkIENoaW5lc2Ugd29yZCBmb3IgImFpcnBsYW5lIj8=",
            "answer": "RmVpamk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN3ZWRpc2ggd29yZCAiR3J1bmthIiBtZWFucyB3aGF0IGluIEVuZ2xpc2g/",
            "answer": "VGhpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhIGRlYWQgbWFsbD8=",
            "answer": "QSBtYWxsIHdpdGggaGlnaCB2YWNhbmN5IHJhdGVzIG9yIGxvdyBjb25zdW1lciBmb290IHRyYWZmaWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTmludGVuZG8gZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDIzcmQsIDE4ODk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCB3b3JkIGZvciAiZ2xhc3MiIGlzICJnbGFjZSIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW1zdGVyZGFtIENlbnRyYWFsIHN0YXRpb24gaXMgdHdpbm5lZCB3aXRoIHdoYXQgc3RhdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TG9uZG9uIExpdmVycG9vbCBTdHJlZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxiZXJ0IEVpbnN0ZWluIGhhZCB0cm91YmxlIHdpdGggbWF0aGVtYXRpY3Mgd2hlbiBoZSB3YXMgaW4gc2Nob29sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIE5ldyBZb3JrIFRpbWVzIHNsb2dhbiBpcywg4oCcQWxsIHRoZSBOZXdzIFRoYXTigJlzIEZpdCB0b+KApuKAnQ==",
            "answer": "UHJpbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgTG9uZG9uIFVuZGVyZ3JvdW5kIGxpbmUgdG8gYmUgYnVpbHQ/",
            "answer": "TWV0cm9wb2xpdGFuIExpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q29tcHV0ZXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIENvbXBhcSB3YXMgYWNxdWlyZWQgZm9yICQyNSBiaWxsaW9uIGRvbGxhcnMgaW4gMjAwMiBieSB3aGljaCBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "SGV3bGV0dC1QYWNrYXJk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmVwaGVsb2NvY2N5Z2lhIGlzIHRoZSBwcmFjdGljZSBvZiBkb2luZyB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "RmluZGluZyBzaGFwZXMgaW4gY2xvdWRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGFyZSBjYXVnaHQgIkdvbGRicmlja2luZyIsIHdoYXQgYXJlIHlvdSBkb2luZyB3cm9uZz8=",
            "answer": "U2xhY2tpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkJ1ZmZhbG8gYnVmZmFsbyBCdWZmYWxvIGJ1ZmZhbG8gYnVmZmFsbyBidWZmYWxvIEJ1ZmZhbG8gYnVmZmFsby4iIGlzIGEgZ3JhbW1hdGljYWxseSBjb3JyZWN0IHNlbnRlbmNlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWFydGggaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBnYWxheHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE1pbGt5IFdheSBHYWxheHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3VtYm8gaXMgYSBzdGV3IHRoYXQgb3JpZ2luYXRlZCBpbiBMb3Vpc2lhbmEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gYSBkYXJ0Ym9hcmQsIHdoYXQgbnVtYmVyIGlzIGRpcmVjdGx5IG9wcG9zaXRlIE5vLiAxPw==",
            "answer": "MTk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TnV0ZWxsYSBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgR2VybWFuIGNvbXBhbnkgRmVycmVyby4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIDg2NDAwIHNlY29uZHMgaW4gYSBkYXku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCB3YXMgSGFyYW1iZSwgd2hvIHdhcyBzaG90IGFmdGVyIGEgY2hpbGQgZmVsbCBpbnRvIGl0J3MgZW5jbG9zdXJlIGF0IHRoZSBDaW5jaW5uYXRpIFpvbz8=",
            "answer": "R29yaWxsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q3VjdW1iZXJzIGFyZSB1c3VhbGx5IG1vcmUgdGhhbiA5MCUgd2F0ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcm9tYW5pemVkIEtvcmVhbiB3b3JkIGZvciAiaGVhcnQiPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltamFuZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgSXRhbGlhbiB3b3JkIGZvciAidG9tYXRvIj8=",
            "answer": "UG9tb2Rvcm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxMCwgVHdpdHRlciBhbmQgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgTGlicmFyeSBvZiBDb25ncmVzcyBwYXJ0bmVyZWQgdG9nZXRoZXIgdG8gYXJjaGl2ZSBldmVyeSB0d2VldCBieSBBbWVyaWNhbiBjaXRpemVucy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBBcHBsZSBJbmMuIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk3Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgdGhlIEJ1cmogS2hhbGlmYT8=",
            "answer": "Miw3MjIgZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNjaWVudGlmaWMgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlIFNvdXRoZXJuIExpZ2h0cyBpcyBBdXJvcmEgQXVzdHJhbGlzPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2lnbiBvZiB0aGUgem9kaWFjIGNvbWVzIGJldHdlZW4gVmlyZ28gYW5kIFNjb3JwaW8/",
            "answer": "TGlicmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkcml2ZXMgb24gdGhlIGxlZnQgc2lkZSBvZiB0aGUgcm9hZD8=",
            "answer": "SmFwYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgQXBwbGUgSW5jLiBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkPw==",
            "answer": "Q3VwZXJ0aW5vLCBDYWxpZm9ybmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBudXRzIGFyZSB1c2VkIGluIHRoZSBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIG9mIG1hcnppcGFuPw==",
            "answer": "QWxtb25kcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhciBzaWduIG9mIHNvbWVvbmUgYm9ybiBvbiBWYWxlbnRpbmVzIGRheT8=",
            "answer": "QXF1YXJpdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENhbmFkaWFuICQxIGNvaW4gaXMgY29sbG9xdWlhbGx5IGtub3duIGFzIGEgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "TG9vbmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGlyZWN0bHkgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBNb251bWVudCBhbmQgdGhlIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgUG9vbCBpcyBhIG1lbW9yaWFsIHRvIHdoaWNoIHdhcj8=",
            "answer": "V29ybGQgV2FyIElJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFBsYXlzdGF0aW9uIDMgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMTEsIDIwMDY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmlyZ2luIFRyYWlucywgVmlyZ2luIEF0bGFudGljIGFuZCBWaXJnaW4gUmFjaW5nLCBhcmUgYWxsIGNvbXBhbmllcyBvd25lZCBieSB3aGljaCBmYW1vdXMgZW50cmVwcmVuZXVyPyAgIA==",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCcmFuc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbWlsbGluZXIgbWFrZSBhbmQgc2VsbD8=",
            "answer": "SGF0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiAiU3VwZXJjYWxpZnJhZ2lsaXN0aWNleHBpYWxpZG9jaW91cyIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN0dWR5IG9uIHBlYW51dHMgaW4gYmFycyBmb3VuZCB0cmFjZXMgb2Ygb3ZlciAxMDAgdW5pcXVlIHNwZWNpbWVucyBvZiB1cmluZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBidWlsZGluZ3MgaXMgZXhhbXBsZSBvZiBhIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBwcmltYXJpbHkgYnVpbHQgaW4gdGhlIEFydCBEZWNvIGFyY2hpdGVjdHVyYWwgc3R5bGU/",
            "answer": "TmlhZ2FyYSBNb2hhd2sgQnVpbGRpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "WW91IGFyZSBhbGxvd2VkIHRvIHNlbGwgeW91ciBzb3VsIG9uIGVCYXku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkFuYW5hcyIgaXMgbW9zdGx5IHVzZWQgYXMgdGhlIHdvcmQgZm9yIFBpbmVhcHBsZSBpbiBvdGhlciBsYW5ndWFnZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2Ugd29tYW4gaXMgNSBpbmNoZXMgLyAxMyBjZW50aW1ldGVycyBzaG9ydGVyIHRoYW4gdGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2UgbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHNhdyBhIHdvcmxkIHJlY29yZCAzMTUgbWlsbGlvbiB2b3RlcnMgdHVybiBvdXQgZm9yIGVsZWN0aW9ucyBvbiBNYXkgMjAsIDE5OTE/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgZGlkIGl0IHRha2UgdGhlIG1vdG9yaXplZCB3aW5kb3cgd2FzaGVycyBvZiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgV29ybGQgVHJhZGUgQ2VudGVyIHRvIGNsZWFuIHRoZSBlbnRpcmUgZXh0ZXJpb3Igb2YgdGhlIGJ1aWxkaW5nPw==",
            "answer": "MSBNb250aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2xvZ2FuIGRpZCB0aGUgZmFzdCBmb29kIGNvbXBhbnksIE1jRG9uYWxkJ3MsIHVzZSBiZWZvcmUgdGhlaXIgIkknbSBMb3ZpbicgSXQiIHNsb2dhbj8=",
            "answer": "V2UgTG92ZSB0byBTZWUgWW91IFNtaWxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGloeWRyb2dlbiBNb25veGlkZSB3YXMgYmFubmVkIGR1ZSB0byBoZWFsdGggcmlza3MgYWZ0ZXIgYmVpbmcgZGlzY292ZXJlZCBpbiAxOTgzIGluc2lkZSBzd2ltbWluZyBwb29scyBhbmQgZHJpbmtpbmcgd2F0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgc29tZW9uZSBzYWlkICJ5b3UgYXJlIG9saWQiLCB3aGF0IHdvdWxkIHRoZXkgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "WW91IHNtZWxsIGV4dHJlbWVseSB1bnBsZWFzYW50Lg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXRlbSBvZiBjbG90aGluZyBpcyB1c3VhbGx5IHdvcm4gYnkgYSBTY290c21hbiBhdCBhIHdlZGRpbmc/",
            "answer": "S2lsdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FuZHkgaXMgTk9UIG1hZGUgYnkgTWFycz8=",
            "answer": "QWxtb25kIEpveQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB6b2RpYWMgc2lnbiBpcyByZXByZXNlbnRlZCBieSBhIHBhaXIgb2Ygc2NhbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "TGlicmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBDeW5vcGhvYmlhIHRoZSBmZWFyIG9mPw==",
            "answer": "RG9ncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB5b3VuZ2VzdCBwZXJzb24gdG8gcmVjaWV2ZSBhIE5vYmVsIFByaXplPw==",
            "answer": "TWFsYWxhIFlvdXNhZnphaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHJvZmVzc2lvbiBvZiBFbG9uIE11c2sncyBtb20sIE1heWUgTXVzaz8=",
            "answer": "TW9kZWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGFuZ3VhZ2UgaXMgTk9UIEluZG8tRXVyb3BlYW4/",
            "answer": "SHVuZ2FyaWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBnZW9tZXRyaWMgc2hhcGUgaXMgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IHVzZWQgZm9yIHN0b3Agc2lnbnM/",
            "answer": "T2N0YWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIllvdVR1YmUiIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "RmVicnVhcnkgMTQsIDIwMDU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBnaXZlbiB0byBJbmRpYW4gZm9vZCBjb29rZWQgb3ZlciBjaGFyY29hbCBpbiBhIGNsYXkgb3Zlbj8=",
            "answer": "VGFuZG9vcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB5b3UgY3J5IGluIHNwYWNlLCB5b3VyIHRlYXJzIHN0aWNrIHRvIHlvdXIgZmFjZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2NhbmRpbmF2aWFuIGxhbmd1YWdlcywgdGhlIGxldHRlciDDhSBtZWFucyByaXZlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG5ldyBPbmUgV29ybGQgVHJhZGUgQ2VudGVyIGluIE1hbmhhdHRhbiwgTmV3IFlvcmsgQ2l0eSB3YXMgZGVzaWduZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggYXJjaGl0ZWN0PyA=",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgQ2hpbGRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXBwbGUgY28tZm91bmRlciBTdGV2ZSBKb2JzIGRpZWQgZnJvbSBjb21wbGljYXRpb25zIG9mIHdoaWNoIGZvcm0gb2YgY2FuY2VyPw==",
            "answer": "UGFuY3JlYXRpYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3Bvb24gdGhlb3J5IGlzIGEgdGhlb3J5LCB1dGlsaXppbmcgIlNwb29ucyIgYXMgYSBtZXRhcGhvciBmb3IgZW5lcmd5IHRoZXkgY2FuIHVzZSBpbiBhIGRheS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtYWNoaW5lIGVsZW1lbnQgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB0aGUgY2VudGVyIG9mIGZpZGdldCBzcGlubmVycz8=",
            "answer": "QmVhcmluZ3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBUYXNtYW5pYT8=",
            "answer": "QW4gQXVzdHJhbGlhbiBTdGF0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZnVybG9uZ3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgbWlsZT8=",
            "answer": "RWlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBzb21lb25lIGlzIGNvd2FyZGx5LCB0aGV5IGFyZSBzYWlkIHRvIGhhdmUgd2hhdCBjb2xvciBiZWxseT8=",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd2VpZ2h0IG9mIGEgR29sZCBCYXIgaW4gRmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2FzPw==",
            "answer": "MzUgUG91bmRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFtb3VzIFBhcGEgSm9obidzIGxhc3QgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "U2NobmF0dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWxlY3Ryb25pYyBtdXNpYyBwcm9kdWNlciBLeWdvJ3MgcG9wdWxhcml0eSBza3lyb2NrZXRlZCBhZnRlciBhIGNlcnRhaW4gcmVtaXguIFdoaWNoIHNvbmcgZGlkIGhlIHJlbWl4Pw==",
            "answer": "RWQgU2hlZXJhbiAtIEkgU2VlIEZpcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmlkZW8gc3RyZWFtaW5nIHdlYnNpdGUgWW91VHViZSB3YXMgcHVyY2hhc2VkIGluIGl0J3MgZW50aXJldHkgYnkgRmFjZWJvb2sgZm9yIFVTJDEuNjUgYmlsbGlvbiBpbiBzdG9jay4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3b3JkIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIGxldHRlciAnVCcgaW4gdGhlIE5BVE8gcGhvbmV0aWMgYWxwaGFiZXQ/",
            "answer": "VGFuZ28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGVtaWNhbHMgYXJlIGZvdW5kIGluIGVnZ3BsYW50IHNlZWRzPw==",
            "answer": "Tmljb3RpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gYXZlcmFnZSwgQW1lcmljYW5zIGNvbnN1bWUgMTAwIHBvdW5kcyBvZiB3aGF0IHBlciBzZWNvbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hvY29sYXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHNvZnQgZHJpbmsgUGVwc2kgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "QnJhZCdzIERyaW5r"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2NvdGxhbmQgdm90ZWQgdG8gYmVjb21lIGFuIGluZGVwZW5kZW50IGNvdW50cnkgZHVyaW5nIHRoZSByZWZlcmVuZHVtIGZyb20gU2VwdGVtYmVyIDIwMTQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgSUFUQSBjb2RlIGZvciBNYW5jaGVzdGVyIEFpcnBvcnQ/",
            "answer": "TUFO"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyAgQnJpdGlzaCBNb25hcmNocyBuZXZlciBhcHBlYXJlZCBvbiBhIGNpcmN1bGF0ZWQgcG91bmQgc3RlcmxpbmcgY29pbj8=",
            "answer": "RWR3YXJkIFZJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGludXMgUGF1bGluZywgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBvbmx5IHdpbm5lcnMgb2YgbXVsdGlwbGUgTm9iZWwgUHJpemVzLCBlYXJuZWQgaGlzIE5vYmVsIFByaXplcyBpbiBDaGVtaXN0cnkgYW5kIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "UGVhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbG9naWNhbCBmYWxsYWN5IG1lYW5zIHRvIGF0dGFjayB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mIHlvdXIgb3Bwb25lbnQgcmF0aGVyIHRoYW4gdGhlaXIgYXJndW1lbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "QWQgaG9taW5lbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBmYXN0IGZvb2QgY2hhaW4gaGFzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGxvY2F0aW9ucyBnbG9iYWxseT8g",
            "answer": "U3Vid2F5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgMyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IGludmVudG9yeSBzbG90cyBkb2VzIEppbGwgaGF2ZSBhdCB0aGUgc3RhcnQgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Um9sZXggaXMgYSBjb21wYW55IHRoYXQgc3BlY2lhbGl6ZXMgaW4gd2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIHByb2R1Y3Q/",
            "answer": "V2F0Y2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWlyc3BlZWQgdmVsb2NpdHkgb2YgYW4gdW5sYWRlbiBzd2FsbG93Pw==",
            "answer": "MjQgTVBI"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcm9tYW5pemVkIEFyYWJpYyB3b3JkIGZvciAibW9vbiI/",
            "answer": "UWFtYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2l0dGluZyBmb3IgbW9yZSB0aGFuIHRocmVlIGhvdXJzIGEgZGF5IGNhbiBjdXQgdHdvIHllYXJzIG9mZiBhIHBlcnNvbidzIGxpZmUgZXhwZWN0YW5jeS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY2Fsb3JpZXMgYXJlIGluIGEgMzU1IG1sIGNhbiBvZiBQZXBzaSBDb2xhPw==",
            "answer": "MTUw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJvZHVjdCBkaWQgTm9raWEsIHRoZSB0ZWxlY29tbXVuaWNhdGlvbnMgY29tcGFueSwgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBzZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "UGFwZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gZmxpZ2h0IHN5c3RlbXMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyB0aGUgaW5pdGlhbGlzbSAiVENBUyIgc3RhbmQgZm9yPw==",
            "answer": "VHJhZmZpYyBDb2xsaXNpb24gQXZvaWRhbmNlIFN5c3RlbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFF1YWRyYW5ndWxhcmlzIFJldmVyc3VtIGlzIGJlc3QgZGVzY3JpYmVkIGFzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmc/",
            "answer": "QSBwZXJjdXNzaW9uIGluc3RydW1lbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgVHJhcHBpc3QgYnJld2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QmVsZ2l1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2xvdmFraWEgaXMgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgRXVyb3BlYW4gVW5pb24t",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2l0aWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIE1pbnRpbmcgbG9jYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "U3QuIExvdWlzLCBNTw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJhbmsgTGxveWQgV3JpZ2h0IHdhcyB0aGUgYXJjaGl0ZWN0IGJlaGluZCB3aGF0IGZhbW91cyBidWlsZGluZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEd1Z2dlbmhlaW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIGFpcmNyYWZ0IHdhcyBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgSWdvciBTaWtvcnNreSBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBpbiAxOTQyPw==",
            "answer": "SGVsaWNvcHRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGludmVudGVkIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBldmVyIGNob2NvbGF0ZSBiYXIsIGluIDE4NDc/",
            "answer": "Sm9zZXBoIEZyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERlY2xhcmF0aW9uIG9mIEluZGVwZW5kZW5jZSBhcHByb3ZlZCBieSB0aGUgU2Vjb25kIENvbnRpbmVudGFsIENvbmdyZXNzPw==",
            "answer": "SnVseSA0LCAxNzc2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IHdvdWxkIG9uZSBzYXkgZ29vZGJ5ZSBpbiBTcGFuaXNoPw==",
            "answer": "QWRpw7Nz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2lnbiBvZiB0aGUgem9kaWFjIGlzIHJlcHJlc2VudGVkIGJ5IHRoZSBDcmFiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuY2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SXQgaXMgYXV0b21hdGljYWxseSBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGVudHJhcG1lbnQgaW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgaWYgdGhlIHBvbGljZSBzZWxsIHlvdSBpbGxlZ2FsIHN1YnN0YW5jZXMgd2l0aG91dCByZXZlYWxpbmcgdGhlbXNlbHZlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGx1dG8gaXMgYSBwbGFuZXQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgd2FzIG9uY2UgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSB0aGUgMjd0aCBsZXR0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGFscGhhYmV0Pw==",
            "answer": "QW1wZXJzYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsYW5ndWFnZXMgZG9lcyBOT1QgdXNlIGdlbmRlciBhcyBhIHBhcnQgb2YgaXRzIGdyYW1tYXI/",
            "answer": "VHVya2lzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIHdvcmQgZm9yICJmaXNoIj8=",
            "answer": "cG9pc3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mICJUaGUgTGVnbyBHcm91cCI/",
            "answer": "T2xlIEtpcmsgQ2hyaXN0aWFuc2Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYSAxOTk0IENCUyBpbnRlcnZpZXcsIE1pY3Jvc29mdCBjby1mb3VuZGVyIEJpbGwgR2F0ZXMgcGVyZm9ybWVkIHdoYXQgdW51c3VhbCB0cmljayBvbiBjYW1lcmE/",
            "answer": "SnVtcGluZyBvdmVyIGFuIG9mZmljZSBjaGFpcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIGlzIG5vdCBvbiBNb3VudCBSdXNobW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBGLiBLZW5uZWR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEdyZWF0IFdhbGwgb2YgQ2hpbmEgaXMgdmlzaWJsZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBtb29uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgSmV3aXNoIE5ldyBZZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zaCBIYXNoYW5haA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSBKYXBhbmVzZSBzeXN0ZW0gb2YgYWx0ZXJuYXRpdmUgbWVkaWNpbmUsIGxpdGVyYWxseSBtZWFuaW5nICJmaW5nZXIgcHJlc3N1cmUiPw==",
            "answer": "U2hpYXRzdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBNY0RvbmFsZCdzIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk1NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgQmFuayBvZiBBbWVyaWNhIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgZXN0YWJsaXNoZWQgYXM/",
            "answer": "QmFuayBvZiBJdGFseQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZGlkIHRoZSBwaW5lYXBwbGUgcGxhbnQgb3JpZ2luYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "U291dGggQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGFyY2hpdGVjdCBrbm93biBhcyBMZSBDb3JidXNpZXIgd2FzIGFuIGltcG9ydGFudCBmaWd1cmUgaW4gd2hhdCBzdHlsZSBvZiBhcmNoaXRlY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "TW9kZXJuaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGRlcGljdGVkIG9uIHRoZSBVUyBodW5kcmVkIGRvbGxhciBiaWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgbGV0dGVycyBpbiB0aGUgR01UIHRpbWUgem9uZSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW53aWNoIE1lYW4gVGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4tb3duZWQgYnJld2VyeSBsZWQgdGhlIGNvdW50cnkgaW4gc2FsZXMgYnkgdm9sdW1lIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "RC4gRy4gWXVlbmdsaW5nIGFuZCBTb24sIEluYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIDIwMTYgUHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIENhbXBhaWduIHByb21pc2VzIHdhcyB0byBidWlsZCBhIGJvcmRlciB3YWxsIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgYW5kIE1leGljby4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXJib25hdGVkIHNvZnQgZHJpbmtzIHdlcmUgaW50cm9kdWNlZCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIFBlcHBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIHdlYnNpdGUgIkZhY2Vib29rIiBsYXVuY2g/",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBmaWVsZCBpcyBzb21ldGltZXMga25vd24gYXMg4oCcVGhlIERpc21hbCBTY2llbmNlLuKAnQ==",
            "answer": "RWNvbm9taWNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGxpa2VuZXNzIG9mIHdoaWNoIHByZXNpZGVudCBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBvbiB0aGUgcmFyZSAkMiBiaWxsIG9mIFVTQSBjdXJyZW5jeT8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gSmFwYW5lc2UgbWlsaXRhcnkgZGljdGF0b3JzIHdobyBydWxlZCB0aGUgY291bnRyeSB0aHJvdWdoIHRoZSAxMnRoIGFuZCAxOXRoIENlbnR1cnk/",
            "answer": "U2hvZ3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkJhdHRsZSBDYXRzIiwgd2hhdCBpcyBNb25la28gLyBNSVNTIE1vbmVrbydzIGNyaXRpY2FsIHBlcmNlbnRhZ2UgcmF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB3YXRlciBmcm9tIFBvbGFuZCBTcHJpbmcgd2F0ZXIgYm90dGxlcyBjb21lIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "TWFpbmUsIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEZsYWcgb2YgdGhlIEV1cm9wZWFuIFVuaW9uIGhhcyBob3cgbWFueSBzdGFycyBvbiBpdD8=",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYWVyb2R5bmFtaWNzLCB3aGljaCBmb3JjZSBwdXNoZXMgYW4gb2JqZWN0IHVwd2FyZHM/",
            "answer": "TGlmdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmFua3MgYXJlIE5PVCBhdXRob3JpemVkIHRvIGlzc3VlIGN1cnJlbmN5IG5vdGVzIGluIEhvbmcgS29uZz8=",
            "answer": "T0NCQw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBtb3N0IGV4cGVuc2l2ZSBzcGljZSBieSB3ZWlnaHQ/",
            "answer": "U2FmZnJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29sb3JzIGFyZSB0aGVyZSBpbiBhIHJhaW5ib3c/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExlZ28gR3JvdXAgd2FzIGZvdW5kZWQgaW4gMTkzMi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rml2ZSBkb2xsYXJzIGlzIHdvcnRoIGhvdyBtYW55IG5pY2tsZXM/",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgImFidWxpYSIgbWVhbnMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIGluYWJpbGl0eSB0byBtYWtlIGRlY2lzaW9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29jYS1Db2xhJ3Mgb3JpZ2luYWwgY29sb3VyIHdhcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW1lcmNpYWwgVUsgY2hhbm5lbCBJVFYgc3RhbmRzIGZvciAiSW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBUZWxldmlzaW9uIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhdXRob3JzIHdhcyBub3QgYm9ybiBpbiBFbmdsYW5kPyA=",
            "answer": "QXJ0aHVyIENvbmFuIERveWxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiQSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBBbmQgRmlyZSIgZmFudGFzeSBub3ZlbCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFIuIFIuIE1hcnRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJlYXRyaXggUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzLCB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgYW5pbWFsIGlzIFRvbW15IEJyb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "QmFkZ2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgIlRoZSBNYXJ0aWFuIiwgaG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIE1hcmsgV2F0bmV5IHRyYXBwZWQgb24gTWFycyAoaW4gU29scyk/",
            "answer": "NTQ5IERheXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAxOTY3IGhvcnJvciBub3ZlbCAiUm9zZW1hcnkncyBCYWJ5Ij8=",
            "answer": "SXJhIExldmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyBDb3JuZWxpdXMgRnVkZ2UncyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "T3N3YWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hvIGRvZXMgRHJhY28gTWFsZm95IGVuZCB1cCBtYXJyeWluZz8=",
            "answer": "QXN0b3JpYSBHcmVlbmdyYXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZXJtaW9uZSBHcmFuZ2VyJ3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBSb24gV2Vhc2xleSdzIG1pZGRsZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QmlsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgQW5kIEhhbSIgaXMgYSBib29rIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIFNldXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE15c3RlcmlvdXMgSXNsYW5kLCBpbiBKdWxlcyBWZXJuZSdzICJUaGUgTXlzdGVyaW91cyBJc2xhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "TGluY29sbiBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIEVyaWMgQmxhaXIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBIZWFkbWFzdGVyIER1bWJsZWRvcmUncyBmdWxsIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "QWxidXMgUGVyY2l2YWwgV3VsZnJpYyBCcmlhbiBEdW1ibGVkb3Jl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUaGUgSG9iYml0Iiwgd2hvIGtpbGxzIFNtYXVnPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5kZXIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZGlkIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBwdWJsaXNoIGZpdmUgbm92ZWxzIGJldHdlZW4gMTk3NyBhbmQgMTk4ND8=",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCYWNobWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJPZiBNaWNlIEFuZCBNZW4iIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2sg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U3RlcGhlbiBDaGJvc2t5IHdyb3RlIHRoZSBib29rICdUaGUgUGVya3Mgb2YgQmVpbmcgQSBXYWxsZmxvd2VyJy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5nIGNvbXBsZXRlZCAiSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGFuZCB0aGUgRGVhdGhseSBIYWxsb3dzIiBpbiB3aGljaCBob3RlbCBpbiBFZGluYnVyZ2gsIFNjb3RsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhbG1vcmFs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkVsZW1lbnRhcnksIG15IGRlYXIgV2F0c29uIiBpcyBhIHBocmFzZSB0aGF0IGlzIG5ldmVyIHRydWx5IHNhaWQgd2l0aGluIHRoZSBDb25hbiBEb3lsZSBib29rcyBvZiBTaGVybG9jayBIb2xtZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIEFkb2xmIEhpdGxlcidzIGF1dG9iaW9ncmFwaHkgIk1laW4gS2FtcGYiIGlzIHdoYXQgd2hlbiB0cmFuc2xhdGVkIHRvIEVuZ2xpc2g/",
            "answer": "TXkgU3RydWdnbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gYXV0aG9yIHdhcyBhbHNvIGEgYnVkZGluZyB0cmF2ZWwgd3JpdGVyIGFuZCB3cm90ZSBvZiBoaXMgYWR2ZW50dXJlcyB3aXRoIGhpcyBkb2cgQ2hhcmxleT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIFRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSBib29rLCB0aGUgYW5zd2VyIHRvIGxpZmUsIHRoZSB1bml2ZXJzZSBhbmQgZXZlcnl0aGluZyBlbHNlIGlzLi4u",
            "answer": "NDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFycnkgUG90dGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIG9uIEp1bHkgMzFzdCwgMTk4MC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FuZyB0aGF0IFBvbnlib3kgaXMgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIGluIHRoZSBib29rLCBUaGUgT3V0c2lkZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdyZWFzZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSB3b3JrIGRvbmUgYnkgU2hha2VzcGVhcmU/",
            "answer": "VHJpYWwgb2YgVGVtcGVyYW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTaGVybG9jayBIb2xtZXMncyBicm90aGVyPw==",
            "answer": "TXljcm9mdCBIb2xtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBib29rIHNlcmllcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYnkgSmltIEJ1dGNoZXIgZm9sbG93cyBhIHdpemFyZCBpbiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IENoaWNhZ28/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyZXNkZW4gRmlsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgbWVzc2FnZSBvZiB0aGUgRG9scGhpbnMgaW4gIlRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSI/",
            "answer": "IlNvIGxvbmcsIGFuZCB0aGFua3MgZm9yIGFsbCB0aGUgZmlzaC4i"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgdGhlIGF1dGhvciBvZiAiVXNlcm5hbWUgRXZpZSI/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIFN1Z2c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWxpY2UgaW4gV29uZGVybGFuZCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBBbGljZSdzIGtpdHRlbj8=",
            "answer": "RGluYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgYW5kIEhhbSIgY29uc2lzdHMgb2Ygb25seSA1MCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgd29yZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgZW50cnkgd3JpdHRlbiBmb3IgdGhlIFNDUCBGb3VuZGF0aW9uIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRpdmUgd3JpdGluZyBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U0NQLTE3Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgTk9UIGEgYm9vayBpbiB0aGUgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIFNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdXNlIEVsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsIDE5ODQsIHdyaXR0ZW4gYnkgR2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdG90YWxpdGFyaWFuIHJlZ2ltZSB0aGF0IGNvbnRyb2xzIE9jZWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "SU5HU09D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycnkgUHJhdGNoZXR0J3MgRGlzY3dvcmxkIG5vdmVsICdXeXJkIFNpc3RlcnMnLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhcmUgbm90IG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgbWFpbiB3aXRjaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "V2lubnkgSGF0aGVyc2hhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhdXRob3Igb2YgdGhlIHNlcmllcyAiTWFsYXphbiBCb29rIG9mIHRoZSBGYWxsZW4iPw==",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIEVyaWtzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3JpZ2luYWxseSwgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBDaGFybGllIGZyb20gQ2hhcmxpZSBhbmQgdGhlIENob2NvbGF0ZSBGYWN0b3J5IHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZSBibGFjay4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSB3b3JrIGF1dGhvcmVkIGJ5IEZ5b2RvciBEb3N0b2V2c2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5uYSBLYXJlbmluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRob3Igd3JvdGUgdGhlIGVwaWMgbm92ZWwgV2FyIGFuZCBQZWFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFRvbHN0b3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgU2lyIEhhbmRlbCdzIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgaW4gIlRoZSBSYWlsd2F5IFNlcmllcyIgYW5kIGl0J3MgYW5pbWF0ZWQgY291bnRlcnBhcnQgIlRob21hcyBhbmQgRnJpZW5kcz8i",
            "answer": "RmFsY29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2h1Yi1OaWdndXJhdGggaXMgYSBjcmVhdHVyZSB0aGF0IHdhcyBjcmVhdGVkIGJ5IAlKLiBSLiBSLiBUb2xraWVuIGluIGhpcyBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIExvcmQgb2YgVGhlIFJpbmdzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgT2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgIkxhbW9yYSIgbWVhbiBpbiBUaHJvbmUgVGhlcmluPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhZG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgb2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IHRpdGxlIGlzIExvY2tlIGtub3duIGJ5IGluIHRoZSBjcmltaW5hbCB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRob3JuIG9mIENhbW9ycg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiQSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBBbmQgRmlyZSIgZmFudGFzeSBub3ZlbCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFIuIFIuIE1hcnRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCB3cm90ZSB0aGlzIGJvb2ssIHdoaWNoIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgb24gZ292ZXJubWVudCBvdmVyc2lnaHQu",
            "answer": "MTk4NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGFuZCBwb2V0IGZhbW91c2x5IHdyb3RlIHRoZSBsaW5lLCAiVGhlIGZlbWFsZSBvZiB0aGUgc3BlY2llcyBpcyBtb3JlIGRlYWRseSB0aGFuIHRoZSBtYWxlIj8=",
            "answer": "UnVkeWFyZCBLaXBsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgIlRoZSBNYXJ0aWFuIiwgaG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIE1hcmsgV2F0bmV5IHRyYXBwZWQgb24gTWFycyAoaW4gU29scyk/",
            "answer": "NTQ5IERheXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgYm9vaz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyBDb3JuZWxpdXMgRnVkZ2UncyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "T3N3YWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hvIGRvZXMgRHJhY28gTWFsZm95IGVuZCB1cCBtYXJyeWluZz8=",
            "answer": "QXN0b3JpYSBHcmVlbmdyYXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZXJtaW9uZSBHcmFuZ2VyJ3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSBpcyBKYWNrIERhd2tpbnMga25vd24gaW4gdGhlIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbCwgJ09saXZlciBUd2lzdCc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFydGZ1bCBEb2RnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGJvb2sgb2YgdGhlIE9sZCBUZXN0YW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "TnVtYmVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAnRmVhciBBbmQgTG9hdGhpbmcgSW4gTGFzIFZlZ2FzJz8=",
            "answer": "SHVudGVyIFMuIFRob21wc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE15c3RlcmlvdXMgSXNsYW5kLCBpbiBKdWxlcyBWZXJuZSdzICJUaGUgTXlzdGVyaW91cyBJc2xhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "TGluY29sbiBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIEVyaWMgQmxhaXIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBjaGlsZHJlbidzIHN0b3J5ICJUaGUgTGl0dGxlIE1hdGNoIEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFucyBDaHJpc3RpYW4gQW5kZXJzZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBIZWFkbWFzdGVyIER1bWJsZWRvcmUncyBmdWxsIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "QWxidXMgUGVyY2l2YWwgV3VsZnJpYyBCcmlhbiBEdW1ibGVkb3Jl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUaGUgSG9iYml0Iiwgd2hvIGtpbGxzIFNtYXVnPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5kZXIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZGlkIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBwdWJsaXNoIGZpdmUgbm92ZWxzIGJldHdlZW4gMTk3NyBhbmQgMTk4ND8=",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCYWNobWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlcidzIGRhZCdzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgUG90dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJPZiBNaWNlIEFuZCBNZW4iIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2sg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U3RlcGhlbiBDaGJvc2t5IHdyb3RlIHRoZSBib29rICdUaGUgUGVya3Mgb2YgQmVpbmcgQSBXYWxsZmxvd2VyJy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgSi5ELiBTYWxpbmdlcidzIG5vdmVsIENhdGNoZXIgaW4gdGhlIFJ5ZT8=",
            "answer": "SG9sZGVuIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9vayBzZXJpZXMgaXMgYnkgSmFtZXMgUGF0dGVyc29uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4aW11bSBSaWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsICJMb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBSaW5ncyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJpbmdzIG9mIHBvd2VyIHdlcmUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIG5vdmVscywgd2hhdCBtdXN0IGEgSG9nd2FydHMgc3R1ZGVudCBkbyB0byBlbnRlciB0aGUgUmF2ZW5jbGF3IENvbW1vbiBSb29tPw==",
            "answer": "QW5zd2VyIGEgcmlkZGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgbWVzc2FnZSBvZiB0aGUgRG9scGhpbnMgaW4gIlRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSI/",
            "answer": "IlNvIGxvbmcsIGFuZCB0aGFua3MgZm9yIGFsbCB0aGUgZmlzaC4i"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCAgdGhlIEFudGlxdWl0aWVzLCBJY2UgQWdlLCBhbmQgQWxsaWFuY2VzIGV4cGFuc2lvbnMgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBvbiB3aGljaCBjb250aW5lbnQ/",
            "answer": "VGVyaXNpYXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGljaCBwbGFuZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBIb21lbGFuZHMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "VWxncm90aGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBpcyB0aGVyZSBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBuYW1lZCBIb21lciBTaW1wc29uPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIERheSBvZiB0aGUgTG9jdXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBFcmFnb24ncyBkcmFnb24gaW4gIkVyYWdvbiI/",
            "answer": "U2FwaGlyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgZW50cnkgd3JpdHRlbiBmb3IgdGhlIFNDUCBGb3VuZGF0aW9uIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRpdmUgd3JpdGluZyBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U0NQLTE3Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgTk9UIGEgYm9vayBpbiB0aGUgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIFNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdXNlIEVsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsIDE5ODQsIHdyaXR0ZW4gYnkgR2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdG90YWxpdGFyaWFuIHJlZ2ltZSB0aGF0IGNvbnRyb2xzIE9jZWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "SU5HU09D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGNvLXdyb3RlICJUaGUgQ29tbXVuaXN0IE1hbmlmZXN0byIgYWxvbmdzaWRlIEthcmwgTWFyeD8=",
            "answer": "RnJpZWRyaWNoIEVuZ2Vscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmljdGlvbmFsIEVuZ2xpc2ggY291bnR5IHdhcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgVGhvbWFzIEhhcmR5J3Mgbm92ZWxzPw==",
            "answer": "V2Vzc2V4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBzZXJpZXMgb2YgYm9va3MsIGNvbWJpbmVkLCBhcmUgb3ZlciAxLDAwMCwwMDAgd29yZHMgaW4gbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhdXRob3Igb2YgdGhlIHNlcmllcyAiTWFsYXphbiBCb29rIG9mIHRoZSBGYWxsZW4iPw==",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIEVyaWtzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3JpZ2luYWxseSwgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBDaGFybGllIGZyb20gQ2hhcmxpZSBhbmQgdGhlIENob2NvbGF0ZSBGYWN0b3J5IHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZSBibGFjay4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRob3Igd3JvdGUgdGhlIGVwaWMgbm92ZWwgV2FyIGFuZCBQZWFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFRvbHN0b3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgU2lyIEhhbmRlbCdzIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgaW4gIlRoZSBSYWlsd2F5IFNlcmllcyIgYW5kIGl0J3MgYW5pbWF0ZWQgY291bnRlcnBhcnQgIlRob21hcyBhbmQgRnJpZW5kcz8i",
            "answer": "RmFsY29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2h1Yi1OaWdndXJhdGggaXMgYSBjcmVhdHVyZSB0aGF0IHdhcyBjcmVhdGVkIGJ5IAlKLiBSLiBSLiBUb2xraWVuIGluIGhpcyBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIExvcmQgb2YgVGhlIFJpbmdzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdG93biBpbiB3aGljaCBMaWx5IGFuZCBKYW1lcyBQb3R0ZXIgYXJlIGJ1cmllZD8=",
            "answer": "R29kcmljJ3MgSG9sbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgT2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgIkxhbW9yYSIgbWVhbiBpbiBUaHJvbmUgVGhlcmluPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhZG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgVGhyZWUgS2luZ2RvbXMsIHdobyB3YXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBQZWFjaCBHYXJkZW4gT2F0aD8=",
            "answer": "WmhhbyBZdW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhdXRob3JzIHdhcyBub3QgYm9ybiBpbiBFbmdsYW5kPyA=",
            "answer": "QXJ0aHVyIENvbmFuIERveWxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAiTW9ieS1EaWNrIj8=",
            "answer": "SGVybWFuIE1lbHZpbGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2FwdGFpbiBOZW1vJ3Mgc3VibWFyaW5lIGluICIyMCwwMDAgTGVhZ3VlcyBVbmRlciB0aGUgU2VhIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5hdXRpbHVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAxOTY3IGhvcnJvciBub3ZlbCAiUm9zZW1hcnkncyBCYWJ5Ij8=",
            "answer": "SXJhIExldmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZXJtaW9uZSBHcmFuZ2VyJ3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb3NpdGlvbiBkb2VzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBwbGF5IGluIFF1aWRkaXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "U2Vla2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGJvb2sgb2YgdGhlIE9sZCBUZXN0YW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "TnVtYmVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAnRmVhciBBbmQgTG9hdGhpbmcgSW4gTGFzIFZlZ2FzJz8=",
            "answer": "SHVudGVyIFMuIFRob21wc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgQW5kIEhhbSIgaXMgYSBib29rIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIFNldXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE15c3RlcmlvdXMgSXNsYW5kLCBpbiBKdWxlcyBWZXJuZSdzICJUaGUgTXlzdGVyaW91cyBJc2xhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "TGluY29sbiBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIEVyaWMgQmxhaXIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlbiBuYW1lIG9mIG5vdmVsaXN0LCBNYXJ5IEFubiBFdmFucz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEVsaW90"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgMTk4NCB3YXMgcHVibGlzaGVkIGluIDE5NDku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5kZXIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZGlkIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBwdWJsaXNoIGZpdmUgbm92ZWxzIGJldHdlZW4gMTk3NyBhbmQgMTk4ND8=",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCYWNobWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlcidzIGRhZCdzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgUG90dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJPZiBNaWNlIEFuZCBNZW4iIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2sg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHllYXIgMTgxOCwgbm92ZWxpc3QgTWFyeSBTaGVsbHkgaXMgY3JlZGl0ZWQgd2l0aCB3cml0aW5nIGEgZmljdGlvbiBub3ZlbCBhbmQgY3JlYXRpbmcgdGhpcyBpbmZhbW91cyBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWluJ3MgbW9uc3Rlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkVsZW1lbnRhcnksIG15IGRlYXIgV2F0c29uIiBpcyBhIHBocmFzZSB0aGF0IGlzIG5ldmVyIHRydWx5IHNhaWQgd2l0aGluIHRoZSBDb25hbiBEb3lsZSBib29rcyBvZiBTaGVybG9jayBIb2xtZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgaGVhZGVkIGRvZyBpbiBIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIgYW5kIHRoZSBTb3JjZXJlcidzIFN0b25lPw==",
            "answer": "Rmx1ZmZ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgSi5ELiBTYWxpbmdlcidzIG5vdmVsIENhdGNoZXIgaW4gdGhlIFJ5ZT8=",
            "answer": "SG9sZGVuIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcyBib29rIGJ5IEFydGh1ciBDb25hbiBEb3lsZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBTdHVkeSBpbiBTY2FybGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgYm9vayAiVGhlIFNpbGVuY2Ugb2YgdGhlIExhbWJzIiBnZXQgaXRzIHRpdGxlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "VGhlIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyJ3MgdHJhdW1hIGluIGNoaWxkaG9vZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsICJMb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBSaW5ncyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJpbmdzIG9mIHBvd2VyIHdlcmUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIG5vdmVscywgd2hhdCBtdXN0IGEgSG9nd2FydHMgc3R1ZGVudCBkbyB0byBlbnRlciB0aGUgUmF2ZW5jbGF3IENvbW1vbiBSb29tPw==",
            "answer": "QW5zd2VyIGEgcmlkZGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSB3b3JrIGRvbmUgYnkgU2hha2VzcGVhcmU/",
            "answer": "VHJpYWwgb2YgVGVtcGVyYW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBib29rIHNlcmllcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYnkgSmltIEJ1dGNoZXIgZm9sbG93cyBhIHdpemFyZCBpbiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IENoaWNhZ28/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyZXNkZW4gRmlsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgbWVzc2FnZSBvZiB0aGUgRG9scGhpbnMgaW4gIlRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSI/",
            "answer": "IlNvIGxvbmcsIGFuZCB0aGFua3MgZm9yIGFsbCB0aGUgZmlzaC4i"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFrZSBhbmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgdGhlIHRvdXIgdmVoaWNsZXMgaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiICgxOTkwKT8=",
            "answer": "MTk4OSBUb3lvdGEgTGFuZCBDcnVpc2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgc2VyaWVzICJPZGQgVGhvbWFzIiwgRGFubnkgSmVzc3VwIGhhcyB3aGF0IGdlbmV0aWMgZGlzZWFzZT8g",
            "answer": "IE9zdGVvZ2VuZXNpcyBJbXBlcmZlY3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgdGhlIGF1dGhvciBvZiAiVXNlcm5hbWUgRXZpZSI/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIFN1Z2c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB0aGUgRmFsbGVuIEVtcGlyZXMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIG9uIHdoaWNoIGNvbnRpbmVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2FycGFkaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGljaCBwbGFuZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBIb21lbGFuZHMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "VWxncm90aGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWxpY2UgaW4gV29uZGVybGFuZCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBBbGljZSdzIGtpdHRlbj8=",
            "answer": "RGluYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgYm9vayBpbiBHZW9yZ2UgUi4gUi4gTWFydGluJ3MgJ0EgU29uZyBvZiBJY2UgYW5kIEZpcmUnIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "QSBDbGFzaCBvZiBLaW5ncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBFcmFnb24ncyBkcmFnb24gaW4gIkVyYWdvbiI/",
            "answer": "U2FwaGlyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgZW50cnkgd3JpdHRlbiBmb3IgdGhlIFNDUCBGb3VuZGF0aW9uIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRpdmUgd3JpdGluZyBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U0NQLTE3Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsIDE5ODQsIHdyaXR0ZW4gYnkgR2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdG90YWxpdGFyaWFuIHJlZ2ltZSB0aGF0IGNvbnRyb2xzIE9jZWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "SU5HU09D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm92ZWwgYnkgSm9obiBHcmlzaGFtIHdhcyBjb25jZWl2ZWQgb24gYSByb2FkIHRyaXAgdG8gRmxvcmlkYSB3aGlsZSB0aGlua2luZyBhYm91dCBzdG9sZW4gYm9va3Mgd2l0aCBoaXMgd2lmZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FtaW5vIElzbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmljdGlvbmFsIEVuZ2xpc2ggY291bnR5IHdhcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgVGhvbWFzIEhhcmR5J3Mgbm92ZWxzPw==",
            "answer": "V2Vzc2V4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBieSBNYXJrIFR3YWluIGRpZCBhIGJlZ2dhciBhbmQgUHJpbmNlIG9mIFdhbGVzIHN3aXRjaCBjbG90aGVzLCBhbmQgbGVhcm4gYWJvdXQgc29jaWFsIGNsYXNzIGluZXF1YWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZSBhbmQgdGhlIFBhdXBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3JpZ2luYWxseSwgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBDaGFybGllIGZyb20gQ2hhcmxpZSBhbmQgdGhlIENob2NvbGF0ZSBGYWN0b3J5IHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZSBibGFjay4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSB3b3JrIGF1dGhvcmVkIGJ5IEZ5b2RvciBEb3N0b2V2c2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5uYSBLYXJlbmluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgU2lyIEhhbmRlbCdzIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgaW4gIlRoZSBSYWlsd2F5IFNlcmllcyIgYW5kIGl0J3MgYW5pbWF0ZWQgY291bnRlcnBhcnQgIlRob21hcyBhbmQgRnJpZW5kcz8i",
            "answer": "RmFsY29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgVGhyZWUgS2luZ2RvbXMsIHdobyB3YXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBQZWFjaCBHYXJkZW4gT2F0aD8=",
            "answer": "WmhhbyBZdW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiQSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBBbmQgRmlyZSIgZmFudGFzeSBub3ZlbCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFIuIFIuIE1hcnRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGFuZCBwb2V0IGZhbW91c2x5IHdyb3RlIHRoZSBsaW5lLCAiVGhlIGZlbWFsZSBvZiB0aGUgc3BlY2llcyBpcyBtb3JlIGRlYWRseSB0aGFuIHRoZSBtYWxlIj8=",
            "answer": "UnVkeWFyZCBLaXBsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJlYXRyaXggUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzLCB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgYW5pbWFsIGlzIFRvbW15IEJyb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "QmFkZ2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2FwdGFpbiBOZW1vJ3Mgc3VibWFyaW5lIGluICIyMCwwMDAgTGVhZ3VlcyBVbmRlciB0aGUgU2VhIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5hdXRpbHVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyBDb3JuZWxpdXMgRnVkZ2UncyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "T3N3YWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZXJtaW9uZSBHcmFuZ2VyJ3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdzLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGZhdGhlciBvZiB0aGUgZHdhcmYgR2ltbGk/",
            "answer": "R2xvaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSBpcyBKYWNrIERhd2tpbnMga25vd24gaW4gdGhlIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbCwgJ09saXZlciBUd2lzdCc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFydGZ1bCBEb2RnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGJvb2sgb2YgdGhlIE9sZCBUZXN0YW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "TnVtYmVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAnRmVhciBBbmQgTG9hdGhpbmcgSW4gTGFzIFZlZ2FzJz8=",
            "answer": "SHVudGVyIFMuIFRob21wc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHNweSBub3ZlbGlzdCB3cm90ZSB0aGUgY2hpbGRyZW5zJyBzdG9yeSAiQ2hpdHR5LUNoaXR0eS1CYW5nLUJhbmciPw==",
            "answer": "SWFuIEZsZW1pbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE15c3RlcmlvdXMgSXNsYW5kLCBpbiBKdWxlcyBWZXJuZSdzICJUaGUgTXlzdGVyaW91cyBJc2xhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "TGluY29sbiBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIEVyaWMgQmxhaXIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBjaGlsZHJlbidzIHN0b3J5ICJUaGUgTGl0dGxlIE1hdGNoIEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFucyBDaHJpc3RpYW4gQW5kZXJzZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBIZWFkbWFzdGVyIER1bWJsZWRvcmUncyBmdWxsIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "QWxidXMgUGVyY2l2YWwgV3VsZnJpYyBCcmlhbiBEdW1ibGVkb3Jl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUaGUgSG9iYml0Iiwgd2hvIGtpbGxzIFNtYXVnPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJCZXJlbnN0ZWluIEJlYXJzIiBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiB0aGUgZWR1Y2F0aW9uYWwgY2hpbGRyZW4ncyBib29rIHNlcmllcycgbmFtZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5kZXIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZGlkIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBwdWJsaXNoIGZpdmUgbm92ZWxzIGJldHdlZW4gMTk3NyBhbmQgMTk4ND8=",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCYWNobWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJKYW5lIEV5cmUiIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxvdHRlIEJyb250w6s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSB5b3VuZyBhZHVsdCBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIEZhdWx0IGluIE91ciBTdGFycyI/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBHcmVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5nIGNvbXBsZXRlZCAiSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGFuZCB0aGUgRGVhdGhseSBIYWxsb3dzIiBpbiB3aGljaCBob3RlbCBpbiBFZGluYnVyZ2gsIFNjb3RsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhbG1vcmFs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHllYXIgMTgxOCwgbm92ZWxpc3QgTWFyeSBTaGVsbHkgaXMgY3JlZGl0ZWQgd2l0aCB3cml0aW5nIGEgZmljdGlvbiBub3ZlbCBhbmQgY3JlYXRpbmcgdGhpcyBpbmZhbW91cyBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWluJ3MgbW9uc3Rlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkVsZW1lbnRhcnksIG15IGRlYXIgV2F0c29uIiBpcyBhIHBocmFzZSB0aGF0IGlzIG5ldmVyIHRydWx5IHNhaWQgd2l0aGluIHRoZSBDb25hbiBEb3lsZSBib29rcyBvZiBTaGVybG9jayBIb2xtZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcyBib29rIGJ5IEFydGh1ciBDb25hbiBEb3lsZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBTdHVkeSBpbiBTY2FybGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gYXV0aG9yIHdhcyBhbHNvIGEgYnVkZGluZyB0cmF2ZWwgd3JpdGVyIGFuZCB3cm90ZSBvZiBoaXMgYWR2ZW50dXJlcyB3aXRoIGhpcyBkb2cgQ2hhcmxleT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIFRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSBib29rLCB0aGUgYW5zd2VyIHRvIGxpZmUsIHRoZSB1bml2ZXJzZSBhbmQgZXZlcnl0aGluZyBlbHNlIGlzLi4u",
            "answer": "NDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgYm9vayAiVGhlIFNpbGVuY2Ugb2YgdGhlIExhbWJzIiBnZXQgaXRzIHRpdGxlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "VGhlIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyJ3MgdHJhdW1hIGluIGNoaWxkaG9vZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFycnkgUG90dGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIG9uIEp1bHkgMzFzdCwgMTk4MC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9vayBzZXJpZXMgaXMgYnkgSmFtZXMgUGF0dGVyc29uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4aW11bSBSaWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsICJMb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBSaW5ncyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJpbmdzIG9mIHBvd2VyIHdlcmUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgbWVzc2FnZSBvZiB0aGUgRG9scGhpbnMgaW4gIlRoZSBIaXRjaGhpa2VyJ3MgR3VpZGUgdG8gdGhlIEdhbGF4eSI/",
            "answer": "IlNvIGxvbmcsIGFuZCB0aGFua3MgZm9yIGFsbCB0aGUgZmlzaC4i"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFrZSBhbmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgdGhlIHRvdXIgdmVoaWNsZXMgaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiICgxOTkwKT8=",
            "answer": "MTk4OSBUb3lvdGEgTGFuZCBDcnVpc2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgc2VyaWVzICJPZGQgVGhvbWFzIiwgRGFubnkgSmVzc3VwIGhhcyB3aGF0IGdlbmV0aWMgZGlzZWFzZT8g",
            "answer": "IE9zdGVvZ2VuZXNpcyBJbXBlcmZlY3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGljaCBwbGFuZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBIb21lbGFuZHMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "VWxncm90aGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWxpY2UgaW4gV29uZGVybGFuZCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBBbGljZSdzIGtpdHRlbj8=",
            "answer": "RGluYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBFcmFnb24ncyBkcmFnb24gaW4gIkVyYWdvbiI/",
            "answer": "U2FwaGlyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgTk9UIGEgYm9vayBpbiB0aGUgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIFNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdXNlIEVsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm92ZWwgYnkgSm9obiBHcmlzaGFtIHdhcyBjb25jZWl2ZWQgb24gYSByb2FkIHRyaXAgdG8gRmxvcmlkYSB3aGlsZSB0aGlua2luZyBhYm91dCBzdG9sZW4gYm9va3Mgd2l0aCBoaXMgd2lmZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FtaW5vIElzbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGNvLXdyb3RlICJUaGUgQ29tbXVuaXN0IE1hbmlmZXN0byIgYWxvbmdzaWRlIEthcmwgTWFyeD8=",
            "answer": "RnJpZWRyaWNoIEVuZ2Vscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBzZXJpZXMgb2YgYm9va3MsIGNvbWJpbmVkLCBhcmUgb3ZlciAxLDAwMCwwMDAgd29yZHMgaW4gbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSB3b3JrIGF1dGhvcmVkIGJ5IEZ5b2RvciBEb3N0b2V2c2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5uYSBLYXJlbmluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRob3Igd3JvdGUgdGhlIGVwaWMgbm92ZWwgV2FyIGFuZCBQZWFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFRvbHN0b3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2h1Yi1OaWdndXJhdGggaXMgYSBjcmVhdHVyZSB0aGF0IHdhcyBjcmVhdGVkIGJ5IAlKLiBSLiBSLiBUb2xraWVuIGluIGhpcyBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIExvcmQgb2YgVGhlIFJpbmdzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgVGhyZWUgS2luZ2RvbXMsIHdobyB3YXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBQZWFjaCBHYXJkZW4gT2F0aD8=",
            "answer": "WmhhbyBZdW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCB3cm90ZSB0aGlzIGJvb2ssIHdoaWNoIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgb24gZ292ZXJubWVudCBvdmVyc2lnaHQu",
            "answer": "MTk4NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJlYXRyaXggUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzLCB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgYW5pbWFsIGlzIFRvbW15IEJyb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "QmFkZ2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAiTW9ieS1EaWNrIj8=",
            "answer": "SGVybWFuIE1lbHZpbGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIHRoZSBDaHJvbmljbGVzIG9mIE5hcm5pYSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2FwdGFpbiBOZW1vJ3Mgc3VibWFyaW5lIGluICIyMCwwMDAgTGVhZ3VlcyBVbmRlciB0aGUgU2VhIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5hdXRpbHVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgIlRoZSBNYXJ0aWFuIiwgaG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIE1hcmsgV2F0bmV5IHRyYXBwZWQgb24gTWFycyAoaW4gU29scyk/",
            "answer": "NTQ5IERheXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgYm9vaz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyBDb3JuZWxpdXMgRnVkZ2UncyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "T3N3YWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBSb24gV2Vhc2xleSdzIG1pZGRsZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QmlsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb3NpdGlvbiBkb2VzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBwbGF5IGluIFF1aWRkaXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "U2Vla2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSBpcyBKYWNrIERhd2tpbnMga25vd24gaW4gdGhlIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbCwgJ09saXZlciBUd2lzdCc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFydGZ1bCBEb2RnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGJvb2sgb2YgdGhlIE9sZCBUZXN0YW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "TnVtYmVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWJlbCBNYWd3aXRjaCBpcyBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbD8=",
            "answer": "R3JlYXQgRXhwZWN0YXRpb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgQW5kIEhhbSIgaXMgYSBib29rIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIFNldXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHNweSBub3ZlbGlzdCB3cm90ZSB0aGUgY2hpbGRyZW5zJyBzdG9yeSAiQ2hpdHR5LUNoaXR0eS1CYW5nLUJhbmciPw==",
            "answer": "SWFuIEZsZW1pbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlbiBuYW1lIG9mIG5vdmVsaXN0LCBNYXJ5IEFubiBFdmFucz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEVsaW90"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBjaGlsZHJlbidzIHN0b3J5ICJUaGUgTGl0dGxlIE1hdGNoIEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFucyBDaHJpc3RpYW4gQW5kZXJzZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUaGUgSG9iYml0Iiwgd2hvIGtpbGxzIFNtYXVnPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJCZXJlbnN0ZWluIEJlYXJzIiBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiB0aGUgZWR1Y2F0aW9uYWwgY2hpbGRyZW4ncyBib29rIHNlcmllcycgbmFtZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgMTk4NCB3YXMgcHVibGlzaGVkIGluIDE5NDku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5kZXIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZGlkIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBwdWJsaXNoIGZpdmUgbm92ZWxzIGJldHdlZW4gMTk3NyBhbmQgMTk4ND8=",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBCYWNobWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJKYW5lIEV5cmUiIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxvdHRlIEJyb250w6s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSB5b3VuZyBhZHVsdCBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIEZhdWx0IGluIE91ciBTdGFycyI/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBHcmVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgSi5ELiBTYWxpbmdlcidzIG5vdmVsIENhdGNoZXIgaW4gdGhlIFJ5ZT8=",
            "answer": "SG9sZGVuIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcyBib29rIGJ5IEFydGh1ciBDb25hbiBEb3lsZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBTdHVkeSBpbiBTY2FybGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gYXV0aG9yIHdhcyBhbHNvIGEgYnVkZGluZyB0cmF2ZWwgd3JpdGVyIGFuZCB3cm90ZSBvZiBoaXMgYWR2ZW50dXJlcyB3aXRoIGhpcyBkb2cgQ2hhcmxleT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFycnkgUG90dGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIG9uIEp1bHkgMzFzdCwgMTk4MC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9vayBzZXJpZXMgaXMgYnkgSmFtZXMgUGF0dGVyc29uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4aW11bSBSaWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsICJMb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBSaW5ncyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJpbmdzIG9mIHBvd2VyIHdlcmUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FuZyB0aGF0IFBvbnlib3kgaXMgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIGluIHRoZSBib29rLCBUaGUgT3V0c2lkZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdyZWFzZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSB3b3JrIGRvbmUgYnkgU2hha2VzcGVhcmU/",
            "answer": "VHJpYWwgb2YgVGVtcGVyYW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTaGVybG9jayBIb2xtZXMncyBicm90aGVyPw==",
            "answer": "TXljcm9mdCBIb2xtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBib29rIHNlcmllcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYnkgSmltIEJ1dGNoZXIgZm9sbG93cyBhIHdpemFyZCBpbiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IENoaWNhZ28/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyZXNkZW4gRmlsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFrZSBhbmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgdGhlIHRvdXIgdmVoaWNsZXMgaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiICgxOTkwKT8=",
            "answer": "MTk4OSBUb3lvdGEgTGFuZCBDcnVpc2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgc2VyaWVzICJPZGQgVGhvbWFzIiwgRGFubnkgSmVzc3VwIGhhcyB3aGF0IGdlbmV0aWMgZGlzZWFzZT8g",
            "answer": "IE9zdGVvZ2VuZXNpcyBJbXBlcmZlY3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkxpdHRsZSBXb21lbiIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBNYXJjaCBzaXN0ZXJzIG1hcnJpZWQgTGF1cmllPw==",
            "answer": "QW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCAgdGhlIEFudGlxdWl0aWVzLCBJY2UgQWdlLCBhbmQgQWxsaWFuY2VzIGV4cGFuc2lvbnMgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBvbiB3aGljaCBjb250aW5lbnQ/",
            "answer": "VGVyaXNpYXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgYm9vayBpbiBHZW9yZ2UgUi4gUi4gTWFydGluJ3MgJ0EgU29uZyBvZiBJY2UgYW5kIEZpcmUnIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "QSBDbGFzaCBvZiBLaW5ncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBpcyB0aGVyZSBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBuYW1lZCBIb21lciBTaW1wc29uPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIERheSBvZiB0aGUgTG9jdXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgYW5kIEhhbSIgY29uc2lzdHMgb2Ygb25seSA1MCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgd29yZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGNvLXdyb3RlICJUaGUgQ29tbXVuaXN0IE1hbmlmZXN0byIgYWxvbmdzaWRlIEthcmwgTWFyeD8=",
            "answer": "RnJpZWRyaWNoIEVuZ2Vscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmljdGlvbmFsIEVuZ2xpc2ggY291bnR5IHdhcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgVGhvbWFzIEhhcmR5J3Mgbm92ZWxzPw==",
            "answer": "V2Vzc2V4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycnkgUHJhdGNoZXR0J3MgRGlzY3dvcmxkIG5vdmVsICdXeXJkIFNpc3RlcnMnLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhcmUgbm90IG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgbWFpbiB3aXRjaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "V2lubnkgSGF0aGVyc2hhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSB3b3JrIGF1dGhvcmVkIGJ5IEZ5b2RvciBEb3N0b2V2c2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5uYSBLYXJlbmluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgVGhyZWUgS2luZ2RvbXMsIHdobyB3YXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBQZWFjaCBHYXJkZW4gT2F0aD8=",
            "answer": "WmhhbyBZdW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhdXRob3JzIHdhcyBub3QgYm9ybiBpbiBFbmdsYW5kPyA=",
            "answer": "QXJ0aHVyIENvbmFuIERveWxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "Si5LLiBSb3dsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiQSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBBbmQgRmlyZSIgZmFudGFzeSBub3ZlbCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFIuIFIuIE1hcnRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCB3cm90ZSB0aGlzIGJvb2ssIHdoaWNoIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgb24gZ292ZXJubWVudCBvdmVyc2lnaHQu",
            "answer": "MTk4NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGFuZCBwb2V0IGZhbW91c2x5IHdyb3RlIHRoZSBsaW5lLCAiVGhlIGZlbWFsZSBvZiB0aGUgc3BlY2llcyBpcyBtb3JlIGRlYWRseSB0aGFuIHRoZSBtYWxlIj8=",
            "answer": "UnVkeWFyZCBLaXBsaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGJvb2sgaXMgc3ViLXRpdGxlZCAnVGhlIE1vZGVybiBQcm9tZXRoZXVzJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIHRoZSBDaHJvbmljbGVzIG9mIE5hcm5pYSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2FwdGFpbiBOZW1vJ3Mgc3VibWFyaW5lIGluICIyMCwwMDAgTGVhZ3VlcyBVbmRlciB0aGUgU2VhIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5hdXRpbHVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgYm9vaz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdzLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGZhdGhlciBvZiB0aGUgZHdhcmYgR2ltbGk/",
            "answer": "R2xvaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb3NpdGlvbiBkb2VzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBwbGF5IGluIFF1aWRkaXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "U2Vla2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAnRmVhciBBbmQgTG9hdGhpbmcgSW4gTGFzIFZlZ2FzJz8=",
            "answer": "SHVudGVyIFMuIFRob21wc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWJlbCBNYWd3aXRjaCBpcyBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbD8=",
            "answer": "R3JlYXQgRXhwZWN0YXRpb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBjaGlsZHJlbidzIHN0b3J5ICJUaGUgTGl0dGxlIE1hdGNoIEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFucyBDaHJpc3RpYW4gQW5kZXJzZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUaGUgSG9iYml0Iiwgd2hvIGtpbGxzIFNtYXVnPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJCZXJlbnN0ZWluIEJlYXJzIiBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiB0aGUgZWR1Y2F0aW9uYWwgY2hpbGRyZW4ncyBib29rIHNlcmllcycgbmFtZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgMTk4NCB3YXMgcHVibGlzaGVkIGluIDE5NDku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlcidzIGRhZCdzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgUG90dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJKYW5lIEV5cmUiIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxvdHRlIEJyb250w6s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZG9lcyBDaGFybGllIE5PVCByZWFkIGluIFRoZSBQZXJrcyBvZiBCZWluZyBhIFdhbGxmbG93ZXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdyYXBlcyBvZiBXcmF0aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgaGVhZGVkIGRvZyBpbiBIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIgYW5kIHRoZSBTb3JjZXJlcidzIFN0b25lPw==",
            "answer": "Rmx1ZmZ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIEFkb2xmIEhpdGxlcidzIGF1dG9iaW9ncmFwaHkgIk1laW4gS2FtcGYiIGlzIHdoYXQgd2hlbiB0cmFuc2xhdGVkIHRvIEVuZ2xpc2g/",
            "answer": "TXkgU3RydWdnbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcyBib29rIGJ5IEFydGh1ciBDb25hbiBEb3lsZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBTdHVkeSBpbiBTY2FybGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gYXV0aG9yIHdhcyBhbHNvIGEgYnVkZGluZyB0cmF2ZWwgd3JpdGVyIGFuZCB3cm90ZSBvZiBoaXMgYWR2ZW50dXJlcyB3aXRoIGhpcyBkb2cgQ2hhcmxleT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFycnkgUG90dGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIG9uIEp1bHkgMzFzdCwgMTk4MC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9vayBzZXJpZXMgaXMgYnkgSmFtZXMgUGF0dGVyc29uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4aW11bSBSaWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSB3b3JrIGRvbmUgYnkgU2hha2VzcGVhcmU/",
            "answer": "VHJpYWwgb2YgVGVtcGVyYW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBib29rIHNlcmllcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYnkgSmltIEJ1dGNoZXIgZm9sbG93cyBhIHdpemFyZCBpbiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IENoaWNhZ28/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyZXNkZW4gRmlsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgc2VyaWVzICJPZGQgVGhvbWFzIiwgRGFubnkgSmVzc3VwIGhhcyB3aGF0IGdlbmV0aWMgZGlzZWFzZT8g",
            "answer": "IE9zdGVvZ2VuZXNpcyBJbXBlcmZlY3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkxpdHRsZSBXb21lbiIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBNYXJjaCBzaXN0ZXJzIG1hcnJpZWQgTGF1cmllPw==",
            "answer": "QW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCAgdGhlIEFudGlxdWl0aWVzLCBJY2UgQWdlLCBhbmQgQWxsaWFuY2VzIGV4cGFuc2lvbnMgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBvbiB3aGljaCBjb250aW5lbnQ/",
            "answer": "VGVyaXNpYXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgYm9vayBpbiBHZW9yZ2UgUi4gUi4gTWFydGluJ3MgJ0EgU29uZyBvZiBJY2UgYW5kIEZpcmUnIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "QSBDbGFzaCBvZiBLaW5ncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgYW5kIEhhbSIgY29uc2lzdHMgb2Ygb25seSA1MCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgd29yZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBFcmFnb24ncyBkcmFnb24gaW4gIkVyYWdvbiI/",
            "answer": "U2FwaGlyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgZW50cnkgd3JpdHRlbiBmb3IgdGhlIFNDUCBGb3VuZGF0aW9uIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRpdmUgd3JpdGluZyBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U0NQLTE3Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgTk9UIGEgYm9vayBpbiB0aGUgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIFNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdXNlIEVsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm92ZWwgYnkgSm9obiBHcmlzaGFtIHdhcyBjb25jZWl2ZWQgb24gYSByb2FkIHRyaXAgdG8gRmxvcmlkYSB3aGlsZSB0aGlua2luZyBhYm91dCBzdG9sZW4gYm9va3Mgd2l0aCBoaXMgd2lmZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FtaW5vIElzbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmljdGlvbmFsIEVuZ2xpc2ggY291bnR5IHdhcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgVGhvbWFzIEhhcmR5J3Mgbm92ZWxzPw==",
            "answer": "V2Vzc2V4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBieSBNYXJrIFR3YWluIGRpZCBhIGJlZ2dhciBhbmQgUHJpbmNlIG9mIFdhbGVzIHN3aXRjaCBjbG90aGVzLCBhbmQgbGVhcm4gYWJvdXQgc29jaWFsIGNsYXNzIGluZXF1YWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZSBhbmQgdGhlIFBhdXBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBzZXJpZXMgb2YgYm9va3MsIGNvbWJpbmVkLCBhcmUgb3ZlciAxLDAwMCwwMDAgd29yZHMgaW4gbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhdXRob3Igb2YgdGhlIHNlcmllcyAiTWFsYXphbiBCb29rIG9mIHRoZSBGYWxsZW4iPw==",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIEVyaWtzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRob3Igd3JvdGUgdGhlIGVwaWMgbm92ZWwgV2FyIGFuZCBQZWFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFRvbHN0b3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgT2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgIkxhbW9yYSIgbWVhbiBpbiBUaHJvbmUgVGhlcmluPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhZG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgb2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IHRpdGxlIGlzIExvY2tlIGtub3duIGJ5IGluIHRoZSBjcmltaW5hbCB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRob3JuIG9mIENhbW9ycg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiQSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBBbmQgRmlyZSIgZmFudGFzeSBub3ZlbCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFIuIFIuIE1hcnRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCB3cm90ZSB0aGlzIGJvb2ssIHdoaWNoIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgb24gZ292ZXJubWVudCBvdmVyc2lnaHQu",
            "answer": "MTk4NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBub3ZlbCAiTW9ieS1EaWNrIj8=",
            "answer": "SGVybWFuIE1lbHZpbGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJvb2sgIlRoZSBNYXJ0aWFuIiwgaG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIE1hcmsgV2F0bmV5IHRyYXBwZWQgb24gTWFycyAoaW4gU29scyk/",
            "answer": "NTQ5IERheXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAxOTY3IGhvcnJvciBub3ZlbCAiUm9zZW1hcnkncyBCYWJ5Ij8=",
            "answer": "SXJhIExldmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyBDb3JuZWxpdXMgRnVkZ2UncyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "T3N3YWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hvIGRvZXMgRHJhY28gTWFsZm95IGVuZCB1cCBtYXJyeWluZz8=",
            "answer": "QXN0b3JpYSBHcmVlbmdyYXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdzLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGZhdGhlciBvZiB0aGUgZHdhcmYgR2ltbGk/",
            "answer": "R2xvaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb3NpdGlvbiBkb2VzIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBwbGF5IGluIFF1aWRkaXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "U2Vla2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSBpcyBKYWNrIERhd2tpbnMga25vd24gaW4gdGhlIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbCwgJ09saXZlciBUd2lzdCc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFydGZ1bCBEb2RnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGJvb2sgb2YgdGhlIE9sZCBUZXN0YW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "TnVtYmVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWJlbCBNYWd3aXRjaCBpcyBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIENoYXJsZXMgRGlja2VucyBub3ZlbD8=",
            "answer": "R3JlYXQgRXhwZWN0YXRpb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkdyZWVuIEVnZ3MgQW5kIEhhbSIgaXMgYSBib29rIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIFNldXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE15c3RlcmlvdXMgSXNsYW5kLCBpbiBKdWxlcyBWZXJuZSdzICJUaGUgTXlzdGVyaW91cyBJc2xhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "TGluY29sbiBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlbiBuYW1lIG9mIG5vdmVsaXN0LCBNYXJ5IEFubiBFdmFucz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEVsaW90"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJCZXJlbnN0ZWluIEJlYXJzIiBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiB0aGUgZWR1Y2F0aW9uYWwgY2hpbGRyZW4ncyBib29rIHNlcmllcycgbmFtZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJKYW5lIEV5cmUiIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxvdHRlIEJyb250w6s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdmVsICJPZiBNaWNlIEFuZCBNZW4iIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoYXQgYXV0aG9yPyA=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2sg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHllYXIgMTgxOCwgbm92ZWxpc3QgTWFyeSBTaGVsbHkgaXMgY3JlZGl0ZWQgd2l0aCB3cml0aW5nIGEgZmljdGlvbiBub3ZlbCBhbmQgY3JlYXRpbmcgdGhpcyBpbmZhbW91cyBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtlbnN0ZWluJ3MgbW9uc3Rlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgSi5ELiBTYWxpbmdlcidzIG5vdmVsIENhdGNoZXIgaW4gdGhlIFJ5ZT8=",
            "answer": "SG9sZGVuIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gYXV0aG9yIHdhcyBhbHNvIGEgYnVkZGluZyB0cmF2ZWwgd3JpdGVyIGFuZCB3cm90ZSBvZiBoaXMgYWR2ZW50dXJlcyB3aXRoIGhpcyBkb2cgQ2hhcmxleT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBTdGVpbmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIlRoZSBMaXR0bGUgUHJpbmNlIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieS4uLg==",
            "answer": "QW50b2luZSBkZSBTYWludC1FeHVww6lyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgYm9vayAiVGhlIFNpbGVuY2Ugb2YgdGhlIExhbWJzIiBnZXQgaXRzIHRpdGxlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "VGhlIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyJ3MgdHJhdW1hIGluIGNoaWxkaG9vZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWljaGFlbCBDcmljaHRvbidzIG5vdmVsICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiwgSm9obiBIYW1tb25kIG1lZXRzIGhpcyBkZW1pc2UgYXQgdGhlIGNsYXdzIG9mIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvY29tcHNvZ25hdGh1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIiIG5vdmVscywgd2hhdCBtdXN0IGEgSG9nd2FydHMgc3R1ZGVudCBkbyB0byBlbnRlciB0aGUgUmF2ZW5jbGF3IENvbW1vbiBSb29tPw==",
            "answer": "QW5zd2VyIGEgcmlkZGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FuZyB0aGF0IFBvbnlib3kgaXMgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIGluIHRoZSBib29rLCBUaGUgT3V0c2lkZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdyZWFzZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvb2sgIkZhaHJlbmhlaXQgNDUxIiB3YXMgd3JpdHRlbiBieSB3aG9tPw==",
            "answer": "UmF5IEJyYWRidXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBib29rIHNlcmllcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYnkgSmltIEJ1dGNoZXIgZm9sbG93cyBhIHdpemFyZCBpbiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IENoaWNhZ28/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyZXNkZW4gRmlsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFyZ2FyZXQgQXR3b29kJ3MgIlRoZSBIYW5kbWFpZCdzIFRhbGUiLCB3aGF0IGlzIE9mZnJlZCdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBpbXBsaWVkIHRvIGJlPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgdGhlIGF1dGhvciBvZiAiVXNlcm5hbWUgRXZpZSI/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIFN1Z2c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkxpdHRsZSBXb21lbiIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBNYXJjaCBzaXN0ZXJzIG1hcnJpZWQgTGF1cmllPw==",
            "answer": "QW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB0aGUgRmFsbGVuIEVtcGlyZXMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIG9uIHdoaWNoIGNvbnRpbmVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2FycGFkaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZ2ljOiBUaGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGljaCBwbGFuZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBIb21lbGFuZHMgZXhwYW5zaW9uIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "VWxncm90aGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWxpY2UgaW4gV29uZGVybGFuZCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBBbGljZSdzIGtpdHRlbj8=",
            "answer": "RGluYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBpcyB0aGVyZSBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBuYW1lZCBIb21lciBTaW1wc29uPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIERheSBvZiB0aGUgTG9jdXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgZW50cnkgd3JpdHRlbiBmb3IgdGhlIFNDUCBGb3VuZGF0aW9uIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRpdmUgd3JpdGluZyBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U0NQLTE3Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgTk9UIGEgYm9vayBpbiB0aGUgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIFNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdXNlIEVsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG5vdmVsIDE5ODQsIHdyaXR0ZW4gYnkgR2VvcmdlIE9yd2VsbCwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdG90YWxpdGFyaWFuIHJlZ2ltZSB0aGF0IGNvbnRyb2xzIE9jZWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "SU5HU09D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm92ZWwgYnkgSm9obiBHcmlzaGFtIHdhcyBjb25jZWl2ZWQgb24gYSByb2FkIHRyaXAgdG8gRmxvcmlkYSB3aGlsZSB0aGlua2luZyBhYm91dCBzdG9sZW4gYm9va3Mgd2l0aCBoaXMgd2lmZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FtaW5vIElzbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXV0aG9yIGNvLXdyb3RlICJUaGUgQ29tbXVuaXN0IE1hbmlmZXN0byIgYWxvbmdzaWRlIEthcmwgTWFyeD8=",
            "answer": "RnJpZWRyaWNoIEVuZ2Vscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmljdGlvbmFsIEVuZ2xpc2ggY291bnR5IHdhcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgVGhvbWFzIEhhcmR5J3Mgbm92ZWxzPw==",
            "answer": "V2Vzc2V4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBub3ZlbCBieSBNYXJrIFR3YWluIGRpZCBhIGJlZ2dhciBhbmQgUHJpbmNlIG9mIFdhbGVzIHN3aXRjaCBjbG90aGVzLCBhbmQgbGVhcm4gYWJvdXQgc29jaWFsIGNsYXNzIGluZXF1YWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZSBhbmQgdGhlIFBhdXBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycnkgUHJhdGNoZXR0J3MgRGlzY3dvcmxkIG5vdmVsICdXeXJkIFNpc3RlcnMnLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhcmUgbm90IG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgbWFpbiB3aXRjaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "V2lubnkgSGF0aGVyc2hhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBzZXJpZXMgb2YgYm9va3MsIGNvbWJpbmVkLCBhcmUgb3ZlciAxLDAwMCwwMDAgd29yZHMgaW4gbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3JpZ2luYWxseSwgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBDaGFybGllIGZyb20gQ2hhcmxpZSBhbmQgdGhlIENob2NvbGF0ZSBGYWN0b3J5IHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZSBibGFjay4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJBIFRhbGUgb2YgVHdvIENpdGllcyI/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBEaWNrZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRob3Igd3JvdGUgdGhlIGVwaWMgbm92ZWwgV2FyIGFuZCBQZWFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFRvbHN0b3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2h1Yi1OaWdndXJhdGggaXMgYSBjcmVhdHVyZSB0aGF0IHdhcyBjcmVhdGVkIGJ5IAlKLiBSLiBSLiBUb2xraWVuIGluIGhpcyBub3ZlbCAiVGhlIExvcmQgb2YgVGhlIFJpbmdzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExpZXMgT2YgTG9ja2UgTGFtb3JhLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgIkxhbW9yYSIgbWVhbiBpbiBUaHJvbmUgVGhlcmluPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhZG93"
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgTWFyeCBCcm90aGVycyBmaWxtIHRvIGZlYXR1cmUgWmVwcG8/",
            "answer": "RHVjayBTb3Vw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkICJFLlQuIHRoZSBFeHRyYS1UZXJyZXN0cmlhbCIgKDE5ODIpPw==",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIFNwaWVsYmVyZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHN0YXJyZWQgaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gMTk3MyBtb3ZpZSAiRW50ZXIgVGhlIERyYWdvbiI/",
            "answer": "QnJ1Y2UgTGVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcGxheWVkIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgMTk5MCBmaWxtICJFZHdhcmQgU2Npc3NvcmhhbmRzIj8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obm55IERlcHA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vdmllICJUaGUgTmlnaHRtYXJlIGJlZm9yZSBDaHJpc3RtYXMiIHdhcyBhbGwgZG9uZSB3aXRoIHBoeXNpY2FsIG9iamVjdHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBtb3ZpZXMgIlB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiIsICJSZXNlcnZvaXIgRG9ncyIgYW5kICJEamFuZ28gVW5jaGFpbmVkIj8=",
            "answer": "UXVlbnRpbiBUYXJhbnRpbm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlbid0IGFueSBsaXZlLWFjdGlvbiBjbG9uZXMgaW4gIlN0YXIgV2FyczogRXBpc29kZSBJSUkgLSBSZXZlbmdlIG9mIHRoZSBTaXRoIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBKYW1lcyBEZWFuJ3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAxOTU1IG1vdmllICJSZWJlbCBXaXRob3V0IGEgQ2F1c2UiPw==",
            "answer": "SmltIFN0YXJr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSAyMDE1IG1vdmllICJUaGUgUmV2ZW5hbnQiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxlamFuZHJvIEcuIEnDscOhcnJpdHU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFF1ZWVuIHNvbmcgYEEgS2luZCBPZiBNYWdpY2AgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggMTk4NiBmaWxtPw==",
            "answer": "SGlnaGxhbmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJOb2JvZHkgcHV0cyBCYWJ5IGluIGEgY29ybmVyLiI=",
            "answer": "RGlydHkgRGFuY2luZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTAgZmlsbSAiVGhlIFNvY2lhbCBOZXR3b3JrIiBpcyBhIGJpb2dyYXBoaWNhbCBkcmFtYSBmaWxtIGFib3V0IE15U3BhY2UgZm91bmRlciBUb20gQW5kZXJzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb3JhbmdlIGFuZCB3aGl0ZSBib3QncyBuYW1lIGluICJTdGFyIFdhcnM6IFRoZSBGb3JjZSBBd2FrZW5zIj8=",
            "answer": "QkItOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgVHJhbnNmb3JtZXJzIG1vdmllIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgIkluY2VwdGlvbiIgY2FtZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDEwIGJsb2NrYnVzdGVyIGhpdCAiSW5jZXB0aW9uIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYXNzYXNzaW4gaW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJIZWxsYm95IiBtb3ZpZT8=",
            "answer": "S2FybCBSdXByZWNodCBLcm9lbmVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIlN0YXIgV2FycyIgZmlsbSBieSByZWxlYXNlIG9yZGVyPw==",
            "answer": "QSBOZXcgSG9wZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQXJ0aWZpY2lhbCBJbnRlbGxpZ2VuY2Ugc3lzdGVtIGluIHRoZSAxOTgzIGZpbG0sICJXYXJHYW1lcyI/",
            "answer": "V2FyIE9wZXJhdGlvbiBQbGFuIFJlc3BvbnNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1vdmluZyBwaWN0dXJlIGRlcGljdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBnYWxsb3BpbmcgaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaWNvbmljIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBtb3ZpZXMgc3VjaCBhcyAiVGhlIEVuZm9yY2VyIiwgIlN1ZGRlbiBJbXBhY3QiLCBhbmQgIlRoZSBEZWFkIFBvb2wiPw==",
            "answer": "RGlydHkgSGFycnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NzEgZmlsbSAiV2lsbHkgV29ua2EgJiB0aGUgQ2hvY29sYXRlIEZhY3RvcnkiLCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIFdpbGx5IFdvbmthPw==",
            "answer": "R2VuZSBXaWxkZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdmlsbGlhbiBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNSBSdXNzaWFuLUFtZXJpY2FuIFNjaS1GaSBNb3ZpZSAiSGFyZGNvcmUgSGVucnkiPw==",
            "answer": "QWthbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBCYXJvbiBWaWN0b3IgRnJhbmtlc3RlaW4gaW4gdGhlIDE5NTcgSGFtbWVyIGhvcnJvciBmaWxtICJUaGUgQ3Vyc2Ugb2YgRnJhbmtlbnN0ZWluIj8=",
            "answer": "UGV0ZXIgQ3VzaGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFjdGlvbiBtb3ZpZXMgYXJlIHNob3QgZW50aXJlbHkgaW4gb25lIHRha2U/",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWxmcmVkIEhpdGNoY29jaydzIGZpbG0gJ1BzeWNobycgaXQgaXMgc2FpZCBoZSB1c2VkIGNob2NvbGF0ZSBzeXJ1cCB0byBzaW11bGF0ZSB0aGUgYmxvb2QgaW4gdGhlIGZhbW91cyBzaG93ZXIgc2NlbmUgZnJvbSA=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgYW5vdGhlciBzdWdnZXN0ZWQgbmFtZSBmb3IsIHRoZSAxOTg1IGZpbG0sIEJhY2sgdG8gdGhlIEZ1dHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U3BhY2VtYW4gRnJvbSBQbHV0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFN0YXIgV2FycyB0cmlsb2d5LCBEYXZpZCBQcm93c2Ugd2FzIHRoZSBhY3RvciB3aG8gcGh5c2ljYWxseSBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgRGFydGggVmFkZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgbW92aWUgIlBvbGljZSBBY2FkZW15IiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk4NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2VhbiBDb25uZXJ5IHdhc24ndCBpbiAiSW5kaWFuYSBKb25lcyBhbmQgdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gb2YgdGhlIENyeXN0YWwgU2t1bGwiIGJlY2F1c2UgaGUgZm91bmQgcmV0aXJlbWVudCB0b28gZW5qb3lhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdzOiBUaGUgRmVsbG93c2hpcCBvZiB0aGUgUmluZywgd2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tIHRoZSBib29rIHdhcyBsZWZ0IG91dCBvZiB0aGUgZmlsbT8=",
            "answer": "VG9tIEJvbWJhZGls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaXR5IGRpZCB0aGUgbW9uc3RlciBhdHRhY2sgaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0sICJDbG92ZXJmaWVsZCI/",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcmssIE5ldyBZb3Jr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBzcGVsbGluZyBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGJvb2sgaW4gVGhlIE5ldmVyRW5kaW5nIFN0b3J5ICgxOTg0KT8=",
            "answer": "QXRyZXl1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbW92aWUgZG9lcyBSb2JpbiBXaWxsaWFtcycgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGhhdmUgdG8gZGlzZ3Vpc2UgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyBpbnRvIGEgd29tYW4/",
            "answer": "TXJzLiBEb3VidGZpcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNoZWVzZSwgbG92ZWQgYnkgV2FsbGFjZSBhbmQgR3JvbWl0LCBoYWQgaXQncyBzYWxlIHByaWNlcyByaXNlIGFmdGVyIHRoZWlyIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWwgc2hvcnQgZmlsbXM/",
            "answer": "V2Vuc2xleWRhbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyayBXYWhsYmVyZyBwbGF5ZWQgdGhlIHRpdHVsYXIgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mIHdoaWNoIDIwMDggdmlkZW8tZ2FtZSBhZGFwdGF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4IFBheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRvZXMgSnVyYXNzaWMgV29ybGQgb3BlbiBpbiB0aGUgIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiIHVuaXZlcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFdvcmxkIiwgd2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBwdXJjaGFzZXMgSW5HZW4gYW5kIGNyZWF0ZXMgSnVyYXNzaWMgV29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "TWFzcmFuaSBHbG9iYWwgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24g"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgQnJ1Y2UgQ2FtcGJlbGwncyBpY29uaWMgb25lLWxpbmVyIGFmdGVyIGdldHRpbmcgYSBjaGFpbnNhdyBoYW5kIGluIEV2aWwgRGVhZCAyPw==",
            "answer": "R3Jvb3Z5Lg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgRHIuIEdyYWNlIEF1Z3VzdGluZSBpbiB0aGUgSmFtZXMgQ2FtZXJvbiBtb3ZpZSAiQXZhdGFyIj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnb3VybmV5IFdlYXZlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcGxheXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciAiVG9tbXkgSmFydmlzIiBpbiAiRnJpZGF5IHRoZSAxM3RoOiBUaGUgRmluYWwgQ2hhcHRlciIgKDE5ODQpPw==",
            "answer": "Q29yZXkgRmVsZG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZlYXR1cmUtbGVuZ3RoIGNvbXB1dGVyLWFuaW1hdGVkIG1vdmllPw==",
            "answer": "VG95IFN0b3J5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQmlnIEhlcm8gNiwgd2hhdCBmaWN0aW9uYWwgY2l0eSBpcyB0aGUgQmlnIEhlcm8gNiBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "U2FuIEZyYW5zb2t5bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEZyaWRheSBUaGUgMTN0aCBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgSmFzb24ncyBtb3RoZXIncyBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UGFtZWxh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgRnJpZGF5IFRoZSAxM3RoIG1vdmllIHRha2UgcGxhY2U/",
            "answer": "Q2FtcCBDcnlzdGFsIExha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkZvb2RmaWdodCEiIGVhcm5lZCBsZXNzIHRoYW4gJDgwLDAwMCBhdCBib3ggb2ZmaWNlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTWFydmVsIHN1cGVyaGVybyBkaWQgQ2hyaXMgRXZhbnMgcGxheSBwcmlvciB0byBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBDYXB0YWluIEFtZXJpY2E/",
            "answer": "SHVtYW4gVG9yY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "WW91VHViZSBwZXJzb25hbGl0eSBKZW5uYSBNYXJibGVzIHNlcnZlZCBhcyBhbiBleGVjdXRpdmUgcHJvZHVjZXIgb2YgdGhlIGZpbG0gTWF4aW11bSBSaWRlICgyMDE2KS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJWIGZvciBWZW5kZXR0YSwiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGRhdGUgdGhhdCBtYXNrZWQgdmlnaWxhbnRlICJWIiB1cmdlcyBwZW9wbGUgdG8gcmVtZW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgNXRo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcGxheXMgdGhlIHJvbGUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gYW50YWdvbmlzdCBpbiB0aGUgMjAxMSBtb3ZpZSAiVG93ZXIgSGVpc3Q/Ig==",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBBbGRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3ZXJlIHRoZSBDaGlsbGVkIE1vbmtleSBCcmFpbnMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIGR1cmluZyBJbmRpYW5hIEpvbmVzIGFuZCB0aGUgVGVtcGxlIG9mIERvb20/",
            "answer": "Q3VzdGFyZCBhbmQgUmFzcGJlcnJ5IFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSAiQm9uZCBHaXJsIj8g",
            "answer": "VmFuZXNzYSBLZW5zaW5ndG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGFuaWVsIFJhZGNsaWZmZSBiZWNhbWUgYSBnbG9iYWwgc3RhciBpbiB0aGUgZmlsbSBpbmR1c3RyeSBkdWUgdG8gaGlzIHBlcmZvcm1hbmNlIGluIHdoaWNoIGZpbG0gZnJhbmNoaXNlPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycnkgUG90dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHN0YXJyZWQgYXMgQnJ1Y2UgV2F5bmUgYW5kIEJhdG1hbiBpbiBUaW0gQnVydG9uJ3MgMTk4OSBtb3ZpZSAiQmF0bWFuIj8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBLZWF0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBvZiBBbGZyZWQgSGl0Y2hjb2NrJ3MgbW92aWVzIHRvIGJlIGZpbG1lZCBpbiBjb2xvdXI/",
            "answer": "Um9wZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCB0aGUgZmVtYWxlIGxlYWQgaW4gdGhlIDE5MzMgZmlsbSAiS2luZyBLb25nIj8=",
            "answer": "RmF5IFdyYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2VgcyBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIGluIHRoZSBmaWxtICJTb21lIExpa2UgSXQgSG90Ij8=",
            "answer": "U3VnYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBkYW5jZWQgdGhlIHR3aXN0IHdpdGggSm9obiBUcmF2b2x0YSBpbiAnUHVscCBGaWN0aW9uJz8=",
            "answer": "VW1hIFRodXJtYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWF0dCBEYW1vbiBwbGF5ZWQgYW4gYXN0cm9uYXV0IHN0cmFuZGVkIG9uIGFuIGV4dHJhdGVycmVzdHJpYWwgcGxhbmV0IGluIGJvdGggb2YgdGhlIG1vdmllcyBJbnRlcnN0ZWxsYXIgYW5kIFRoZSBNYXJ0aWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSAxOTczIGZpbG0gIkFtZXJpY2FuIEdyYWZmaXRpIj8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEx1Y2Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJJIGZlZWwgdGhlIG5lZWQgLi4uIHRoZSBuZWVkIGZvciBzcGVlZCEi",
            "answer": "VG9wIEd1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJXaGF0IHdlJ3ZlIGdvdCBoZXJlIGlzIGEgZmFpbHVyZSB0byBjb21tdW5pY2F0ZS4i",
            "answer": "Q29vbCBIYW5kIEx1a2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggQWZyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgMjAwNiBmaWxtICdCbG9vZCBEaWFtb25kJyBtb3N0bHkgc2V0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "U2llcnJhIExlb25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHBsYW5ldCBpbiAiQWxpZW5zIj8=",
            "answer": "TFYtNDI2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbW92aWVzIGRpZCBKZWZmIEJyaWRnZXMgbm90IHN0YXIgaW4/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhhdGVmdWwgRWlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXlzIEFsaWNlIGluIHRoZSBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIG1vdmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWlsbGEgSm92b3ZpY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NzkgQnJpdGlzaCBmaWxtICJRdWFkcm9waGVuaWEiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gcHJvdGFnb25pc3Q/",
            "answer": "SmltbXkgQ29vcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2FtdWVsIEwuIEphY2tzb24gaGFkIHRoZSB3b3JkcywgJ0JhZCBNb3RoZXJmKmNrZXInIGluLXNjcmlwdGVkIG9uIGhpcyBsaWdodHNhYmVyIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgZmlsbWluZyBvZiBTdGFyIFdhcnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgSmFtZXMgQ2FtZXJvbiBmaWxtICJUaXRhbmljIiBjb21lIG91dCBpbiB0aGVhdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCB0aGUgQ2Vub2JpdGUgY2FsbGVkICJQaW5oZWFkIiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgSGVsbHJhaXNlciBmaWxtcz8=",
            "answer": "RG91ZyBCcmFkbGV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJCbGFkZSBSdW5uZXIiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSB0ZXJtIHVzZWQgZm9yIGh1bWFuLWxpa2UgYW5kcm9pZHMgPw==",
            "answer": "UmVwbGljYW50cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gRGkgQ2FwcmlvIHdvbiBoaXMgZmlyc3QgQmVzdCBBY3RvciBPc2NhciBmb3IgaGlzIHBlcmZvcm1hbmNlIGluIHdoaWNoIGZpbG0/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJldmVuYW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZG9jdW1lbnRhcnkgZmlsbSBtYWtlciB3cm90ZSBhbmQgc3RhcnJlZCBpbiB0aGUgZmlsbSAiTXkgU2NpZW50b2xvZ3kgTW92aWUiIHdoaWNoIGZpcnN0IGRlYnV0ZWQgaW4gMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "TG91aXMgVGhlcm91eA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvICJTdGFyIFdhcnMiIGxvcmUsIHdoaWNoIHBsYW5ldCBkb2VzIE9iaS1XYW4gS2Vub2JpIGNvbWUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "U3Rld2pvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgaXNsYW5kIHRoYXQgY29udGFpbnMgSW5HZW4ncyBTaXRlIEI/",
            "answer": "SXNsYSBTb3JuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFrZSBhbmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgdGhlIHRvdXIgdmVoaWNsZXMgaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiICgxOTkzKT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5MiBGb3JkIEV4cGxvcmVyIFhMVA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBtb3ZpZSAiQWxpZW4iPw==",
            "answer": "UmlkbGV5IFNjb3R0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0aHJlZSBtb3ZpZXMsIGluIG9yZGVyIGZyb20gcmVsZWFzZSBkYXRlLCBtYWtlIHVwIHRoZSAiRG9sbGFycyBUcmlsb2d5Ij8=",
            "answer": "IkEgRmlzdGZ1bCBvZiBEb2xsYXJzIiwgIkZvciBhIEZldyBEb2xsYXJzIE1vcmUiLCAiVGhlIEdvb2QsIHRoZSBCYWQsIGFuZCB0aGUgVWdseSI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3JzIG1hZGUgdXAgdGhlIHRyaW8gaW4gIlRoZSBHb29kLCB0aGUgQmFkLCBhbmQgdGhlIFVnbHkiPyA=",
            "answer": "Q2xpbnQgRWFzdHdvb2QsIEVsaSBXYWxsYWNoLCBhbmQgTGVlIFZhbiBDbGVlZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdG93biBpcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBmb3IgdGhlIERpc25leSBtb3ZpZSBUaGUgTG92ZSBCdWcgKDE5NjgpPw==",
            "answer": "U2FuIEZyYW5jaXNjbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmluZGluZyBOZW1vLCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOZW1vJ3MgbW9tPw==",
            "answer": "Q29yYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQmlnIEhlcm8gNiwgd2hhdCB3ZXJlIEJheW1heCdzIG1vdGlvbnMgbW9kZWxlZCBhZnRlcj8=",
            "answer": "QmFieSBwZW5ndWlucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEZyaWRheSBUaGUgMTN0aCBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgeWVhciBkaWQgSmFzb24gZHJvd24gaW4/",
            "answer": "MTk1Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZmlsbSBkb2VzIEh1bXBocmV5IEJvZ2FydCBzYXkgdGhlIGZhbW91cyBsaW5lLCAiSGVyZSdzIGxvb2tpbmcgYXQgeW91LCBraWQiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FzYWJsYW5jYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggOTAncyBjb21lZHkgY3VsdCBjbGFzc2ljIGZlYXR1cmVzIGNhbWVvcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlcyBmcm9tIE1lYXQgTG9hZiwgQWxpY2UgQ29vcGVyIGFuZCBDaHJpcyBGYXJsZXk/",
            "answer": "V2F5bmUncyBXb3JsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmljdGlvbmFsIHJldHJvLW1vZCBiYW5kIHN0YXJyaW5nIEF1c3RpbiBQb3dlcnMgYXMgdGhlIGxlYWQgdm9jYWxpc3Q/",
            "answer": "TWluZyBUZWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBlcmZvcm1lZCB0aGUgb3BlbmluZyB0aGVtZSBzb25nIGZvciB0aGUgSmFtZXMgQm9uZCAwMDcgbW92aWUgIkdvbGRmaW5nZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "U2hpcmxleSBCYXNleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnJlbmRhbiBGcmFzZXIgc3RhcnJlZCBpbiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIG1vdmllcywgZXhjZXB0IHdoaWNoIG9uZT8=",
            "answer": "VGl0YW5pYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hZCBNYXggZnJhbmNoaXNlLCB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBQdXJzdWl0IFNwZWNpYWwgZHJpdmVuIGJ5IE1heD8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZCBGYWxjb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBicmVlZCBvZiBkb2cgd2FzIE1hcmxleSBpbiB0aGUgZmlsbSAiTWFybGV5ICYgTWUiICgyMDA4KT8=",
            "answer": "TGFicmFkb3IgUmV0cmlldmVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtb3ZpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBiYXNlZCBvbiBhIG5vdmVsIGJ5IFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZz8g",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRoaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllIOKAnFRoZSBJcm9uIEdpYW50LOKAnSB0aGlzIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qu",
            "answer": "SG9nYXJ0aCBIdWdoZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gIkludGVyc3RlbGxhciIsIGhvdyBsb25nIGRpZCB0aGV5IHNwZW5kIG9uIE1pbGxlcidzIHBsYW5ldD8=",
            "answer": "MjMgeWVhcnMsIDQgbW9udGhzLCBhbmQgOCBkYXlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBEZXB1dHkgTWFyc2hhbCBTYW11ZWwgR2VyYXJkIGluIHRoZSAxOTkzIGZpbG0gIlRoZSBGdWdpdGl2ZSI/",
            "answer": "VG9tbXkgTGVlIEpvbmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGFuIFNvbG8ncyBjby1waWxvdCBhbmQgYmVzdCBmcmllbmQsICJDaGV3YmFjY2EiLCBpcyBhbiBFd29rLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVsbWEgS2VsbHkgYW5kIFJveGllIEhhcnQgYXJlIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdHMgb2Ygd2hpY2ggT3NjYXIgd2lubmluZyBtb3ZpZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpY2Fnbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJIb3VzdG9uLCB3ZSBoYXZlIGEgcHJvYmxlbS4i",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxvIDEz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEphbWVzIEJvbmQgZmlsbT8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIE5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgaW5jbHVkZXMgYSBnaWFudCBidW5ueS1saWtlIHNwaXJpdCB3aG8gaGFzIG1hZ2ljIHBvd2VycyBpbmNsdWRpbmcgZ3Jvd2luZyB0cmVlcz8=",
            "answer": "TXkgTmVpZ2hib3IgVG90b3Jv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5OTQgbW92aWUgIlNwZWVkIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWluaW11bSBzcGVlZCB0aGUgYnVzIG11c3QgZ28gdG8gcHJldmVudCB0byBib21iIGZyb20gZXhwbG9kaW5nPw==",
            "answer": "NTAgbXBo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2xkZXN0IERpc25leSBmaWxtPw==",
            "answer": "U25vdyBXaGl0ZSBhbmQgdGhlIFNldmVuIER3YXJmcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RXdhbiBNY0dyZWdvciBkaWQgbm90IGtub3cgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNlY29uZCBwcmVxdWVsIGZpbG0gb2YgU3RhciBXYXJzIGR1cmluZyBhbmQgYWZ0ZXIgZmlsbWluZy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFjdG9ycyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGN1dCBmcm9tIHRoZSBmaWxtICdFLlQuIHRoZSBFeHRyYS1UZXJyZXN0cmlhbCc/",
            "answer": "SGFycmlzb24gRm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgb2YgZmlsbSBkaXJlY3RvciBTdGFubGV5IEt1YnJpY2sgaXMga25vd24gdG8gYmUgYW4gYWRhcHRhdGlvbiBvZiBhIFN0ZXBoZW4gS2luZyBub3ZlbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNoaW5pbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBwaHJhc2UgZm9yIHRoZSBMYXRpbiBzYXlpbmcgIlJvbWFuZXMgRXVudCBEb211cyIgaW4gTW9udHkgUHl0aG9uJ3MgTGlmZSBvZiBCcmlhbj8=",
            "answer": "Um9tYW5pIEl0ZSBEb211bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFdvcmxkIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZGlub3NhdXIgdGhhdCBpcyBhIGdlbmV0aWMgaHlicmlkPw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb21pbnVzIFJleA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJTY3JlYW0iIHdobyBpcyBHaG9zdCBGYWNlPw==",
            "answer": "QmlsbHkgTG9vbWlzIGFuZCBTdHUgTWFjaGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMDIgZmlsbSAiMjggRGF5cyBMYXRlciIgaXMgbWFpbmx5IHNldCBpbiB3aGljaCBFdXJvcGVhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "VW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTIgZmlsbSwgIlRoZSBMb3JheCIsIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgYW50YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "QWxveXNpdXMgTydIYXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXQgdGhlIGVuZCBvZiB0aGUgMjAwMSBmaWxtICJSYXQgUmFjZSIsIHdob3NlIGNvbmNlcnQgZG8gdGhlIGNvbnRlc3RhbnRzIGNyYXNoPw==",
            "answer": "U21hc2ggTW91dGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgb2YgUG8gaW4gdGhlIEt1bmcgRnUgUGFuZGEgbW92aWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SmFjayBCbGFjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWN0b3IgVG9tbXkgQ2hvbmcgc2VydmVkIHByaXNvbiB0aW1lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgaXNsYW5kIHRoYXQgIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiIGlzIGJ1aWx0IG9uPw==",
            "answer": "SXNsYSBOdWJsYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHByb3ZpZGVkIGEgbWFqb3JpdHkgb2YgdGhlIHNvbmdzIGFuZCBseXJpY3MgZm9yICJTcGlyaXQ6IFN0YWxsaW9uIG9mIHRoZSBDaW1hcnJvbiI/",
            "answer": "QnJ5YW4gQWRhbXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3RhbmQtdXAgY29tZWRpYW4gdm9pY2VkIHRoZSB0YWxraW5nIHBhcnJvdCAiSWFnbyIgaW4gRGlzbmV5J3MgMTk5MiBhZGFwdGF0aW9uIG9mIEFsYWRkaW4/",
            "answer": "R2lsYmVydCBHb3R0ZnJpZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYm94ZXIgd2FzIGZhbW91cyBmb3Igc3RyaWtpbmcgdGhlIGdvbmcgaW4gdGhlIGludHJvZHVjdGlvbiB0byBKLiBBcnRodXIgUmFuayBmaWxtcz8=",
            "answer": "Qm9tYmFyZGllciBCaWxseSBXZWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3RhciBhY3RvciB3YXMgaW4gIlRvcCBHdW4iLCAiSmVycnkgTWFndWlyZSIgYW5kICJCb3JuIG9uIHRoZSBGb3VydGggb2YgSnVseSI/",
            "answer": "VG9tIENydWlzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkFMRiIsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFMRidzIHJlYWwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFNodW13YXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTQgZmlsbSAiQmlyZG1hbiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHByaW1hcnkgaW5zdHJ1bWVudCBpbiB0aGUgc2NvcmU/",
            "answer": "RHJ1bXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbXVzaWNhbCBhcnRpc3QgaGFkIGEgcHJvbWluZW50IHJvbGUgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTcgZmlsbSAiS2luZ3NtYW46IFRoZSBHb2xkZW4gQ2lyY2xlIj8=",
            "answer": "RWx0b24gSm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgSW5kaWEsIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnkgcHJvZHVjZXMgdGhlIHNlY29uZCBtb3N0IG1vdmllcyBwZXIgeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "TmlnZXJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXlzIEphY2sgQnVydG9uIGluIHRoZSBtb3ZpZSAiQmlnIFRyb3VibGUgaW4gTGl0dGxlIENoaW5hPyI=",
            "answer": "S3VydCBSdXNzZWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJCYWNrIHRvIHRoZSBGdXR1cmUsIiB3aGF0IHNwZWVkIGRvZXMgRG9jIEJyb3duJ3MgRGVMb3JlYW4gbmVlZCB0byByZWFjaCBpbiBvcmRlciB0byB0cmF2ZWwgdGhyb3VnaCB0aW1lPw==",
            "answer": "ODggbXBo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZm9sZXkgYXJ0aXN0IHdobyBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgZmFtb3VzIHNvdW5kcyBvZiBTdGFyIFdhcnMsIGluY2x1ZGluZyBDaGV3YmFjY2EncyByb2FyIGFuZCBSMi1EMidzIGJlZXBzIGFuZCB3aGlzdGxlcz8=",
            "answer": "QmVuIEJ1cnR0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZmlsbXMgaXMgTk9UIHNldCBpbiBMb3MgQW5nZWxlcz8=",
            "answer": "Um9ib0NvcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAxNiBmZWF0dXJlcyBTdXBlcm1hbiBhbmQgQmF0bWFuIGZpZ2h0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QmF0bWFuIHYgU3VwZXJtYW46IERhd24gb2YgSnVzdGljZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIG1vdmllICdDb24gQWlyJyByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggMTk3MyBmaWxtIGRvZXMgWXVsIEJyeW5uZXIgcGxheSBhIHJvYm90aWMgY293Ym95IHdobyBtYWxmdW5jdGlvbnMgYW5kIGdvZXMgb24gYSBraWxsaW5nCXNwcmVlPw==",
            "answer": "V2VzdHdvcmxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcm9ib3QgaW4gdGhlIDE5NTEgc2NpZW5jZSBmaWN0aW9uIGZpbG0gY2xhc3NpYyAnVGhlIERheSB0aGUgRWFydGggU3Rvb2QgU3RpbGwnPw==",
            "answer": "R29ydA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFRJRSBzdGFuZCBmb3IgaW4gcmVmZXJlbmNlIHRvIHRoZSBUSUUgRmlnaHRlciBpbiAiU3RhciBXYXJzIj8=",
            "answer": "VHdpbiBJb24gRW5naW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgcGlsbHMgaW4gdGhlIE1hdHJpeCB3ZXJlIEJsdWUgYW5kIFllbGxvdy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIHNjcmlwdCBvZiAiVGhlIE1hdHJpeCIsIHRoZSBtYWNoaW5lcyB1c2VkIGh1bWFucyBhcyBhZGRpdGlvbmFsIGNvbXB1dGluZyBwb3dlciBpbnN0ZWFkIG9mIGJhdHRlcmllcy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgc2VxdWVsIGhhZCBpbXByb3ZlZCBib3ggb2ZmaWNlIHJlc3VsdHMgY29tcGFyZWQgdG8gaXRzIG9yaWdpbmFsIGZpbG0/",
            "answer": "VG95IFN0b3J5IDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFhlbm9tb3JwaCBmcm9tIHRoZSBzY2llbmNlIGZpY3Rpb24gZmlsbSAiQWxpZW4iIGhhcyBhY2lkaWMgYmxvb2Qu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXlzIHRoZSBOZW1lc2lzIGluIHRoZSBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIG1vdmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWF0dGhldyBUYXlsb3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NzkgQnJpdGlzaCBmaWxtICJRdWFkcm9waGVuaWEiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNlYXNpZGUgY2l0eSB0aGUgbW9kcyBhcmUgdmlzaXRpbmc/",
            "answer": "QnJpZ2h0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJDYXN0IEF3YXkiIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgYmVzdCBmcmllbmQgd2hpbGUgb24gdGhlIGlzbGFuZCBpcyBuYW1lZA==",
            "answer": "V2lsc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBTZ3QuIEdvcmRvbiBFbGlhcyBpbiAnUGxhdG9vbicgKDE5ODYpPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGVtIERhZm9l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcGxheXMgT2JpLVdhbiBLZW5vYmkgaW4gU3RhciBXYXJzIEVwaXNvZGVzIEktbGxsPw==",
            "answer": "RXdhbiBNY0dyZWdvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5OTkgbW92aWUgRmlnaHQgQ2x1Yiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgcnVsZSBvZiB0aGUgImZpZ2h0IGNsdWIiPw==",
            "answer": "QWx3YXlzIHdlYXIgYSBzaGlydA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1vbnN0ZXIgdG8gYXBwZWFyIGFsb25nc2lkZSBHb2R6aWxsYT8=",
            "answer": "QW5ndWlydXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlZCBNZXRhbGJlYXJkIGluICJUaGUgTGVnbyBNb3ZpZSI/",
            "answer": "TmljayBPZmZlcm1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBkaXJlY3RvciBvZiB0aGUgMTk5MSBmaWxtICJTaWxlbmNlIG9mIHRoZSBMYW1icyI/",
            "answer": "Sm9uYXRoYW4gRGVtbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayBOZW1lc2lzIiwgd2h5IHdhcyBQcmFldG9yIFNoaW56b24gY3JlYXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "VG8gcmVwbGFjZSBQaWNhcmQgYXMgYSBSb211bGFuIEFnZW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFN0YXIgVHJlayBhY3RvciBkaXJlY3RlZCBUaHJlZSBNZW4gYW5kIGEgQmFieSAoMTk4Nyk/",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZCBOaW1veQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmaWxtcyB3YXMgZGlyZWN0ZWQgYnkgSXZhbiBSZWl0bWFuLCB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IEdhcnkgUm9zcywgZmVhdHVyZWQgS2V2aW4gS2xpbmUsIGFuZCB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMTk5Mz8=",
            "answer": "RGF2ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIFdpbm5pZSB0aGUgUG9vaCBmaWxtcyB3YXMgYWRkZWQgYnkgRGlzbmV5IGFuZCBkb2VzIG5vdCBhcHBlYXIgaW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIGJvb2tzPw==",
            "answer": "R29waGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIE5pY29sYXMgQ2FnZSBwbGF5cyBpbiB0aGUgbW92aWUgIk5hdGlvbmFsIFRyZWFzdXJlPyI=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4gR2F0ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDE5OTYgZmlsbSAnRmFyZ28nIGlzIHByaW1hcmlseSBzZXQgaW4gd2hpY2ggVVMgc3RhdGU/",
            "answer": "TWlubmVzb3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmV0aXJlZCBBbWVyaWNhbiBmb290YmFsbCBxdWFydGVyYmFjayBwbGF5ZWQgaGltc2VsZiBpbiAnQWNlIFZlbnR1cmE6IFBldCBEZXRlY3RpdmUnIGFuZCAnTGl0dGxlIE5pY2t5Jz8=",
            "answer": "RGFuIE1hcmlubw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpbG0gIjIwMDE6IEEgU3BhY2UgT2R5c3NleSIgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIG9uIERlY2VtYmVyIDMxc3QsIDIwMDAu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBCYXRtYW4gaW4gdGhlIDE5OTcgZmlsbSAiQmF0bWFuIGFuZCBSb2JpbiI/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIENsb29uZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDE5MzkgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBXaXphcmQgb2YgT3oiIGNvbnRhaW5lZCBhIGhvcnNlIHRoYXQgY2hhbmdlZCBjb2xvciwgd2hhdCBtYXRlcmlhbCBkaWQgdGhleSB1c2UgdG8gYWNoaWV2ZSB0aGlzIGVmZmVjdD8=",
            "answer": "R2VsYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluLCB0aGUgMTk4NSBmaWxtLCBCYWNrIHRvIHRoZSBGdXR1cmU/",
            "answer": "TWFydHkgTWNGbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFN0YXIgV2FycyB0cmlsb2d5LCBBbGVjIEd1aW5uZXNzIHByb3ZpZGVkIHRoZSB2b2ljZSBmb3IgRGFydGggVmFkZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyB0cm9wZSByZWZlcnMgdG8gbWlub3IgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB0aGF0IGFyZSBraWxsZWQgb2ZmIHRvIHNob3cgaG93IGEgbW9uc3RlciB3b3Jrcy4=",
            "answer": "UmVkIFNoaXJ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIEx1Y2FzIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBlbnRpcmUgb3JpZ2luYWwgU3RhciBXYXJzIHRyaWxvZ3ku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1pbmlvbnMiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBvbiB0aGUgSnVuZSAxMHRoLCAyMDE1Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5OTUgZmlsbSAiQmFsdG8iLCB3aG8gYXJlIFN0ZWVsZSdzIGFjY29tcGxpY2VzPw==",
            "answer": "S2FsdGFnLCBOaWtraSwgYW5kIFN0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcXVlZW4ncyBwZXQgaW4gQSBCdWcncyBMaWZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXBoaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGlyZWN0b3IgZGlyZWN0ZWQgdGhlIG1vdmllICJQYW4ncyBMYWJ5cmludGgiPw==",
            "answer": "R3VpbGxlcm1vIERlbCBUb3Jv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgRGlzbmV5IGNsYXNzaWNzIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAxOTcwPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFyaXN0b2NhdHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSHVtcGhyZXkgQm9nYXJ0J3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "RGVGb3Jlc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhY3RvcnMgaGFzIG9ubHkgYmVlbiBpbiBhIFF1ZW50aW4gVGFyYW50aW5vIGRpcmVjdGVkIGZpbG0gb25jZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBUcmF2b2x0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmlydGggbmFtZSBvZiBNaWNoYWVsIEtlYXRvbj8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBEb3VnbGFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5ODQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBUZXJtaW5hdG9yIiwgd2hhdCBtb2RlbCBudW1iZXIgaXMgdGhlIFRlcm1pbmF0b3IgcG9ydHJheWVkIGJ5IEFybm9sZCBTY2h3YXJ6ZW5lZ2dlcj8=",
            "answer": "VC04MDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NjQgZmlsbSAiWnVsdSIsIHdoYXQgc29uZyBkb2VzIHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIEFybXkgY29tcGFueSBzaW5nIGJlZm9yZSB0aGUgZmluYWwgYmF0dGxlPw==",
            "answer": "TWVuIG9mIEhhcmxlY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJTcGFjZWJhbGxzIiwgd2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFNwYWNlYmFsbHMgYXR0ZW1wdGluZyB0byBzdGVhbCBmcm9tIFBsYW5ldCBEcnVpZGlhPw==",
            "answer": "QWly"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQmFjayB0byB0aGUgRnV0dXJlIFBhcnQgSUksIE1hcnR5IGFuZCBEci4gRW1tZXR0IEJyb3duIGdvIHRvIHdoaWNoIGZ1dHVyZSBkYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyMSwgMjAxNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGFydGggVmFkZXIncyBmYW1vdXMgcmV2ZWFsIHRvIEx1a2UgaXMgaWNvbmljLiBCdXQgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIHJpZ2h0IG9uZT8=",
            "answer": "Ik5vLiBJIGFtIHlvdXIgZmF0aGVyLiI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0ZWQgZmlsbSBkaWQgU3RldmVuIExpc2JlcmdlciBkaXJlY3QgaW4gMTk4MCBiZWZvcmUgZ29pbmcgb24gdG8gZGlyZWN0IFRyb24/",
            "answer": "QW5pbWFseW1waWNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXlzICJCcnVjZSBXYXluZSIgaW4gdGhlIDIwMDggbW92aWUgIlRoZSBEYXJrIEtuaWdodCI/",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0aWFuIEJhbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBmaWxtIGRpZCBKYW1lcyBDYW1lcm9uJ3MgQXZhdGFyIGRldGhyb25lIGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0LWdyb3NzaW5nIGZpbG0gZXZlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGl0YW5pYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vdmllICJUcm9uIiByZWNlaXZlZCBhbiBPc2NhciBub21pbmF0aW9uIGZvciBCZXN0IFZpc3VhbCBFZmZlY3RzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpZCB0aGUgc2NvcmUgdG8gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIEJsYWRlIFJ1bm5lcj8=",
            "answer": "VmFuZ2VsaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmaWxtcyB3YXMgTk9UIGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IFF1ZW50aW4gVGFyYW50aW5vPw==",
            "answer": "RnJvbSBEdXNrIHRpbGwgRGF3bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhY3RvcnMgZG9lcyBub3QgcGxheSBhIHJvbGUgaW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJUaGUgVXN1YWwgU3VzcGVjdHM/Ig==",
            "answer": "U3RldmUgQnVzY2VtaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmlydGggbmFtZSBvZiBNaWNoYWVsIENhaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljZSBNaWNrbGV3aGl0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBxdW90ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTQyIGZpbG0gQ2FzYWJsYW5jYT8g",
            "answer": "IkZyYW5rbHksIG15IGRlYXIsIEkgZG9uJ3QgZ2l2ZSBhIGRhbW4uIg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgRG9yb3RoeSdzIHN1cm5hbWUgaW4gJ1RoZSBXaXphcmQgT2YgT3onPw==",
            "answer": "R2FsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGZpbG1zIGFyZSBzaG90IGVudGlyZWx5IGluIG9uZS10YWtlPw==",
            "answer": "UnVzc2lhbiBBcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIFB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiBzYXlzICJObywgdGhleSBnb3QgdGhlIG1ldHJpYyBzeXN0ZW0gdGhlcmUsIHRoZXkgd291bGRuJ3Qga25vdyB3aGF0IHRoZSBmdWNrIGEgUXVhcnRlciBQb3VuZGVyIGlzLiI=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCBWZWdh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkb2VzICJSb2d1ZSBPbmU6IEEgU3RhciBXYXJzIFN0b3J5IiB0YWtlIHBsYWNlIGNocm9ub2xvZ2ljYWxseSBpbiB0aGUgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QmV0d2VlbiBFcGlzb2RlIDMgYW5kIDQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZGlyZWN0b3Igb2YgIlNjb3R0IFBpbGdyaW0gdnMuIHRoZSBXb3JsZCAoMjAxMCkiPw==",
            "answer": "RWRnYXIgV3JpZ2h0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHdlYXBvbiBDbGludCBFYXN0d29vZCB1c2VzIGluICJEaXJ0eSBIYXJyeSIgd2FzIGEgLjQ0IEF1dG9tYWcu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIElJSSIgd2FzIGZpbmFsaXplZCBhbmQgdGhlIFNwaW5vc2F1cnVzIHdhcyBjaG9zZW4sIHdoaWNoIGRpbm9zYXVyIHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZSB0aGUgc3Rhcj8=",
            "answer": "QmFyeW9ueXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hlbiBkaWQgIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcms6IFNhbiBEaWVnbyIgYmVnaW4gY29uc3RydWN0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "MTk4NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NzQgQ2hyaXN0bWFzIGZsaWNrICJUaGUgWWVhciBXaXRob3V0IGEgU2FudGEgQ2xhdXMsIiB3aGF0IGFyZSB0aGUgbmFtZXMgb2YgdGhlIHR3byBlbHZlcyB3aG8gaGVscCBNcnMuIENsYXVzIHNhdmUgQ2hyaXN0bWFzPw==",
            "answer": "SmluZ2xlICYgSmFuZ2xl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgQWxmcmVkIEhpdGNoY29jayB1c2UgYXMgYmxvb2QgaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gIlBzeWNobyI/IA==",
            "answer": "Q2hvY29sYXRlIHN5cnVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZG9nIHRoYXQgcGxheWVkIFRvdG8gaW4gdGhlIDE5MzkgZmlsbSAiVGhlIFdpemFyZCBvZiBPeiI/",
            "answer": "VGVycnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1vdmllIHRvIGV2ZXIgdXNlIGEgV2lsaGVsbSBTY3JlYW0/",
            "answer": "RGlzdGFudCBEcnVtcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllIFRoZSBSZXZlbmFudCwgRGlDYXByaW8ncyBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaHVudHMgZG93biB0aGUga2lsbGVyIG9mIGhpcyBzb24u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnJhbmRvbiBSb3V0aCBwbGF5cyB0aGUgdGl0dWxhciBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIG1vdmllICJKb2huIFdpY2siLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSBtb3ZpZSBDb21tYW5kbyAoMTk4NSk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBNYXRyaXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gb3JkZXIgdG8gY3V0IGNvc3RzLCB3aGF0IHdlcmUgbW9zdCBvZiB0aGUgZXh0cmFzIG9mIE1hZCBNYXggKDE5NzkpIHBhaWQgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "QmVlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJKdXJhc3NpYyBQYXJrIiB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGRpbm9zYXVyIGNsb25lZCBieSBJbkdlbiBpbiAxOTg2Pw==",
            "answer": "VmVsb2NpcmFwdG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9yIHRoZSBmaWxtICJSYWlkZXJzIG9mIFRoZSBMb3N0IEFyayIsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEhhcnJpc29uIEZvcmQgc2ljayB3aXRoIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgZmlsbWluZyBvZiB0aGUgQ2Fpcm8gY2hhc2U/",
            "answer": "RHlzZW50ZXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWQgS29jaCwgdGhlIE1heW9yIG9mIE5ldyBZb3JrIGluIDE5ODQsIHBsYXllZCBoaW1zZWxmIGluIHdoaWNoIE11cHBldHMgbW92aWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE11cHBldHMgVGFrZSBNYW5oYXR0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gIlJlcXVpZW0gZm9yIGEgRHJlYW0iLCB3aGF0IGRydWcgZG9lcyBKYXJlZCBMZXRvJ3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGdldCBhZGRpY3RlZCB0bz8=",
            "answer": "SGVyb2lu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWJvdXQgaG93IG11Y2ggbW9uZXkgZGlkIGl0IGNvc3QgZm9yIFRvbW15IFdpc2VhdSB0byBtYWtlIGhpcyBtYXN0ZXJwaWVjZSAiVGhlIFJvb20iICgyMDAzKT8=",
            "answer": "JDYgTWlsbGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGtpbGxlciBpbiB0aGUgMTk4MSBmaWxtICdNeSBCbG9vZHkgVmFsZW50aW5lJyB3ZWFycyB3aGF0IHNvcnQgb2Ygb3V0Zml0Pw==",
            "answer": "TWluaW5nIGdlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggMTk1OCBtb3ZpZSBzdGFycmVkIEtpcmsgRG91Z2xhcyBhbmQgVG9ueSBDdXJ0aXMgYXMgaGFsZi1icm90aGVycyBFaW5hciBhbmQgRXJpYz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFZpa2luZ3Mg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gRGlDYXByaW8gd29uIGFuIE9zY2FyIGZvciBCZXN0IEFjdG9yIGluIDIwMDQncyAiVGhlIEF2aWF0b3IiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW92aWUgY29udGFpbnMgdGhlIHF1b3RlLCAiU2F5IGhlbGxvIHRvIG15IGxpdHRsZSBmcmllbmQhIj8=",
            "answer": "U2NhcmZhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBEaXNuZXkgbW92aWUgY2FuIHlvdSBzcG90IHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgIlBhYy1NYW4iIGluIGlmIHlvdSBsb29rIGNsb3NlbHkgZW5vdWdoIGluIHNvbWUgc2NlbmVzPw==",
            "answer": "VHJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTAgTmlnaHRtYXJlIG9uIEVsbSBTdHJlZXQgcmVib290LCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEZyZWRkeSBLcnVnZXI/",
            "answer": "SmFja2llIEVhcmxlIEhhbGV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHNpbmdlciB3YXMgcG9ydHJheWVkIGJ5IGFjdG9yIEtldmluIFNwYWNleSBpbiB0aGUgMjAwNCBiaW9ncmFwaGljYWwgZmlsbSAiQmV5b25kIHRoZSBTZWEiPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgRGFyaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgRGlzbmV5IGFuaW1hdGVkIGZpbG0gJ01vYW5hJyBpcyBiYXNlZCBvbiB3aGljaCBjdWx0dXJlPw==",
            "answer": "UG9seW5lc2lhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc3VwZXJjb21wdXRlciBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHRoZSBjb250cm9sIHJvb20gaW4gIkp1cmFzc2ljIFBhcmsiICgxOTkzKT8=",
            "answer": "VGhpbmtpbmcgTWFjaGluZXMgQ00tNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBRdWVlbiBzb25nIHBsYXlzIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgZmluYWwgZmlnaHQgc2NlbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZpbG0gIkhhcmRjb3JlIEhlbnJ5Ij8=",
            "answer": "RG9uJ3QgU3RvcCBNZSBOb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgTW92aWVzIHdhcyBOT1QgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMTk5Nj8=",
            "answer": "R2xhZGlhdG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBLaWxsIEJpbGwgbW92aWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UXVlbnRpbiBUYXJhbnRpbm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdpZmkgcGFzc3dvcmQgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gU3RlcGhlbiBTdHJhbmdlIGluIERvY3RvciBTdHJhbmdlPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhbWJhbGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9obm55IERlcHAgbWFkZSBoaXMgYmlnLXNjcmVlbiBhY3RpbmcgZGVidXQgaW4gd2hpY2ggZmlsbT8=",
            "answer": "QSBOaWdodG1hcmUgb24gRWxtIFN0cmVldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRpZCBUb20gSGFua3MgZ2l2ZSB0byBoaXMgdm9sbGV5YmFsbCBjb21wYW5pb24gaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gYENhc3QgQXdheWA/",
            "answer": "V2lsc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0ZWQgbW92aWUgd2FzIGZpcnN0IHRvIGZlYXR1cmUgYSBjZWxlYnJpdHkgYXMgYSB2b2ljZSBhY3Rvcj8=",
            "answer": "QWxhZGRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBKYW1lcyBCb25kIHZpbGxhaW5zIGlzIG5vdCBhZmZpbGlhdGVkIHdpdGggdGhlIFNQRUNUUkUgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "QXVyaWMgR29sZGZpbmdlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5OTIgZmlsbSAiQXJteSBvZiBEYXJrbmVzcyIsIHdoYXQgbmFtZSBkb2VzIEFzaCBnaXZlIHRvIGhpcyBkb3VibGUtYmFycmVsZWQgc2hvdGd1bj8=",
            "answer": "Qm9vbXN0aWNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBDbGludCBFYXN0d29vZCBzdGFyIGFzIEluc3BlY3RvciBIYXJyeSBDYWxsYWhhbiBpbiB0aGUgZmlsbSAiRGlydHkgSGFycnkiPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gIkhhcnJ5IFBvdHRlciBhbmQgdGhlIE9yZGVyIG9mIFRoZSBQaG9lbml4Iiwgd2h5IHdhcyBIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIncyBzY3JlYW0sIGFmdGVyIFNpcml1cyBCbGFjayBkaWVkLCBtdXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "VG9vIEFnb25pemluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBoaXN0b3JpY2FsIHRpbWUgcGVyaW9kIHdhcyB0aGUgY2VudGVyIG9mIHRoZSBBc3Nhc3NpbuKAmXMgQ3JlZWQgbW92aWUgKDIwMTYpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaCBJbnF1aXNpdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIGFuZCBkaXJlY3RlZCB0aGUgMTk4NiBmaWxtICdQbGF0b29uJz8=",
            "answer": "T2xpdmVyIFN0b25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYWN0b3JzL2FjdHJlc3NlcyBpcyBOT1QgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBjYXN0IGZvciB0aGUgMjAxNiBtb3ZpZSAiU3VpY2lkZSBTcXVhZCI/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmxldHQgSm9oYW5zc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxMiwgd2hpY2ggbW92aWUgd29uIGV2ZXJ5IGNhdGVnb3J5IGluIHRoZSAzMm5kICJHb2xkZW4gUmFzcGJlcnJ5IEF3YXJkcyI/",
            "answer": "SmFjayBhbmQgSmlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Sm9hbiBDdXNhY2sgc3RhcnJlZCBpbiB0aGUgMjAwOSBkaXNhc3RlciBtb3ZpZSwgIjIwMTIiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3BlY2llcyBvZiB0aGUgIlByZWRhdG9yIiBpbiB0aGUgMTk4NyBtb3ZpZSAiUHJlZGF0b3IiPw==",
            "answer": "WWF1dGph"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTXVsYW4gKDE5OTgpLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgSHVucz8=",
            "answer": "U2hhbiBZdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggMTk5NCBmaWxtIGRpZCBSb2dlciBFYmVydCBmYW1vdXNseSBkZXNwaXNlLCBzYXlpbmcgIkkgaGF0ZWQgaGF0ZWQgaGF0ZWQgaGF0ZWQgaGF0ZWQgdGhpcyBtb3ZpZSIu",
            "answer": "Tm9ydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgYW5kIG1hcnRpYWwgYXJ0aXN0IHN0YXJyZWQgYXMgQ29sb25lbCBHdWlsZSBpbiB0aGUgMTk5NCBhY3Rpb24gZmlsbSBhZGFwdGF0aW9uIG9mIFN0cmVldCBGaWdodGVyPw==",
            "answer": "SmVhbi1DbGF1ZGUgVmFuIERhbW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgQmx1IGluIHRoZSAyMDExIGFuaW1hdGVkIGZpbG0gIlJpbyI/",
            "answer": "SmVzc2UgRWlzZW5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGFjdG9yIHdobyBwbGF5ZWQgTGVhdGhlcmZhY2UgaW4gdGhlIDE5NzQgaG9ycm9yIGZpbG0sIFRoZSBUZXhhcyBDaGFpbnNhdyBNYXNzYWNyZT8=",
            "answer": "R3VubmFyIEhhbnNlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBmaXJzdCBydWxlIGlzOiB5b3UgZG9uJ3QgdGFsayBhYm91dCBpdCIgaXMgYSByZWZlcmVuY2UgdG8gd2hpY2ggbW92aWU/",
            "answer": "RmlnaHQgQ2x1Yg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIGVuZGluZyBvZiAiTGl0dGxlIFNob3AgT2YgSG9ycm9ycyIgaGFzIHRoZSBwbGFudHMgdGFraW5nIG92ZXIgdGhlIHdvcmxkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlZCB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIERyYWNvIGluIHRoZSAxOTk2IG1vdmllICdEcmFnb25IZWFydCc/",
            "answer": "U2VhbiBDb25uZXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggMTk1NSBmaWxtIGRvZXMgRnJhbmsgU2luYXRyYSBwbGF5IE5hdGhhbiBEZXRyb2l0Pw==",
            "answer": "R3V5cyBhbmQgRG9sbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2hhcXVpbGxlIE8nTmVhbCBhcHBlYXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgMTk5NyBmaWxtICJTcGFjZSBKYW0iLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG1vdmllIEdyZW1saW5zLCBhZnRlciB3aGF0IHRpbWUgb2YgZGF5IHNob3VsZCB5b3Ugbm90IGZlZWQgTW9nd2FpPw==",
            "answer": "TWlkbmlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2NpLWZpIGN1bHQgZmlsbXMgcGxvdCBjb25jZXJucyBhbGllbnMgYXR0ZW1wdGluZyB0byBwcmV2ZW50IGh1bWFucyBmcm9tIGNyZWF0aW5nIGEgZG9vbXNkYXkgd2VhcG9uPw==",
            "answer": "UGxhbiA5IGZyb20gT3V0ZXIgU3BhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgbm90IG9uZSBvZiAiVGhlIE1hZ25pZmljZW50IFNldmVuIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2xpbnQgRWFzdHdvb2Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NzYgZmlsbSAnVGF4aSBEcml2ZXInLCBob3cgbWFueSBndW5zIGRpZCBUcmF2aXMgYnV5IGZyb20gdGhlIHNhbGVzbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkN1YmUiLCAiQ3ViZSAyOiBIeXBlcmN1YmUiIGFuZCAiQ3ViZSBaZXJvIiB3ZXJlIGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IHRoZSBzYW1lIHBlcnNvbi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpbG0gTWFkIE1heDogRnVyeSBSb2FkIGZlYXR1cmVzIHRoZSBEaWVzIElyYWUgIGZyb20gd2hpY2ggY29tcG9zZXIncyByZXF1aWVtPw==",
            "answer": "VmVyZGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBMaWxvJ3MgbGFzdCBuYW1lIGZyb20gTGlsbyBhbmQgU3RpdGNoPw==",
            "answer": "UGVsZWthaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2luZ2VyIGlzIHBvcnRyYXllZCBieSBCcnVjZSBDYW1wYmVsbCBpbiB0aGUgMjAwMiBmaWxtICdCdWJiYSBIby1UZXAnPw==",
            "answer": "RWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBCb25kIG1vdmllLCByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAxOTYyPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuIE5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb3ZpZSBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgcXVvdGUsICJJIGxvdmUgdGhlIHNtZWxsIG9mIG5hcGFsbSBpbiB0aGUgbW9ybmluZyEi",
            "answer": "QXBvY2FseXBzZSBOb3c="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhcnRpc3Qgb2YgdGhlIHJlY2VudCBuZXcgYWxidW0gdGhlIFVuY2FubnkgVmFsbGV5Pw==",
            "answer": "UGVydHVyYmF0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljIGdyb3VwIERhZnQgUHVuayBnb3QgdGhlaXIgbmFtZSBmcm9tIGEgbmVnYXRpdmUgcmV2aWV3IHRoZXkgcmVjaWV2ZWQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRnJlbmNoIGR1byBoYWQgVUsgaGl0cyBpbiAxOTk4IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmdzICdTZXh5IEJveScsICdLZWxseSBXYXRjaCBUaGUgU3RhcnMnICYgJ0FsbCBJIE5lZWQnPw==",
            "answer": "QWly"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gZmFtaWx5IGJhbmQgaGFkIGEgMTk4NiB0b3AgMTAgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ0NydXNoIE9uIFlvdSc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEpldHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5NjkgdG9wIDUgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcsICAnQSBCb3kgTmFtZWQgU3VlJz8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obm55IENhc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRWx0b24gSm9obiBoaXQgc3RhcnRzIHdpdGggdGhlIGxpbmUgIldoZW4gYXJlIHlvdSBnb25uYSBjb21lIGRvd24iPw==",
            "answer": "R29vZGJ5ZSBZZWxsb3cgQnJpY2sgUm9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHlwaWNhbGx5LCBob3cgbWFueSBrZXlzIGFyZSBvbiBhIHBpYW5vPw==",
            "answer": "ODg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3Mgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDE5OTY/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNtYXNoaW5nIFB1bXBraW5zIC0gIjE5Nzki"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmcm9udG1hbiBvZiB0aGUgYmFuZCAzMCBTZWNvbmRzIHRvIE1hcnM/",
            "answer": "SmFyZWQgTGV0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2F1bCBIdWRzb24gKFNsYXNoKSBvZiB0aGUgYmFuZCBHdW5zIE4nIFJvc2VzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwbGF5aW5nIHdoYXQgdHlwZSBvZiBndWl0YXI/",
            "answer": "TGVzIFBhdWwgU3RhbmRhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIlR3aW4gU2l6ZSBNYXR0cmVzcyIgd2FzIHdyaXR0ZW4gYnkgd2hpY2ggYmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZyb250IEJvdHRvbXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmVzdCBzZWxsaW5nIGFsYnVtIG9mIGFsbCB0aW1lIGZyb20gMTk3NiB0byAyMDE4Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhyaWxsZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgZHJ1bW1lciBmb3IgVGhlIEJlYXRsZXM/",
            "answer": "VG9tbXkgTW9vcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcmltYXJ5IGx5cmljaXN0IGZvciBDYW5hZGlhbiBwcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSByb2NrIGJhbmQgUnVzaD8=",
            "answer": "TmVpbCBQZWFydA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBGb28gRmlnaHRlcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgdGhlIGRydW1tZXIgZm9yIE5pcnZhbmE/",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBHcm9obA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW1lcmljYW4gcmFwcGVyIERyLiBEcmUgYWN0dWFsbHkgaGFzIGEgUGguRC4gZG9jdG9yYXRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgYnkgU2tyaWxsZXggZmVhdHVyZXMgRmF0bWFuIFNjb29wIGFzIGEgc2lkZSBhcnRpc3Q/",
            "answer": "UmVjZXNz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBpcyBub3QgYnkgVGhlRmF0UmF0Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNjZW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmluaXNoIHRoZXNlIGx5cmljcyBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDE2IHNvbmcgIlBhbmRhIiBieSBEZXNpaWduZXI6ICJJIGdvdCBicm9hZHMgaW4gX19fX19fXyIu",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFkb25uYSdzIHNvbmcgIkh1bmcgVXAiIGluY2x1ZGVzIGEgcGllY2UgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBwb3B1bGFyIDcwcyBzb25nPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbWllISBHaW1taWUhIEdpbW1lISAoQSBNYW4gQWZ0ZXIgTWlkbmlnaHQp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2Ygc2luZ2VyIEZyYW5rIE9jZWFuJ3Mgc2Vjb25kIHN0dWRpbyBhbGJ1bSwgd2hpY2ggd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIG9uIEF1Z3VzdCAyMCwgMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmVhdGxlcyBhbGJ1bSBkb2VzIE5PVCBmZWF0dXJlIGFueSBvZiB0aGUgYmFuZCBtZW1iZXJzIG9uIGl0J3MgY292ZXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJlYXRsZXMgKFdoaXRlIEFsYnVtKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCByZWxlYXNlZCBzb25ncyBzdWNocyBhcyAiUmlvIiwgIkdpcmxzIG9uIEZpbG0iLCBhbmQgIlRoZSBSZWZsZXgiPw==",
            "answer": "RHVyYW4gRHVyYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFsdGVybmF0aXZlIHJvY2sgYmFuZCwgVGhleSBNaWdodCBCZSBHaWFudHMsIHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZWlyIGFsYnVtICdGbG9vZCcgaW4gMTk5MC4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmcm9udG1hbiBvZiBNdXNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWF0dCBCZWxsYW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIDkwJ3MgcmFwIGFsYnVtIGlzIGNvbW1vbmx5IHJlZmVycmVkIHRvIGFzICJUaGUgQmlibGUgb2YgSGlwIEhvcCI/",
            "answer": "SWxsbWF0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gS2VuZHJpY2sgTGFtYXIncyAyMDEyIGFsYnVtLCAiR29vZCBLaWQsIE0uQS5BLkQgQ2l0eSIsIHRoZSBhbGJ1bSdzIHN0b3J5IHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGluIHdoaWNoIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "Q29tcHRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIGEgc29uZyBieSBCZWxpbmRhIENhcmxpc2xlLCBIZWF2ZW4gaXMgYSBwbGFjZSBvbiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "RWFydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBhbGJ1bSBjb3ZlciBmb3IgVHJ1ZSBSb21hbmNlLCBhbiBhbGJ1bSBieSBFc3RlbGxlPw==",
            "answer": "UmViZWNjYSBTdWdhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgUmFkaW9oZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gSG9uZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkFsbCB0aGUgQm95cyIgYnkgUGFuaWMhIEF0IHRoZSBEaXNjbyB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgYXMgYSBib251cyB0cmFjayBvbiB3aGF0IGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "VG9vIFdlaXJkIFRvIExpdmUsIFRvbyBSYXJlIFRvIERpZSE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGluayBHdXkncyBkZWJ1dCBhbGJ1bSB3YXMgIlBpbmsgU2Vhc29uIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgc29uZyBieSBQZWdib2FyZCBOZXJkcz8=",
            "answer": "V2lGaSBUZWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpY2FsIGNvbXBvc2VyIHdyb3RlIHRoZSAiTW9vbmxpZ2h0IFNvbmF0YSI/",
            "answer": "THVkdmlnIFZhbiBCZWV0aG92ZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgVGFtZSBJbXBhbGEgcmVsZWFzZSB0aGVpciBzZWNvbmQgYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgRGF2aWQgQm93aWUncyByZWFsIHN1cm5hbWU/",
            "answer": "Sm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGhpcCBob3AgZ3JvdXAgS2FueWUgV2VzdCB3YXMgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgaW4gdGhlIGxhdGUgOTBzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdvLUdldHRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWxlY3Ryb25pYyBhcnRpc3RzIEJveXMgTm9pemUgYW5kIFNrcmlsbGV4IGhhdmUgY29sbGFib3JhdGVkIGFuZCByZWxlYXNlZCB0cmFja3MgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "RG9nIEJsb29k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IG9yIGdyb3VwIGRpZCBKb2huIExlbm5vbiBjb25zaWRlciAic29uKHMpIG9mIHRoZSBCZWF0bGVzIj8=",
            "answer": "SmVmZiBMeW5uZSdzIEVsZWN0cmljIExpZ2h0IE9yY2hlc3RyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmrDtnJrJ3MgIlVuaXNvbiIgY29udGFpbnMgYSBzYW1wbGUgb2Ygd2hpY2ggT3ZhbCBzb25nPw==",
            "answer": "QWVybyBEZWNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TXVzaWNhbCBhcnRpc3QsIEZ1dHVyZSwgY29sbGFib3JhdGVkIHdpdGggS2VuZHJpY2sgTGFtYXIgZm9yIHRoZSBzb25nOiAiTWFzayBPZmYiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgaXMgTk9UIGluIFRoZSBCZWF0bGVzJyBhbGJ1bSAiU2d0LiBQZXBwZXIncyBMb25lbHkgSGVhcnRzIENsdWIgQmFuZCI/",
            "answer": "U3RyYXdiZXJyeSBGaWVsZHMgRm9yZXZlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgSm9obnMgd2FzIG11cmRlcmVkIGJ5IGd1bnNob3RzIG91dHNpZGUgdGhlIERha290YSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBpbiAxOTgwPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBMZW5ub24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNpbmdlciBCaWxsaWUgSG9saWRheSB3YXMgYWxzbyBrbm93biBhcyAiTGFkeSBEYXkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm92ZWx0eSBiYW5kIHdhcyBiZXN0IGtub3duIGZvciB0aGVpciBVSyBjaGFydCBoaXRzICJDb21iaW5lIEhhcnZlc3RlciIgYW5kICJJIEFtIGEgQ2lkZXIgRHJpbmtlciIgaW4gMTk3Nj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFd1cnplbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJ0aXMgTGVvbiBJdmV5IEpyLiBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggcmFwIGFydGlzdD8=",
            "answer": "Q29vbGlv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIGNvdmVyIG9mICdBYmJleSBSb2FkLCcgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIEJlYXRsZXMgaXMgbm90IHdlYXJpbmcgc2hvZXM/",
            "answer": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSB2aXJ0dWFsIGJhbmQgR29yaWxsYXo/",
            "answer": "UGhpIEN5cGhlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgVGhlIFZlbHZldCBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZCdzIGZpcnN0IGFsYnVtIGNhbGxlZD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFZlbHZldCBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZCAmIE5pY28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBGb28gRmlnaHRlcnM/",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBHcm9obA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5ODMgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ0FmcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG90bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvdmVyIG9mIFRoZSBCZWF0bGVzIGFsYnVtICJBYmJleSBSb2FkIiBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gQmVldGxlIGluIHRoZSBiYWNrZ3JvdW5kLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmVhdGxlIGxlZCB0aGUgd2F5IGFjcm9zcyB0aGUgemVicmEgY3Jvc3Npbmcgb24gdGhlIEFiYmV5IFJvYWQgYWxidW0gY292ZXI/",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9wdWxhciByb2NrIGJhbmQgaGFzIGEgb25lLWFybWVkIGRydW1tZXI/",
            "answer": "RGVmIExlcHBhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBzaW5nZXIgS3lhcnkgUGFteXUgUGFteXUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "SmFwYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWxidW0gcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAxNCBieSBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kIE1hcm9vbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Vg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBpbiByYXBwZXIgS2FueWUgV2VzdCdzIGFsYnVtICJUaGUgTGlmZSBvZiBQYWJsbyIgZmVhdHVyZXMgUmloYW5uYT8=",
            "answer": "RmFtb3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tm9yd2VnaWFuIHByb2R1Y2VyIEt5Z28gcmVsZWFzZWQgYSByZW1peCBvZiB0aGUgc29uZyAiU2V4dWFsIEhlYWxpbmciIGJ5IE1hcnZpbiBHYXllLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHJhcHBlciBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBKYWNrIMOcIChTa3JpbGxleCBhbmQgRGlwbG8pJ3MgMjAxNSBzaW5nbGUgY2FsbGVkICJGZWJyZXplIj8=",
            "answer": "MiBDaGFpbno="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvdW50cnkgc29uZyAg4oCcQSBCb3kgTmFtZWQgU3Vl4oCdIHdhcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IFNoZWwgU2lsdmVyc3RlaW4u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJ0aXN0cyBkbyBOT1Qgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIENoZW1pY2FsIEJyb3RoZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYWxpYXNlcyBoYXMgTk9UIGJlZW4gdXNlZCBieSBlbGVjdHJvbmljIG11c2ljaWFuIEFwaGV4IFR3aW4/",
            "answer": "QnVyaWFs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBGaW5uaXNoIERKIERhcnVkZSdzIGhpdCBzaW5nbGUgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gT2N0b2JlciAxOTk5Pw==",
            "answer": "U2FuZHN0b3Jt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgb24gdGhlIGNvdmVyIG9mIEVuZ2xpc2ggZWxlY3Ryb25pYyBtdXNpYyBncm91cCBUaGUgUHJvZGlneSdzIGFsYnVtLCAiVGhlIEZhdCBvZiB0aGUgTGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "Q3JhYg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIFNha2Ftb3RvIEt5dSdzIHNvbmcgIlVlIG8gTXVpdGUgQXJ1a291IiAoSSBMb29rIFVwIEFzIEkgV2FsaykgY2hhbmdlZCB0byBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "U3VraXlha2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgdGhlIGFsYnVtICJGbG9yYWwgU2hvcHBlIiBieSBNYWNpbnRvc2ggUGx1cyByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBhbGJ1bSwgbm93IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gYmUgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBncmVhdGVzdCBvZiBhbGwgdGltZSwgd2FzIGEgY29tbWVyY2lhbCBmYWlsdXJlIHdoZW4gaXQgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkLg==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFZlbHZldCBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZCBhbmQgTmljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkb2VzIHRoZSBlbGVjdHJvbmljIG11c2ljIGR1byAiVGhlIEtuaWZlIiBvcmlnaW5hdGUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "U3dlZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBpbiBEcmFrZSdzICJWaWV3cyIgZmVhdHVyZXMgRnV0dXJlPw==",
            "answer": "R3JhbW15cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWxidW0gd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGJ5IEthbnllIFdlc3QgaW4gMjAxMz8=",
            "answer": "WWVlenVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9yIGhpcyBwZXJmb3JtYW5jZSBhdCBDb21wbGV4Q29uIDIwMTYgaW4gTG9uZyBCZWFjaCwgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSwgU2tyaWxsZXggcmV2aXZlZCBoaXMgIk1vdGhlcnNoaXAiIHNldCBwaWVjZSBmb3Igb25lIG5pZ2h0IG9ubHku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBCYXN0aWxsZT8=",
            "answer": "RGFuIFNtaXRo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBzb25nICJZb3UgS25vdyBZb3UgTGlrZSBJdCI/",
            "answer": "QWx1bmFHZW9yZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIkNhcmFtZWxsZGFuc2VuIiBpcyBjb21tb25seSBtaXN0YWtlbiBhcyBhIEphcGFuZXNlIHNvbmcsIHdoYXQgbGFuZ3VhZ2UgaXMgdGhlIHNvbmcgYWN0dWFsbHkgc3VuZyBpbj8=",
            "answer": "U3dlZGlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgdGhlIGFuaW1hdGlvbiBmb3IgUGV0ZXIgR2FicmllbCdzIFZpZGVvIFNsZWRnZWhhbW1lciAoMTk4Nik/",
            "answer": "QWFyZG1hbiBBbmltYXRpb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWxsaWUgR291bGRpbmcncyBlYXJsaWVzdCBhbGJ1bSB3YXMgbmFtZWQ/",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgaXMgbm90IG9uIHRoZSAidW50aXRsZWQiIGFsYnVtIGJ5IExlZCBaZXBwZWxpbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2VsZWJyYXRpb24gRGF5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCByZWxlYXNlZCB0aGUgYWxidW0gIlNvbmljIEhpZ2h3YXlzIiBpbiAyMDE0Pw==",
            "answer": "Rm9vIEZpZ2h0ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyByYXBwZXIgRHJha2UncyByZWFsIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgbmFtZSBvZiBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZCBzaW5nZXIgUGhpbGxpcGEgIlBpcCIgQnJvd24/",
            "answer": "TGFkeWhhd2tl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHJvY2sgYmFuZCB0aGF0IE5vYnVvIFVlbWF0c3UgZm9ybWVkIHRoYXQgcGxheWVkIHNvbmdzIGZyb20gdmFyaW91cyBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IGdhbWVzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIE1hZ2Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJhbmQgTXVzZSByZWxlYXNlZCB0aGVpciBmaXJzdCBhbGJ1bSwgU2hvd2JpeiwgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgU2NhdG1hbidzIFdvcmxkIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBhZnRlciBTY2F0bWFuIChTa2ktQmEtQm9wLUJhLURvcC1Cb3ApLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgdHJhY2sgb24gdGhlIERhdmUgTWF0dGhld3MgQmFuZCBhbGJ1bSAiQmVmb3JlIFRoZXNlIENyb3dkZWQgU3RyZWV0cyI/",
            "answer": "UGFudGFsYSBOYWdhIFBhbXBh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBKb25lcyIsICJUdXJuIEJhY2sgVGltZSIgYW5kICJCYXJiaWUgR2lybCIgd2VyZSBVSyBudW1iZXIgb25lcyBmb3Igd2hpY2ggRXVyb2RhbmNlIGdyb3VwPw==",
            "answer": "QXF1YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWV0YWxsaWNhIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRlZCB3aXRoIFJvd2FuIEF0a2luc29uJ3MgTXIgQmVhbiBvbiBhIDE5OTIgY29taWMgcmVsaWVmIHNpbmdsZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBDYWl4YSBNYWxhY2FjaGV0YSBpcyB3aGF0IGtpbmQgb2YgbXVzaWNhbCBpbnN0cnVtZW50IHdoaWNoIGlzIGNvbW1vbmx5IHVzZWQgaW4gTGF0aW4gQW1lcmljYW4gbXVzaWM/",
            "answer": "U25hcmUgRHJ1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbXVzaWMgcHVibGljYXRpb24gaXMgb2Z0ZW4gYWJicmV2aWF0ZWQgdG8gTk1FPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IE11c2ljYWwgRXhwcmVzcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Sm9obiBXaWxsaWFtcyBjb21wb3NlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWMgZm9yICJTdGFyIFdhcnMiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik5ldXRyYWwgTWlsayBIb3RlbCIgaXMgYSByZWFsIGJhbmQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFd1LVRhbmcgQ2xhbiBhbGJ1bSBNYXJ0aW4gU2hrcmVsaSBib3VnaHQgZm9yICQyIG1pbGxpb24gZG9sbGFycz8=",
            "answer": "T25jZSBVcG9uIGEgVGltZSBpbiBTaGFvbGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJ1c2ggc29uZyAiWVlaIiBkZXJpdmVzIGl0cyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIElBVEEgYWlwb3J0IGlkZW50aWZpY2F0aW9uIGNvZGUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "VG9yb250bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBlb3BsZSBoYXMgYmVlbiBpbiB0aGUgYmFuZCAnJ01ldGFsbGljYScnIGluIHRoZSBwYXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBNdXN0YWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3R1ZGlvIGFsYnVtcyBoYXZlIHRoZSBoZWF2eSBtZXRhbCBiYW5kLCAnTWV0YWxsaWNhJyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgcGVyaW9kIGJldHdlZW4gMTk4MyBhbmQgMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFByb2NsYWltZXJzIC0gSSdtIEdvbm5hIEJlICg1MDAgTWlsZXMpIHJlYWNoZWQgd2hhdCBwb3NpdGlvbiBvbiB0aGUgVVMgSG90IDEwMCBDaGFydHMgaW4gMTk5Mz8=",
            "answer": "M3Jk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIEFCQkFgcyBmaXJzdCBVSyBoaXQgc2luZ2xlPw==",
            "answer": "V2F0ZXJsb28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgQXBoZXggVHdpbiBhbGJ1bSByZWxlYXNlZCBiZWZvcmUgaGlzIGRlY2FkZS1sb25nIGhpYXR1cz8=",
            "answer": "RHJ1a3Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTTgzIGFsYnVtIGlzIHRoZSBzb25nICJNaWRuaWdodCBDaXR5IiBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "SHVycnkgVXAsIFdlJ3JlIERyZWFtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RURNIHByb2R1Y2VyIE1hcnNobWVsbG8gcGVyZm9ybXMgbGl2ZSB3ZWFyaW5nIGNsb3RoZXMgYW5kIGEgbWFyc2htYWxsb3cgbWFzayBvZiB3aGF0IGNvbG91cj8=",
            "answer": "V2hpdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVHdpdGNoIHN0cmVhbWVyIGlzIHRoZSB2b2NhbGlzdCBmb3IgUmVkIFZveD8=",
            "answer": "VmluZXNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiB0aW1lIHNpZ25hdHVyZSBmb3Igcm9jayBzb25ncz8=",
            "answer": "NC80"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdCBhY3RpdmUgYmFuZCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQgd2l0aCBubyBicmVha3Mgb3IgbGluZS11cCBjaGFuZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "VTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgRW5nbGlzaCB0aXRsZSBvZiB0aGUgdmFwb3J3YXZlIHRyYWNrICLjg6rjgrXjg5Xjg6njg7Pjgq80MjAgLyDnj77ku6Pjga7jgrPjg7Pjg5Tjg6Xjg7wiIGJ5IE1hY2ludG9zaCBQbHVzIChWZWt0cm9pZCk/",
            "answer": "TGlzYSBGcmFuayA0MjAgLyBNb2Rlcm4gQ29tcHV0aW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBIdXVuIEh1dXIgVHUncyBhbGJ1bSBBbHRhaSBTYXlhbiBUYW5keS1VdWxhIHJlbGVhc2VkPyA=",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgMjAxNiBzdHVkaW8gYWxidW0gYnkgdGhlIEZyZW5jaCBlbGVjdHJvbmljIG11c2ljIGR1byBKdXN0aWNlPw==",
            "answer": "V29tYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIENhbmFkaWFuIGVsZWN0cm9uaWMgbXVzaWMgcHJvZHVjZXIgZGVhZG1hdTU/",
            "answer": "Sm9lbCBaaW1tZXJtYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2FueWUgV2VzdCBhdCAyMDA5IFZNQSdzIGludGVycnVwdGVkIHdoaWNoIGNlbGVicml0eT8=",
            "answer": "VGF5bG9yIFN3aWZ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGtleSBvZiBzaGFycHMgZG9lcyB0aGUga2V5IG9mIEcjIG1pbm9yIGNvbnRhaW4/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xsYWJvcmF0aXZlIGFsYnVtIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBieSBLYW55ZSBXZXN0IGFuZCBKYXktWiBpbiAyMDExPw==",
            "answer": "V2F0Y2ggdGhlIFRocm9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgVGhlIEJlYXRsZXMgcmVsZWFzZSB0aGUgTFAgIlBsZWFzZSBQbGVhc2UgTWUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTk2Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkxpZnQgWW91ciBTcGlyaXQiIGlzIGFuIGFsYnVtIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGFydGlzdD8=",
            "answer": "QWxvZSBCbGFjYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGJhbmQgU1RSRktSIHdhcyBhbHNvIGJyaWVmbHkga25vd24gYXMgUHlyYW1pZGRkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q3J5b3NoZWxsLCBrbm93biBmb3IgIkNyZWVwaW5nIGluIE15IFNvdWwiIGRpZCB0aGUgYWR2ZXJ0aXNpbmcgbXVzaWMgZm9yIHdoYXQgTGVnbyBUaGVtZT8=",
            "answer": "QmlvbmljbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBUaGUgTHVtaW5lZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "V2VzbGV5IFNjaHVsdHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgUGluayBGbG95ZCdzIGZpcnN0IHN0dWRpbyBhbGJ1bT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBpcGVyIGF0IHRoZSBHYXRlcyBvZiBEYXdu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGV0ZSBUb3duc2hlbmQncyBzb2xvIGFsYnVtLCAiV2hpdGUgQ2l0eTogQSBOb3ZlbCIsIGlzIHNldCBpbiB0aGUgbWV0cm9wb2xpdGFuIGFyZWEgb2YgQ2hpY2Fnby4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbHlyaWMgaXMgYWJvdXQgUmVkIEhvdCBDaGlsaSBQZXBwZXJzIGZyb250bWFuIEFudGhvbnkgS2llZGlzPw==",
            "answer": "IkEgcmFpbnkgTGl0aHVhbmlhbiAvIElzIGRhbmNpbmcgYXMgYW4gSW5kaWFuIg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNvbGQtd2FyIHNpbmdlciB3aG8gaGFzIGEgc29uZyBpbiBHcmFuZCBUaGVmdCBBdXRvIElWLCBhbmQgYSB3YWxsIGxhbmRtYXJrIGluIE1vc2NvdyBmb3IgaGlzIG1lbW9yaWFsPw==",
            "answer": "VmlrdG9yIFRzb2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWxidW0gYnkgQW1lcmljYW4gcmFwcGVyIEthbnllIFdlc3QgY29udGFpbmVkIHNvbmdzIHN1Y2ggYXMgIkxvdmUgTG9ja2Rvd24iLCAiUGFyYW5vaWQiIGFuZCAiSGVhcnRsZXNzIj8=",
            "answer": "ODA4cyAmIEhlYXJ0YnJlYWs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGlhbSBIb3dsZXR0IGZvdW5kZWQgd2hpY2ggZWxlY3Ryb25pYyBtdXNpYyBncm91cCBpbiAxOTkwPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByb2RpZ3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBGYWNlYm9vayBjYW1wYWlnbiBwbGFjZWQgUmFnZSBBZ2FpbnN0IFRoZSBNYWNoaW5lJ3MgIktpbGxpbmcgaW4gdGhlIE5hbWUgT2YiIGFzIHRoZSBVSyBDaHJpc3RtYXMgTnVtYmVyIDEgaW4gMjAwOS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Jzc04oCTJzc1IGlzIGEgMTk5MyBzaW5nbGUgZnJvbSB0aGUgYWxidW0gUmluZyBieSB3aGF0IEFtZXJpY2FuIGJhbmQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIENvbm5lbGxz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBwcmV2aW91c2x5IHJlY29yZGVkIGJ5IEVsdmlzIFByZXNsZXkgd2FzIGNvdmVyZWQgYnkgVUI0MCB3aXRoIGEgcmVnZ2FlIGJlYXQ/",
            "answer": "Q2FuJ3QgSGVscCBGYWxsaW5nIGluIExvdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBSaXZlcnMgQ3VvbW8ncyB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "S3lva28gSXRv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGVhZCBTaW5nZXIgUml2ZXJzIEN1b21vIG9mIEFtZXJpY2FuIHJvY2sgYmFuZCBXZWV6ZXIgYXR0ZW5kZWQgSGFydmFyZC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3JlZW4gRGF5J3MgYWxidW0gJ0FtZXJpY2FuIElkaW90JyBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGEgInB1bmsgcm9jayBvcGVyYS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhbiBhbGJ1bSBieSBwdW5rIHJvY2sgYmFuZCBBbnRpLUZsYWc/",
            "answer": "Rm9yIEJsb29kIEFuZCBFbXBpcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBoaXRzIGluIHRoZSA3MHMgd2l0aCB0aGUgc29uZ3MgIkxvbmVseSBCb3kiIGFuZCAiTmV2ZXIgTGV0IEhlciBTbGlwIEF3YXkiPw==",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEdvbGQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2luZ2VyIHdhcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBKYWNrIMOcIChTa3JpbGxleCAmIERpcGxvKSdzIDIwMTUgc29uZyAnV2hlcmUgQXJlIMOcIE5vdyc/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIEJpZWJlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJlZCBIb3QgQ2hpbGkgUGVwcGVyIHNvbmcgIkdpdmUgSXQgQXdheSIgaXMgZnJvbSB3aGF0IGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "Qmxvb2QgU3VnYXIgU2V4IE1hZ2lr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvc2Ugc2lnbmF0dXJlIGd1aXRhciB0ZWNobmlxdWUgaXMgY2FsbGVkIHRoZSAid2luZG1pbGwiPw==",
            "answer": "UGV0ZSBUb3duc2hlbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbWVtYmVycyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gdGhlIGJhbmQgTmlydmFuYT8=",
            "answer": "VGhyZWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBFbmdsaXNoIGJhbmQgIlRoZSB4eCIgcmVsZWFzZWQgdGhlaXIgc29sbyBhbGJ1bSAiSW4gQ29sb3VyIiBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmFtaWUgeHg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBnZW5yZSBvZiBFRE0gaXMgdGhlIER1dGNoIERKLCBtdXNpY2lhbiwgYW5kIHJlbWl4ZXIgQXJtaW4gdmFuIEJ1dXJlbiBtb3N0IHdlbGwta25vd24gZm9yPw==",
            "answer": "VHJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNSwgRGF2aWQgSGFzc2VsaG9mIHJlbGVhc2VkIGEgc2luZ2xlIGNhbGxlZC4uLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBTdXJ2aXZvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbWVtYmVycyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gdGhlIGlkb2wgZ3JvdXAgIsK1J3MiPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJ0aXN0cyBkaWQgTk9UIHJlbWl4IHRoZSBzb25nICJGYWRlZCIgYnkgQWxhbiBXYWxrZXI/",
            "answer": "U2tyaWxsZXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGFuIGFsYnVtIHJlbGVhc2VkIGJ5IE1pYW1pLWJhc2VkIHByb2R1Y2VyIERKIEtoYWxlZD8=",
            "answer": "RG9uJ3QgRXZlciBQbGF5IFlvdXJzZWxm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnJpYW4gTWF5IHdhcyB0aGUgZ3VpdGFyaXN0IGZvciB3aGljaCBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "UXVlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHN1YmplY3Qgb2YgdGhlIDIwMTQgc29uZyAiQ29DbyIgYnkgQW1lcmljYW4gcmFwcGVyIE8uIFQuIEdlbmFzaXM/",
            "answer": "Q29jYWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGluayBGbG95ZCBtYWRlIHRoaXMgc29uZyBmb3IgdGhlaXIgcHJldmlvdXMgbGVhZCBzaW5nZXIgU3lkIEJhcnJldHQu",
            "answer": "U2hpbmUgT24gWW91IENyYXp5IERpYW1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBGcmVuY2ggZWxlY3Ryb25pYyBtdXNpYyBwcm9kdWNlciBNYWRlb24ncyAyMDE1IGRlYnV0IHN0dWRpbyBhbGJ1bT8=",
            "answer": "QWR2ZW50dXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBCcmlhbiBNYXkncyBndWl0YXIgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "UmVkIFNwZWNpYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2FueWUgV2VzdCdzICJHb2xkIERpZ2dlciIgZmVhdHVyZWQgd2hpY2ggT3NjYXItd2lubmluZyBhY3Rvcj8=",
            "answer": "SmFtaWUgRm94eA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBvbiBEYWZ0IFB1bmsncyAiUmFuZG9tIEFjY2VzcyBNZW1vcmllcyIgZmVhdHVyZXMgUGhhcnJlbGwgV2lsbGlhbXM/",
            "answer": "R2V0IEx1Y2t5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbWVtYmVycyBhcmUgaW4gdGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIHJvY2sgYmFuZCBTQ0FOREFMPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZyaWNhbi1BbWVyaWNhbiBwZXJmb3JtZXIgU2FtbXkgRGF2aXMgSnIuIHdhcyBrbm93biBmb3IgbG9zaW5nIHdoaWNoIHBhcnQgb2YgaGlzIGJvZHkgaW4gYSBjYXIgYWNjaWRlbnQ/",
            "answer": "TGVmdCBFeWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBTaW5naW5nIENvd2JveSIgR2VuZSBBdXRyeSBpcyBjcmVkaXRlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBmaXJzdCByZWNvcmRpbmcgZm9yIGFsbCBidXQgd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBDaHJpc3RtYXMgamluZ2xlPw==",
            "answer": "V2hpdGUgQ2hyaXN0bWFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnJvbnRtYW4ncyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBtZXRhbCBiYW5kIE1lZ2FkZXRoPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBNdXN0YWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSAxOTkxIGFsYnVtICJPdXQgb2YgVGltZSI/",
            "answer": "Ui5FLk0u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk5MywgUHJpbmNlIGNoYW5nZWQgaGlzIG5hbWUgdG8gYW4gdW5wcm9ub3VuY2VhYmxlIHN5bWJvbCBiZWNhdXNlIGhlIHdhcyB1bmhhcHB5IHdpdGggaGlzIGNvbnRyYWN0IHdpdGggV2FybmVyIEJyb3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBSSUFBOiBXaGljaCBhcnRpc3QgaGFzIHNvbGQgdGhlIG1vc3QgYWxidW1zIGJ5IHRoZSBtaWxsaW9uPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJlYXRsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB3YWxraW5nIGxpa2UgYW4gRWd5cHRpYW4gaW4gMTk4MT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhbmdsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVuayByb2NrIGJhbmQgcmVsZWFzZWQgaGl0IHNvbmdzIHN1Y2ggYXMgIkNhbGlmb3JuaWNhdGlvbiIsICJDYW4ndCBTdG9wIiBhbmQgIlVuZGVyIHRoZSBCcmlkZ2UiPw==",
            "answer": "UmVkIEhvdCBDaGlsbGkgUGVwcGVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmljayBBc3RsZXkncyBoaXQgc29uZyAiTmV2ZXIgR29ubmEgR2l2ZSBZb3UgVXAiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MTk4Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgQnJpdG5leSBTcGVhcnMnIGRlYnV0IHNpbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "Li4uQmFieSBPbmUgTW9yZSBUaW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb3BlbmluZyB0cmFjayBvbiBMb3JkZSdzIFB1cmUgSGVyb2luZT8=",
            "answer": "VGVubmlzIENvdXJ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIE5pY2tpIE1pbmFqIGJvcm4/",
            "answer": "VHJpbmlkYWQgYW5kIFRvYmFnbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIE5PVCBhIE1lbiBhdCBXb3JrIHNvbmc/",
            "answer": "QmFza2V0IENhc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmVhdGxlIHdyb3RlIGFuZCBzYW5nIHRoZSBzb25nICJXaHkgRG9uJ3QgV2UgRG8gSXQgaW4gdGhlIFJvYWQiIGFmdGVyIGJlaW5nIGluc3BpcmVkIGJ5IHNlZWluZyB0d28gbW9ua2V5cyBjb3B1bGF0aW5nIGluIHRoZSBzdHJlZXQ/",
            "answer": "UGF1bA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgUmFla3dvbiB0aGUgQ2hlZnMgZGVidXQgc29sbyBhbGJ1bT8=",
            "answer": "T25seSBCdWlsdCA0IEN1YmFuIExpbng="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBub3QgYSB3aW5kIGluc3RydW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "VmlvbGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCBoYWQgaGl0cyBpbiAxOTcyIHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmdzICJCYWJ5IEknbSBBIFdhbnQgWW91IiwgIkV2ZXJ5dGhpbmcgSSBPd24iIGFuZCAiVGhlIEd1aXRhciBNYW4i",
            "answer": "QnJlYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCByZWxlYXNlZCBzb25ncyBzdWNoIGFzICJFbGVjdHJpYyBGZWVsIiwgIktpZHMiLCBhbmQgIlRpbWUgdG8gUHJldGVuZCI/",
            "answer": "TUdNVA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJ0aXN0cyB3YXMgTk9UIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBlbGVjdHJvbmljIG11c2ljIHN1cGVyZ3JvdXAgU3dlZGlzaCBIb3VzZSBNYWZpYSwgd2hpY2ggc3BsaXQgdXAgaW4gMjAxMz8=",
            "answer": "QWxlc3Nv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVG9yb250byBsYW5kbWFyayB3YXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgb24gdGhlIGNvdmVyIGFydCBvZiBDYW5hZGlhbiByYXBwZXIgRHJha2UncyAyMDE2IGFsYnVtICJWaWV3cyI/",
            "answer": "Q04gVG93ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJ0aXN0cyBoYXMgTk9UIGJlZW4gYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgZGFuY2VoYWxsIGdyb3VwIE1ham9yIExhemVyPw==",
            "answer": "U2tyaWxsZXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBTaWx2ZXJjaGFpcj8=",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIEpvaG5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCB0ZXJtIGZvciBhIDY0dGggbm90ZT8=",
            "answer": "SGVtaWRlbWlzZW1pcXVhdmVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IGNvbGxhYm9yYXRlZCB3aXRoIEFtZXJpY2FuIERKIERpbGxvbiBGcmFuY2lzIHRvIHJlbGVhc2UgdGhlIHNvbmcgMjAxNiAiTmVlZCBZb3UiPw==",
            "answer": "TkdIVE1SRQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaWNvbmljIGFsYnVtIGNvdmVyIGZlYXR1cmVzIHRoZSBwdWxzYXIgd2F2ZXMgb2YgQ1AgMTkxOSBwbGFjZWQgaW4gdGhlIGNlbnRlciBvZiB0aGUgY292ZXI/",
            "answer": "VW5rbm93biBQbGVhc3VyZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5IGRpZCB0aGUgc29uZyAiR2FuZ25hbSBTdHlsZSIgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "U291dGggS29yZWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAwNiwgd2hpY2ggYmFuZCByZWxlYXNlZCB0aGVpciBkZWJ1dCBhbGJ1bSAiQSBGZXZlciBZb3UgQ2FuJ3QgU3dlYXQgT3V0Ij8=",
            "answer": "UGFuaWMhIEF0IHRoZSBEaXNjbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBmaWxtIHdhcyB0aGUgTWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIHNvbmcgIldpbGwgWW91IEJlIFRoZXJlIiBmZWF0dXJlZD8=",
            "answer": "RnJlZSBXaWxseQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBlcmZvcm1lZCAiSSBUb29rIEEgUGlsbCBJbiBJYml6YSI/",
            "answer": "TWlrZSBQb3NuZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbGVhZCBzaW5nZXIgYW5kIGZyb250bWFuIG9mIHJvY2sgYmFuZCBSLkUuTT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBTdGlwZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgc2luZ2xlIGJ5IFBpbmsgRmxveWQgZ3VpdGFyaXN0LCBEYXZpZCBHaWxtb3VyPw==",
            "answer": "U3Vuc2V0IFN0cmlw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCByZWNvcmRlZCB0aGUgYWxidW0gIlBhcmFsbGVsIExpbmVzIj8=",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFtaW5hIGFuZCBQYXBhZ2VubyBhcmUgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpbiB3aGF0IE1vemFydCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE1hZ2ljIEZsdXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgYWxidW1zIGluY2x1ZGVkICJCYWNrIGluIEJsYWNrIiBhbmQgIkJhbGxicmVha2VyIj8=",
            "answer": "QUMvREM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQWVyb3NtaXRoIGFsYnVtIGZlYXR1cmVkICJXYWxrIFRoaXMgV2F5Ij8=",
            "answer": "VG95cyBpbiB0aGUgQXR0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBHZW5pdXMiIGlzIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBhbmQgc2Vjb25kYXJ5IG5hbWUgb2Ygd2hpY2ggV3UtVGFuZyBDbGFuIG1lbWJlcj8=",
            "answer": "R1pB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQXVndXN0IDE5NjQsIHdobyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIHRoZSBCZWF0bGVzIHRvIGNhbm5hYmlzPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9iIER5bGFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdyYW5kZSBWYWxzZSIgaXMgYSBwaHJhc2UgZnJvbSB0aGUgc29uZyAiR3JhbiBWYWxzIi4gV2hhdCBpcyB0aGF0IHNvbmcgc2VnbWVudCBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "Tm9raWEgVHVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBNODMgd2FzIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gVidzIHJhZGlvPw==",
            "answer": "TWlkbmlnaHQgQ2l0eQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlNvbWUgcGVvcGxlIGNhbGwgbWUgdGhlIHNwYWNlIGNvd2JveSIgaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGxpbmUgZnJvbSB3aGF0IHNvbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEpva2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5NzYgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ1lvdSBNYWtlIE1lIEZlZWwgTGlrZSBEYW5jaW5nJz8=",
            "answer": "TGVvIFNheWVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBQZWFybCBKYW0/",
            "answer": "RWRkaWUgVmVkZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3R1ZGlvIGFsYnVtcyBoYXZlIHRoZSBkdW8gRGFmdCBQdW5rIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgTWFjIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIG5hbWUgRmxlZXR3b29kIE1hYyBjb21lIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBNY1ZpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SXJpc2ggbXVzaWNpYW4gSG96aWVyIHJlbGVhc2VkIGEgbXVzaWMgdHJhY2sgaW4gMjAxMyB0aXRsZWQsICJUYWtlIE1lIHRvIF9fX19fXyI=",
            "answer": "Q2h1cmNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2NvdHRpc2ggcHJvZHVjZXIgQ2FsdmluIEhhcnJpcyBpcyBmcm9tIHRoZSB0b3duIG9mIER1bWZyaWVzLCBTY290bGFuZC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUXVlZW4gc29uZyB3YXMgY292ZXJlZCBieSBCcml0dGFueSBNdXJwaHkgaW4gdGhlIDIwMDYgZmlsbSAiSGFwcHkgRmVldCI/",
            "answer": "U29tZWJvZHkgdG8gTG92ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSBzb25nIGJ5IFRlYXJzIGZvciBGZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "U2hvdXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYW4gb3JjaGVzdHJhLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBsb3dlc3QgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBicmFzcyBmYW1pbHk/",
            "answer": "VHViYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbGJ1bSBkaWQgVGhlIEx1bWluZWVycyByZWxlYXNlIGluIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "Q2xlb3BhdHJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc29uZyBieSBCZXlvbmPDqSBhbmQgQWxlamFuZHJvIEZlcm7DoW5kZXogcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAwNz8=",
            "answer": "QW1vciBHaXRhbm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgTWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uJ3MgYWxidW1zIHNvbGQgdGhlIG1vc3QgY29waWVzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhyaWxsZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFwcGVyIGhhZCBhbiBhbGJ1bSB0aGF0IHdlbnQgZG91YmxlIHBsYXRpbnVtIHdpdGggbm8gZmVhdHVyZXM/",
            "answer": "Si4gQ29sZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgdGhlIE1lZ2FkZXRoIGFsYnVtICJQZWFjZSBTZWxscy4uLiBidXQgV2hvJ3MgQnV5aW5nPyIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk4Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBlcmZvcm1lZCB0aGUgZ3VpdGFyIHNvbG8gb24gTWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uJ3MgaGl0ICJCZWF0IEl0Ij8=",
            "answer": "RWRkaWUgVmFuIEhhbGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGF2ZSBHcm9obCByZWNvcmRlZCB0aGUgRm9vIEZpZ2h0ZXJzJyBkZWJ1dCwgIkZvbyBGaWdodGVycywiIGJ5IGhpbXNlbGYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJCcml0aXNoIEludmFzaW9uIiB3YXMgYSBjdWx0dXJhbCBwaGVub21lbm9uIGluIG11c2ljIHdoZXJlIEJyaXRpc2ggYm95IGJhbmRzIGJlY2FtZSBwb3B1bGFyIGluIHRoZSBVU0EgaW4gd2hhdCBkZWNhZGU/",
            "answer": "NjAncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGRpZCBTaGlybGV5IEJhc3NleSBvcmlnaW5hdGUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "V2FsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgc29uZyBvbiB0aGUgYWxidW0gR3JhZHVhdGlvbiBieSBLYW55ZSBXZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "V2F2ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtdXNpYyBiYW5kcyBpcyBub3QgZnJvbSBGaW5sYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "U2FiYXRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggYXJ0aXN0L2JhbmQgaXMga25vd24gZm9yIHBsYXlpbmcgb24gdGhlIG1pZGkgaW5zdHJ1bWVudCAiTGF1bmNocGFkIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFkZW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBTaW5lYWQgT2BDb25ub3IgaGl0ICdOb3RoaW5nIENvbXBhcmVzIDIgVSc/",
            "answer": "UHJpbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIFVTIGFuZCBVSyBudW1iZXIgMSBoaXQgaW4gMTk2MiB3aXRoIHRoZSBpbnN0cnVtZW50YWwsICdUZWxzdGFyJz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRvcm5hZG9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHJlY29yZGVkIHRoZSAxOTc1IGFsYnVtICdDYXB0YWluIEZhbnRhc3RpYyBhbmQgdGhlIEJyb3duIERpcnQgQ293Ym95Jz8=",
            "answer": "RWx0b24gSm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFwIGdyb3VwIHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSBhbGJ1bSAiU3RyYWlnaHQgT3V0dGEgQ29tcHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "Ti5XLkE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXJjYWRlIEZpcmUncyAnVGhlIFN1YnVyYnMnIHdvbiB0aGUgQWxidW0gb2YgdGhlIFllYXIgYXdhcmQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTEgR3JhbW15cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmFwcGVyIFNub29wIERvZ2cncyByZWFsIG5hbWUgaXMgJ0NvcmRvemFyIENhbHZpbiBCcm9hZHVzLCBKci4nLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiB0aGUgYmFuZCBDb2xkcGxheT8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgTWFydGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5ODEgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgIkphcGFuZXNlIEJveSI/",
            "answer": "QW5la2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzIHdhcyBOT1QgaW5jbHVkZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTYgc29uZyAiRG9uJ3QgTWluZCIgYnkgS2VudCBKb25lcz8=",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSAyMDEyIHNpbmdsZSAiSGFybGVtIFNoYWtlIiwgd2hpY2ggd2FzIHVzZWQgaW4gbnVtZXJvdXMgWW91VHViZSB2aWRlb3MgaW4gMjAxMz8=",
            "answer": "QmFhdWVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIFJhbW1zdGVpbiBzb25ncyBoYXMgdHdvIG9mZmljaWFsIG11c2ljIHZpZGVvcz8=",
            "answer": "RHUgUmllY2hzdCBTbyBHdXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgUmFnZSBBZ2FpbnN0IHRoZSBNYWNoaW5lJ3MgZGVidXQgYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "UmFnZSBBZ2FpbnN0IHRoZSBNYWNoaW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTWVhbiBHaXJscywgd2hvIGhhcyBicmVhc3RzIHRoYXQgdGVsbCB3aGVuIGl0J3MgcmFpbmluZz8=",
            "answer": "S2FyZW4gU21pdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIEVkIFNoZWVyYW4gYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "LQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2NhdG1hbiBKb2huJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIHdhcyBKb2huIFBhdWwgTGFya2luLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mICJUaGUgQmVhdGxlcyIgbmFycmF0ZWQgZXBpc29kZXMgb2YgIlRob21hcyB0aGUgVGFuayBFbmdpbmUiPw==",
            "answer": "UmluZ28gU3RhcnI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm9jayBiYW5kIHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSBhbGJ1bSAiVGhlIEJlbmRzIiBpbiBNYXJjaCAxOTk1Pw==",
            "answer": "UmFkaW9oZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmljayBNYXNvbiBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBtZW1iZXIgdG8gYXBwZWFyIG9uIGV2ZXJ5IFBpbmsgRmxveWQgYWxidW0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdJbiB0aGUgRmxlc2gnIHRvdXIgd2FzIHVzZWQgaW4gc3VwcG9ydCBvZiB3aGF0IFBpbmsgRmxveWQgYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "QW5pbWFscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBzdHVkaW8gYWxidW0gYnkgdGhlIGJhbmQgUGluayBGbG95ZD8=",
            "answer": "TW92aW5nIFBpY3R1cmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbGJ1bSBkaWQgR29yaWxsYXogcmVsZWFzZSBpbiAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "SHVtYW56"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzb25nIG9uIFNjSG9vbGJveSBRJ3MgYWxidW0gQmxhY2sgRmFjZSBMUCBmZWF0dXJlZCBLYW55ZSBXZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "VEhhdCBQYXJ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ2FuYWRpYW4gcmVnZ2FlIG11c2ljaWFuIGhhZCBhIDE5OTMgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ0luZm9ybWVyJz8=",
            "answer": "U25vdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBndWl0YXJpc3QgaGFzIHRoZSBuaWNrbmFtZSAiU2xvd2hhbmQiPw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBDbGFwdG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFydGlzdHMgYXBwZWFycyBpbiB0aGUgYWxidW0gRGVsdHJvbiAzMDMwPw==",
            "answer": "RGFuIHRoZSBBdXRvbWF0ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgc29uZyBvbiBUaGUgQmVhdGxlcycgMTk2OCBzZWxmIHRpdGxlZCBhbGJ1bSwgYWxzbyBrbm93biBhcyB0aGUgV2hpdGUgYWxidW0/",
            "answer": "QmVpbmcgRm9yIFRoZSBCZW5lZml0IE9mIE1yLiBLaXRlIQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNvbmdzIGRpZCB0aGUgZ3JvdXAgIk1lbiBBdCBXb3JrIiBOT1QgbWFrZT8=",
            "answer": "U2FmZXR5IERhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgZnJvbSB0aGUgbXVzaWMgdmlkZW8gb2YgIlNoZWx0ZXIiIGJ5IFBvcnRlciBSb2JpbnNvbiBhbmQgQS0xIFN0dWRpb3M/",
            "answer": "Umlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBSZWQgSG90IENoaWxsIFBlcHBlcidzIGFsYnVtICJDYWxpZm9ybmljYXRpb24iIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBTYXhvcGhvbmUgaXMgYSBicmFzcyBpbnN0cnVtZW50Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgdHJhY2sgb24gS2FueWUgV2VzdCdzIDgwOHMgJiBIZWFydGJyZWFrPw==",
            "answer": "U2F5IFlvdSBXaWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBHcmVlbiBEYXk/",
            "answer": "QmlsbGllIEpvZSBBcm1zdHJvbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgIkNhcmF2YW4gUGFsYWNlIiByZWxlYXNlIHRoZWlyIGZpcnN0IGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB2b2NhbGlzdCBhbmQgZnJvbnRtYW4gb2Ygcm9jayBiYW5kICJHdW5zIE4nIFJvc2VzIj8=",
            "answer": "QXhsIFJvc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmFuZHMgd2FzIGEgZmVhdHVyaW5nIGFydGlzdCBpbiBDb21wdG9uIHJhcHBlciBLZW5kcmljayBMYW1hcidzIDIwMTcgYWxidW0sICJEQU1OLiI/",
            "answer": "VTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgZGlkIEppbWkgSGVuZHJpeCBjb3Zlcj8=",
            "answer": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNvbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JvdXAgcGVyZm9ybXMgdGhlIHNvbmcgIkNyYXNoIGludG8gTWUiPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBNYXR0aGV3cyBCYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCAxOTcwJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gYmFsbGFkIHJlZmVycmVkIHRvIHRoZSAxOTU5IHBsYW5lIGNyYXNoIGFzIHRoZSAidGhlIGRheSB0aGUgbXVzaWMgZGllZCI/",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gUGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzb25nIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgcGVyZm9ybWVkIGJ5IFRoZSBCZWUgR2VlcyBpbiAxOTc4IGhhZCBhIGNvdmVyIHZlcnNpb24gYnkgU3RlcHMgMjAgeWVhcnMgbGF0ZXI/",
            "answer": "VHJhZ2VkeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgQm9uIEl2ZXIncyBkZWJ1dCBhbGJ1bSByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDA3Pw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yIEVtbWEsIEZvcmV2ZXIgQWdv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkhhbGxlbHVqYWgiIGlzIGEgc29uZyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIENhbmFkaWFuIHJlY29yZGluZyBhcnRpc3Q/",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZCBDb2hlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2VucmUgb2YgSGlwIEhvcCBkb2VzIE1DIEZyb250YWxvdCByYXA/",
            "answer": "TmVyZGNvcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBEaXJlIFN0cmFpdHMncyBTb25nICJNb25leSBmb3IgTm90aGluZyIgcmVsZWFzZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk4NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgdGhlIGFsYnVtICJZZWFyIG9mIHRoZSBTbml0Y2giIGJ5IERlYXRoIEdyaXBzIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICBSb3NzaW5pIG9wZXJhLCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiAnVGhlIEJhcmJlciBvZiBTZXZpbGxlJz8=",
            "answer": "RmlnYXJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmluZ28gU3RhcnIgb2YgVGhlIEJlYXRsZXMgbWFpbmx5IHBsYXllZCB3aGF0IGluc3RydW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "RHJ1bXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljIHZpZGVvIHRvIFRoZSBCdWdnbGUncyAiVmlkZW8gS2lsbGVkIHRoZSBSYWRpbyBTdGFyIiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG11c2ljIHZpZGVvIHRvIGJyb2FkY2FzdCBvbiBNVFYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2luZ2VyIHdhcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBTd2VkaXNoIHByb2R1Y2VyIEF2aWNpaSdzIHNvbmcgIldha2UgTWUgVXAiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxvZSBCbGFjYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgc29uZyBmZWF0dXJlZCBvbiB0aGUgTG9ja2phdyBFUCByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDEzIGJ5IEZsdW1lICYgQ2hldCBGYWtlcj8=",
            "answer": "TGVmdCBBbG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgbmFtZSBvZiBFbmdsaXNoIGZlbWFsZSByYXBwZXIgTWF0aGFuZ2kgQXJ1bHByYWdhc2FtLCB3aG8gaXMga25vd24gZm9yIHRoZSBzb25nICJQYXBlciBQbGFuZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TS5JLkEu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSByZWFsIHNvbmcgZnJvbSB0aGUgYmFuZCBUaG91c2FuZCBGb290IEtydXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "TGltaXRsZXNzIEZ1cnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmFuZHMgYXJlIE5PVCBmcm9tIEF1c3RyYWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5ha2VkIGFuZCBGYW1vdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U3RpbmcsIHRoZSBsZWFkIHZvY2FsaXN0IG9mIFRoZSBQb2xpY2UsIHByaW1hcmlseSBwbGF5cyB3aGF0IGluc3RydW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "QmFzcyBHdWl0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlR3ZW50eSBPbmUgUGlsb3RzIiBtYWRlIHRoZSBzb25nICJUaGUgTW90aW9uIiBmZWF0dXJpbmcgU2FtcGhhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkRyaW5rIHRoZSBTZWEiIGlzIGFuIGFsYnVtIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGVsZWN0cm9uaWMgbXVzaWMgYXJ0aXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdsaXRjaCBNb2I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbGJ1bSBkaWQgQm9uIEl2ZXIgcmVsZWFzZSBpbiAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "MjIsIEEgTWlsbGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgR2FuZ25hbSBTdHlsZSB1cGxvYWRlZCB0byBZb3VUdWJlPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TW9ieSwgYW4gQW1lcmljYW4gREosIHNpbmdlciwgYW5kIG11c2ljaWFuLCBhY2hpZXZlZCB3b3JsZHdpZGUgc3VjY2VzcyBmb3IgdGhlIDE5OTkgcmVsZWFzZSBvZiB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIGFsYnVtcz8=",
            "answer": "UGxheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSXJvbiBNYWlkZW4gYWxidW0gZGlkIHRoZSBzb25nICJEcmVhbSBvZiBNaXJyb3JzIiBmZWF0dXJlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "QnJhdmUgTmV3IFdvcmxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5IGRvZXMgdGhlIHBpYW5vIG9yaWdpbmF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTEgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbiIgd2FzIGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IFN0ZXZlbiBTcGllbGJlcmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkYXRlIGlzIHJlZmVyZW5jZWQgaW4gdGhlIDE5NzEgc29uZyAiU2VwdGVtYmVyIiBieSBFYXJ0aCwgV2luZCAmIEZpcmU/",
            "answer": "MjFzdCBvZiBTZXB0ZW1iZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBtYWRlIGJ5IE1BTiBXSVRIIEEgTUlTU0lPTiB3YXMgdXNlZCBhcyB0aGUgb3BlbmluZyBmb3IgdGhlIGFuaW1lICJMb2cgSG9yaXpvbiI/",
            "answer": "IkRhdGFiYXNlIg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBXdS1UYW5nIENsYW4gaGFkIG9ubHkgb25lIHZlcnNlIGluIHRoZWlyIGRlYnV0IGFsYnVtIEVudGVyIHRoZSBXdS1UYW5nICgzNiBDaGFtYmVycyk/",
            "answer": "TWFzdGEgS2lsbGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCBoYWQgaGl0cyBpbiAxOTc1IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmdzLCAnT25lIE9mIFRoZXNlIE5pZ2h0cycgJiAnTHlpbiBFeWVzJz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVhZ2xlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGFuIGFsYnVtIHJlbGVhc2VkIGJ5IFRoZSBCZWF0bGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXNobGV5IEZyYW5naXBhbmUgcGVyZm9ybXMgdW5kZXIgdGhlIHN0YWdlIG5hbWUgSGFsc2V5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyBieSBTd2VkaXNoIGVsZWN0cm9uaWMgbXVzaWNpYW4gQXZpY2lpIHNhbXBsZXMgdGhlIHNvbmcgIlNvbWV0aGluZydzIEdvdCBBIEhvbGQgT24gTWUiIGJ5IEV0dGEgSmFtZXM/",
            "answer": "TGV2ZWxz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRGVhdGggR3JpcHMgYWxidW0gaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgb25lIHRvIGZlYXR1cmUgYSBiYW5kIG1lbWJlcj8=",
            "answer": "Tm8gTG92ZSBEZWVwIFdlYg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmlydmFuYSBhbGJ1bSBoYWQgYSBuYWtlZCBiYWJ5IG9uIHRoZSBjb3Zlcj8=",
            "answer": "TmV2ZXJtaW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmFuZHMgaXMgdGhlIG9sZGVzdD8=",
            "answer": "UGluayBGbG95ZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBhbmljISBBdCB0aGUgRGlzY28ncyBzb25nICJOb3RoZXJuIERvd25wb3VyIiwgd2hpY2ggbHlyaWMgZm9sbG93cyAnSSBrbm93IHRoZSB3b3JsZCdzIGEgYnJva2VuIGJvbmUnLg==",
            "answer": "IlNvIG1lbHQgeW91ciBoZWFkYWNoZXMgY2FsbCBpdCBob21lIg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3RldmllIFdvbmRlcidzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBpcyBTdGV2bGFuZCBIYXJkYXdheSBNb3JyaXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIGJveS1iYW5kIHN0YXIgcmVsZWFzZWQgaGl0IHNvbG8gc2luZ2xlICJBbmdlbHMiIGluIDE5OTc/",
            "answer": "Um9iYmllIFdpbGxpYW1z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzb25ncyBkaWQgRWx0b24gSm9obiBwZXJmb3JtIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQcmluY2VzcyBEaWFuZSdzIHBhc3Npbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2FuZGxlcyBpbiB0aGUgV2luZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIHdyb3RlIFRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyBzb25nICJEbyB0aGUgQmFydG1hbiIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWx0ZXJuYXRpdmUgcm9jayBiYW5kIHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSBjcml0aWNhbGx5LWFjY2xhaW1lZCBhbGJ1bSAiT0sgQ29tcHV0ZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "UmFkaW9oZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHNpbmdzIHRoZSByYXAgc29uZyAiU2VjcmV0IFdhcnMgUGFydCAxIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExhc3QgRW1wZXJvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZ3VpdGFyaXN0IGluIHRoZSBiYW5kICJUaGUgRG9vcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "Um9iYnkgS3JpZWdlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZWlyIDE5NzQgaGl0LCB3aGF0IHdlcmUgQnJvd25zdmlsbGUgU3RhdGlvbiBkb2luZyAiSW4gVGhlIEJveXMnIFJvb20iPw==",
            "answer": "U21va2luJw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDE5NTIgbXVzaWNhbCBjb21wb3NpdGlvbiA0JzMzIiwgY29tcG9zZWQgYnkgcHJvbGlmaWMgQW1lcmljYW4gY29tcG9zZXIgSm9obiBDYWdlLCBpcyBtYWlubHkgY29tcHJpc2VkIG9mIHdoYXQgc291bmQ/",
            "answer": "U2lsZW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIFBpbmsgRmxveWQgYWxidW1zIHdlcmUgYWxzbyBhIG1vdmllPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgYnkgYXJ0aXN0IEVtaW5lbSBjb250YWluIHRoZSBseXJpYyAiTmljZSB0byBtZWV0IHlvdS4gSGksIG15IG5hbWUgaXMuLi4gSSBmb3Jnb3QgbXkgbmFtZSEiPw==",
            "answer": "UmFpbiBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkb2VzIHRoZSBwb3dlciBtZXRhbCBiYW5kICJTYWJhdG9uIiBvcmlnaW5hdGUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "U3dlZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIk15c3RlcnkgVHJhaW4iIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBieSBhcnRpc3QgIkxpdHRsZSBKdW5pb3IncyBCbHVlIEZsYW1lcyIgaW4gMTk1My4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtdXNpY2lhbiBtYWRlIHRoZSBzb25nICJGdWNraW5gIFBlcmZlY3QiIGluIDIwMTA/",
            "answer": "UCFuaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "MyBtZW1iZXJzIG9mIDIgTGl2ZSBDcmV3IHdlcmUgYXJyZXN0ZWQgZm9yIHBsYXlpbmcgc29uZ3MgZnJvbSB0aGVpciBhbGJ1bSwgQXMgTmFzdHkgQXMgVGhleSBXYW5uYSBCZSwgbGl2ZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGJlc3Qgc2VsbGluZyBhbGJ1bSBvZiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "QWRlbGUsIDI1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGhlYXZ5IG1ldGFsIGJhbmQgQmxhY2sgU2FiYmF0aCBoYWlsIGZyb20gd2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "QmlybWluZ2hhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGV0ZSBUb3duc2hlbmQgY29sbGFib3JhdGVkIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIGd1aXRhcmlzdCBmb3IgYW4gZXZlbnQgYXQgQnJpeHRvbiBBY2FkZW15IGluIDE5ODU/",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgR2lsbW91cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZGlkIHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIEJveSBCYW5kICJCcm9zIiBjb21lIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Q2FtYmVybGV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBvZiBQcmluY2UncyBiYWNraW5nIGJhbmQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJldm9sdXRpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIHBvcCBncm91cCAiVGhlIFNwaWNlIEdpcmxzIiB3YXMga25vd24gYXMgR2luZ2VyIFNwaWNlPw==",
            "answer": "R2VyaSBIYWxsaXdlbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBMZWQgWmVwcGVsaW4gYWxidW0gY29udGFpbnMgIlN0YWlyd2F5IHRvIEhlYXZlbiI/",
            "answer": "TGVkIFplcHBlbGluIElW"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RXVyb2JlYXQgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGFuIEl0YWxpYW4gZ2VucmUgb2YgbXVzaWMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGFuIGFsYnVtIHJlbGVhc2VkIGJ5IEFtZXJpY2FuIHJhcHBlciBWaXBlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExpZmUgb2YgUGFibG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgMjAxNiBtaXh0YXBlIHJlbGVhc2VkIGJ5IFZlbmV6dWVsYW4gZWxlY3Ryb25pYyBwcm9kdWNlciBBcmNhPw==",
            "answer": "RW50cmHDsWFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYW4gQW1lcmljYW4gcHN5Y2hlZGVsaWMgcm9jayBiYW5kIGZvcm1lZCBpbiAyMDAyIGJ5IEJlbmphbWluIEdvbGR3YXNzZXIgYW5kIEFuZHJldyBWYW5XeW5nYXJkZW4/",
            "answer": "TUdNVA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIDNyZCBhbGJ1bSAiTm90ZXMgZnJvbSB0aGUgVW5kZXJncm91bmQiIG9mIHRoZSBiYW5kICJIb2xseXdvb2QgVW5kZWFkIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2hpbm8gTW9yZW5vIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiB3aGljaCBhbHRlcm5hdGl2ZSBtZXRhbCBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "RGVmdG9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJ0aXN0cyBkaWQgTk9UIGZlYXR1cmUgaW4gdGhlIGZpdGZoIHN0dWRpbyBhbGJ1bSAiSHVtYW56IiBieSBCcml0aXNoIHZpcnR1YWwgYmFuZCBHb3JpbGxhej8=",
            "answer": "U25vb3AgRG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIGFuZCBsZWFkZXIgb2YgaW5kdXN0cmlhbCByb2NrIGJhbmQsICdOaW5lIEluY2ggTmFpbHMnPw==",
            "answer": "VHJlbnQgUmV6bm9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkb2VzIHRoZSBiYW5kIFJhbW1zdGVpbiBoYWlsIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHJlY29yZGVkIHRoZSBhbGJ1bSBjYWxsZWQgIkRvd24gdG8gdGhlIE1vb24iIGluIDE5ODY/",
            "answer": "QW5kcmVhcyBWb2xsZW53ZWlkZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBndWl0YXJpc3RzIHJlY29yZGVkIGFuIGFsYnVtIGFzIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBSZWQgSG90IENoaWxpIFBlcHBlcnM/",
            "answer": "RGF2ZSBOYXZhcnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiB0aGUgU21hc2hpbmcgUHVtcGtpbnM/",
            "answer": "QmlsbHkgQ29yZ2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyAiS3VuZyBGdSBGaWdodGluZyIgaW4gMTk3ND8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybCBEb3VnbGFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U291bGphIEJveSdzICdDcmFuayBUaGF0JyB3b24gYSBHcmFtbXkgZm9yIEJlc3QgUmFwIFNvbmcgaW4gMjAwNy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBQaW5rIEZsb3lkIHNvbmcgIlNoaW5lIE9uIFlvdSBDcmF6eSBEaWFtb25kIiB3cml0dGVuIGFib3V0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lkIEJhcnJldHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIGEgQmVhdGxlcyBzb25nLCB3aG8ga2VwdCBoZXIgZmFjZSBpbiBhIGphciBieSB0aGUgZG9vcj8=",
            "answer": "RWxlYW5vciBSaWdieQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGNvbXBvc2l0aW9uLCAiUmhhcHNvZHkgSW4gQmx1ZSI/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEdlcnNod2lu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2l0eSBkaWQgQW1lcmljYW4gcmFwIHByb2R1Y2VyIERKIEtoYWxlZCBvcmlnaW5hdGUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "TWlhbWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMTk4OSBEcnVtIENvcnBzIEludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgY2hhbXBpb25zaGlwcz8=",
            "answer": "U2FudGEgQ2xhcmEgVmFuZ3VhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBNaW4gWW9vbmdpIGZyb20gU291dGggS29yZWEgYm95IGJhbmQgIkJUUyIgYm9ybiBpbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk5Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGljaCBhbGJ1bSBpcyB0aGUgR29yaWxsYXogc29uZywgIk9uIE1lbGFuY2hvbHkgSGlsbCIgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "UGxhc3RpYyBCZWFjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggQmVhdGxlcyBhbGJ1bSB3b3VsZCB5b3UgZmluZCB0aGUgc29uZyAnRWxlYW5vciBSaWdieSc/",
            "answer": "UmV2b2x2ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgaXMgTk9UIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSBTdWljaWRlIFNxdWFkIE9TVD8=",
            "answer": "U2tpZXMgb24gRmlyZSAtIEFDL0RD"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RURNIGxhYmVsIE1vbnN0ZXJjYXQgc2lnbnMgdHJhY2tzIGluc3RlYWQgb2YgYXJ0aXN0cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdobydzIGVwb255bW91cyBsaW5lLCAiVGVlbmFnZSBXYXN0ZWxhbmQiLCBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZWlyIHNvbmdzPw==",
            "answer": "QmFiYSBPJyBSaWxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRXVyb3BlYW4gY2FwaXRhbCBjaXR5IGdpdmVzIGl0cyBuYW1lIHRvIGEgMTk4MSBzb25nIGJ5IFVsdHJhdm94Pw==",
            "answer": "Vmllbm5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNvbmcg4oCcVGhlIFVsdGltYXRlIFNob3dkb3duIG9mIFVsdGltYXRlIERlc3Rpbnks4oCdIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBvbmUgdG8gc3Vydml2ZSB0aGUgYmF0dGxlPw==",
            "answer": "TXIuIFJvZ2Vycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBub3QgaW4gdGhlIGJhbmQgIlRoZSBTbWl0aHMiPw==",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIENoYW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnJhc3MgaW5zdHJ1bWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGxvd2VzdCBwaXRjaCBpbiBhbiBvcmNoZXN0cmE/",
            "answer": "VHViYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVsYXRpb25zaGlwIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIGJhbmQgbWVtYmVycyBvZiBBbWVyaWNhbiByb2NrIGJhbmQgS2luZyBvZiBMZW9uPw==",
            "answer": "QnJvdGhlcnMgJiBjb3VzaW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlRoZSBEaXZpc2lvbiBCZWxsIiBpcyB0aGUgZmluYWwgYWxidW0gb2YgdGhlIHByb2dyZXNzaXZlIHJvY2sgYmFuZCBQaW5rIEZsb3lkLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIlN0cm9uZ2VyIFRoYW4gWW91IiBpcyBhIHNpbmdsZSBieSBFc3RlbGxlLCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEdhcm5ldCBpbiBTdGV2ZW4gVW5pdmVyc2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgc29uZyAiU3RhcmJveSIgYnkgQ2FuYWRpYW4gc2luZ2VyIFRoZSBXZWVrbmQgZmVhdHVyZXMgd2hpY2ggcHJvbWluZW50IGVsZWN0cm9uaWMgYXJ0aXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGFmdCBQdW5r"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBUY2hhaWtvdnNreSdzIDE4MTIgT3ZlcnR1cmUgY29tcG9zZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTg4MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFuaWMhIEF0IHRoZSBEaXNjbydzIHNpeHRoIGFsYnVtICJQcmF5IEZvciBUaGUgV2lja2VkIiB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgb24gd2hpY2ggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "SnVuZSAyMiwgMjAxOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIkZlZWwgR29vZCBJbmMuIiBieSBCcml0aXNoIGJhbmQgR29yaWxsYXogZmVhdHVyZXMgd2hpY2ggaGlwIGhvcCBncm91cD8=",
            "answer": "RGUgTGEgU291bA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBzb25nIG9uIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBQYW5pYyEgQXQgdGhlIERpc2NvIGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "QnVpbGQgR29kLCBUaGVuIFdlJ2xsIFRhbGs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgRGFmdCBQdW5rJ3MgZmlyc3Qgc3R1ZGlvIGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "SG9tZXdvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWF5IDE2dGggb2YgZXZlcnkgeWVhciBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBfX19fX19fX19fIERheSwgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBwdW5rIGJhbmQgcHJvbWluZW50IGluIHRoZSAxOTkwcy4=",
            "answer": "TGFnd2Fnb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBiYW5kcyBpcyBUb20gRGVMb25nZSBub3QgYSBwYXJ0IG9mPw==",
            "answer": "KzQ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIHJhcHBlciBFYXp5LUUgZGllPw==",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggMjYsIDE5OTU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBBcmN0aWMgTW9ua2V5cz8=",
            "answer": "QWxleCBUdXJuZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5NzMgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ0hvY3VzIFBvY3VzJz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9jdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiByYXBwZXIgTmVsbHksIHdoYXQgc2hvdWxkIHlvdSBkbyB3aGVuIGl0cyBob3QgaW4gaGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFrZSBvZmYgYWxsIHlvdXIgY2xvdGhlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHJhcHBlcnMgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSByYXAgZ3JvdXAgV3UtVGFuZyBDbGFuPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuRHJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgcGlvbmVlciBvZiAiTWluaW1hbCBNdXNpYyIgaW4gMTk2MHM/",
            "answer": "U3RldmUgUmVpY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IGN1cmF0ZWQgdGhlIG9mZmljaWFsIHNvdW5kdHJhY2sgZm9yICJUaGUgSHVuZ2VyIEdhbWVzOiBNb2NraW5namF5IC0gUGFydCAxIj8=",
            "answer": "TG9yZGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RURNIHJlY29yZCBsYWJlbCBNb25zdGVyY2F0IGlzIGJhc2VkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RyaW5ncyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgb24gYSBjZWxsbz8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYWxidW1zIGlzIGEgV3UtVGFuZyBDbGFuIGFsYnVtPw==",
            "answer": "SXJvbiBGbGFn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggODBzIGJhbmQgaXMgZnJvbnRlZCBieSBzaW5nZXIvZ3VpdGFyaXN0IFJvYmVydCBTbWl0aD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEN1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBwb3Agcm9jayBiYW5kIENvbGRwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgTWFydGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU3R1ZGlvIEFsYnVtIHRvIGJlIHJlbGVhc2VkIG9uIHRoZSBJbnRlcm5ldCB3aXRoIGEgIlBheS1XaGF0LVlvdS1XYW50IiBwcmljZT8=",
            "answer": "SW4gUmFpbmJvd3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Ik1ha2UgWW91IEZlZWwgTXkgTG92ZSIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgd3JpdHRlbiBhbmQgcGVyZm9ybWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIHNpbmdlci1zb25nd3JpdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9iIER5bGFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbmFtZSBvZiBhbiBhbGJ1bSByZWxlYXNlZCBieSBBbWVyaWNhbiByYXBwZXIgUGl0YnVsbD8=",
            "answer": "V2VsY29tZSB0byBNaWFtaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGFmdCBQdW5rIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgaW4gRnJhbmNlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29waWVzIGhhdmUgTWV0YWxsaWNhIGFsYnVtICJNZXRhbGxpY2EiIChBLksuQSBUaGUgQmxhY2sgQWxidW0pIHNvbGQgd29ybGR3aWRlIChpbiBNaWxsaW9ucyBvZiBDb3BpZXMpPw==",
            "answer": "MjAuNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgc29uZyAiV29yZHMiIGJ5IEZlaW50PyA=",
            "answer": "TGF1cmEgQnJlaG0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgaXMgbm90IGJ5IFRhdHN1cm8gWWFtYXNoaXRhPw==",
            "answer": "THVja3kgTGFkeSBGZWVsIFNvIEdvb2Qg"
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWNhbHMgJiBUaGVhdHJlcw==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHBsYXkgIk1hY2JldGgiIHdyaXR0ZW4/",
            "answer": "MTYwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBpbnNwaXJlZCB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCAnV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Jz8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZW8gJiBKdWxpZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBkb2VzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgTWFyY2VsbHVzIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aGluZyBpcyByb3R0ZW4gaW4gdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIERlbm1hcmsiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBsYXkgT2VkaXB1cyBSZXgsIE9lZGlwdXMga2lsbHMgaGlzIGZhdGhlciBkdWUgdG8gamVhbG91c3kgaW4gbG92aW5nIGhpcyBtb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
            "answer": "UmVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5IHdpbGwgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlIHN1aWNpZGUgb2YgT3BoZWxpYT8=",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=",
            "answer": "TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIGRpcmVjdG9yIGZvciB0aGUgYXdhcmQgd2lubmluZyBtdXNpY2FsICJIYW1pbHRvbiI/",
            "answer": "QWxleCBMYWNhbW9pcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBCcm9hZHdheSdzIGZpcnN0ICJsb25nLXJ1biIgbXVzaWNhbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VvcmdlIEJpemV0J3MgbGFzdCBvcGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBwbGF5IEp1bGl1cyBDYWVzYXIsIENhZXNhcidzIGxhc3Qgd29yZHMgd2VyZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "RXQgdHUsIEJydXRlPyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTGVzIE1pc8OpcmFibGVzLCB3aG8gaXMgUHJpc29uIENvZGUgMjQ2MDE/",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBWYWxqZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSmVmZiBXYXluZSdzIE11c2ljYWwgVmVyc2lvbiBvZiBXYXIgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkcywgdGhlIGNoYW5jZXMgb2YgYW55dGhpbmcgY29taW5nIGZyb20gTWFycyBhcmUuLi4=",
            "answer": "QSBtaWxsaW9uIHRvIG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwbGF5IGlzIHRoZSBxdW90ZSAiSGVsbCBpcyBvdGhlciBwZW9wbGUiIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Tm8gRXhpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgZm9yIExlb25hcmQgQmVybnN0ZWluJ3MgMTk1NyBCcm9kd2F5IG11c2ljYWwgV2VzdCBTaWRlIFN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "U3RlcGhlbiBTb25kaGVpbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheXMgaXMgU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgZ2VuZXJhbGx5IGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gaGF2ZSB3cml0dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFjYmV0aCwgdGhlIGV5ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltYWxzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgV2l0Y2hlcycgY2F1bGRyb24/",
            "answer": "TmV3dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwaWVjZSBmcm9tIHRoZSAxOTUwJ3MgbXVzaWNhbCBXZXN0IFNpZGUgU3Rvcnk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhY2sgQWxsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRvY3RvciBXaG8iIHN0YXIgRGF2aWQgVGVubmFudCBwZXJmb3JtZWQgaW4gYSByZW5kaXRpb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmVhbiBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbGV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHNlcnZlcyBhcyB0aGUgc3BlYWtlciBvZiB0aGUgcHJvbG9ndWUgaW4gU2hha2VzcGVhcmUncyBSb21lbyBhbmQgSnVsaWV0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hvcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgRW5nbGFuZCwgbW9yZSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSBwbGF5cyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoaXMgcHJlc2VudCBkYXkgY291bnRyeSB0aGFuIGluIGFueSBvdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCAiQ2hhcmxpZSBQcmljZSIgaW4gdGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIktpbmt5IEJvb3RzIiBvbiBCcm9hZHdheSBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBmcm9tIE1heSAyNnRoIC0gQXVnIDZ0aCAyMDE3Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJlbmRvbiBVcmll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG11c2ljYWwgIkRpcnR5IFJvdHRlbiBTY291bmRyZWxzIiBpcyBzZXQgaW4gd2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2hha2VzcGVhcmUgcGxheSBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgc3RhZ2UgZGlyZWN0aW9uICJFbnRlciBhIG1lc3Nlbmdlciwgd2l0aCB0d28gaGVhZHMgYW5kIGEgaGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "VGl0dXMgQW5kcm9uaWN1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIENoZXNzIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCBpbiBDaGVzcywgQWN0IDEgaXMgc2V0IGluIHdoaWNoIEl0YWxpYW4gY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TWVyYW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGxheXMgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5IGZpcnN0IHBlcmZvcm1lZCBwb3N0aHVtb3VzbHkgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlIHBsYXl3cmlnaHQgY29tbWl0dGVkIHN1aWNpZGU/",
            "answer": "NC40OCBQc3ljaG9zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBNYXJxdWlzIGRlIExhZmF5ZXR0ZSBhbmQgVGhvbWFzIEplZmZlcnNvbiBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQnJvYWR3YXkgcnVuIG9mIEhhbWlsdG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RGF2ZWVkIERpZ2dz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZHJldyBMbG95ZCBXZWJiZXIgbXVzaWNhbCAiQ2F0cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIGEgYm9vayBvZiBwb2VtcyB3cml0dGVuIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGF1dGhvcj8=",
            "answer": "VC5TLiBFbGxpb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBKZWFuIFZhbEplYW4ncyBmaXJzdCBwcmlzb25lciBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjQ2MDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBwbGF5ICdBbmdlbHMgaW4gQW1lcmljYSc/",
            "answer": "VG9ueSBLdXNoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZXMgaW4gJ1dobydzIEFmcmFpZCBvZiBWaXJnaW5pYSBXb29sZicsIEdlb3JnZSBhbmQgTWFydGhhLCB3ZXJlIGRlcml2ZWQgZnJvbSBHZW9yZ2UgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiBhbmQgaGlzIHdpZmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGF0IHNob3cgaXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciAiSmFtZXMgRG9ha2VzIj8g",
            "answer": "RGV4dGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNlcmllcyAiUGVyc29uIG9mIEludGVyZXN0Iiwgd2hvIHBsYXlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgIkhhcm9sZCBGaW5jaCI/",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBFbWVyc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHBvbGljZSBvZmZpY2VyIGluIHRoZSBjYXJ0b29uICJUb3AgQ2F0Ij8=",
            "answer": "RGliYmxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdHJhY2sgYnkgIk1hc3NpdmUgQXR0YWNrIiBpcyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgdGhlbWUgb2YgIkhvdXNlIj8g",
            "answer": "VGVhcmRyb3A="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgJ00qQSpTKkgnLCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgb2YgQ29ycG9yYWwgV2FsdGVyIE8nUmVpbGx5Pw==",
            "answer": "UmFkYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIERvY3RvciBXaG8gc2VyaWVzICgxOTYzKSwgZm91cnRoIGRvY3RvciBUb20gQmFrZXIncyBzY2FyZiB3YXMgaG93IGxvbmc/",
            "answer": "NyBNZXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFN0YXIgVHJlayBUViBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIENhcHRhaW4gSmFtZXMgVC4gS2lyaydzIG1pZGRsZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGliZXJpdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIERyLiBEb29mZW5zaG1pcnR6IGZpcnN0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SGVpbno="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgU3RyYW5nZXIgVGhpbmdzLCB3aGF0IGlzIEVsZXZlbidzIGZhdm9yaXRlIGJyZWFrZmFzdCBmb29kPw==",
            "answer": "RWdnbyBXYWZmbGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkl0J3MgQWx3YXlzIFN1bm55IGluIFBoaWxhZGVscGhpYSIgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgRnJhbmsncyB3cmVzdGxpbmcgcGVyc29uYT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRyYXNoIE1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQc3ljaG8iIHNlcmllcyBvZiB2aWRlb3Mgb24gWW91VHViZSB3YXMgY3JlYXRlZCBieSB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "UmlER2lEIFNUVURpT1M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgc2hvdyAiQnVybiBOb3RpY2UiPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBXZXN0ZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNvLWZvdW5kZWQgdGhlIFlvdVR1YmUgTGV0J3MgUGxheSBjaGFubmVsICJHYW1lIEdydW1wcyIgYWxvbmdzaWRlIE5ld2dyb3VuZHMgYW5pbWF0b3IgRWdvcmFwdG9yPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9uVHJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBoYXMgZXhjbHVzaXZlIHJpZ2h0cyB0byBhaXIgZXBpc29kZXMgb2YgdGhlICJUaGUgR3JhbmQgVG91ciI/",
            "answer": "QW1hem9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFN0YXIgVHJlayB1bml2ZXJzZSwgd2hhdCBjb2xvciBpcyBWdWxjYW4gYmxvb2Q/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmFydXRvOiBTaGlwcHVkZW4sIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgZWxlbWVudHMgaXMgYSAiS2Vra2VpIFTFjXRhPyI=",
            "answer": "UGFydGljbGUgU3R5bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgUmljayBhbmQgTW9ydHkgZmlyc3QgYWlyIG9uIEFkdWx0IFN3aW0/",
            "answer": "MjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRHVja1RhbGVzLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaXR5IHdoZXJlIGFsbCB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGxpdmU/",
            "answer": "RHVja2J1cmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5ldGZsaXggc2hvdywgU3RyYW5nZXIgVGhpbmdzLCB3aGF0IHNvbmcgd291bGQgV2lsbCBzaW5nIHRvIGhpbXNlbGYgYXMgaGUgd2FzIG1pc3Npbmc/",
            "answer": "U2hvdWxkIEkgU3RheSBvciBTaG91bGQgSSBHbz8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkb2VzIHRoZSBZb3VUdWJlciAiU2lub3dCZWF0cyIgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "U2NvdGxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIlRlbmdlbiBUb3BwYSBHdXJyZW4gTGFnYW5uIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgd2hvIGZvcmNlIGV2ZXJ5b25lIHRvIGxpdmUgdW5kZXJncm91bmQ/",
            "answer": "TG9yZGdlbm9tZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3VybmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIERhcnlsIGluIEFNQydzIHNob3cgVGhlIFdhbGtpbmcgRGVhZD8=",
            "answer": "RGl4b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2hvdyBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgdGhlIHNvbmdzICJZb3UgYXJlIGEgUGlyYXRlIiwgIkNvb2tpbmcgYnkgdGhlIEJvb2siIGFuZCAiV2UgQXJlIE51bWJlciBPbmUiPw==",
            "answer": "TGF6eVRvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3RhciBUcmVrLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIFNwb2NrJ3MgZmF0aGVyPw==",
            "answer": "U2FyZWs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmF0dGxlc3RhciBHYWxhY3RpY2EgKDIwMDQpLCBDeWxvbnMgd2VyZSBjcmVhdGVkIGJ5IG1hbiBhcyBjeWJlcm5ldGljIHdvcmtlcnMgYW5kIHNvbGRpZXJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2hvdyAiTGF6eSBUb3duIiwgd2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhY3RvciBvZiBSb2JiaWUgUm90dGVuPw==",
            "answer": "U3RlZsOhbiBTdGVmw6Fuc3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgZm9sbG93aW5nIGlzIHJ1ZGUgYW5kIGRpc2hvbm9yYWJsZSBieSBLbGluZ29uIHN0YW5kYXJkcz8=",
            "answer": "VGFraW5nIGhpcyBEJ2sgdGFoZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIEtsaW5nb25zIHJlc3BlY3QgV2lsbGlhbSBTaGFrZXNwZWFyZSwgdGhleSBldmVuIHN1c3BlY3QgaGltIGhhdmluZyBhIEtsaW5nb24gbGluZWFnZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2Vhc29ucyBkaWQgdGhlIFNjaS1GaSB0ZWxldmlzaW9uIHNob3cgIlN0YXJnYXRlIFVuaXZlcnNlIiBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAwOCwgQnJpdGlzaCBjZWxlYnJpdHkgY2hlZiBHb3Jkb24gUmFtc2F5IGJlbGlldmVzIGhlIGFsbW9zdCBkaWVkIGFmdGVyIHN1ZmZlcmluZyB3aGF0IGFjY2lkZW50IGluIEljZWxhbmQgd2hpbGUgZmlsbWluZz8=",
            "answer": "U2xpcHBpbmcgb2ZmIGEgY2xpZmYsIGFuZCBuZWFybHkgZHJvd25pbmcgaW4gaWN5IHdhdGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlcGlzb2RlIG9mICJNci4gQmVhbiIgc2F3IGhpbSB0cnlpbmcgdG8gcHJldmVudCBwZW9wbGUgZnJvbSBzZWVpbmcgaGltIG5ha2VkPw==",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJlYW4gaW4gUm9vbSA0MjY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxhbiBSZWVkIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwcm92aWRpbmcgdGhlIHZvaWNlIG9mIHdoaWNoIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "RnJlZCBGbGludHN0b25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQmF0dGxlc3RhciBHYWxhY3RpY2EgKDIwMDQpLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFR3ZWx2ZSBDb2xvbmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TGF1cmEgUm9zbGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhbGxzaWduIG9mIENvbW1hbmRlciBXaWxsaWFtIEFkYW1hIGluIEJhdHRsZXN0YXIgR2FsYWN0aWNhICgyMDA0KT8=",
            "answer": "SHVza2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBOQkMgc2l0Y29tIG9uY2Ugc2F3IHR3byBvZiBpdHMgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB0cnkgdG8gcGl0Y2ggTkJDIG9uIGEgc2l0Y29tIGFib3V0IG5vdGhpbmc/",
            "answer": "U2VpbmZlbGQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggV1dGIHdyZXN0bGVyIGhhZCB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgIlRoZSBBeWF0b2xsYWggb2YgUm9jayAnTicgUm9sbGEiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgSmVyaWNobw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBDaHJpcydzIGJyb3RoZXIgaW4gIkV2ZXJ5Ym9keSBIYXRlcyBDaHJpcyI/",
            "answer": "RHJldw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIE5CQyBzaG93IENvbW11bml0eSwgd2hvc2UgY2F0Y2gtcGhyYXNlIHdhcyAiUG9wISBQb3AhIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFnbml0dWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIE5CQyBzaG93IENvbW11bml0eSB3aGF0IHdhcyBTdGFyIEJ1cm5zJyByZWFsIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "QWxleA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgd2lubmVyIG9mICJCaWcgQnJvdGhlciIgU2Vhc29uIDEwPw==",
            "answer": "RGFuIEdoZWVzbGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYm94aW5nIHBlcnNvbmFsaXR5IHdhcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIHByZXNlbnRlcnMgaW4gdGhlIDE5OTkgcmV2aXZhbCBvZiBJdCdzIGEgS25vY2tvdXQ/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgQnJ1bm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2VzYXIgUm9tZXJvIHBsYXllZCB3aGljaCBpY29uaWMgQmF0bWFuIHZpbGxhaW4gZnJvbSB0aGUgMTk2MCdzIFRWIHNob3c/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEpva2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgZnJvbSBUaGUgWW91bmcgT25lcyBhbHNvIHBsYXllZCBMb3JkIEZsYXNoaGVhcnQgaW4gb25lIGVwaXNvZGUgb2YgQmxhY2thZGRlciBJST8=",
            "answer": "UmlrIE1heWFsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR2FtZSBvZiBUaHJvbmVzIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgSm9uIFNub3cncyBzd29yZD8=",
            "answer": "TG9uZ2NsYXc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBOaWNrZWxvZGVvbiBnYW1lIHNob3cgZmVhdHVyZWQgYSBob3VzZSBvbiB0aGUgc2V0IHRoYXQgdGhlIGNvbnRlc3RhbnRzIHdvdWxkIHJhbnNhY2sgdG8gZmluZCBoaWRkZW4gb2JqZWN0cz8=",
            "answer": "RmluZGVycyBLZWVwZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDE5ODUgVG95b3RhIENvcm9sbGEgIkFFODYiIHdhcyB0aGUgaGVybyBjYXIgZm9yIHdoYXQgYW5pbWU/IA==",
            "answer": "SW5pdGlhbCBE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFNjaS1GaSB0ZWxldmlzaW9uIHNob3cgRG9jdG9yIFdobywgd2hvIHBsYXlzIHRoZSBUZW50aCBEb2N0b3I/",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgVGVubmFudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIHRoZSAzIFRvdHMgaW4gVG90cyBUViwgd2hvIHNwZWFrcyBGcmVuY2ggaW4gdGhlIFVLIFZlcnNpb24gYW5kIFNwYW5pc2ggaW4gdGhlIFVTIFZlcnNpb24/",
            "answer": "VGlsbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIlRoZSBPZmZpY2UiIHdobyBkb2VzIE1pY2hhZWwgU2NvdHQgZXZlbnR1YWxseSBlbmQgdXAgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "SG9sbHkgRmxheA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVHdvIGFuZCBhIEhhbGYgTWVuLCB3aGF0IGlzIEFsYW4gSGFycGVyJ3Mgc29uJ3MgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERvY3RvciBXaG8gdW5pdmVyc2UsIGhvdyBtYW55IHRpbWVzIGNhbiBhIHRpbWUgbG9yZCBub3JtYWxseSByZWdlbmVyYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIkNoZWVycyIsIFNhbSBNYWxvbmUgd2FzIGEgZm9ybWVyIHJlbGllZiBwaXRjaGVyIGZvciB3aGljaCBiYXNlYmFsbCB0ZWFtPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9zdG9uIFJlZCBTb3g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyBwbGF5ZWQgYnkgRHVzdGluIERpYW1vbmQgaW4gdGhlIHNpdGNvbSAnU2F2ZWQgYnkgdGhlIEJlbGwnPw==",
            "answer": "U2NyZWVjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBBZ2VudCBGb3ggTXVsZGVyIGluIHRoZSBUViBzY2ktZmkgZHJhbWEgIlRoZSBYLUZpbGVzIj8=",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgRHVjaG92bnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHNhbmcgdGhlIHRoZW1lIHNvbmcgZm9yIHRoZSBUViBzaG93ICdSYXdoaWRlJz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtpZSBMYWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiVGhlIEJpZyBCYW5nIFRoZW9yeSIgZGVidXQgb24gQ0JTPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzdGFyIG9mIHRoZSBBTUMgc2VyaWVzIEJyZWFraW5nIEJhZD8=",
            "answer": "V2FsdGVyIFdoaXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R3JhbnQgR3VzdGluIHBsYXlzIHdoaWNoIHN1cGVyaGVybyBvbiB0aGUgQ1cgc2hvdyBvZiB0aGUgc2FtZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZsYXNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQm9qYWNrIEhvcnNlbWFuIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaXMgYSBodW1hbj8=",
            "answer": "VG9kZCBDaGF2ZXo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgc3RhciBvZiB0aGUgVFYgc2VyaWVzICIyNCI/",
            "answer": "S2llZmVyIFN1dGhlcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGVwaXNvZGUgb2YgU3BvbmdlQm9iIFNxdWFyZVBhbnRzLCAiU3Vydml2YWwgb2YgdGhlIElkaW90cyIsIFNwb25nZWJvYiBjYWxsZWQgUGF0cmljayB3aGljaCBuaWNrbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "UGluaGVhZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2hvdyBEb2N0b3IgV2hvIGZpcnN0IGFpcmVkIGluIDE5NjMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIENvcnkgaW4gdGhlIEhvdXNlIHNldCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR2FtZSBvZiBUaHJvbmVzLCB3aGF0IGlzIExpdHRsZWZpbmdlcidzIHJlYWwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "UGV0eXIgQmFlbGlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiBCaWcgQnJvdGhlciAyMDE0IFVLPw==",
            "answer": "SGVsZW4gV29vZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBNZWcncyBmdWxsIG5hbWUgaW4gIkZhbWlseSBHdXkiPw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYXRyb24gR3JpZmZpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkJyZWFraW5nIEJhZCIsIFdhbHRlciBXaGl0ZSBpcyBhIGhpZ2ggc2Nob29sIHRlYWNoZXIgZGlhZ25vc2VkIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBjYW5jZXI/",
            "answer": "THVuZyBDYW5jZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGlrZSBoaXMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluICJQYXJrcyBhbmQgUmVjcmVhdGlvbiIsIEF6aXogQW5zYXJpIHdhcyBib3JuIGluIFNvdXRoIENhcm9saW5hLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qm9iIFJvc3Mgd2FzIGEgVVMgQWlyIEZvcmNlIHBpbG90Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S2xpbmdvbnMgcmVzcGVjdCB0aGVpciBkaXNhYmxlZCBjb21yYWRlcywgYW5kIHRob3NlIHdobyBhcmUgb2xkLCBpbmp1cmllZCwgYW5kIGhlbHBsZXNzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTmlja2Vsb2Rlb24ncyBvcmlnaW5hbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlud2hlZWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIHdoYXQgc2F1Y2UgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkgdXNlZCBieSBLbGluZ29ucyBvbiBicmVnaXQgbHVuZz8=",
            "answer": "R3JhcG9rIHNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2Vhc29ucyBkaWQgdGhlIFNjaS1GaSB0ZWxldmlzaW9uIHNob3cgIlN0YXJnYXRlIEF0bGFudGlzIiBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkRvY3RvciBXaG8iLCB0aGUgRG9jdG9yIGdldHMgaGlzIFRBUkRJUyBieSBzdGVhbGluZyBpdC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcGxhbmV0IHRoYXQgdGhlIERvY3RvciBmcm9tIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2VyaWVzICJEb2N0b3IgV2hvIiBjb21lcyBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R2FsbGlmcmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCB0aGUgV2FpdHJlc3MgaW4gdGhlIFNwYW0gc2tldGNoIG9mICJNb250eSBQeXRob24ncyBGbHlpbmcgQ2lyY3VzIj8=",
            "answer": "VGVycnkgSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gc2Vhc29uIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgVVMgS2l0Y2hlbiBOaWdodG1hcmVzLCBHb3JkYW4gUmFtc2F5IHRyaWVkIHRvIHNhdmUgMTAgZGlmZmVyZW50IHJlc3RhdXJhbnRzLiBIb3cgbWFueSBlbmRlZCB1cCBjbG9zaW5nIGFmdGVyd2FyZHM/",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcG9ydHJheXMgIldhbHRlciBXaGl0ZSIgaW4gdGhlIHNlcmllcyAiQnJlYWtpbmcgQmFkIj8=",
            "answer": "IEJyeWFuIENyYW5zdG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhCTyBzZXJpZXMgIkdhbWUgb2YgVGhyb25lcyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb24gd2hpY2ggc2VyaWVzIG9mIGJvb2tzPw==",
            "answer": "QSBTb25nIG9mIEljZSBhbmQgRmlyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIENvcm9uYXRpb24gU3RyZWV0IGFjdHJlc3Mgd2FzIG9uY2UgYSBob3N0ZXNzIG9uIHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIEdhbWUgU2hvdyAiRG91YmxlIFlvdXIgTW9uZXkiPw==",
            "answer": "QW1hbmRhIEJhcnJpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHRlZW5hZ2Ugd2l0Y2ggcGxheWVkIGJ5IE1lbGlzYSBKb2FuIEhhcnQgd2hvIGxpdmVzIHdpdGggaGVyIHdpdGNoIGF1bnRzIEhpbGRhIGFuZCBaZWxkYT8=",
            "answer": "U2FicmluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggc3RhdGUgb2YgQW1lcmljYSB3YXMgdGhlIEZyZXNoIFByaW5jZSBvZiBCZWwtQWlyIGJvcm4gYW5kIHJhaXNlZCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "UGVubnN5bHZhbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgaW5zcGVjdG9yIGluIHRoZSBzZXJpZXMgIk9uIHRoZSBCdXNlcyI/",
            "answer": "Qmxha2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyIgZmFtaWx5IGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIGNyZWF0b3IgTWF0dCBHcm9lbmluZydzIHJlYWwgZmFtaWx5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIEJhcnQgc2VsbCBoaXMgc291bCBmb3IgaW4gVGhlIFNpbXBzb25zIGVwaXNvZGUgJ0JhcnQgU2VsbHMgSGlzIFNvdWwnPw==",
            "answer": "JDU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIkRyYWdvbmJhbGwgWiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQ2VsbCdzIG1vc3QgcG93ZXJmdWwgYXR0YWNrPw==",
            "answer": "U29sYXIgS2FtZWhhbWVoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIkZ1dHVyYW1hIiB3aGF0IGlzIEZyeSdzIGZ1bGwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "UGhpbGlwIEouIEZyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QU1DJ3MgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiLCBSaWNrLCBDYXJsLCBEYXJ5bCwgTW9yZ2FuLCBDYXJvbCBhbmQgTWFnZ2llIHdlcmUgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0byB1cyBpbiBTZWFzb24gMS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2YgVGhlIEFsbG1hbiBCcm90aGVycyBCYW5kIGluc3RydW1lbnRhbCB1c2VkIGFzIHRoZSB0aGVtZSB0byB0aGUgQkJDIG1vdG9yaW5nIHNob3csICdUb3AgR2Vhcic/",
            "answer": "SmVzc2ljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRoZW1lIGZvciB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBzY2llbmNlIGZpY3Rpb24gc2VyaWVzICJEb2N0b3IgV2hvIiB3YXMgY29tcG9zZWQgYnkgd2hvPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uIEdyYWluZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpbiAiU3RyYW5nZXIgVGhpbmdzIiBoYXMgdGhlIHBvd2VyIG9mIFRlbGVraW5lc2lzPw==",
            "answer": "RWxldmVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGRvZXMgdm9pY2UgYWN0cmVzcyBUYXJhIFN0cm9uZyBOT1Qgdm9pY2U/",
            "answer": "QnViYmxlcyAoMjAxNik="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNlcmllcyBSZWQgRHdhcmYsIEtyeXRlbidzIGZ1bGwgbmFtZSBpcyBLcnl0ZW4gMlg0Qi01MjNQLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVlIGZyb20gIkl0J3MgQWx3YXlzIFN1bm55IGluIFBoaWxhZGVscGhpYSIgaGFzIGRhdGVkIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIGd1eXMgRVhDRVBU",
            "answer": "TWF0dGhldyAiUmlja2V0eSBDcmlja2V0IiBNYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIEtlbiBKZW5uaW5ncycgd2luIHN0cmVhayBvbiBKZW9wYXJkeT8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQnJpdGlzaCB3cml0ZXIgd3JvdGUgZm9yIGJvdGggRG9jdG9yIFdobyBhbmQgU2hlcmxvY2s/",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIE1vZmZhdHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2Vhc29ucyBkaWQgdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIkRvbmtleSBLb25nIENvdW50cnkiIGxhc3Q/",
            "answer": "Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIFNob3cgIkRvbmtleSBLb25nIENvdW50cnkiLCB3aGljaCBlcGlzb2RlIGRpZCB0aGUgc29uZyAiRWRkaWUsIExldCBNZSBHbyBCYWNrIFRvIE15IEhvbWUiIHBsYXkgaW4/",
            "answer": "SXQncyBhIFdvbmRlcmZ1bCBMaWZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBEb25rZXkgS29uZyBkaWVkIGluIHRoZSAiRG9ua2V5IEtvbmcgQ291bnRyeSIgZXBpc29kZSAiSXQncyBhIFdvbmRlcmZ1bCBMaWZlIiwgd2hvIHdhcyBoaXMgZ3VhcmRpYW4gYW5nZWw/",
            "answer": "RWRkaWUgdGhlIE1lYW4gT2xkIFlldGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaW4gdGhlIFN0YXIgVHJlayBzZXJpZXMgaXMgTk9UIEtsaW5nb24gZm9vZD8=",
            "answer": "SG9ycyBkJ29ldXZyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIEtsaW5nb25zIGFyZSBjb21tb25seSByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBhcyAiQmxhY2sgRWx2ZXMiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFjZSBlbmpveXMgYSBnbGFzcyBvZiB3YXJtIGJhZ2hvbCBpbiAiU3RhciBUcmVrIj8=",
            "answer": "S2xpbmdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugdm9pY2VzIHdhc24ndCBhIGNob2ljZSBmb3IgdGhlIEhvdXNlIEFJIGluICJUaGUgU2ltcHNvbnMgVHJlZWhvdXNlIG9mIEhvcnJvciIgc2hvcnQsIEhvdXNlIG9mIFdoYWNrcz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIENsb29uZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgbm90IGFuIGFjdG9yL2FjdHJlc3Mgb24gdGhlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2hvdyAiU2F0dXJkYXkgTmlnaHQgTGl2ZSIgaW4gU2Vhc29uIDQyPw==",
            "answer": "VGluYSBGZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJpY2sgQW5kIE1vcnR5Iiwgd2hvIHNob3QgIk1yLiBQb29weWJ1dHRob2xlIiBpbiB0aGUgZXBpc29kZSAiVG90YWwgUmlja2FsbCI/",
            "answer": "QmV0aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBGaXJlc3Rvcm0ncyByaXZhbCBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIHJ1biBvZiBVSyBSb2JvdCBXYXJzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFuaWMgQXR0YWNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNhcnRvb24gJ1Nwb25nZUJvYiBTcXVhcmVQYW50cycsIHdoYXQgZGlkIHRoZSBhY3JvbnltIEUuVi5JLkwgc3RhbmQgZm9yPw==",
            "answer": "RXZlcnkgVmlsbGFpbiBJcyBMZW1vbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhd2FyZHMgZG8gTWF0dCBTdG9uZSBhbmQgVHJleSBQYXJrZXIgTk9UIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "T3NjYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGRhdGUgb2Ygb3JpZ2luYWwgYWlyaW5nIG9mIHRoZSBwaWxvdCBlcGlzb2RlIG9mIE15IExpdHRsZSBQb255OiBGcmllbmRzaGlwIGlzIE1hZ2ljPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAxMHRoLCAyMDEw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpY3Rpb25hbCBtb3ZpZSAnUm9jaGVsbGUsIFJvY2hlbGxlJyBmZWF0dXJlcyBpbiB3aGljaCBzaXRjb20/",
            "answer": "U2VpbmZlbGQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBjb21wYW55IEJCQyBvZmZpY2lhbGx5IGxhdW5jaCB0aGUgY2hhbm5lbCBCQkMgT25lPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2Vhc29ucyBkaWQgIlN0YXJnYXRlIFNHLTEiIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5IiwgaW4gZXBpc29kZSAiVG90YWwgUmlja2FsbCIsIHdobyB3YXMgYSBwYXJhc2l0ZT8=",
            "answer": "UGVuY2lsdmVzdGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93cyBtYWtlcyBldmVyeW9uZSBsb29rIHVuZGVyIHRoZWlyIGNoYWlyPw==",
            "answer": "T3ByYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIlRoZSBGbGFzaCIgVFYgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QmFycnkgQWxsZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgIkZsYXNoIiBhbmQgIkFycm93IiBzcGlub2ZmIGZlYXR1cmluZyBhIHRlYW0gb2YgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB0aGF0IGhhdmUgYXBwZWFyZWQgb24gYm90aCBzaG93cz8=",
            "answer": "TGVnZW5kcyBvZiBUb21vcnJvdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIEtsaW5nb24gZGVsaWNhY3kgb2YgImdhZ2giIG1hZGUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "U2VycGVudCB3b3Jtcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlazogVGhlIE5leHQgR2VuZXJhdGlvbiIsIERhdGEgaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgYW5kcm9pZCBpbiBleGlzdGVuY2Uu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gZXBpc29kZSBvZiAiVGhlIFNpbXBzb25zIiBpcyBkZWRpY2F0ZWQgdG8gTW9lIFN6eXNsYWsncyBiYXIgcmFnLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQU1DJ3MgVFYgU2VyaWVzICJUaGUgV2Fsa2luZyBEZWFkIiB3aGF0IGFyZSAiWm9tYmllcyIgcmVmZXJyZWQgdG8gYXM/",
            "answer": "V2Fsa2Vycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmFyb24gU2lsYXMgR3JlZW5iYWNrIGlzIHRoZSBhcmNoIG5lbWVzaXMgb2Ygd2hpY2ggY2FydG9vbiBoZXJvPw==",
            "answer": "RGFuZ2VyIE1vdXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcmFjZSBob3JzZSB0aGF0IFRvbnkgU29wcmFubyBiZWNvbWVzIGF0dGFjaGVkIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "UGllLU8tTXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggQnJpdGlzaCBzZWFzaWRlIHRvd24gd2FzIHRoZSBCQkMgc2l0Y29tICJGYXdsdHkgVG93ZXJzIiBzZXQ/",
            "answer": "VG9ycXVheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBdXRvYm90IG5hbWVzIGluIE1pY2hhZWwgQmF5J3MgbW92aWVzIHdhcyBOT1QgYSBuYW1lIGZvciBhIFRyYW5zZm9ybWVyIGluIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCAxOTgwJ3MgY2FydG9vbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVkZmxhcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgUm9zcycgcGV0IG1vbmtleSBvbiAiRnJpZW5kcyI/",
            "answer": "TWFyY2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBlcGlzb2RlIG9mIERvY3RvciBXaG8gdG8gYWlyIGluIDE5NjM/",
            "answer": "QW4gVW5lYXJ0aGx5IENoaWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBmYW1vdXMgc3BhbmlzaCBodW1vcmlzdCwgRWwgUmlzaXRhcz8=",
            "answer": "SnVhbiBKb3lhIEJvcmdh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBCaWcgQmFuZyBUaGVvcnkiLCB3aGF0IGlzIEhvd2FyZCBXb2xvd2l0eidzIG5pY2tuYW1lIGluIFdvcmxkIG9mIFdhcmNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "V29sb3dpemFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnJpdGlzaCBhY3RvciBEYXZpZCBNb3JyaXNzZXkgc3RhcnMgYXMgd2hpY2ggcm9sZSBpbiAiVGhlIFdhbGtpbmcgRGVhZCI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdvdmVybm9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIEZlcmVuZ2kncyBGaXJzdCBSdWxlIG9mIEFjcXVpc2l0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "T25jZSB5b3UgaGF2ZSB0aGVpciBtb25leSwgeW91IG5ldmVyIGdpdmUgaXQgYmFjay4g"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEtsaW5nb24gaG9tZSBwbGFuZXQgaXMgUW8nbm9TLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgS2xpbmdvbidzIGFmdGVybGlmZSBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "U3RvLXZvLWtvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIEtsaW5nb25zIGFyZSBhbGllbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBicmVlZCBvZiBkb2cgaXMgIlNjb29ieSBEb28iPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlYXQgRGFuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UHJpb3IgdG8gd29ya2luZyBhdCBXaXphcmRzIG9mIHRoZSBDb2FzdCwgIk1hcmsgUm9zZXdhdGVyIiB3YXMgYSB3cml0ZXIgZm9yIHdoaWNoIHNob3c/",
            "answer": "Um9zZWFubmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhY3RvciBwb3J0cmF5cyBIb2dhbiAiV2FzaCIgV2FzaGJ1cm5lIGluIHRoZSBUViBTaG93IEZpcmVmbHk/",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBUdWR5aw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3Igd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1ham9yIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBUViBTaG93IEZyZWFrcyBhbmQgR2Vla3M/",
            "answer": "Sm9uYWggSGlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2V0dGluZyBvZiB0aGUgc2hvdyAiUGFya3MgYW5kIFJlY3JlYXRpb24iPw==",
            "answer": "UGF3bmVlLCBJbmRpYW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R3V5J3MgR3JvY2VyeSBHYW1lcyBpcyBob3N0ZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggcHJlc2VudGVyPw==",
            "answer": "R3V5IEZpZXJp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2hvdyBCcmVha2luZyBCYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHN0cmVldCBuYW1lIG9mIFdhbHRlciBhbmQgSmVzc2UncyBub3RvcmlvdXMgcHJvZHVjdD8=",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZSBTa3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCB0aGUgc3VuIGJhYnkgaW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIHJ1biBvZiBUZWxldHViYmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SmVzc2ljYSBTbWl0aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzZXJpZXMgIlRoZSBCaWxsIiBlbmQ/",
            "answer": "MjAxMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gc2Vhc29uIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgTmV0ZmxpeCBwb2xpdGljYWwgZHJhbWEgIkhvdXNlIG9mIENhcmRzIiwgd2hhdCBnb3Zlcm5tZW50IHBvc2l0aW9uIGRvZXMgRnJhbmsgVW5kZXJ3b29kIGhvbGQ/",
            "answer": "SG91c2UgTWFqb3JpdHkgV2hpcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgRGlzbmV5IHNob3dzIGlzIGNsYXNzaWZpZWQgYXMgYW4gYW5pbWU/",
            "answer": "U3RpdGNoIQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S2xpbmdvbnMgb25jZSBoYWQgYSBwZXJpb2Qgb2YgRGVtb2NyYWN5IGluIHRoZWlyIGhpc3RvcnksIHRoZXkgcmVmZXJyZWQgdG8gaXQgYXMgdGhlICJEYXJrIFRpbWVzIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGluZmxhdGFibGUgZHVjayBzYWNyaWZpZWQgdG8gdGhlIGNyb3dkIGF0IHRoZSBlbmQgb2YgRXBpc29kZSAzNCBvZiB0aGUgMTh0aCBzZWFzb24gb2YgQmlnIEJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIk1hZCBNZW4iLCB3aGF0IHdhcyBEb25hbGQgRHJhcGVyJ3MgYmlydGhuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCAiRGljayIgV2hpdG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBBIFRlYW0iIGZpcnN0IGFpcmVkIGluIHRoZSBVU0EgYW5kIGluIHRoZSBVSyBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgJ0RvY3RvciBXaG8nLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSB0aW1lLWNhcHN1bGUgbW9kZWwgc3RvbGVuIGJ5ICd0aGUgRG9jdG9yJz8=",
            "answer": "VFQgVHlwZSA0MCwgTWFyayAzIChUQVJESVMp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQnJlYWtpbmcgQmFkLCB0aGUgaW5pdGlhbHMgVy5XLiByZWZlciB0byB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsdGVyIFdoaXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR2FtZSBvZiBUaHJvbmVzLCB3aGF0IGNvbnRpbmVudCBsaWVzIGFjcm9zcyB0aGUgTmFycm93IFNlYSBmcm9tIFdlc3Rlcm9zPw==",
            "answer": "RXNzb3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkRvbmtleSBLb25nIENvdW50cnkiLCB3aHkgZG9lcyBEb25rZXkgS29uZyB3YW50IHRvIGtub3cgdGhlIHNlY3JldCBvZiB0aGUgY3J5c3RhbCBjb2NvbnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "SGUncyB0aGUgYmlnIGthaHVuYS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIEtsaW5nb24gZGVhdGggcml0dWFsPw==",
            "answer": "TG9vayBpbnRvIHNreSBhbmQgeWVsbCBsb3VkbHkgaW4gbW91cm5pbmcu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhY3RvcnMgcG9ydHJheWVkIHRoZSBOaW50aCBEb2N0b3IgaW4gdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93ICJEb2N0b3IgV2hvIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgRWNjbGVzdG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBhbnRhZ29uaXN0cyBpbiBCYXR0bGVzdGFyIEdhbGFjdGljYT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEN5bG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgTmlja2Vsb2Rlb24gZ2FtZSBzaG93cyBhaXJlZCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "RG91YmxlIERhcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3csIERvY3RvciBXaG8sIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBULkEuUi5ELkkuUyBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "VGltZSBBbmQgUmVsYXRpdmUgRGltZW5zaW9ucyBJbiBTcGFjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3VwZXJuYXR1cmFsLCB3aGF0J3MgaXMgU2FtJ3MgYnJvdGhlcnMgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "RGVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBUViBzaG93IGlzIGFib3V0IGEgZ3JhbmRmYXRoZXIgZHJhZ2dpbmcgaGlzIGdyYW5kc29uIGFyb3VuZCBvbiBhZHZlbnR1cmVzPw==",
            "answer": "UmljayAmIE1vcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3RhciBUcmVrOiBUaGUgTmV4dCBHZW5lcmF0aW9uLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIERhdGEncyBjYXQ/",
            "answer": "U3BvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S2xpbmdvbnMgZXhwcmVzcyBlbW90aW9uIGluIGFydCB0aHJvdWdoIG9wZXJhIGFuZCBwb2V0cnku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlazogVm95YWdlciIsIHdoaWNoIGVwaXNvZGUgZGlkIFZveWFnZXIgZXN0YWJsaXNoIHJlYWwtdGltZSBjb21tdW5pY2F0aW9uIHdpdGggU3RhcmZsZWV0IEhlYWRxdWFydGVycz8=",
            "answer": "UGF0aGZpbmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3b24gdGhlIGZpcnN0IHNlYXNvbiBvZiBBbWVyaWNhbiBJZG9sIGluIDIwMDI/",
            "answer": "S2VsbHkgQ2xhcmtzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIFVLICJXaG8gV2FudHMgdG8gYmUgYSBNaWxsaW9uYWlyZT8iIGNoZWF0aW5nIHNjYW5kYWwga25vd24gYXM/",
            "answer": "TWFqb3IgRnJhdWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IGhhbGYtaG91ciBDR0kgY2FydG9vbiwgUmVCb290LCBhaXJlZCBvbiB3aGljaCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgd2lubmVyIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE2IFdXRSBSb3lhbCBSdW1ibGU/",
            "answer": "VHJpcGxlIEg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGZvdW5kZXIgb2YgdGhlIEtsaW5nb24gRW1waXJlIGFuZCBpdHMgcGhpbG9zb3BoeT8=",
            "answer": "S2FobGVzcyB0aGUgVW5mb3JnZXR0YWJsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXIgVHJlayIsIEtsYWFuZyBpcyBhIHR5cGljYWwgS2xpbmdvbiBtYWxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBvZiAiQ29taWMgQm9vayBHdXkiPw==",
            "answer": "SmVmZiBBbGJlcnRzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZXZlciBhY3RvciB0byBwbGF5ICJUaGUgRG9jdG9yIiBvbiAiRG9jdG9yIFdobyI/",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIYXJ0bmVsbA=="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZ2FtZXMgaW4gdGhlIENyYXNoIEJhbmRpY29vdCBzZXJpZXMgd2VyZSByZWxlYXNlZCBvbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgUGxheXN0YXRpb24/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgdGVycm9yaXN0IGZhY3Rpb24gaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgKDIwMDApPw==",
            "answer": "TWlkd2VzdCBNaWxpdGlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBQaWthY2h1J3MgTmF0aW9uYWwgUG9rw6lEZXggTnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "IzAyNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzbm93eSBtb2Igd2FzIGFkZGVkIGluIE1pbmVjcmFmdCAxLjEwPw==",
            "answer": "UG9sYXIgYmVhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3R1ZGVudCBpbiBZYW5kZXJlIFNpbXVsYXRvciBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgYXNraW5nIGlycml0YXRpbmcgYW5kIHN0dXBpZCBxdWVzdGlvbnM/",
            "answer": "TWlkb3JpIEd1cmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFjY2VsZXJhdGlvbiBvZiBNYXJpbyBpZiBoZSB3YXMgaW4gZnJlZSBmYWxsPw==",
            "answer": "OTEuMjggbS9zXjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggZG9lcyB0aGUgJ0FXUCcgY29zdCBpbiBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZT8=",
            "answer": "JDQ3NTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNlY3JldCBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gaW4gdGhlIEhvdGxpbmUgTWlhbWkgc2VyaWVzPyA=",
            "answer": "NTAgQmxlc3Npbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgT3ZlcndhdGNoPw==",
            "answer": "SW52b2tlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHV6emxlIGdhbWUgd2FzIGRlc2lnbmVkIGJ5IGEgUnVzc2lhbiBwcm9ncmFtbWVyLCBmZWF0dXJpbmcgUnVzc2lhbiBidWlsZGluZ3MgYW5kIG11c2ljPw==",
            "answer": "VGV0cmlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIDNEIFdvcmxkIiwgdGhlIERvdWJsZSBDaGVycnkgcG93ZXItdXAgb3JpZ2luYXRlZCBmcm9tIGEgZGV2ZWxvcGVyIGFjY2lkZW50YWxseSBtYWtpbmcgdHdvIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgY29udHJvbGxhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGV1cyBFeCAoMjAwMCkgZG9lcyBub3QgZmVhdHVyZSB0aGUgV29ybGQgVHJhZGUgQ2VudGVyIGJlY2F1c2UgaXQgd2FzIGRlc3Ryb3llZCBieSB0ZXJyb3Jpc3QgYXR0YWNrcyBhY2NvcmRpbmcgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUncyBwbG90Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWVyY3kncyAidWx0aW1hdGUgYWJpbGl0eSI/",
            "answer": "VmFsa3lyaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgQmF0dGxlYmxvY2sgVGhlYXRlciwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIHdobyB2b2ljZWQgdGhlIG5hcnJhdG9yPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbCBTdGFtcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJDYXZlIFN0b3J5IiBpcyBuYW1lZA==",
            "answer": "UXVvdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIk1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQiLCB3aGF0IGRpZCBSZXZvbHZlciBPY2Vsb3QgY29uc2lkZXIgdGhlIGdyZWF0ZXN0IGhhbmRndW4gZXZlciBtYWRlPw==",
            "answer": "Q29sdCBTaW5nbGUgQWN0aW9uIEFybXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gWGVub2JsYWRlIENocm9uaWNsZXMgWCwgd2hpY2ggY2xhc3MgaGFzIGEgc25pcGVyIHJpZmxlIGFzIGl0J3MgcHJpbWFyeSB3ZWFwb24/",
            "answer": "UGFydGlzYW4gRWFnbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgZ2FtZSBmZWF0dXJlZCB0aGUgY2FzdCBvZiAiVGhlIFdvcmxkIEVuZHMgV2l0aCBZb3UiPw==",
            "answer": "RHJlYW0gRHJvcCBEaXN0YW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBwbGFuZXQgaW4gS2VyYmFsIFNwYWNlIFByb2dyYW0/",
            "answer": "Sm9vbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcGFjZSBzaG9vdGVyIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBjYW1lIG91dCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "U3BhY2UgSW52YWRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgVjogVGhlIFBoYW50b20gUGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "UHVuaXNoZWQgIlZlbm9tIiBTbmFrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGhpbCBGaXNoIHdhcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "RmV6"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdHJvcGhpZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluICJTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiBmb3IgTmludGVuZG8gM0RTIj8=",
            "answer": "Njg1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIDZ0aCBvZiBKdW5lIDIwMDYsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBpbmZhbW91cyBnbGl0Y2ggdGhhdCBvY2N1cnJlZCBpbiB0aGUgTU1PIFJ1bmVTY2FwZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZhbGFkb3IgTWFzc2FjcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIHdhcyBOT1QgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiTGVnbyBEaW1lbnNpb25zIj8=",
            "answer": "QnJlYWtpbmcgQmFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmFsdmUncyAiUG9ydGFsIiBhbmQgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSIgZnJhbmNoaXNlcyBleGlzdCB3aXRoaW4gdGhlIHNhbWUgaW4tZ2FtZSB1bml2ZXJzZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3RhZ2VzIGlzIG5vdCBwbGF5YWJsZSBpbiAiU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gZm9yIFdpaSBVIj8=",
            "answer": "Rm91bnRhaW4gb2YgRHJlYW1z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIGFjY29yZGluZyB0byB0aGUgYXNzZXQgZmlsZXMsIHRoZSBkZXNjcmlwdGlvbiBvZiB0aGUgIkVyY2hpdXMgR2hvc3QiIGlzIHRoZSBzYW1lIGFzIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIGFzc2V0cz8=",
            "answer": "U3Bvb2tpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZXIgd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyI/",
            "answer": "VHJleWFyY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQsIHdoaWNoIHJhaWQgaW5zdGFuY2UgZmVhdHVyZXMgYSBjaGVzcyBldmVudD8=",
            "answer": "S2FyYXpoYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgaW50cm91ZGNlZCBLbnVja2xlcyB0aGUgRWNoaWRuYT8=",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIDM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyBOT1QgYSBib3NzIGluIENyYXNoIEJhc2g/",
            "answer": "UmlwcGVyIFJvbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBpbiAiWGVub2JsYWRlIENocm9uaWNsZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2h1bGs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBOaW50ZW5kbyBnYW1lIGNvbnNvbGU/",
            "answer": "RHJlYW1jYXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGFuIG9wdGlvbmFsIGJvc3MgeW91IGNhbiBmaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "TWFzdGVyIFllbiBTaWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2VucmUgaXMgdGhlIFRvdWhvdSBQcm9qZWN0IGFzc29jaWF0ZWQgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ2VtIHVwIChidWxsZXQtaGVsbCkgJiBGaWdodGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBWZWx2ZXQgUm9vbSBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gUGVyc29uYSA0IEFyZW5hIFVsdGltYXg/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAwNCwgd2hpY2ggcGVyc29uKHMpIGNyZWF0ZWQgIlJvYmxveCI/",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgQmFzenVja2kgYW5kIEVyaWsgQ2Fzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tIEZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgVklJSSBwcmltYXJpbHkgc3Bva2UgaW4gb25lIHdvcmQgc2VudGVuY2VzPw==",
            "answer": "RnVqaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgMiBWYWx2ZSBHYW1lcyBhcmUgc2V0IGluIHRoZSBzYW1lIHVuaXZlcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZi1saWZlIGFuZCBQb3J0YWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vYmlsZSBnYW1lICJKZXRwYWNrIEpveXJpZGUiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/IA==",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgdGhlIEJyb3RoZXJob29kIG9mIE5vZCBpbiB0aGUgQ29tbWFuZCBhbmQgQ29ucXVlciBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "S2FuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIExpZmUgaXMgU3RyYW5nZTogQmVmb3JlIFRoZSBTdG9ybT8=",
            "answer": "Q2hsb2UgUHJpY2Ug"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIEdhbWUgU3BsYXRvb24gMiwgd2hhdCBpcyBNYXJpbmEncyBzY3JlZW4gbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "REpfSHlwZXJmcmVzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q291bnRpbmcgdGhlIEJsb29kIGFuZCBXaW5lIERMQywgaG93IG1hbnkgSGVybyBDYXJkcyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gdG90YWwgaW4gVGhlIFdpdGNoZXIgMz8=",
            "answer": "MjU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVybWFuZW50IGNvbXBhbmlvbnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSBiYXNlIGdhbWUgdmVyc2lvbiBvZiBGYWxsb3V0OiBOZXcgVmVnYXM/",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgYSBtYXAgdGhhdCB3YXMgaW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIGF0IGxhdW5jaD8=",
            "answer": "R3JhdmVsIFBpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTQgUG9rZW1vbiBWR0MgRmluYWxzLCB3aGljaCBQb2tlbW9uIHdhcyBmYW1vdXMgZm9yIGJyaW5naW5nIHRoZSB3aW5uZXIgdG8gdmljdG9yeT8=",
            "answer": "UGFjaGlyaXN1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiBEaWFtb25kLCBQZWFybCBhbmQgUGxhdGludW0sIHdoZXJlIGNhbiBhIE11bmNobGF4IGJlIGZvdW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SG9uZXkgVHJlZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNob3RndW4gYXBwZWFycyBpbiBldmVyeSBudW1iZXJlZCBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MuIFNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBZb3NoaSdzIHNjaWVudGlmaWMgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VC4gWW9zaGlzYXVyIE11bmNoYWtvb3Bhcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBoZWFsaW5nIGl0ZW0gaW4gRGFyayBTb3Vscz8=",
            "answer": "RXN0dXMgRmxhc2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGVubmlzIGZvciBUd28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG1hc2NvdCBvZiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBOaW50ZW5kbyBnYW1lLCAiU3BsYXRvb24iIHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRm9yemEgTW90b3JzcG9ydCA2LCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB0cmFjay1leGNsdXNpdmUgY2FycyB3YXMgTk9UIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lLCBlaXRoZXIgb3JpZ2luYWxseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBnYW1lIG9yIGFkZGVkIGFzIERMQz8=",
            "answer": "QXN0b24gTWFydGluIFZ1bGNhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiAiVGhlIFN0YW5sZXkgUGFyYWJsZSI/",
            "answer": "U3RhbmxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSB3YXMgcmVjYWxsZWQgZm9yIGNvbnRhaW5pbmcgYSBoaWRkZW4sIHBsYXlhYmxlIFNvdXRoIFBhcmsgZXBpc29kZT8=",
            "answer": "VGlnZXIgV29vZHMgOTkgUEdBIFRvdXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFjLU1hbiB3YXMgaW52ZW50ZWQgYnkgdGhlIGRlc2lnbmVyIFRvcnUgSXdhdGFuaSB3aGlsZSBoZSB3YXMgZWF0aW5nIHBpenphLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBzcGVlZCBwb3NzaWJsZSBpbiBUcmFja21hbmlhwrI6IFN0YWRpdW0/",
            "answer": "MTAwMCAga20vaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyBNYXggUGF5bmUgaW4gdGhlIDIwMDEgZ2FtZSAiTWF4IFBheW5lIj8=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgTWNDYWZmcmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZmVtYWxlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIGEgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "U2FtdXMgQXJhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHYWJlIE5ld2VsbCdzIGZhdm9yaXRlIGNsYXNzIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMj8=",
            "answer": "U3B5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hvIG9yZ2FuaXplZCB0aGUgY3JlYXRpb24gb2YgdGhlIFBhbGFkaW5zPw==",
            "answer": "QWxvbnN1cyBGYW9s"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWluZWNyYWZ0IGNhbiBiZSBwbGF5ZWQgd2l0aCBhIHZpcnR1YWwgcmVhbGl0eSBoZWFkc2V0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSByYWNlIGluIHRoZSBNTU9SUEcgR3VpbGQgV2FycyAyPyA=",
            "answer": "VGVuZ3U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRvZXMgdGhlIGxpdHRsZSBoZWFkY3JhYiBpbiAiSGFsZiBMaWZlIDIiIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "TGFtYXJy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBNLXJhdGVkIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZGV2ZWxvcGVkIGJ5IFNxdWFyZXNvZnQvU3F1YXJlIEVuaXg/",
            "answer": "UGFyYXNpdGUgRXZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEZhbGxvdXQgc2VyaWVzLCBvbiB3aGljaCBkYXRlIGRpZCBUaGUgR3JlYXQgV2FyIGhhcHBlbj8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyM3JkLCAyMDc3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgc3VwcG9zZWQgdG8gYmUgcGFja2FnZWQgd2l0aCBTb25pYyAzLCBidXQgd2FzIGN1dCBpbiBoYWxmIGR1ZSB0byB0aW1lIGNvbnN0cmFpbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgJiBLbnVja2xlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZSBmcmFuY2hpc2VzIHdlcmUgbWFkZSBieSBOYW1jbz8=",
            "answer": "VGVra2Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSGFsbyAyLCBob3cgbWFueSByb3VuZHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTTZDIGhvbGQgaW4gYSBzaW5nbGUgbWFnYXppbmU/",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiBSZWQgJiBCbHVlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEhNMDU/",
            "answer": "Rmxhc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRWxpbWluYXRvciIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVEYyIExvcmUsIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgSGVhdnkncyB5b3VuZ2VyIHNpc3RlcnM/",
            "answer": "WWFuYSBhbmQgQnJvbmlzbGF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSGl0bWFuOiBCbG9vZCBNb25leSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGFyZ2V0IGluIHRoZSBtaXNzaW9uICJEZWF0aCBvZiBhIFNob3dtYW4iPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9zZXBoIENsYXJlbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IC5oYWNrIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "LmhhY2svL0luZmVjdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlZmF1bHQgcGxheWVybW9kZWwgb2YgR2FycnkncyBNb2QgaXMgdGhpcyBIYWxmIExpZmUgMiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "SXNhYWMgS2xlaW5lcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZXMgTm8gTWFu4oCZcyBTa3kgYW5kIE1pZ2h0eSBOby4gOSBoYXZlIGluIGNvbW1vbj8=",
            "answer": "Qm90aCB3ZXJlIGFubm91bmNlZCBpbiAyMDEzLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbGVtZW50IGRvZXMgdGhlIFppbm9ncmUgdXNlIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyPw==",
            "answer": "VGh1bmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHN0YXJzIGluIEJydXRhbCBMZWdlbmQ/",
            "answer": "SmFjayBCbGFjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2l0aG91dCBlbmNoYW50bWVudHMsIHdoaWNoIHBpY2theGUgaW4gbWluZWNyYWZ0IG1pbmVzIGJsb2NrcyB0aGUgcXVpY2tlc3Qu",
            "answer": "R29sZGVuIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBDb3B5IEFiaWxpdGllcyB3YXMgb25seSBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiAiS2lyYnkgJiBUaGUgQW1hemluZyBNaXJyb3IiPw==",
            "answer": "TWluaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkJyYXdsaGFsbGEiLCB3aGF0IHNwZWNpZXMgaXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBCw7ZkdmFyIGlzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZiBIdW1hbiAvIEhhbGYgQmVhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgZWFzdGVyIGVnZyB3aWxsIHJld2FyZCB5b3Ugd2l0aCB0aGUgYWNoaWV2ZW1lbnQsICJUaW1lIFRyYXZlbCBXaWxsIFRlbGwiPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhbmdyaS1MYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBQb2vDqW1vbiBEaWFtb25kICYgUGVhcmwgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgb25lIHRvIHJldHVybiB0byB0aGUgc2VyaWVzIGFmdGVyIGJlaW5nIGFic2VudCBmcm9tIGEgcHJldmlvdXMgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIE1hcmlv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNjcmFwcGVkIFNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIGxldmVsICJIaWRkZW4gUGFsYWNlIFpvbmUiIHdhcyBsYXRlciByZXVzZWQgaW4gdGhlIGlPUyBwb3J0IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lLiA=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgQWdlbnQgNDcgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzICJIaXRtYW4iPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuIE90dG8gV29sZmdhbmcgT3J0LU1leWVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMgTk9UIGFwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBHcmFuZCBUaGVmdCBBdXRvIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBDYXJkZW5hcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWxpZW4gc3BlY2llcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIFNoYWRvdyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2cgKDIwMDUpPw==",
            "answer": "QmxhY2sgQXJtcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBoYXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "VGltZXNwbGl0dGVyczogRnV0dXJlIFBlcmZlY3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBNb2Rlcm4gV2FyZmFyZSAyLCBob3cgbWFueSBjb25zZWN1dGl2ZSBraWxscyBkb2VzIGl0IHJlcXVpcmUgdG8gZWFybiB0aGUgIlRhY3RpY2FsIE51a2UiIGtpbGxzdHJlYWs/",
            "answer": "MjU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZHJpdmUgZm9ybSB3YXMgYWRkZWQgaW50byBLaW5nZG9tIEhlYXJ0cyBJSSBGaW5hbCBNaXg/",
            "answer": "TGltaXQgRm9ybQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvLW9wIHNob290ZXIgUGF5ZGF5IDIsIHdoaWNoIGNvbnRhY3QgaGVscHMgeW91IGJyZWFrIG91dCBIb3h0b24/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERlbnRpc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFZpZGVvIEdhbWUsIEhhbGYtbGlmZSwgd2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIFVTIG1pbGl0YXJ5IGZvcmNlIHN0YXJ0cyBjbGVhcmluZyBvdXQgdGhlIEJsYWNrIE1lc2EgUmVzZWFyY2ggRmFjaWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhFQ1U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhbmNlbGVkIHByb2plY3RlZCBieSBCbGl6emFyZCBFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IHRoYXQgd291bGQgYmUgbGF0ZXIgYmVjb21lIE92ZXJ3YXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "VGl0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1haW4gZW5kaW5ncyBhcmUgdGhlcmU/",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCBWOiBUaGUgUGhhbnRvbSBQYWluIHJ1bnMgb24gdGhlIEZveCBFbmdpbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugb25saW5lIGdhbWVzIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IG5hbWVkIExpbmRlbldvcmxkIGluIGl0J3MgZWFybHkgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "U2Vjb25kTGlmZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG9ueSBIYXdrJ3MgUHJvIFNrYXRlciB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMTk5OS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkZXZpY2UgYWxsb3dzIFRyYWNlciB0byBtYW5pcHVsYXRlIGhlciBvd24gdGltZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyb25hbCBBY2NlbGVyYXRvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21wYW55IGNyZWF0ZWQgYW5kIGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "QmxpenphcmQgRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiBTZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "TWFzYWhpcm8gU2FrdXJhaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIDIwMTEgVmlkZW8gR2FtZSAiTWluZWNyYWZ0Ij8=",
            "answer": "TWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGdlbnJlIGlzIHRoZSBjb250cm92ZXJzaWFsIDIwMTUgZ2FtZSAiSGF0cmVkIj8=",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ0VtIFVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBEaXNob25vcmVkIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCBhbGlhcyB0aGF0IFByaW5jZXNzIEdhcm5ldCBnb2VzIGJ5IGluIEZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgSVg/",
            "answer": "RGFnZ2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV2FyaW9XYXJlOiBTbW9vdGggTW92ZXMsIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBOT1QgYSBGb3JtPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdHNob3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgY2l0eSBpbiB0aGUgR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "U2FuIEFuZHJlYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBva8OpbW9uIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggdHlwZSBpcyBTdWRvd29vZG8sIHRoZSBJbWl0YXRpb24gUG9rw6ltb24/",
            "answer": "Um9jaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIGdhbWUgZ2V0IHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCBob3cgbXVjaCBkbyBTcGlkZXIgRG9udXRzIGNvc3QgaW4gSG90bGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "OTk5OUc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUnVuZVNjYXBlLCBvbmUgbXVzdCBjb21wbGV0ZSB0aGUgIkRyYWdvbiBTbGF5ZXIiIHF1ZXN0IGJlZm9yZSBlcXVpcHBpbmcgUnVuZSBQbGF0ZWxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhhbG8gMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1vbml0b3Igb2YgSW5zdGFsbGF0aW9uIDA1Pw==",
            "answer": "MjQwMSBQZW5pdGVudCBUYW5nZW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBuYW1lcyBpcyB0aGUgIk1lZ2EgTWFuIiBGcmFuY2hpc2Uga25vd24gYXMgaW4gSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "Um9ja21hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlRyYW5zaXN0b3IiLCAiUmVkIiBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRG90YSAyLCB3aGF0IGlzIEVhcnRoc2hha2VyJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UmFpZ29yIFN0b25laG9vZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGZyb20gdGhlIE1lZ2EgTWFuIHNlcmllcyBtYWRlIGEgc21hbGwgY2FtZW8gb24gVm9sdCBDYXRmaXNoJ3MgaW50cm9kdWN0aW9uIHNjZW5lIGluIENEIHZlcnNpb25zIG9mIE1lZ2EgTWFuIFgzPw==",
            "answer": "QXV0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gQ29ucXVlc3QsIGhvdyBtYW55IGtpbmdkb21zIG1ha2UgdXAgdGhlIHJlZ2lvbiBvZiBSYW5zZWk/",
            "answer": "MTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIGhvdyBtdWNoIGhlYWx0aCBkb2VzIFJvYWRob2cncyAiVGFrZSBhIEJyZWF0aGVyIiBhYmlsaXR5IHJlY292ZXI/",
            "answer": "MzAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkVhcnRoYm91bmQiLCBob3cgZG9lcyBvbmUgZW50ZXIgIk1hc3RlciBCZWxjaCdzIiBmYWN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "V2FpdCAzIE1pbnV0ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGluZGllIGFkdmVudHVyZSBnYW1lICJOaWdodCBpbiB0aGUgV29vZHMiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxlYyBIb2xvd2th"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHlvdSBjYW4gdXBncmFkZSB0aGUgIkFwb3RoaWNvbiBTZXJ2YW50IiBpbiB0aGUgIlNoYWRvd3MgT2YgRXZpbCIgbWFwLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZ2FtZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSAiQ29sb255IFdhcnMiIHNlcmllcyBmb3IgdGhlIFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgTGVvbiBLZW5uZWR5J3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "U2NvdHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBHZW5lcmF0aW9uIElJSSBQb2tlbW9uIHdob3NlIG5hbWUgYmVnaW5zIHdpdGggdGhlIGxldHRlciBJPw==",
            "answer": "SWxsdW1pc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBJY2UgQ2xpbWJlcnMgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgSWNlIENsaW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "UG9wbyBhbmQgTmFuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgR2VuZXJhdGlvbiAxIFBva2Vtb24gZGlkIE5PVCBoYXZlIGFuIGV2b2x1dGlvbiBpbiBHZW5lcmF0aW9uIDQ/",
            "answer": "SnlueA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkOiBQb3JzY2hlIFVubGVhc2hlZCIsIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXIgY2FuIG9ubHkgZHJpdmUgY2FycyBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZWQgYnkgUG9yc2NoZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ29EOiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUlJLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSByb2d1ZSBBLkkuIGFudGFnb25pc3Q/",
            "answer": "Q29ydnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBW4oCZcyBzdG9yeSBtb2RlPw==",
            "answer": "VG9tbXkgVmVyY2V0dGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBCaWxsJ3MgbGFzdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "T3ZlcmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU2lkIE1laWVyJ3MgQ2l2aWxpemF0aW9uIFYsIHdoaWNoIFdvcmxkIFdvbmRlciBjYW4gb25seSBiZSBidWlsdCBpbiBjaXRpZXMgb24gb3IgbmV4dCB0byBhIGRlc2VydD8=",
            "answer": "UGV0cmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGl2aW5pdHk6IE9yaWdpbmFsIFNpbiBJSSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc2tlbGV0YWwgb3JpZ2luIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "RmFuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhIFRldHJpcyBwaWVjZSBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGV0cm9taW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIkpldHBhY2sgSm95cmlkZSIgd2FzIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgIlJlZGJyaWNrIFN0dWRpb3MiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWluZWNyYWZ0IHdhc27igJl0IHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBuYW1lIHRvIE1pbmVjcmFmdC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29jY2VyIHBsYXllciBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBvbiB0aGUgY292ZXIgb2YgRUEgU3BvcnQncyBGSUZBIDE4Pw==",
            "answer": "Q3Jpc3RpYW5vIFJvbmFsZG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgeW91IHBsYXkgYXMgaW4gWXVtZSBOaWtraT8=",
            "answer": "TWFkb3RzdWtp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlBvc3RhbCAyIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBQb3N0YWwgRHVkZSdzIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbXA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgIlNvbmljIFRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgbWFrZSBoaXMgZmlyc3QgYXBwZWFyYW5jZSBpbj8=",
            "answer": "UmFkIE1vYmlsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiAiQXJraGFtIiBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "QXJraGFtIEFzeWx1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsIDIsIHRoZSBpY29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdMYURPUyBpcyB0dXJuZWQgaW50bzo=",
            "answer": "QSBwb3RhdG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYWN0b3JzIGRpZCBub3Qgdm9pY2UgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIlNhaW50cyBSb3c6IFRoZSBUaGlyZCI/",
            "answer": "Um9uIEplcmVteQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgMzogU25ha2UgRWF0ZXIiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIG9uIFNoYWRvdyBNb3NlcyBJc2xhbmQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRmFsbG91dCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgTWFyaW8gd2FzIHZvaWNlZCBieSBDaGFybGVzIE1hcnRpbmV0Pw==",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8ncyBHYW1lIEdhbGxlcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBjaXR5IGluIHRoZSBkeXN0b3BpYSBhbHRlcm5hdGUgZnV0dXJlIG9mIEhhbGYtTGlmZSAyIGRvIHlvdSBmaXJzdCBzdGFydCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2l0eSAxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSGFsZi1MaWZlIDIsIGlmIHlvdSBwbGF5IHRoZSB6b21iaWVzJyBzcGVlY2ggaW4gcmV2ZXJzZSwgdGhleSBhY3R1YWxseSBzcGVhayBjb2hlcmVudCBFbmdsaXNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSBjdXQgZW5lbXkgZnJvbSAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIDIiPw==",
            "answer": "SHlkcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgZmFjdGlvbiBpbmNsdWRlZCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Qk9QRQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Um9ja2V0IExlYWd1ZSBpcyBhIGdhbWUgd2hpY2ggZmVhdHVyZXMuLg==",
            "answer": "Q2Fycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21wYW55IGRldmVsb3BzIHRoZSBSb2NrIEJhbmQgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHJoeXRobSBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "SGFybW9uaXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgaGFuZGhlbGQgZ2FtZSBkZXZpY2U/",
            "answer": "TWF0dGVsIEF1dG8gUmFjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCBUYWlscycgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIE1pbGVzIFByb3dlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgQW5ubyBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgIkVjbyBCYWxhbmNlIiBnYW1lcGxheSBtZWNoYW5pYz8=",
            "answer": "QW5ubyAyMDcw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IE1NT1JQRyB0byBwb3B1bGFyaXplIHRoZSBnZW5yZT8=",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hIE9ubGluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24gU3VuIGFuZCBNb29uLCBhIG1hbGUgU2FsYW5kaXQgY2FuIGV2b2x2ZSB0byBhIFNhbGF6emxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFNvbGlkIFNuYWtlIHVzZSB0byBoaWRlIGhpbXNlbGYgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "Q2FyZGJvYXJkIEJveA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE92ZXJ3YXRjaCdzIGxvcmUsIHdobyB3YXMgb25jZSBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgRGVhZGxvY2sgR2FuZz8=",
            "answer": "TWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHdlYXBvbiBwYWNrIGZvciAiUEFZREFZIDIiPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdhZ2UgV2VhcG9uIFBhY2sgIzE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpcyBOT1QgcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgU2NpZW5jZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUgc2VyaWVzIGJ5IDVwYi4gYW5kIE5pdHJvcGx1cz8=",
            "answer": "T2NjdWx0aWM7IE5pbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhlYXJ0aHN0b25lIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmVzdCByYW5rIHBvc3NpYmxlPw==",
            "answer": "UmFuayAxIExlZ2VuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYSBmcmFuY2hpc2Ugd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIEphcGFuIGJlZm9yZSBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVGhlIE1pbmlzaCBDYXA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIHRoZSB0cmFjayBwbGF5ZWQgYnkgdGhlIERlY29yYXRlZCBNdXNpYyBCb3ggaXMgbmFtZWQgIkF0bGFzIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgbGV2ZWwgaW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogV29ybGQgYXQgV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "U2VtcGVyIEZp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiTW9vbiIsIHRoZXJlIGlzIGEgc2Vjb25kYXJ5IGNhbGxlZCB0aGUgUUVELiBXaGF0IGRvZXMgUUVEIHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "answer": "UXVhbnR1bSBFbnRhbmdsZW1lbnQgRGV2aWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQQVlEQVkiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIga25vd24gYXMgIkRhbGxhcyI/",
            "answer": "TmF0aGFuIFN0ZWVsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xvcnMgZG9lcyB0aGUgWm9tYmllIGV5ZXMgZ2xvdyBpbiB0aGUgIk51a2V0b3duIiBtYXAgaW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJIiBab21iaWVzIG1vZGU/",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93IGFuZCBCbHVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiSnVzdCBDYXVzZSAzIj8=",
            "answer": "UmljbyBSb2RyaWd1ZXo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFZhbHZlIENvcnBvcmF0aW9uIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0IDI0LCAxOTk2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiBHcmFuZCBUaGVmdCBBdXRvIFY/",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDE3LCAyMDEz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBva8OpbW9uIFN1biBhbmQgTW9vbiIsIFRlYW0gU2t1bGwgdG9vayBvdmVyIHdoaWNoIHRvd24/",
            "answer": "UG8gVG93bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtaWxpdGFyeSByYW5rIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCAiTm9tYWQiIGluICJDcnlzaXMiPw==",
            "answer": "Rmlyc3QgTGlldXRlbmFudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nJ3Mgb3JpZ2luYWwgaHVtYW4gZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "TWFkb25uYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFua3ksIEZ1bmt5LCBhbmQgQ2h1bmt5IGFyZSBhbGwgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBzZXJpZXMgb3duZWQgYnkgTmludGVuZG8/",
            "answer": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbGYtTGlmZSB1bml2ZXJzZSwgdGhlIEJsYWNrIE1lc2EgUmVzZWFyY2ggRmFjaWxpdHkgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBVUyBzdGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IE1leGljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2FzLCB1cG9uIHN0YXJ0aW5nIGVhY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb3VyIGNhbXBhaWduIERMQ3MsIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVtIGRvZXMgbm90IGhhdmUgYSB3YXJuaW5nIHNjcmVlbi9yZWNvbW1lbmRlZCBsZXZlbD8g",
            "answer": "SG9uZXN0IEhlYXJ0cyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYW1waW9ucyBmcm9tIHRoZSBNT0JBICdMZWFndWUgb2YgTGVnZW5kcycgaXMgTk9UIGEgWW9yZGxlPw==",
            "answer": "QW5uaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsYXN0IGJvc3MgaW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzJyBEZW1vbnRvd2VyIG1pbmlnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsb29kIFRoaWVm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlNwbGF0b29uIiwgdGhlIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgd2VyZSBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGdvaW5nIHRvIGJlIHJhYmJpdHMgaW5zdGVhZCBvZiBzcXVpZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtYWlubHkgZmF2b3JlZCByaWZsZSBpcyB1c2VkIGJ5IHRoZSBUZXJyb3Jpc3RzIGluIENvdW50ZXIgU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QUstNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFydG5lcnMgY2FuIHlvdSBvYnRhaW4gaW4gUGFwZXIgTWFyaW86IFRoZSBUaG91c2FuZC1ZZWFyIERvb3I/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgMiIsIHdoaWNoIHZpcnVzIHdhcyBXaWxsaWFtIEJpcmtpbiBtdXRhdGVkIGJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "Ry1WaXJ1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgamVkaSB0aGF0IFN0YXJraWxsZXIgaGFkIHRvIGtpbGwgaW4gU3RhciBXYXJzOiBUaGUgRm9yY2UgVW5sZWFzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "UmFobSBLb3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB3cml0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSI/",
            "answer": "TWFyYyBMYWlkbGF3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYW4gb2ZmaWNpYWwgZ2FtZSBpbiBOaW50ZW5kbydzIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "U3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gQ3J1c2FkZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFjZSBBdHRvcm5leSB0cmlsb2d5IHdhcyBzdXBwb3NlIHRvIGVuZCB3aXRoICJQaG9lbml4IFdyaWdodDogQWNlIEF0dG9ybmV5IOKIkiBUcmlhbHMgYW5kIFRyaWJ1bGF0aW9ucyIgYXMgaXRzIGZpbmFsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2VhcG9ucyBpcyBOT1QgYXZhaWxhYmxlIHRvIHRoZSBUZXJyb3Jpc3QgdGVhbSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSwgIkNvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlIj8=",
            "answer": "U0NBUi0yMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRvbWIgUmFpZGVyIiBpY29uIExhcmEgQ3JvZnQgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgY2FsbGVkLi4u",
            "answer": "TGF1cmEgQ3J1eg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgVkEtMTEgSEFMTC1BOiBDeWJlcnB1bmsgQmFydGVuZGVyIEFjdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "SmlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggTWFyaW8gZ2FtZSBkaWQgdGhlIE1lZ2EgTXVzaHJvb20gbWFrZSBpdHMgZGVidXQ/",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8gUGFydHkgNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGhlcm8gTWNDcmVlJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmVzc2UgTWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IHBsYXkgdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFJQRyBhbmQgbmFwIGluIGEgcmVudGVkIGhvdGVsIHJvb20sIHlvdSB3aWxsIHdha2UgdXAgbmV4dCB0byB3aGF0IGZhbWlsaWFyIGxvb2tpbmcgY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "TGluaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAoMjAwNik/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWlycm9yJ3MgRWRnZSBDYXRhbHlzdCB0YWtlcyBwbGFjZSBpbiB0aGUgQ2l0eSBvZi4uLj8=",
            "answer": "R2xhc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgaXMgb24gTGluaydzIHBhamFtYXMgaW4gVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVGhlIFdpbmQgV2FrZXI/",
            "answer": "Q3Jhd2Zpc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiQW50aWNoYW1iZXIiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzOiBCaXJ0aCBieSBTbGVlcD8=",
            "answer": "SWduaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBFbGl0ZSBGb3VyIG1lbWJlcnMgZnJvbSB0aGUgNnRoIEdlbmVyYXRpb24gb2YgUG9rw6ltb24gd2FzIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIFRlYW0gRmxhcmU/",
            "answer": "TWFsdmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXMgYWxtb3N0IGFkZGVkIGludG8gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gTWVsZWUsIGJ1dCBub3QgaW5jbHVkZWQgYXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgd2FzIHRvbyBmYXIgaW4gZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "U29saWQgU25ha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lICJMdWlnaSdzIE1hbnNpb24iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IGxldHRlciB0byBub3QgYXBwZWFyIHdpdGggYSBwYWlyIG9mIGV5ZXMgaW4gaXQ/",
            "answer": "cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGlzdG9ucyB3ZXJlIGFkZGVkIHRvIE1pbmVjcmFmdCBpbiBCZXRhIDEuNS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24sIEJ1bGJhc2F1ciBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBzdGFydGVyIHBva2Vtb24gdGhhdCBpcyBhIEdyYXNzL1BvaXNvbiB0eXBlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gZm9yIE5pbnRlbmRvIDNEUyBhbmQgTmludGVuZG8gV2lpIFUsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIHNpeHRoIGZpZ2h0ZXIgdG8gYmUgYWRkZWQgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUgcG9zdC1sYXVuY2g/",
            "answer": "Q29ycmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBoYXMgSmVubmlmZXIgVGF5bG9yIE5PVCB2b2ljZWQ/",
            "answer": "U2FyYWggS2VycmlnYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Ik1pbmVjcmFmdCIgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGZyb20gYmV0YSBpbiAyMDExIGR1cmluZyBhIGNvbnZlbnRpb24gaGVsZCBpbiB3aGljaCBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "TGFzIFZlZ2Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXBlcnR1cmUgU2NpZW5jZSBDRU8gQ2F2ZSBKb2huc29uIGlzIHZvaWNlZCBieSB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBhY3Rvcj8=",
            "answer": "Si5LLiBTaW1tb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGVuZ2luZSBkb2VzIHRoZSB2aWRlb2dhbWUgUXVha2UgMiBydW4gaW4/",
            "answer": "aUQgVGVjaCAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYnJvd3NlciBnYW1lIEthbnRhaSBDb2xsZWN0aW9uIGhlYXZpbHkgaW5zcGlyZWQgYnk/",
            "answer": "U2Vjb25kIFdvcmxkIFdhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIERPT00gKDE5OTMpIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2hlYXQgY29kZT8=",
            "answer": "SURDTElQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxvIiBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgYWxpZW5zIGh1bWFucyByZWZlciB0byBhcyAiR3J1bnRzIj8=",
            "answer": "VW5nZ295"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZGlmZmVyZW50IG5vdGVzIGlzIHRoZSB0dW5lLCAiU29uZyBvZiBIZWFsaW5nIiwgY29tcHJpc2VkIG9mIGluICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhOiBNYWpvcmEncyBNYXNrIj8=",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgcHVibGlzaGVyICJVYmlzb2Z0IiBmb3VuZGVkID8=",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggMTk4Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCdzIG9wZW5pbmcgY3V0c2NlbmUgc2hvd3MgIlJpY2h0b2ZlbiIga2lsbGluZyBhbm90aGVyIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgaGltc2VsZj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdpYW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IGNvbXBvc2VkIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBzb3VuZHRyYWNrIGZvciAiV2F0Y2ggRG9ncyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "SHVkc29uIE1vaGF3a2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgZ3JvdXAgZG9lcyBEb2N0b3IgTWF4aXMgd29yayBmb3I/",
            "answer": "R3JvdXAgOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVsbHRhbGUgR2FtZXMnICJUaGUgV2Fsa2luZyBEZWFkOiBTZWFzb24gT25lIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIENsZW1lbnRpbmUncyBmYXRoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbG8gc2VyaWVzLCB3aGljaCBlcmEgb2YgU1BBUlRBTiBpcyBNYXN0ZXIgQ2hpZWY/IA==",
            "answer": "U1BBUlRBTi1JSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgU2FucyBhbmQgUGFweXJ1cyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciBpbiAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIj8=",
            "answer": "Rm9udHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIE5PVCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiAiTmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IEhvdCBQdXJzdWl0IDIiPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIE1SMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBoZW9uaXggV3JpZ2h0OiBBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHdoaWNoIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyB0aGUgRGlzdHJpY3QgQ2hpZWYgb2YgUG9saWNlPw==",
            "answer": "RGFtb24gR2FudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2hhbmcgVHN1bmcgaXMgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gTW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCBYTC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiwgdGhlIGFiaWxpdHkgV29uZGVyIEd1YXJkIGlzIGV4Y2x1c2l2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBQb2tlbW9uPyA=",
            "answer": "U2hlZGluamEg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGVyZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNoYXJhY3RlciBNYXJpbyBkZXJpdmUgaGlzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIGxhbmRsb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR2VvbWV0cnkgRGFzaCwgd2hhdCBpcyBsZXZlbCAxMz8=",
            "answer": "RWxlY3Ryb21hbiBBZHZlbnR1cmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5sb2NrYWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gRm9yIFdpaSBVIGFuZCAzRFMgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSBmb3VnaHQgdG8gYmUgdW5sb2NrZWQ/",
            "answer": "TWlpIEZpZ2h0ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVHJhY2tNYW5pYSBlbnZpcm9ubWVudHMgd2FzIE5PVCBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "QmF5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjcmVhdGVkIGFuZCBkaXJlY3RlZCB0aGUgS2F0YW1hcmkgRGFtYWN5IHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "S2VpdGEgVGFrYWhhc2hp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vc3QgZ3JhcGhpY2FsbHkgdmlvbGVudCBnYW1lIHRvIHByZWNlZGUgdGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBFU1JCIChFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IFNvZnR3YXJlIFJhdGluZyBCb2FyZCkgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "TW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1lbWJlcnMgZG9lcyBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gWElJSSBoYXZlIGluIHRvdGFsPw==",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgU3RhciBTcGlyaXRzIGRvIHlvdSByZXNjdWUgaW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIDY0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlBhcGVyIE1hcmlvIj8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgNjQiLCBXYWx1aWdpIGlzIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWFpbiBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gViI/",
            "answer": "TGFtYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdm9pY2UgYWN0b3IgZm9yIFNuYWtlIGluIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgVjogVGhlIFBoYW50b20gUGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "S2llZmVyIFN1dGhlcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBWLCB3aGF0IHdhcyBNaWNoYWVsIERlIFNhbnRhJ3MgZm9ybWVyIHN1cm5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VG93bmxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb3JkZXIgZG8geW91IG5lZWQgdG8gaGl0IHNvbWUgRGVrdSBTY3J1YnMgdG8gb3BlbiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgYm9zcyBkb29yIGluICJPY2FyaW5hIG9mIFRpbWUiPw==",
            "answer": "MiwgMywgMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdmlydXMgaW4gIk1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgMSI/",
            "answer": "Rk9YRElF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHZpcnVzLCBhcyBkZXNpZ25hdGVkIGJ5IENFREEsIHRoYXQgY2F1c2VzIG1vc3QgaHVtYW5zIHRvIHR1cm4gaW50byB0aGUgSW5mZWN0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gRmx1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyLCB3aGljaCBjbGFzcyB3aWVsZHMgYSBzaG90Z3VuPw==",
            "answer": "RXZlcnlvbmUgTGlzdGVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWluZWNyYWZ0IGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIHRvIHRoZSBwdWJsaWM/",
            "answer": "TWF5IDE3dGgsIDIwMDk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMDUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5IDI6IEJpZyBSZWQgT25lIiBpcyBub3QgYXZhaWxhYmxlIG9uIFBDLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBNeXN0aWMgaW4gUG9rw6ltb24gR28/",
            "answer": "QmxhbmNoZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAyMDA1IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgS2lsbGVyNz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgU21pdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGVzdGlueSwgd2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBQZXRlciBEaW5rbGFnZSBpbiB2b2ljaW5nIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCdzICJHaG9zdCI/",
            "answer": "Tm9sYW4gTm9ydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbG8gc2VyaWVzLCB3aGF0IGZsZWV0IHdhcyBUaGVsICdWYWRhbSBzdXByZW1lIGNvbW1hbmRlciBvZiBiZWZvcmUgYmVpbmcgYnJhbmRlZCBhbiBBcmJpdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "RmxlZXQgb2YgUGFydGljdWxhciBKdXN0aWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUG9rw6ltb24gY2Fubm90IGxlYXJuIFN1cmY/",
            "answer": "QXJib2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcmVndWxhciBTdW5rZW4gU2VhIFNjcm9sbHMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluICJTcGxhdG9vbiI/",
            "answer": "Mjc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZXNlIG1hcHMgd2VyZSBpbiAiVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgU2l4IFNpZWdlIiBvbiBpdHMgaW5pdGlhbCByZWxlYXNlOiBIb3VzZSwgQ2x1YmhvdXNlLCBCb3JkZXIsIENvbnN1bGF0ZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugb3BlcmF0b3JzIGZyb20gIlRvbSBDbGFuY3kncyBSYWluYm93IFNpeCBTaWVnZSIgaGFzIHRoZSBhYmlsaXR5IHRvIGRhbWFnZSByZWluZm9yY2VkIHdhbGxzPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9yZGFuICJUaGVybWl0ZSIgVHJhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFbmdsaXNoIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBTb3JhIGZyb20gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SGFsZXkgSm9lbCBPc21lbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFEQU0gY29sbGVjdGVycyBpbiB0aGUgQmlvc2hvY2sgc2VyaWVzIGFyZSBrbm93biBhcyBMaXR0bGUgU2lzdGVycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIk1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIiBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgIkluc2VjdCBHbGFpdmUiIHdlYXBvbj8=",
            "answer": "TW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVsYXRpb25zaGlwIGJldHdlZW4gQXBvbGxvIEp1c3RpY2UgYW5kIFRydWN5IFdyaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGhleSdyZSBoYWxmLXNpYmxpbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIgbWFwIGludHJvZHVjZWQgdGhlICJTdGFmZnMgT2YgVGhlIEFuY2llbnRzIj8=",
            "answer": "T3JpZ2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsICJSaWNodG9mZW4iIGlzIGluIHBvc3Nlc3Npb24gb2YgdHdvIGZpbGxlZCBibG9vZCB2aWFscyBiZWxvbmdpbmcgdG8gd2hvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsIERlTHVjYSBhbmQgRmlubiBPJ0xlYXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbWFsbCBkb2VzICJEZWFkIFJpc2luZyIgdGFrZSBwbGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGFtZXR0ZSBQYXJrdmlldyBNYWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hZ2lja2EiLCB3aGljaCB0d28gZWxlbWVudHMgYXJlIGNvbWJpbmVkIHRvIGNhc3QgdGhlIHNwZWxsLCAiTnVsbGlmeSI/",
            "answer": "QXJjYW5lICsgU2hpZWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWN0aXZpc2lvbiBjcmVhdGVkIEJhdHRsZWZpZWxkIDEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgOHRoIGluc3RhbGxtZW50IGluIHRoZSBGaXJlIEVtYmxlbSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNhY3JlZCBTdG9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsLCB3aGF0IGNvbG9yIGlzIHRoZSBNb3JhbGl0eSBDb3JlPw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQ2l0eSBpbiBTYWludHMgUm93IFRoZSBUaGlyZD8=",
            "answer": "U3RlZWxwb3J0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3b24gdGhlICJHYW1lcyBmb3IgSW1wYWN0IiBhd2FyZCBpbiBUaGUgR2FtZSBBd2FyZHMgMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "TGlmZSBpcyBTdHJhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgNyIgaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZpcnN0LXBlcnNvbiBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbWFzY290IG9mIFNFR0EgYmVmb3JlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciPw==",
            "answer": "QWxleCBLaWRk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgZGlkIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIiBydW4gb24/",
            "answer": "R29sZFNyYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SnVzdCBDYXVzZSAyIHdhcyBtYWlubHkgc2V0IGluIHdoYXQgZmljdGlvbmFsIFNvdXRoZWFzdCBBc2lhbiBpc2xhbmQgY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuYXU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hbm4gQ28uIFN0b3JlIGZyb20gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIGhhcyB0aGUgc2xvZ2FuICJXZSBoaXJlIG1lcmNlbmFyaWVzIGFuZCBnZXQgaW4gZmlnaHRzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFsZi1MaWZlIGJ5IFZhbHZlIHVzZXMgdGhlIEdvbGRTcmMgZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmUsIHdoaWNoIGlzIGEgaGlnaGx5IG1vZGlmaWVkIHZlcnNpb24gb2Ygd2hhdCBlbmdpbmU/",
            "answer": "UXVha2UgRW5naW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBmaXJzdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNvbnNvbGU/",
            "answer": "TWFnbmF2b3ggT2R5c3NleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNpdHkgb2YgUm9ja3BvcnQgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2aWRlbyBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "TmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiB0aGVtZSBzb25nIG9mICJTb25pYyBBZHZlbnR1cmUgMiI/",
            "answer": "TGl2ZSBhbmQgTGVhcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgQ2hhb3MgRW1lcmFsZHMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiB1bml2ZXJzZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMidzIGZpY3Rpb25hbCBjb21wYW55ICJNYW5uIENvIj8=",
            "answer": "WmVwaGVuaWFoIE1hbm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoaWNoIHF1b3RlIGRvZXMgdGhlIGhlcm8gIk1jQ3JlZSIgTk9UIHNheSB1cG9uIHVzaW5nIGhpcyBmbGFzaGJhbmcgYWJpbGl0eT8=",
            "answer": "IllvdSBkb25lPyI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc291bHMgZ2FtZSB3YXMgbm90IGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IEhpZGV0YWthIE1peWF6YWtpPw==",
            "answer": "RGFyayBTb3VscyAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBWYWxvciBpbiBQb2vDqW1vbiBHbz8=",
            "answer": "Q2FuZGVsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG91aG91OiBFbWJvZGltZW50IG9mIFNjYXJsZXQgRGV2aWwsIHdoYXQgc29uZyBwbGF5cyBkdXJpbmcgRmxhbmRyZSBTY2FybGV0J3MgYm9zcyBmaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VS5OLiBPd2VuIFdhcyBIZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZGlmZmVyZW50bHkgc2hhcGVkIFRldHJpcyBwaWVjZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBWSSB3YXMgb3JpZ2luYWxseSByZWxlYXNlZCBvdXRzaWRlIEphcGFuIHVuZGVyIHdoYXQgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYViByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMjl0aCwgMjAxNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdG90YWwgbW9uc3RlcnMgYXBwZWFyIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIEdlbmVyYXRpb25zPw==",
            "answer": "MTA1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIERPT00gZ2FtZXMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgZGVtb25zIGlzIGEgcmVjb2xvciBvZiB0aGUgQmFyb24gb2YgSGVsbCwgYnV0IGlzIHdlYWtlciB0aGFuIHRoZSBCYXJvbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVsbCBLbmlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBsYXN0IGxldmVsIHdoZXJlIHlvdSBwbGF5IGFzIGFuIEFtZXJpY2FuIHNvbGRpZXI/",
            "answer": "RmVzdHVuZyBSZWNvZ25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIGhhZCBhIHNwZWNpYWwgZXZlbnQgaG9zdGVkIGluIHRoZSBwb3B1bGFyIE1NT1JQRyBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhJVjogQSBSZWFsbSBSZWJvcm4/",
            "answer": "WW8ta2FpIFdhdGNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRWxpdGUgRm91ciBtZW1iZXIgZnJvbSB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBvZiBQb2vDqW1vbiBiZWNhbWUgdGhlIGNoYW1waW9uIGluIHRoZSBuZXh0IGdlbmVyYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "TGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBzZXJpZXMgb2YgZ2FtZXMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGZvdW5kZXIgb2YgQXBlcnR1cmUgU2NpZW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2F2ZSBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIGdhbWUgd2FzIGZvciB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gV2lpPw==",
            "answer": "QW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nOiBDaXR5IEZvbGs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2x1YiBQZW5ndWluIGxhdW5jaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNCwgMjAwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCB0byBiZSBkaXJlY3RlZCBieSBKYXNvbiBCbHVuZGVsbD8=",
            "answer": "TW9iIE9mIFRoZSBEZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFNlYXNvbiBPbmUgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwIG9mICJMZWFndWUgb2YgTGVnZW5kcyIsIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGFjaGlldmFibGUgcmFuayB3YXMgRGlhbW9uZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ3J5cHQgb2YgdGhlIE5lY3JvRGFuY2VyICgyMDE1KSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGFzIGEgc291bmR0cmFjayBieSBKYWtlICJWaXJ0IiBLYXVmbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "VW5jbGUgRWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcmltYXJ5IGZlbWFsZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFZJSUk/",
            "answer": "SGVhcnRpbGx5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGFsa2luZyBjYXQgaW4gUGVyc29uYSA1Pw==",
            "answer": "TW9yZ2FuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU29uaWMgRm9yY2VzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHdhcyBub3QgZnJvbSBhIHByZXZpb3VzIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "SW5maW5pdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9kICJDcnkgb2YgRmVhciIgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIG9mPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZi1MaWZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIFNvcmEncyBOb2JvZHkgaW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHM/",
            "answer": "Um94YXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFBhcmFkb3ggSW50ZXJhY3RpdmUgZ2FtZSAiU3RlbGxhcmlzIiB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAxNi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZnJhbmNoaXNlICJIYWxvIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgVU5TQydzIG1haW4gb3Bwb3NpbmcgZmFjdGlvbiBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIENvdmVuYW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2V0cyBvZiBncmFuZG1hc3RlciB3aXRjaGVyIGdlYXIgYXJlIGluIFRoZSBXaXRjaGVyIDMncyBCbG9vZCBhbmQgV2luZSBETEM/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkJvcmRlcmxhbmRzIj8=",
            "answer": "R2VhcmJveCBTb2Z0d2FyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBnaXZlbiB0byBTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2cgNCBkdXJpbmcgaXRzIGRldmVsb3BtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "UHJvamVjdCBOZWVkbGVtb3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdmlydXMgdGhhdCBpbmZlY3RlZCBOZXcgWW9yayBpbiBUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgVGhlIERpdmlzaW9uPw==",
            "answer": "RG9sbGFyIEZsdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIHdobyB3YXMgTWV0dGF0b24ncyBjcmVhdG9yPw==",
            "answer": "QWxwaHlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBtb2RlbCBmb3IgSGFsZi1MaWZlJ3MgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QgR29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4/",
            "answer": "SXZhbiB0aGUgU3BhY2UgQmlrZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpbiAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIiBjYW4gdGhlIHBsYXllciBOT1QgZ28gb24gYSBkYXRlIHdpdGg/",
            "answer": "VG9yaWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiAiTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCAzIj8=",
            "answer": "TmFrZWQgU25ha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlrbyBCZWxsaWMgaXMgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gSVYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGludGVyYWN0aXZlIG1vdmllIHZpZGVvIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "QXN0cm9uIEJlbHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0d28gY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lIFVuZGVydGFsZSBhcmUgbmV2ZXIgaW4gYSByZWxhdGlvbnNoaXAgb3Igbm90IHJlbGF0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "RnJpc2sgJiBDaGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIiByZXZlYWxlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFNuaXBlcidzIFNNRyBpbiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIsIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGludGVuZGVkIHRvIGJlIHRoZSBTY291dCdzIHByaW1hcnkgd2VhcG9uLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlN0YXJib3VuZCI/",
            "answer": "RmVuZXJveA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2hhcHRlciAxIG9mIHRoZSBTb3VyY2UgRW5naW5lIG1vZCAiVW5kZXJoZWxsIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDFzdCwgMjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KSwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gYW50YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmVuY2UgIlJhem9yIiBDYWxsYWhhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5hdGlvbmFsIFBva2VkZXggd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgaXMgUG9yeWdvbi1aPw==",
            "answer": "NDc0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGh1bnRlciBhcnRzIGFyZSBleGNsdXNpdmUgdG8gdGhlIExvbmdzd29yZD8=",
            "answer": "VW5oaW5nZWQgU3Bpcml0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgZG9lcyBOT1QgcGxheSBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIFJ1aW5zIHNlZ21lbnRzIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE1IGdhbWUgIlVuZGVydGFsZSI/",
            "answer": "QW5vdGhlciBNZWRpdW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGlzIE5PVCBhIGZlbWFsZSBtYXJyaWFnZSBjYW5kaWRhdGUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXk/",
            "answer": "Q2Fyb2xpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGVhZCBieSBEYXlsaWdodCwgdGhlIGtpbGxlciBNaWNoYWVsIE15ZXJzIGlzIHJlZmVyZWQgdG8gYXMgIlRoZSBTaGFwZSIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaXRlbSByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBzdW1tb24gdGhlIGJvc3MgRHVrZSBGaXNocm9uIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIFRlcnJhcmlhPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZmZsZSBXb3Jt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gZm9yIE5pbnRlbmRvIDNEUyBhbmQgV2lpIFU/",
            "answer": "NTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgNC1hcm1lZCBDaGFvcyBXaXRjaCBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDE2IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkJhdHRsZWJvcm4iPw==",
            "answer": "T3JlbmRp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhhbG8iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwbGFuZXQgd2hpY2ggSW5zdGFsbGF0aW9uIDA0IG9yYml0cz8=",
            "answer": "VGhyZXNob2xk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlICMxIHNlbGxpbmcgZ2FtZSBvbiBTdGVhbSBieSByZXZlbnVlIGluIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "U2lkIE1laWVyJ3MgQ2l2aWxpemF0aW9uIFZJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdW5pcXVlIGl0ZW1zIGRvZXMgIkJvcmRlcmxhbmRzIDIiIGNsYWltIHRvIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "ODcgQmF6aWxsaW9uIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYW5kIHB1Ymxpc2hlZCBHYW1lIERldiBUeWNvb24/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW5oZWFydCBHYW1lcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIHBsYXllciBwbGF5IGFzIGluIHRoZSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lICJCYXN0aW9uIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtpZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QncyBmaXJzdCBQZXJzb25hIGluICJQZXJzb25hIDUiPw==",
            "answer": "QXJzZW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsLCB3aGF0IGNvbG9yIGlzIHRoZSBJbnRlbGxpZ2VuY2UgQ29yZT8=",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGlzIE5PVCBhbiBvZmZpY2lhbCBtYXAgaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmU/",
            "answer": "ZGVfc2Vhc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBVQkFUVExFR1JPVU5EUyIgd2hpY2ggYW1tbyB0eXBlIGRvZXMgdGhlIE0yNCB1c2U/",
            "answer": "Ny42Mm1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIllvISBOb2lkIDIsIiBUaGUgTm9pZCBjYW4gcGVyZm9ybSB3aGF0IHNwZWNpYWwgbW92ZT8=",
            "answer": "RGFi"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwiLCBvbmx5IENocmlzIGhhcyBhY2Nlc3MgdG8gdGhlIGdyZW5hZGUgbGF1bmNoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkdhbGFnYSIgd2FzIGEgc2VxdWVsIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "R2FsYXhpYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIGZyb20gIlNwbGF0b29uIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEluZGllIEdhbWUgRGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgU3R1ZGlvIENpbmcsIGRldmVsb3BlcnMgb2YgSG90ZWwgRHVzayBhbmQgTGFzdCBXaW5kb3csIHdlbnQgYmFua3J1cHQgb24gTWFyY2ggMXN0LCAyMDEwLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIG1hZGUgR2FycnkncyBNb2Q/",
            "answer": "R2FycnkgTmV3bWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBzaGlwIHVzZWQgYnkgQ29tbWFuZGVyIFNoZXBhcmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IEZyYW5jaGlzZSBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "Tm9ybWFuZHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlVuZGVydGFsZSIgaXMgYW4gUlBHIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgVG9ieSBGb3ggYW5kIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDIwMTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIiBmb3IgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcywgd2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgaW5wdXQgaW4gdGhlIHNvdW5kIHRlc3Qgc2NyZWVuIHRvIGFjY2VzcyB0aGUgc2VjcmV0IGxldmVsIHNlbGVjdD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlYWQgUHJvZ3JhbW1lcidzIGJpcnRoZGF5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY2xhc3NlcyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkhhbGYtTGlmZSAyIiBydW5zIG9uIHRoZSBTb3VyY2UgRW5naW5lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDNEIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "T2NhcmluYSBvZiBUaW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHRoZSAiQmlsbCdzIEhhdCIgaXMgYSByZWZlcmVuY2UgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkRvdGEgMiIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIHRoZSBlYXJseSBwcm90b3R5cGVzIG9mIHRoZSBTZWdhIERyZWFtY2FzdCBjb250cm9sbGVyIHJlc2VtYmxlZCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "VGVsZXZpc2lvbiBSZW1vdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCBoYXZpbmcgYSAiRnVuIFZhbHVlIiBzZXQgdG8gNTYtNTcgd2lsbCBwbGF5IHRoZSAiV3JvbmcgTnVtYmVyIFNvbmcgQ2FsbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dCA0LCB3aGljaCB0eXBlIG9mIHBvd2VyIGFybW9yIGlzIGZpcnN0IGVuY291bnRlcmVkIGluIHRoZSBlYXJseSBtaXNzaW9uICJXaGVuIEZyZWVkb20gQ2FsbHMiIGluIGEgY3Jhc2hlZCBWZXJ0aWJpcmQ/",
            "answer": "VC00NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvZ2FtZSBCdWxseSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QncyBsYXN0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SG9wa2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2VhcG9uIGNsYXNzZXMgRE8gTk9UIGFwcGVhciBpbiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "Qm93IA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlN1Ym5hdXRpY2EiLCBhICJDYXZlIENyYXdsZXIiIHdpbGwgYXR0YWNrIHlvdS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgZXZlciByZWxlYXNlZCB0aGF0IHJhbiBvbiB0aGUgU291cmNlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IFNvdXJjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW5hIHdhcyBhZGRlZCBhcyBhIG5ldyBoZXJvIGZvciB0aGUgZ2FtZSBPdmVyd2F0Y2ggb24gSnVseSAxOXRoLCAyMDE2Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24sIEFyYm9rIGV2b2x2ZXMgaW50byBTZXZpcGVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgRWxpemEgIkFzaCIgQ29oZW4gZnJvbSAiVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgU2l4IFNpZWdlIiBib3JuIGluPw==",
            "answer": "SXNyYWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgTWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24/",
            "answer": "RHdhcmYgRm9ydHJlc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIERhbmdhbnJvbnBhIDI6IEdvb2RieWUgRGVzcGFpcj8=",
            "answer": "SGFqaW1lIEhpbmF0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmxvY2tzIGluICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiIGhhcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IGJsYXN0IHJlc2lzdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "U2FuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFpvbWJpZXMgbW9kZSBvZiAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSAiUGFjay1BLVB1bmNoZWQiIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgdGhlICJHYWxpbCIgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGFtZW50YXRpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgIkZseSBUcmFwIiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnPw==",
            "answer": "RGVyIFJpZXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBXaXRuZXNzIiwgaG93IG1hbnkgbGFzZXJzIG11c3QgYmUgYWN0aXZhdGVkIHRvIGdldCBpbnRvIHRoZSBtb3VudGFpbiBhcmVhPw==",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2VhcG9uIHRoYXQgd2FzIGN1dCBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lICJIYWxmIExpZmUgMiIgd2FzIGdvaW5nIHRvIHJlcGxhY2UgdGhlIGNyb3diYXI/",
            "answer": "SWNlIEF4ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB2aWN0aW0gbWVudGlvbmVkIGluIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgS0ctOCBpbmNpZGVudCwgaW4gQWNlIGF0dG9ybmV5IEludmVzdGlnYXRpb25zLCBDYXNlIDQ/",
            "answer": "RGVpZCBNYW5u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlVudGlsIERhd24iIEVtaWx5IGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlciB3aG8gY2FuIGJlIGtpbGxlZCBieSBhbm90aGVyIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBkaXJlY3RseS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmV0cm8gdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgZmlyc3Q/",
            "answer": "U3BhY2UgSW52YWRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgUG9rZW1vbiBHTyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "SnVseSA2dGgsIDIwMTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRW50ZXIgdGhlIEd1bmdlb24sIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdpemFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgTk9UIGdldCBmaW5hbmNlZCB2aWEgQ3Jvd2RmdW5kaW5nPw==",
            "answer": "RW50ZXIgdGhlIEd1bmdlb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiVGhlIFdhbGtpbmcgRGVhZDogU2Vhc29uIE9uZSI/",
            "answer": "TGVlIEV2ZXJldHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ1M6R08gZVNwb3J0cyB0ZWFtIHdvbiB0aGUgbWFqb3IgZXZlbnQgRVNMIE9uZSBDb2xvZ25lIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "U0sgR2FtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgbWFwcyBpcyBhIGJvbWIgZGVmdXNlIHNjZW5hcmlvPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZGlneQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBzZXJpZXMsIEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2Ugd2FzIGZvdW5kZWQgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGluIHRoZSBlYXJseSAxOTQwcz8=",
            "answer": "QXBlcnR1cmUgRml4dHVyZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTWFyaW8gc3Bpbi1vZmYgZ2FtZSBkaWQgV2FsdWlnaSBtYWtlIGhpcyBkZWJ1dD8=",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8gVGVubmlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIYWxmLUxpZmUgZXhwYW5zaW9uIGNhbiB5b3UgZmluZCBHb3Jkb24ncyBwaWN0dXJlIGluIGFuICJFbXBsb3llZSBvZiB0aGUgTW9udGgiIHBpY3R1cmUgZnJhbWU/",
            "answer": "SGFsZi1MaWZlOiBPcHBvc2luZyBGb3JjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIHdlcmUgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBmb3IgaW5jbHVzaW9uIGluIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIE1lbGVlPw==",
            "answer": "THVjYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBGb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KSwgaG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSB0aGVyZSB0byBkZWZlYXQgb24gdGhlIGJsYWNrbGlzdD8=",
            "answer": "MTU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgUlBHICJVbmRlcnRhbGUiLCB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgZG8geW91IGZpcnN0IGVuY291bnRlciBhZnRlciBmYWxsaW5nIGRvd24gaW50byB0aGUgdW5kZXJncm91bmQ/",
            "answer": "Rmxvd2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHNwYXJrZWQgY29udHJvdmVyc3kgYmVjYXVzZSBvZiBpdHMgaGlkZGVuICJIb3QgQ29mZmVlIiBtaW5pZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogU2FuIEFuZHJlYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIk1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IiBnYW1lIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgVGhlIFdvcmxkIEVuZHMgV2l0aCBZb3UsIGFsbCBvZiB0aGVzZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGFjdCBhcyBhIGdhbWUgcGFydG5lciB3aXRoIE5la3UgZm9yIGEgd2VlayBleGNlcHQ6",
            "answer": "Umh5bWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHlvdSBjYW4gY3JhZnQgdGhlIENlbGwgUGhvbmUgcHJlLWhhcmRtb2RlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IExlZnQgNCBEZWFkLCB5b3UgY2FuIHBsYXkgYXMgZWl0aGVyIG9mIHRoZXNlIGZvdXIgY2hhcmFjdGVycy4=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNpcywgQmlsbCwgWm9leSwgYW5kIExvdWlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcHJpbWFyeSB3ZWFwb24gdGhlIHBsYXllciBnZXRzIGluICJQQVlEQVk6IFRoZSBIZWlzdCI/",
            "answer": "QU1DQVItNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTmludGVuZG8ncyBWaXJ0dWFsIEJveSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IHRyaWxvZ3ksIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBwcm90YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "U2hlcGFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGdlbnJlIHdlcmUgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UlRTIChSZWFsIFRpbWUgU3RyYXRlZ3kp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBCaW5kaW5nIG9mIElzYWFjIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmluYWwgYm9zcyB0aGF0IHlvdSBmaWdodCBpbiBUaGUgVm9pZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVsaXJpdW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29tbW9uLCBndW4tdG90aW5nIGVuZW1pZXMgb2YgdGhlICJPZGR3b3JsZCIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "U2xpZ3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgVkkiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIChzdW1tb25lZCkgR2lsZ2FtZXNoJ3Mgd2Vha2VzdCBhdHRhY2s/",
            "answer": "RXhjYWxpcG9vcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIE5pbnRlbmRvIFN3aXRjaCBsYXVuY2ggdGl0bGUgaW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/IA==",
            "answer": "Vm9leg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJMaXR0bGUgTG9zdCBHaXJsIiBFYXN0ZXIgRWdnIGluIENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJLCB3aGF0J3MgdGhlIGxhc3Qgc3RlcCByZXF1aXJlZCBmb3IgdGhlIGFjaGlldmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "UmFpc2UgSGVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lLCAiTGV0aGFsIExlYWd1ZSI/",
            "answer": "UmV4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTb3JhJ3MgaG9tZSB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVzdGlueSBJc2xhbmRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9raSBEb2tpIExpdGVyYXR1cmUgQ2x1YiB3YXMgZGV2ZWxvcGVkIGluIEphcGFuLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzeXN0ZW0gd2FzICJUb3Vob3U6IEhpZ2hseSBSZXNwb25zaXZlIHRvIFByYXllcnMiIHJlbGVhc2VkIG9uPw==",
            "answer": "UEMtOTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSAiTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiBmcmFuY2hpc2U/",
            "answer": "TGluaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHVuaXNobWVudCBmb3IgcGxheWluZyBQb3N0YWwgMiBpbiBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "MTAgeWVhcnMgaW4gcHJpc29uIGFuZCBhIGZpbmUgb2YgJDUwLDAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSB0aXRsZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyOSwgMjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBIYWxvIDM6IE9EU1Qgd2FzIHVudmVpbGVkIGluIDIwMDgsIGl0IGhhZCBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCB0aXRsZS4gV2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgZm9ybWFsbHkgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsbyAzOiBSZWNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHJhZ29uRm9yY2UncyAnVGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgRmlyZSBhbmQgRmxhbWVzJyBpcyB3aWRlbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSB0aGUgaGFyZGVzdCBzb25nIGluIHRoZSBHdWl0YXIgSGVybyBzZXJpZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgU3RlYW0gZmlyc3QgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMiLCBob3cgbWFueSBLZXlibGFkZXMgYXJlIHVzYWJsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNwZWNpYWwgSW5mZWN0ZWQgdGhhdCBpcyB1bnBsYXlhYmxlIGluIFZlcnN1cyBtb2RlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdpdGNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIGFuIGFsbGllZCBNY0NyZWUgd2lsbCBzYXkgIlN0ZXAgcmlnaHQgdXAiIHVwb24gdXNpbmcgaGlzIHVsdGltYXRlIGFiaWxpdHkgRGVhZGV5ZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgdHdvIEF1c3RyYWxpYW4gY3JpbWluYWxzIGZyb20gdGhlIEp1bmtlcnMgZmFjdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVua3JhdCBhbmQgUm9hZGhvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIiBlbnRlciBjbG9zZWQgYmV0YT8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U29saWQgU25ha2UgaXMgYWN0dWFsbHkgYSBjbG9uZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBETkEgb2YgQmlnIEJvc3MgaW4gdGhlIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgc2VyaWVzJyBoaXN0b3J5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJldGEgdmVyc2lvbiBvZiB0aGUgMTk4NiBnYW1lICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiwgcGxheWVycyBoYXZlIHRoZSBjaG9pY2UgYmV0d2VlbiBhIHN3b3JkIGFuZCB3aGF0IG90aGVyIGl0ZW0/",
            "answer": "Qm9vbWVyYW5nIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4sIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIiwgaXMgc2FpZCB0byBoYXZlIG9uY2UgaGFkIGEgcG9ueXRhaWwu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHVsdGltYXRlIHBocmFzZSB1c2VkIGJ5IFBoYXJhaCBmcm9tIE92ZXJ3YXRjaCBpczogIkp1c3RpY2UgcmFpbnMgZnJvbSBhYm92ZSEi",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGEgam9pbnQgcHJvamVjdCBiZXR3ZWVuIFNlZ2EgYW5kIFNvbnkgdGhhdCB3YXMgYSBTZWdhIEdlbmVzaXMgd2l0aCBhIGRpc2MgZHJpdmUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIERlYWQgU3BhY2U/",
            "answer": "SXNhYWMgQ2xhcmtl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgZ2FtZSB1bmRlciB0aGUgV29ybXMgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFqb3IgTWFsZnVuY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBzdW1tb24gaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlNvdXRoIFBhcms6IFRoZSBTdGljayBvZiBUcnV0aCI/",
            "answer": "VG93ZWxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlN1Ym5hdXRpY2EiLCBhICJTcGFkZWZpc2giIHdpbGwgYXR0YWNrIHlvdS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IEhhcHB5IFRyaWdnZXIgSGF2b2MsIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgQW9pIEFzYWhpbmEncyB1bHRpbWF0ZSBhYmlsaXR5IGlzIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hdGUgU3dpbW1lcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUmlvdCBHYW1lcyAiTGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMiIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEhhbGxvd2VlbiBldmVudCBpcyBjYWxsZWQgIlRoZSBSZWNrb25pbmciLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0LCB3aGljaCB0d28gaXRlbXMgbXVzdCBiZSBjb21iaW5lZCB0byBjcmFmdCBhIHRvcmNoPw==",
            "answer": "U3RpY2sgYW5kIENvYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlAuQS5NLkUuTC5BLiIgcmVsZWFzZWQgb24gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggOSwgMjAxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgZmlnaHRlciBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gTWVsZWUiIGNhcGFibGUgb2YgZGVhbGluZyBkYW1hZ2Ugd2l0aCB0aGVpciB0YXVudCBhbmltYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "THVpZ2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIiBTZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "SGlkZW8gS29qaW1h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQb2tlbW9uIFR5cGVzIHdhcyBwcmVzZW50IGluIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBnYW1lcywgUmVkIGFuZCBCbHVlPw==",
            "answer": "SWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1NTyBSUEcgIlJlYWxtIG9mIHRoZSBNYWQgR29kIiwgd2hhdCBjbGFzcyBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IHBvc3NpYmxlIGRlZmVuc2U/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtuaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2FzLCB3aGljaCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FzaW5vcyBjYW4geW91IG5vdCBwbGF5IGluPw==",
            "answer": "THVja3kgMzg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY292ZXJ0IGdyb3VwcyBlbXBsb3lzIFNhbSBGaXNoZXIgdG8gd29yayBhcyBhIFNwbGludGVyIENlbGw/",
            "answer": "VGhpcmQgRWNoZWxvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW1hem9uIGFjcXVpcmVkIFR3aXRjaCBpbiBBdWd1c3QgMjAxNCBmb3IgJDk3MCBtaWxsaW9uIGRvbGxhcnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIGRvZXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0dXJlICJTbG93cG9rZSIgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "UG9rZW1vbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gQnJvcy4gd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDE5OTAu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZmVhdHVyZXMgd2FzIGFkZGVkIGluIHRoZSAxOTk0IGdhbWUgIkhlcmV0aWMiIHRoYXQgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsICJET09NIiBjb3VsZCBub3QgYWRkIGR1ZSB0byBsaW1pdGF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "TG9va2luZyB1cCBhbmQgZG93bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnQgc2VyaWVzIHdobyBwcm92aWRlcyB0aGUgZW5nbGlzaCB2b2ljZSBmb3IgTWFzdGVyIEVyYXF1cz8=",
            "answer": "TWFyayBIYW1pbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJXb3JtcyIgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHZpZGVvIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB3ZWFwb25zIGlzIGFmZmVjdGVkIGJ5IHdpbmQ/",
            "answer": "QmF6b29rYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QncyB0aXRsZSBnaXZlbiBieSB0aGUgZGVtb25zIGluIERPT00gKDIwMTYpPw==",
            "answer": "RG9vbSBTbGF5ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ29vaywgU2VydmUsIERlbGljaW91cyEsIHdoaWNoIGZvb2QgaXMgTk9UIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGRpZCBub3QgYXBwZWFyIGluIHRoZSAyMDAyIExlZ28gR2FtZTogRHJvbWUgUmFjZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "V2FzcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUG9rZW1vbiBnZW5lcmF0aW9uIGRpZCB0aGUgZmFuLW5hbWVkICJNYXN1ZGEgTWV0aG9kIiBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXIgaW4/IA==",
            "answer": "RGlhbW9uZC9QZWFybA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXMgTk9UIHBsYW5uZWQgdG8gYmUgcGxheWFibGUgZm9yIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIDY0Pw==",
            "answer": "UGVhY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHMgVjogU2t5cmltLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGplc3RlciBpbiB0aGUgZGFyayBicm90aGVyaG9vZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2ljZXJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEtvbmFtaSBDb2RlIGlzIGtub3duIGFzIFVwLCBVcCwgRG93biwgRG93biwgTGVmdCwgUmlnaHQsIFJpZ2h0LCBMZWZ0LCBCLCBBLCBTdGFydC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBva8OpbW9uIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBQYWxraWEncyBoaWRkZW4gYWJpbGl0eT8=",
            "answer": "VGVsZXBhdGh5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdlcmUgc2NyZWVuc2hvdHMgYWRkZWQgdG8gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBpcyBTYW5zLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWxsZW4gTWNMYWluLCB0aGUgdm9pY2Ugb2YgR0xhRE9TIGluIHRoZSBQb3J0YWwgZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXMsIGlzIG1hcnJpZWQgdG8gdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciB3aGljaCBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "U25pcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIGNpdHkgZG9lcyB0aGUgbWFwICJDbHViaG91c2UiIGluICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "SGFubm92ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIkRhcmsgU291bHMiIHNlcmllcyBkb2VzIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXIgcGxheSBhcyB0aGUgIkFzaGVuIE9uZSI/",
            "answer": "RGFyayBTb3VscyBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbmFtZSBvZiBhIGNpdHkgaW4gdGhlIG1haW4gaXNsYW5kIG9mIFBMQVlFUlVOS05PV04nUyBCQVRUTEVHUk9VTkRTPw==",
            "answer": "QmVsdXNoeWEgR3ViYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciAiTWFyaW8iIG1ha2UgaGlzIGZpcnN0IGFwcGVhcmFuY2U/",
            "answer": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgb2YgZXhpc3RlbmNlIGluIE1pY3JvUHJvc2UncyAxOTk3ICJNYWdpYyB0aGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIj8=",
            "answer": "U2hhbmRhbGFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTLlQuQS5MLksuRS5SLiIgc2VyaWVzLCB0aGUgRnJlZWRvbSBmYWN0aW9uIHdpc2hlcyB0byBkZXN0cm95IHRoZSBzdXBlcm5hdHVyYWwgYXJlYSBrbm93biBhcyAgInRoZSBab25lIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQaWttaW4iIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBwaWttaW4gdHlwZSB0byBwb3NzZXNzIHZpc2libGUgZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFNweXJvIGdhbWUgd2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB2aWxsYWluPw==",
            "answer": "R25hc3R5IEdub3Jj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgRG9raSBEb2tpIExpdGVyYXR1cmUgQ2x1Yj8=",
            "answer": "Tmljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBob3N0ZWQgdGhlIENTOkdPIERyZWFtaGFjayBPcGVuIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "Q2x1ai1OYXBvY2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHN5Y2hvcGF0aChzKSBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAxIGdhdmUgeW91IHRoZSBzbWFsbCBjaGFpbnNhdz8=",
            "answer": "QWRhbSB0aGUgQ2xvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIGRlYnVmZiBkb2VzIHRoZSBhbmtoIGNoYXJtIG5vdCBwcm92aWRlIGltbXVuaXR5IHRvPw==",
            "answer": "VmVub20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgc2VyaWVzLCBMZW9uIFMuIEtlbm5lZHkgaXMgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgU1RBUlMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNwYWNlIFN0YXRpb24gMTMiLCAgdGhlIHN0YXRpb24gaGFzIGEgY2xvd24gYWJvYXJkIGl0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIERTIGdhbWUgJ0dob3N0IFRyaWNrOiBQaGFudG9tIERldGVjdGl2ZScsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGhpdG1hbiBzZWVuIGF0IHRoZSBzdGFydCBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "TmVhcnNpZ2h0ZWQgSmVlZ28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGFudGFnb25pc3QgaW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBmcmFuY2hpc2U/",
            "answer": "R0xhRE9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIHRoZSBlYXJsaWVzdCBrbm93biBmaXJzdC1wZXJzb24gc2hvb3RlciB3aXRoIGEga25vd24gdGltZSBvZiBwdWJsaWNhdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U3Bhc2lt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RmF1c3QgaXMgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkd1aWx0eSBHZWFyIFhyZCBSZXZlbGF0b3IiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZVNwb3J0cyB0ZWFtIGNhbWUgZmlyc3QgcGxhY2UgaW4gVGhlIEludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgRG90YSAyIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "V2luZ3MgR2FtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHJpZ2h0cyB0byB0aGUgIlJheW1hbiIgc2VyaWVzIGFyZSBvd25lZCBieSB3aGljaCBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "VWJpc29mdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAzIiBmb3IgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sb3Igb2YgdGhlIHNlY29uZCBDaGFvcyBFbWVyYWxkIHlvdSBjYW4gZ2V0IGZyb20gU3BlY2lhbCBTdGFnZXM/",
            "answer": "T3Jhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlJvbGxlcmNvYXN0ZXIgVHljb29uIiB3YXMgcHJvZ3JhbW1lZCBtb3N0bHkgZW50aXJlbHkgaW4uLi4=",
            "answer": "eDg2IEFzc2VtYmx5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcG9zc2libGUgZHJpbmsgdG8gYmUgbWFkZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiVkEtMTEgSEFMTC1BOiBDeWJlcnB1bmsgQmFydGVuZGVyIEFjdGlvbiI/",
            "answer": "U291ciBBcHBsZXRpbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24sIHRoZSBTcXVpZCBTaXN0ZXJzIGFyZSBuYW1lZCBUYWtvIGFuZCBZYWtpLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9ja2V0IExlYWd1ZSwgeW91IGNhbiBwbGF5IEJhc2tldGJhbGwu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIGRldmVsb3BtZW50IG9mICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBXb3JsZCIsIFlvc2hpJ3MgaGFyZCBzYWRkbGUgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2U/",
            "answer": "QSBzaGVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmFsdmUgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24gaXMgYW4gQW1lcmljYW4gdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZXIgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "QmVsbGV2dWUsIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNha2UgZGVwaWN0ZWQgaW4gVmFsdmUncyAiUG9ydGFsIiBmcmFuY2hpc2UgbW9zdCBjbG9zZWx5IHJlc2VtYmxlcyB3aGljaCByZWFsLXdvcmxkIHR5cGUgb2YgY2FrZT8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2sgRm9yZXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHNlcmllcywgd2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdHJ1bHkgcmVzcG9uc2libGUgb2YgdGhlIGZvcmdpbmcgb2YgdGhlIGF1dG9wc3kgcmVwb3J0IG9mIHRoZSBwaXZvdGFsIElTLTcgaW5jaWRlbnQ/",
            "answer": "QmFuc2FpIEljaGl5YW5hZ2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBmcm9tIHRoZSBpbmRpZSBhZHZlbnR1cmUgZ2FtZSAiTmlnaHQgaW4gdGhlIFdvb2RzIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyZ2FyZXQgQm9yb3dza2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIHdoaWNoIGhlcm8gaXMgYWJsZSB0byB3YWxscmlkZT8=",
            "answer": "THVjaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZpYXQgTXVsdGlwbGEgaXMgYSBkcml2YWJsZSBjYXIgaW4gIkZvcnphIEhvcml6b24gMyIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBKb2VsJ3MgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUsICJUaGUgTGFzdCBvZiBVcyI/IA==",
            "answer": "U2FyYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBpc2xhbmQgaW4gUExBWUVSVU5LTk9XTidTIEJBVFRMRUdST1VORFM/",
            "answer": "RXJhbmdlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBmb3JtZXIgTU9CQSwgY3JlYXRlZCBieSBXYXlzdG9uZSBHYW1lcyBhbmQgcHVibGlzaGVkIGJ5IEVBLCB3YXMgc2h1dCBkb3duIGluIDIwMTQ/",
            "answer": "RGF3bmdhdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQb3J0YWwiIHNlcmllcywgd2hvIHdhcyBDYXZlIEpvaG5zb24ncyBwZXJzb25hbCBhc3Npc3RhbnQ/",
            "answer": "Q2Fyb2xpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIaXRtYW4iIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "QWdlbnQgNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWxsaWdhdG9yIGluIFdoZXJlJ3MgTXkgV2F0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3dhbXB5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gT3ZlcndhdGNoLCB3aGF0IGlzIEzDumNpbydzIGZ1bGwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TMO6Y2lvIENvcnJlaWEgRG9zIFNhbnRvcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCA0LCB0aGUgQ2hpY2FnbyBUeXBld3JpdGVyIGhhcyBpbmZpbml0ZSBhbW1vLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBleHBlbnNpdmUgd2VhcG9uIGluIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "U2Nhci0yMC9HM1NHMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhbmNlbGxlZCBzZXF1ZWwgb2YgVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBCcm90aGVyaG9vZCBvZiBBcm1z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW50dXJuZWQgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBzdGFydGVkIGFzIGEgUm9ibG94IGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIDYgbGVnZW5kYXJ5IGNhcmRzIGluICJDbGFzaCBSb3lhbGUiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIkdhcnJ5J3MgTW9kIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVjZW1iZXIgMjQsIDIwMDQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBVbml0ZWQgT2ZmZW5zaXZlLCB3aGF0IHR3byBzb2xkaWVycyBzaGFyZSBhIG5hbWUgb2YgYSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uICYgRnJlZW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBub3QgYSBkZWZhdWx0IGdhbWUgbW9kZSBpbiBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZSAoMjAwMCk/",
            "answer": "QXJtcyBSYWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGF5IGluICJQYXBlcnMsIFBsZWFzZSIgZG9lcyB0aGUgbWFuIGluIHJlZCBhcHBlYXI/",
            "answer": "RGF5IDIz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdpbW1pY2shIiBpcyBhIEphcGFuZXNlIEZhbWljb20gZ2FtZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgYSBzb3VuZCBjaGlwIGV4cGFuc2lvbiBpbiB0aGUgY2FydHJpZGdlLiBXaGF0IGlzIGl0IGNhbGxlZD8=",
            "answer": "Rk1FLTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW9uc3RlciBpbiAiTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgVHJpIiB3YXMgY2F1c2luZyBlYXJ0aHF1YWtlcyBpbiBNb2dhIFZpbGxhZ2U/",
            "answer": "Q2VhZGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHN0ZXBzIGFyZSB0aGVyZSB0byB1cGdyYWRlIGEgU3RhZmY/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIHRoZSBwZXJrICJQaEQgRmxvcHBlciI/",
            "answer": "QXNjZW5zaW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgMjAxNiBmYXJtaW5nIFJQRyAiU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXkiPw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBCYXJvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIGhvdyBtdWNoIGhlYWx0aCBkb2VzIGEgc2NvdXQgaGF2ZSB3aGVuIG92ZXJoZWFsZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTg1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5ODBzLCBhIHNlcnZpY2UgY2FsbGVkIEdhbWVsaW5lIGFsbG93ZWQgdXNlcnMgdG8gZG93bmxvYWQgZ2FtZXMgdG8gd2hhdCBjb25zb2xlPw==",
            "answer": "QXRhcmkgMjYwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJXYXJoZWFkIiBpbiB0aGUgU2VnYSBHZW5lc2lzIGdhbWUgIlZlY3Rvcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "UmFzdGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2h5IHdlcmUgb25seSBvbmx5IDMwMCwwMDAgY29waWVzIG9mIFVuaXJhY2VycyB3ZXJlIHByb2R1Y2VkPw==",
            "answer": "RE1BIERlc2lnbnMgd2FzIHN1ZWQgYnkgUGl4YXIsIHByZXZlbnRpbmcgbW9yZSBjb3BpZXMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBwcm9kdWNlZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQaWttaW4iIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHBpa21pbiBjb2xvcnMgbGFja3MgaXQncyBvd24gIk9uaW9uIiBuZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkZ1ZWwiIGhhcyBhbiBvcGVuIHdvcmxkIHRoYXQgaXMgNSw1NjAgc3F1YXJlIG1pbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29kZW1hc3RlcnMgaXMgdGhlIGRldmVsb3BlciBvZiB0aGUgR3JhbiBUdXJpc21vIHNlcmllcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXIgaXMgQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgYmFzZWQgb24/",
            "answer": "Q29sZCBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIFdpdGNoZXIgMywgdGhlIFpvbHRhbiBDaGl2YXkgR3dlbnQgY2FyZCBjYW4gYmUgZm91bmQgdW5kZXIgdGhlIEhhbmdlZCBNYW4ncyBUcmVlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHJldGFpbCBkaXNjIG9mIFRvbnkgSGF3aydzIFBybyBTa2F0ZXIgNSBvbmx5IGNvbWVzIHdpdGggdGhlIHR1dG9yaWFsLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSB0eXBlIG9mIG1vbnN0ZXIgZm91bmQgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIFNvbmljJ3Mgc2lkZWtpY2s/",
            "answer": "VGFpbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIkJhdHRsZWZpZWxkIDEiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmcgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgc2V0IHRvIGJlIGEgUG9wZXllIGFyY2FkZSBnYW1lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCIgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gTm9ydGggQW1lcmljYT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnkgaG93IG1hbnkgbWludXRlcyBhcmUgeW91IGxhdGUgdG8gd29yayBpbiAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIj8=",
            "answer": "MzA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2FtZSBCb3kgZnJvbSB0aGUgR2FtZSBCb3kgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHBvcnRhYmxlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgY29uc29sZXMgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "R2FtZSBCb3kgQ29sb3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBoYXBwZW5lZCB0byBIYWxmLUxpZmUgMiBwcmlvciB0byBpdHMgcmVsZWFzZSwgd2hpY2ggcmVzdWx0ZWQgaW4gVmFsdmUgc3RhcnRpbmcgb3ZlciB0aGUgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIHNvdXJjZSBjb2RlIGdvdCBsZWFrZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGFyZSB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgY3JlYXRvcnMgb2YgUmFjaGV0ICYgQ2xhbms/",
            "answer": "SW5zb21uaWFjIEdhbWVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2F0Y2hfRG9ncyAyIGlzIGEgcHJlcXVlbC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggS2lyYnkgZ2FtZSBmaXJzdCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIENvcHkgQWJpbGl0aWVzPw==",
            "answer": "S2lyYnkncyBBZHZlbnR1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFBhY2stQS1QdW5jaGVkIENyb3NzYm93Pw==",
            "answer": "QXdmdWwgTGF3dG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3ZXJlIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB0d28gYmxvY2tzIGluICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiPw==",
            "answer": "R3Jhc3MgYW5kIENvYmJsZXN0b25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlkZGVuIGluIHRoZSBmaWxlcyBmb3IgIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgQXJjYWRlIEdQIiBpcyBhIHBpY3R1cmUgb2YgdGhlIEJlc2xhbiBzY2hvb2wgaG9zdGFnZSBjcmlzaXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3b24gdGhlIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIEZpZ2h0ZXIgQmFsbG90IGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "QmF5b25ldHRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBWYW1waXJlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiAiU2hpbmluZyBTb3VsIDIiLg==",
            "answer": "Qmxvb2RzdGFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmludGVuZG8gNjQgZ2FtZSBkaWQgTk9UIGhhdmUgTHVpZ2kgaW4gaXQ/",
            "answer": "U3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gNjQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlN0cmFuZ2VyZWFsIiBpcyBhIGZpY3RpdGlvdXMgRWFydGgtbGlrZSB3b3JsZCBmb3Igd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "QWNlIENvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBUZXJyYW4gdW5pdHMgZnJvbSB0aGUgUlRTIGdhbWUgU3RhcmNyYWZ0IHdhcyBmaXJzdCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSBleHBhbnNpb24gQnJvb2QgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVkaWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG91aG91IDEyOiBVbmRlZmluZWQgRmFudGFzdGljIE9iamVjdCwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "SXpheW9pIFNha3V5YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgR2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd29yayBhdCBiZWZvcmUgZm91bmRpbmcgVmFsdmUgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNvbXBvc2VkIHRoZSBzb3VuZHRyYWNrIGZvciB0aGUgZ2FtZSBWVlZWVlY/",
            "answer": "TWFnbnVzIFDDpWxzc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGEgMjogR29vZGJ5ZSBEZXNwYWlyIGZlYXR1cmVkIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgc3Vydml2aW5nIHN0dWRlbnRzIGZyb20gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUFJPVE9UWVBFIDIuIHdobyBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBhcyAiVGFuZ28gUHJpbWFyeSI/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSGVsbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHdoaWNoIGNsYXNzIGlzIGFibGUgdG8gZG91YmxlIGp1bXA/",
            "answer": "U2NvdXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlRlcnJhcmlhIiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9zc2VzIGFyZSBwcmUtaGFyZG1vZGUgYm9zc2VzPw==",
            "answer": "RXllIG9mIEN0aHVsaHU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWF4aW11bSBIUCBpbiBUZXJyYXJpYT8=",
            "answer": "NTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyB3ZWFwb24gaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmUgZG9lcyBub3QgZXhpc3QgaW4gcmVhbCBsaWZlLg==",
            "answer": "TTRBNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdm9pY2UgY2hhbm5lbHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTeXN0ZW0gc3VwcG9ydCBuYXRpdmVseT8=",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSBnYW1lIHRvIGluY2x1ZGUgdGhlIFpvbWJpZXMgZ2FtZW1vZGU/",
            "answer": "Q2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBXb3JsZCBhdCBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHRvcC1kb3duIG9ubGluZSBSUEcgIlNwYWNlIFN0YXRpb24gMTMiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBhcGVyIE1hcmlvOiBUaGUgVGhvdXNhbmQgWWVhciBEb29yIiwgd2hhdCBpcyBIb29rdGFpbCdzIHdlYWtuZXNzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNvdW5kIG9mIENyaWNrZXRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFdvcmxkIiwgdGhlIHJoaW5vIG1pbmktYm9zcywgUmV6bm9yLCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgbGVhZCBzaW5nZXIgb2YgdGhlIGJhbmQgIk5pbmUgSW5jaCBOYWlscyIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgd29uZGVyIHdlYXBvbiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIj8=",
            "answer": "UjExNSBSZXNvbmF0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtoYWppaXQgYXJlIGEgcmFjZSBvZiBjYXQtbGlrZSBjcmVhdHVyZXMgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBlcGljIHNlcmllcyBvZiByb2xlLXBsYXlpbmcgZ2FtZXMsIHNldCBhY3Jvc3MgdGhlIGxhbmQgb2YgVGFtcmllbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIGl0J3MgcmVkZXNpZ24gb2YgdGhlIGNvbXBhbnkgbG9nbyBpbiB0aGUgeWVhciAyMDAwLCB3aGljaCAzRCBzaGFwZSBpcyBOT1QgcmVwcmVzZW50ZWQgaW4gdGhlIEVsZWN0cm9uaWMgQXJ0cyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "Q3lsaW5kZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBVQkFUVExFR1JPVU5EUyIgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgTWlsaXRhcnkgQmFzZSBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "U29zbm92a2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIGNsYXNzIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJIZWFydGhzdG9uZSI/",
            "answer": "UHJpZXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgdGhlIGRlZmF1bHQgVUkgY29sb3IgdGhhdCBzaWduaWZpZXMgRHJ1aWQgaXMgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "T3Jhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIFRlcnJvciBGaWVuZHMgbW9yZSBjb21tb25seSBmb3VuZCBpbiB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gZ2FtZSBNaWl0b3BpYT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IEx1bW9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBldmVudHMgb2YgSGFsZi1MaWZlOiBPcHBvc2luZyBGb3JjZSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWdlIG9mIEFkcmlhbiBTaGVwaGFyZCwgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiBKYXBhbj8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyOSwgMTk4OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiAiVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIiB1cGRhdGUsIGluIHdoaWNoIGl0IGJlY2FtZSBGcmVlLXRvLXBsYXk/",
            "answer": "w5xiZXIgVXBkYXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgQ2hhb3MgRW1lcmFsZHMgY2FuIHlvdSBjb2xsZWN0IGluIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBTb25pYyBUaGUgSGVkZ2Vob2c/",
            "answer": "U2l4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZhbGxvdXQgNCIgd2hpY2ggZmFjdGlvbiBpcyBub3QgcHJlc2VudCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVuY2xhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2MsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrb3RvIE5hZWdp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIG1hbmFnZXIgb2YgdGhlIHRvd24gc2hvcD8=",
            "answer": "VG9tIE5vb2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBibG9jayBpbiBNaW5lY3JhZnQgaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGJsYXN0IHJlc2lzdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "QmFycmllcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBsZXZlbCBkbyB5b3UgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSB0byBnZXQgYSBzZXJ2aWNlIG1lZGFsIG9uIENTOkdPPw==",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZhbGxvdXQgNCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGRvZyB5b3UgZmluZCBhdCBSZWQgUm9ja2V0IHRydWNrIHN0b3A/",
            "answer": "RG9nbWVhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBob3VzZWhvbGQgaXRlbSBtYWtlIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIG9mICJTdGVpbnM7IEdhdGUiIHRyYXZlbCB0aHJvdWdoIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "TWljcm93YXZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJEZXZpbCBNYXkgQ3J5IiBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIHdoaWNoIGdhbWUgaXMgY2hyb25vbG9naWNhbGx5IGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGV2aWwgTWF5IENyeSAzOiBEYW50ZSdzIEF3YWtlbmluZyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSB3YXMgdXNlZCB0byBjcmVhdGUgdGhlIGdhbWUgIk1pbmVjcmFmdCI/",
            "answer": "SmF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2VhbiBCZWFuIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mICJNYXJ0aW4gU2VwdGltIiBpbiB3aGljaCBFbGRlciBTY3JvbGxzIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHMgSVY6IE9ibGl2aW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gIkJsb29ucyBURCBCYXR0bGVzIj8=",
            "answer": "TW9ua2V5cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGNyZWRpdGVkIHdpdGggaGF2aW5nIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBFYXN0ZXIgRWdnPw==",
            "answer": "V2FycmVuIFJvYmluZXR0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGluZGllIGZhcm1pbmcgZ2FtZSAiU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXkiLCB3aGljaCBOUEMgaGF0ZXMgdGhlICJwcmlzbWF0aWMgc2hhcmQiIGl0ZW0gd2hlbiByZWNlaXZlZCBhcyBhIGdpZnQ/",
            "answer": "SGFsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk1pbmVjcmFmdCIsIGdvbGQgdG9vbHMgYXJlIGZhc3RlciB0aGFuIGRpYW1vbmQgdG9vbHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlhlbm9ibGFkZSBDaHJvbmljbGVzIDIiLCBXaGljaCBwYXJ0eSBtZW1iZXIgY2Fubm90IHVzZSBub3JtYWwgYmxhZGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG9yYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBLaXJieSBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGdvaW5nIHRvIGJlIG5hbWVkPw==",
            "answer": "UG9wb3Bv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIncyBIZWF2eSBXZWFwb25zIEd1eSdzIG1pbmlndW4/",
            "answer": "U2FzaGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1hcCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBBcm1hIDMgbmFtZWQgIkFsdGlzIiBpcyBiYXNlZCBvZmYgb2Ygd2hhdCBHcmVlayBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "TGVtbm9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmVzIHdhcyBtYWRlIGJ5IHRoZSBjb21wYW55IEVwaWMgR2FtZXM/",
            "answer": "VW5yZWFs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIHRoZSBTbmlwZXIgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "THVpZ2kgaXMgdGFsbGVyIHRoYW4gTWFyaW8/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIElXSEJZRCBzdGFuZCBmb3Igb24gdGhlIHNrdWxsIGluIHRoZSBIYWxvIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJlZW4gWW91ciBEYWRkeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgIldvcm1zIiBnYW1lcyBmZWF0dXJlZCAzRCBnYW1lcGxheT8=",
            "answer": "V29ybXMgNDogTWF5aGVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBUaGUgTWVkaWMgd2lsbCBiZSBjcmVkaXRlZCBmb3IgYW4gYXNzaXN0IGlmIGhlIGhlYWxzIGEgU3B5IHRoYXQgc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bGx5IHNhcHMgYSBidWlsZGluZy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgT3ZlcndhdGNoLCB3aGljaCBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMgaW5mYW1vdXMgZm9yIHNheWluZyAiSXQncyBoaWdoIG5vb24uIj8=",
            "answer": "TWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyB0aGUgR29kIG9mIFNwaWRlcnMgaW4gdGhlIHRyb2xsJ3MgbG9hIGJlbGllZnM/",
            "answer": "RWxvcnRoYSBubyBTaGFkcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2F0ZXItdHlwZSBQb2vDqW1vbiBzdGFydGVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSA0dGggZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBvZiB0aGUgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGlwbHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWVwZXIgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0IHdhcyB0aGUgcmVzdWx0IG9mIGEgYnVnIHdoaWxlIGltcGxlbWVudGluZyB3aGljaCBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "UGln"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBCaW5kaW5nIG9mIElzYWFjIiwgd2hpY2ggaXRlbSBpbnN0YW50bHkga2lsbHMgTW9tIGFuZCBNb20ncyBIZWFydD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJpYmxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgbWFpbiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnIHdpbGwgcmV3YXJkIHlvdSB3aXRoIHRoZSBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCwgIkhpZ2ggTWFpbnRlbmFuY2UiPw==",
            "answer": "RGllIFJpc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlJldHVybiB0byBDYXN0bGUgV29sZmVuc3RlaW4iIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBXb2xmZW5zdGVpbiBzZXJpZXMgd2hlcmUgeW91IGRvbid0IHBsYXkgYXMgV2lsbGlhbSAiQi5KLiIgQmxhemtvd2ljei4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGlueSBUaHdvbXBzIGNhbGxlZCBpbiBTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBXb3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "VGh3aW1wcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGludHJvZHVjZWQgaW4gU29uaWMgQm9vbTogUmlzZSBvZiBMeXJpYz8=",
            "answer": "U3RpY2tzIHRoZSBCYWRnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byAoR1RBKSBnYW1lcyBoYXZlIHRoZSBzYW1lIHNldHRpbmc/",
            "answer": "R1RBIFYgYW5kIEdUQSBTYW4gQW5kcmVhcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgb2JzaWRpYW4gYmxvY2tzIGFyZSByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBidWlsZCBhIG5ldGhlciBwb3J0YWwgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IGFtb3VudCBvZiBtYXggaGVhbHRoIHlvdSBjYW4gaGF2ZSBpbiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDI/",
            "answer": "NzA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgRE9UQSAyLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBOT1QgYSBoZXJvPw==",
            "answer": "RHJhZ29uIENoYW1waW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRpZCAiTWFyaW8iLCBmcm9tICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm90aGVycyIsIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "T3NzYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFN0YXIgV2FyczogQmF0dGxlZnJvbnQgSUkgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAzMSwgMjAwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlICJOaW50ZW5kbyBHYW1lY3ViZSI/",
            "answer": "RG9scGhpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFBsYW5ldHNpZGUgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIE5vcnRoIEFtZXJpY2Egb24uLi4=",
            "answer": "TWF5IDIwLCAyMDAz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCBGUFMgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZXMgc3VjaCBhcyBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZSwgc2hvb3Rpbmcgd2hpY2ggcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgYm9keSBkb2VzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGRhbWFnZT8=",
            "answer": "SGVhZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXRlbXMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTWFydGlhbiBTYXVjZXIgbWluaS1ib3NzIE5PVCBkcm9wPw==",
            "answer": "RHJpbGwgQ29udGFpbm1lbnQgVW5pdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgQ3Jhc2ggQmFuZGljb290Pw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGllIFdvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBTZW50cnkgcm9ja2V0IGRhbWFnZSBmYWxsb2ZmIGlzIGNhbGN1bGF0ZWQgYmFzZWQgb24gdGhlIGRpc3RhbmNlIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIHNlbnRyeSBhbmQgdGhlIGVuZW15LCBub3QgdGhlIGVuZ2luZWVyIGFuZCB0aGUgZW5lbXk=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUGFwZXIgTWFyaW8gZm9yIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyA2NCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcGFydG5lciB5b3UgbWVldCBpcyBhIEdvb21iYSwgd2hhdCBpcyBpdHMgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "R29vbWJhcmlv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgQmV0aGVzZGEgcHVyY2hhc2UgdGhlIEZhbGxvdXQgU2VyaWVzIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "SW50ZXJwbGF5IEVudGVydGFpbm1lbnQg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIFJveGFzJ3MgS2V5YmxhZGVzIGluIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIGFyZSAiT2F0aGtlZXBlciIgYW5kICJPYmxpdmlvbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3Vydml2b3IgaW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQgc2FjcmlmaWNlZCB0aGVtc2VsZiB0byBzYXZlIHRoZSBvdGhlciBzdXJ2aXZvcnM/",
            "answer": "QmlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHR1cm5zIG91dCB0byBiZSB0aGUgdHJ1ZSB2aWN0b3IgaW4gdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBBcm1hZ2VkZG9uIGluIE1vcnRhbCBLb21iYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2hhbyBLYWhu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHdhcyBub3QgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgdGhlIEZpZW5kaXNoIEZpdmUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU2x5IENvb3BlciBhbmQgdGhlIFRoaWV2aXVzIFJhY2Nvb251cz8=",
            "answer": "RGltaXRyaSBMb3VzdGVhdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBtb3N0IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgWVMgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QWRvbCBDaHJpc3RpbiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG1heCBIUCBvZiB0aGUgbW9uc3RlciAiUHVuY2h5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NTAsMDAwIEhQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogV29ybGQgQXQgV2FyIiwgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGFwcGVhcmFuY2Ugb2YgdGhlICJQUFNILTQxIiBpbiAiWm9tYmllcyIgd2FzIGluIHRoZSBtYXAgIkRlciBSaWVzZSIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyAiVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogTWFqb3JhJ3MgTWFzayIgdGFrZSBwbGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "VGVybWluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3ZWFwb25zIGluICJDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZSIgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBhIHJpZ2h0LWNsaWNrIGZ1bmN0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "WE0xMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RWFjaCBwaWVjZSBpbiBUZXRyaXMgaXMgY2FsbGVkIGEgdGV0cmlzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBTaW1zIiBzZXJpZXMsIHRoZSBtb3N0IG1lbWJlcnMgaW4gYSBob3VzZWhvbGQgeW91IGNhbiBoYXZlIGlzIDgu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RXhjbHVkaW5nIHRoZWlyIGluc3RydWN0b3IsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1lbWJlcnMgb2YgQ2xhc3MgVklJIGFyZSB0aGVyZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiTGVnZW5kIG9mIEhlcm9lczogVHJhaWxzIG9mIENvbGQgU3RlZWwiPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmluYWwgZ2FtZSBvZiB0aGUgIlplcm8gRXNjYXBlIiBzZXJpZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "WmVybyBFc2NhcGUgWmVybyBUaW1lIERpbGVtbWEg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQb2vDqW1vbiBnYW1lcyByZWxlYXNlZCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "UG9rw6ltb24gQ3J5c3RhbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgTnVjbGVhciBUaHJvbmUsIHdoYXQgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uIGNoYXNlcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGNoYXJhY3RlciB0aHJvdWdob3V0IHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEkuRC5QLkQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBmcm9tIHRoZSBTTkVTIGdhbWUgQ2xvY2sgVG93ZXI/",
            "answer": "SmVubmlmZXIgU2ltcHNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGZyb20gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIgd2FzIHJldmVhbGVkIHRvIGJlIGhvbW9zZXh1YWwgaW4gRGVjZW1iZXIgb2YgMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "VHJhY2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk4NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkZhbGxvdXQ6IE5ldyBWZWdhcyIgcXVlc3QgaXMgTk9UIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIGEgcmVhbC1saWZlIHNvbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhleSBXZW50IFRoYXQtYS1XYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGEgQW5vdGhlciBFcGlzb2RlOiBVbHRyYSBEZXNwYWlyIEdpcmxzIGlzIHNldCBhZnRlciB3aGljaCBEYW5nYW5yb25wYSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFN1bnNoaW5lIiwgaG93IGRvIHlvdSB1bmxvY2sgdGhlICJDb3JvbmEgTW91bnRhaW4iIGxldmVsPw==",
            "answer": "QnkgY2xlYXJpbmcgZXZlcnkgN3RoIGVwaXNvZGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSByYWNlIGluICJGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhJVjogQSBSZWFsbSBSZWJvcm4iPw==",
            "answer": "SHVtZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJlZ2lubmluZyBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU29uaWMgQWR2ZW50dXJlIiwgd2hhdCBjb2xvciBDaGFvcyBFbWVyYWxkIGRvZXMgVGFpbHMgb3duPw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggcGxhbmV0IGRvZXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgRnJlZWRvbSBQbGFuZXQgKDIwMTQpIHRha2UgcGxhY2U/",
            "answer": "QXZhbGljZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoaWNoIGNhbXBhaWduIGhhcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3RzIGdvaW5nIHRocm91Z2ggYSBzdWJ3YXkgaW4gb3JkZXIgdG8gcmVhY2ggYSBob3NwaXRhbCBmb3IgZXZhY3VhdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "Tm8gTWVyY3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkV4aWxlIiBhbmQgIlJldmVsYXRpb25zIiB3ZXJlIHRoZSB0aGlyZCBhbmQgZm91cnRoIGluc3RhbGxtZW50cyBvZiB3aGljaCBQQyBnYW1lIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TXlzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgNiBTaWVnZSwgd2hhdCBvcmdhbml6YXRpb24gaXMgVmFsa3lyaWUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "TmF2eSBTZWFscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDAgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ3JpbXNvbiBTa2llcywiIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdHMnIHplcHBlbGluPw==",
            "answer": "UGFuZG9yYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBBY2UgQ29tYmF0IDU6IFRoZSBVbnN1bmcgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "T3NlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIFNvbGlkIiBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQncyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTb2xpZCBTbmFrZSdzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "TGlxdWlkIFNuYWtl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHBvcHVsYXIgZnJhbmNoaXNlIHRoYXQgaW5jbHVkZXMgcGxhY2luZyBibG9ja3MgZG93biBhbmQgc3Vydml2aW5nIGluIGFuIG9wZW4gd29ybGQ/IA==",
            "answer": "TWluZWNyYWZ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24sIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFnZSB0aGF0IGlua2xpbmdzIGNhbiBmcmVlbHkgY2hhbmdlIGJldHdlZW4gc3F1aWQgYW5kIGh1bWFub2lkIGZvcm1zPw==",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSB0aGUgbG9jYXRpb24tYmFzZWQgYXVnbWVudGVkIHJlYWxpdHkgZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgTmlhbnRpYyBiZWZvcmUgUG9rw6ltb24gR08/",
            "answer": "SW5ncmVzcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3YXMgZXhjbHVzaXZlIHRvIERyZWFtY2FzdD8=",
            "answer": "UGVuIFBlbiBUcmlJY2Vsb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluICJMZWZ0IDQgRGVhZCI/",
            "answer": "Tmljaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uIGdhbWUgdG8gcmVxdWlyZSB0aGUgdXNlIG9mIHRoZSBEdWFsU2hvY2sgY29udHJvbGxlcj8=",
            "answer": "QXBlIEVzY2FwZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGdhbWVzIHdhc24ndCByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "TWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCBW"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMsIGd1aWxkIHN0eWxlIGlzIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBodW50aW5nIHN0eWxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSB0cmFkaXRpb25hbGx5IHJld2FyZCB5b3UgZm9yIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgYSBib3NzIHJvdW5kPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4IEFtbW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIiBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBoYXZlIGEgdGltZSB0cmF2ZWwgc3lzdGVtLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlICJCYXR0bGVmaWVsZCIgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QmF0dGxlZmllbGQgMTk0Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkIElJSTogSG90IFB1cnN1aXQiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBmaWN0aW9uYWwgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "RWwgTmnDsW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBnYW1lIGNvbnNpc3RlZCBvZiBhIGZlbWFsZS1vbmx5IGNhc3Qgb2YgcGFydHkgbWVtYmVycz8=",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYLTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWR2ZW50dXJlciB5b3UgbWVldCBhdCB0aGUgbWluZXMgaW4gU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXk/",
            "answer": "TWFybG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2ZWhpY2xlIGluIFBVQkcgaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IHRvcCBzcGVlZD8=",
            "answer": "TW90b3JjeWNsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24gMiwgd2hvIGFyZSB0aGUgbWVtYmVycyBvZiBPZmYgVGhlIEhvb2s/",
            "answer": "UGVhcmwgJiBNYXJpbmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGRpZ2l0YWwgZGlzdHJpYnV0aW9uIHBsYXRmb3JtIFN0ZWFtPw==",
            "answer": "VmFsdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBmYW1vdXMgbGluZSBWYWFzIHNheXMgaW4gIkZhciBDcnkgMyI/",
            "answer": "RGlkIEkgZXZlciB0ZWxsIHlvdSB0aGUgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiBvZiBJbnNhbml0eT8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBIYWxmLUxpZmU6IE9wcG9zaW5nIEZvcmNlPw==",
            "answer": "QWRyaWFuIFNoZXBoYXJk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMiLCBob3cgbWFueSBwbGF5YWJsZSB3b3JsZHMgd2VyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgSHVtb25nb3VzIEVudGVydGFpbm1lbnQgZ2FtZSBmcmFuY2hpc2U/",
            "answer": "Q29tbWFuZGVyIEtlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE1IFJQRyAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIiBpcyBhIG1vbnN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkxpZmUgaXMgU3RyYW5nZSI/",
            "answer": "TWF4aW5lIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hcmlvICYgU29uaWMgYXQgdGhlIE9seW1waWMgR2FtZXMiLCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGFyZSBzcGxpdCBpbnRvIGhvdyBtYW55IHR5cGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdEJyBpbiB0aGUgdGVybSAiRC1NYWlsIiBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lICJTdGVpbnM7IEdhdGUiIGlzIHNob3J0IGZvciB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGVMb3JlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCA0IHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IG1lYW50IHRvIGJlIGEgTmludGVuZG8gR2FtZUN1YmUgZXhjbHVzaXZlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbG9jYXRpb24gZG9lcyBEYXJrIFN1biBHd3luZG9saW4gcmVzaWRlIGluICJEYXJrIFNvdWxzIj8=",
            "answer": "QW5vciBMb25kbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBDcmVhbSB0aGUgUmFiYml0J3MgbW9tIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "VmFuaWxsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtaW5nIHNlcmllcyBpbmNsdWRlcyAiVGhlIERpYWJvbGljYWwgQm94IiBhbmQgIlRoZSBDdXJpb3VzIFZpbGxhZ2UiPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIExheXRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgQUstNDcncyBuYW1lIGluIENvdW50ZXIgU3RyaWtlOiBTb3VyY2U/",
            "answer": "Q1YtNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBudW1iZXJzIGRpZCBTYXlha2EgTWFpem9ubyB3cml0ZSBvbiB0aGUgd2FsbCBpbiBEYW5nYW4gUm9ucGEgVHJpZ2dlciBIYXBweSBIYXZvYz8=",
            "answer": "MTEwMzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBTb2xpZCBTbmFrZSdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWVyIGNsYXNzIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMj8=",
            "answer": "SGVhbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgdGhlIFBhb3B1IGZydWl0IGlzIHNhaWQgdG8gaW50ZXJ0d2luZSB0aGUgZGVzdGluaWVzIGZvciB0d28gcGVvcGxlIGZvcmV2ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2FtZSBEZXZlbG9wbWVudCBjb21wYW55IG1hZGUgTm8gTWFuJ3MgU2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGVsbG8gR2FtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IHZlcnNpb24gb2YgQmxvY2tsYW5kIGNhbWUgb3V0IGluIHdoaWNoIHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUnVzdCwgaG93IG1hbnkgVGltZWQgRXhwbG9zaXZlIENoYXJnZXMgZG9lcyBpdCB0YWtlIHRvIGRlc3Ryb3kgYSBMYWRkZXIgSGF0Y2g/",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdm9pY2UgY2hhbm5lbHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgU3VwZXIgTmludGVuZG8gRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTeXN0ZW0gc3VwcG9ydD8=",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGl0ZW1zIGlzIE5PVCBjcmFmdGVkIGF0IGEgTXl0aHJpbCBBbnZpbD8=",
            "answer": "QW5raCBDaGFybQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSGVyb2VzIG9mIHRoZSBTdG9ybSwgdGhlIEN1cnNlZCBIb2xsb3cgbWFwIGdpbW1pY2sgcmVxdWlyZXMgcGxheWVycyB0byBraWxsIHRoZSB1bmRlYWQgdG8gY3Vyc2UgdGhlIGVuZW15IHRlYW0u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mICJBY2UgQ29tYmF0IFplcm86IFRoZSBCZWxrYW4gV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2lwaGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIk1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIiBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgbW9uc3RlciAiR29idWwiPw==",
            "answer": "TW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgVHJp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1hY2hpbmUgdGhhdCB1cGdyYWRlcyB3ZWFwb25zPw==",
            "answer": "UGFjay1BLVB1bmNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGZhc3Rlc3QgdGF1bnQga2lsbCB0aGF0IGNhbiBiZSBwdWxsZWQgb2ZmPw==",
            "answer": "U2hvd2Rvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIkx1aWdpJ3MgTWFuc2lvbiAzIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAzMXN0LCAyMDE5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGNhbiB5b3UgcmVjcnVpdCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBTdWlrb2RlbiBpbiBhIHNpbmdsZSBwbGF5dGhyb3VnaD8=",
            "answer": "MTA3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFjaGluZSB0aGF0IGZhaWxzIGFuZCBlc3NlbnRpYWxseSBkb29tcyBtYW5raW5kIGluIHRoZSBiZWdpbm5pbmcgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEhhbGYtTGlmZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aS1tYXNzIHNwZWN0cm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdlcmUgYWNoaXZlbWVudHMgYWRkZWQgdG8gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCB3aGF0J3MgdGhlIHByaXplIGZvciBhbnN3ZXJpbmcgY29ycmVjdGx5Pw==",
            "answer": "TW9yZSBxdWVzdGlvbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaG9ycm9yIG1vdmllIGhhZCBhIHNlcXVlbCBpbiB0aGUgZm9ybSBvZiBhIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gQXVndXN0IDIwLCAyMDAyPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRoaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZmxhZ3NoaXAgbW9uc3RlcnMgYXBwZWFyIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIEdlcm5lcmF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBIZWFydGhzdG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciB3aGljaCBQb3J0YWwgMiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgd2FzIG5vdCBhIFRWIG9yIGZpbG0gYWN0b3IgcHJpb3IgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "R0xhRE9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCB3YXMgYWxtb3N0IGJhc2VkIG9uIEplYW4tQ2xhdWRlIFZhbiBEYW1tZSBtb3ZpZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmUsIHdoYXQncyB0aGUgcmFyaXR5IG9mIGRpc2NvbnRpbnVlZCBza2lucyBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "Q29udHJhYmFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGlzbmV5J3MgIlRvb250b3duIE9ubGluZSIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNwZWNpZXMgd2Fzbid0IGF2YWlsYWJsZSBhcyBhIFRvb24/",
            "answer": "Q293"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUsIEhhbGYtbGlmZSwgd2hhdCBldmVudCBzdGFydGVkIHRoZSBIYWxmLWxpZmUgdW5pdmVyc2UgYXMgd2Uga25vdyB0b2RheT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJlc29uYW5jZSBDYXNjYWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmludGVuZG8gc3RhcnRlZCBvdXQgYXMgYSBwbGF5aW5nIGNhcmQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgd2FzIFRpdGFuZmFsbCBtYWRlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "U291cmNlIEVuZ2luZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MuIiwgdGhlIGNsb3VkcyBhbmQgYnVzaGVzIGhhdmUgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXJ0d29yayBhbmQgYXJlIGp1c3QgZGlmZmVyZW50IGNvbG9ycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2Ygc29uZyBvbiB0aGUgbWFpbiBtZW51IGluIEhhbG8/",
            "answer": "SGFsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgU3RhcmJvdW5kIHJhY2VzIGhhcyBhIFdpbGQgV2VzdCBjdWx0dXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Tm92YWtpZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBoYWxsb3dlZW4tcmVsYXRlZCBTaW1zIDQgU3R1ZmYgUGFjayByZWxlYXNlZCBTZXB0ZW1iZXIgMjl0aCwgMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "U3Bvb2t5IFN0dWZm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gU3Vuc2hpbmUiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgNHRoIGJvc3MgaW4gdGhlIDE5OTcgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ3Jhc2ggQmFuZGljb290IDI6IENvcnRleCBTdHJpa2VzIEJhY2siPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuIE4uIEdpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBBWURBWSBzZXJpZXMsIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgaWNvbmljIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgUEFZREFZIGdhbmc/",
            "answer": "RGFsbGFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHByZS1wcm9kdWN0aW9uIG9mICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiIsIE1hcmlvIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgd2FzIG1lYW50IHRvIHNob290IGJ1bGxldHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRG90YSAxIGhlcm8gY2hhbmdlZCBnZW5kZXIgd2hlbiBwb3J0ZWQgdG8gRG90YSAyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVnaW9uIENvbW1hbmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxvIiBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIGluIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSBpcyBOZXcgTW9tYmFzYT8=",
            "answer": "S2VueWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvJ3MgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBUaHJhbGwgaW4gdGhlIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgTWV0emVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBlYXJuZWQgbXVzaWMgY29tcG9zZXIgTWlrZSBNb3Jhc2t5IHRoZSBtb3N0IGF3YXJkcyBmb3IgaGlzIHdvcms/",
            "answer": "UG9ydGFsIDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qmxpbmt5LCBQaW5reSwgSW5reSBhbmQgQ2x5ZGUgYXJlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBjbGFzc2ljIHZpZGVvIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "UGFjLU1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgYSAiMzYwIG5vLXNjb3BlIiBpcyBvbmUgZnVsbCByb3RhdGlvbiBiZWZvcmUgc2hvb3RpbmcsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJvdGF0aW9ucyB3b3VsZCBhICIxMDgwIG5vLXNjb3BlIiBiZT8=",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbGV2ZWxzIGRvZXMgTk9UIGFwcGVhciBpbiB0aGUgY29uc29sZS9QQyB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU29uaWMgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMiPw==",
            "answer": "TXVzaHJvb20gSGlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEFuaW1hbCBDcm9zc2luZyBzZXJpZXMsIHdoaWNoIGZsb3dlciBpcyBlcnJvbmVvdXNseSBjYWxsZWQgdGhlICJKYWNvYidzIExhZGRlciI/",
            "answer": "TGlseSBvZiB0aGUgVmFsbGV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hvIHdhcyBmaXJzdCB0byBoYXZlIHRoZSB0aXRsZSAiVGhlIEFzaGJyaW5nZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxleGFuZHJvcyBNb2dyYWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBtYWRlIHRoZSBKYXBhbmVzZSBSUEcgIkRyYWdvbiBRdWVzdCI/",
            "answer": "U3F1YXJlIEVuaXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgIlJvYmxveCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIlBvY2tldCBNb3J0eSIgaGFzIGEgTW9ydHkgY2FsbGVkICJQb2NrZXQgTW9ydHlzIE1vcnR5Ij8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGVyZSBkb2VzIEdyZWdnIHdvcms/",
            "answer": "U25hY2sgRmFsY29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIk1lZ2Fsb3ZhbmlhIiBieSBUb2J5IEZveCBtYWRlIGl0cyB0aGlyZCBhcHBlYXJlbmNlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE1IFJQRyAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHRvIGJlIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IGRldmVsb3BtZW50IGNvbXBhbnkgUmFyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2xhbG9t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2h5IHdhcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIFRyZXZvciBQaGlsaXBzIGRpc2NoYXJnZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgQWlyIEZvcmNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWVudGFsIEhlYWx0aCBJc3N1ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0ICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIiBnYW1lIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBmb3IgdGhlIFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uIDEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUFJPVE9UWVBFIDIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYWJpbGl0aWVzL3dlYXBvbnMgaXMgTk9UIG9idGFpbmVkIGJ5IGFuIEV2b2x2ZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGVuZHJpbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE1ldHJvaWQgc2VyaWVzIGNvbWVzIGZyb20gd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QW4gZW5lbXkgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSByZWFsIFBva8OpbW9uPw==",
            "answer": "THVtaW5pZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBTY291dCBpbiAiVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb3BlcmF0aW9uIGluICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIGludHJvZHVjZWQgdGhlICJTa3lzY3JhcGVyIiBtYXA/",
            "answer": "UmVkIENyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJWZXJub24gQ2hlcnJ5IiBpbiAiUmVkIERlYWQgUmVkZW1wdGlvbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2FzZXkgTW9uZ2lsbG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHZpbGxhaW4gb2YgdGhlIENyYXNoIEJhbmRpY29vdCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "RHIuIE5lbyBDb3J0ZXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBuYW1lIGluICJCcmFpZCI/",
            "answer": "VGlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBDb0QgIkRlYXRoc3RyZWFrIiBpcyBvbmx5IGZlYXR1cmVkIGluIENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSA6IE1vZGVybiBXYXJmYXJlIDI/",
            "answer": "Q29weWNhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYSVYsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIERlZXAgRHVuZ2VvbiB0aGF0IHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSBleHBhbnNpb24gcGFjaywgSGVhdmVuc3dhcmQ/",
            "answer": "UGFsYWNlIG9mIHRoZSBEZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGlzIE5PVCBwbGF5YWJsZSBpbiAiUmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCA2Ij8=",
            "answer": "SmlsbCBWYWxlbnRpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb21tZXJjaWFsIHZlaGljbGVzIGZyb20gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBJViBkaWQgTk9UIHJlYXBwZWFyIGluIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gVj8=",
            "answer": "U3RlZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWVyeWwgU2lsdmVyYnVyZ2gsIGEgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgZnJvbSB0aGUgTWV0YWwgR2VhciBzZXJpZXMsIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGEgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHdoaWNoIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "UG9saWNlbmF1dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyB0aGUgbWFzY290IG9mIHRoZSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNvbXBhbnkgU0VHQT8=",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRG90YSAyLCBXcmFpdGggS2luZyB3YXMgcHJldmlvdXNseSBrbm93biBhcy4uLg==",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24gS2luZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyB0aGUgV2FsbCBvZiBGbGVzaCBub3QgZHJvcCB1cG9uIGRlZmVhdD8=",
            "answer": "UGlja3Nhdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgd29ybGQgdGhhdCB0aGUgTU1PICJSdW5lU2NhcGUiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "R2llbGlub3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyBFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IFN5c3RlbSB2b2ljZSBjaGFubmVscyBzdXBwb3J0cyBwbGF5YmFjayBvZiBzb3VuZCBzYW1wbGVzLiBXaGljaCBvbmU/",
            "answer": "RE1D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIlN5c3RlbSBTaG9jayIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAiQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIiBzZXJpZXMgdXNlcyB0aGUgcGhyYXNlICJ6aXAgem9vbSIgd2hlbiB0YWxraW5nIHRvIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXI/",
            "answer": "U2Nvb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogViwgd2hhdCB3YW50ZWQgbGV2ZWwgZG9lcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIHJlY2VpdmUgaWYgdGhleSBlbnRlciBaYW5jdWRvIEFybXkgQmFzZSBub3J0aCBvZiBMb3MgU2FudG9zPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyB3YXMgTk9UIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIFZhbHZlJ3MgT3JhbmdlIEJveD8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHN1cnZpdmFsIGhvcnJvciBnYW1lLCAiQ3J5IG9mIEZlYXIsIiB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTaW1vbidzIGNsb3NlIGZyaWVuZC9wb3RlbnRpYWwgbG92ZSBpbnRlcmVzdD8=",
            "answer": "U29waGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUksIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBhbnRhZ29uaXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "UmF1bCBNZW7DqW5kZXog"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgb2YgTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCAyPw==",
            "answer": "UmFpZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGhlcm8gaW4gdGhlIDgwcyBhbmltYXRlZCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lICdEcmFnb24ncyBMYWlyJz8=",
            "answer": "RGlyayB0aGUgRGFyaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgVGhyYWxsIGlzIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCB3aWVsZGVyIG9mICJEb29taGFtbWVyIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4gaXMgc2FpZCB0byBoYXZlIGJ1cm50IGFuZCBkZXN0cm95ZWQgd2hhdCBmb29kIGluIHRoZSBicmVhayByb29tIG1pY3Jvd2F2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Fzc2Vyb2xl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgem9tYmllcyBuZWVkIHRvIGJlIGtpbGxlZCB0byBnZXQgdGhlICJab21iaWUgR2Vub2NpZGVyIiBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAoMjAwNik/",
            "answer": "NTMsNTk0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyLCBiZWluZyBkaXNndWlzZWQgYXMgYSBzY291dCBvciBtZWRpYyByZXN1bHRzIGluIGEgc3BlZWQgYm9vc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gT3ZlcndhdGNoLCBob3cgb2xkIGlzIFJlaW5oYXJkdCBXaWxoZWxtPw==",
            "answer": "NjE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3b24gdGhlICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIEludml0YXRpb25hbCBFdmVudCBGZWJydWFyeSAyMDE3IGluIHRoZSBQQyBDYXRlZ29yeT8=",
            "answer": "Q29udGludXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG9ieSBGb3gncyAiTWVnYWxvdmFuaWEiIHdhcyBmaXJzdCB1c2VkIHdoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "UmFkaWF0aW9uJ3MgRWFydGhib3VuZCBIYWxsb3dlZW4gSGFjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgbWFpbiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnIHdpbGwgcmV3YXJkIHlvdSB3aXRoIHRoZSBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCwgIkxpdHRsZSBMb3N0IEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "T3JpZ2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwcm9zZWN1dG9yIGluIHRoZSAiQWNlIEF0dG9ybmV5IiB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SmFrZSBNYXJzaGFsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW50aWwgRGF3biwgYm90aCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIFNhbSBhbmQgTWlrZSBjYW5ub3QgYmUga2lsbGVkIHVuZGVyIGFueSBtZWFucyB1bnRpbCB0aGUgZmluYWwgY2hhcHRlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgaW4gdGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGljaCBpbnN0cnVtZW50IGRpZCBDYXNleSBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1bXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU2t5bGFuZGVycyBHaWFudHMsIHdoeSB3YXMgWmFwcycgV293IFBvdyBuYW1lZCAiRm9yIFJpbGV5IiA/",
            "answer": "QXMgYSB0cmlidXRlIHRvIGEgZmFuIHdobyBwYXNzZWQgYXdheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMsIERPVEEgMiwgU21pdGUgYW5kIEhlcm9lcyBvZiB0aGUgU3Rvcm0gYXJlIGFsbCBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGdhbWUgZ2VucmU/",
            "answer": "TXVsdGlwbGF5ZXIgT25saW5lIEJhdHRsZSBBcmVuYSAoTU9CQSk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgcml2YWwgZ2FuZyBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBTYWludCdzIFJvdyAyPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFppbiBFbXBpcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNseSBDb29wZXIgZnJhbmNoaXNlLCB3aGF0IGZhbWlseSBoZWlybG9vbSBkaWQgU2x5IENvb3BlciB3YW50IHRvIHN0ZWFsIGJhY2s/",
            "answer": "VGhpZXZpdXMgUmFjY29vbnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgd2VhcG9uIHlvdSBhY3F1aXJlIGluIEhhbGYtTGlmZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBjcm93YmFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxmLUxpZmUiIHNlcmllcywgIkguRS5WIiBzdGFuZHMgZm9yICJIYXphcmRvdXMgRXZhc2l2ZW5lc3MgVmVzdCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgZG8geW91IGZpZ2h0IHRoZSBJbXByaXNvbmVkIGluIFRoZSBMZWdlbmQgb2YgWmVsZGE6IFNreXdhcmQgU3dvcmQ/",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBnYW1lJ3MgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBldmVyIGNyZWF0ZWQgUG9rw6ltb24/",
            "answer": "Umh5aG9ybg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgaW5mYW1vdXMgQ2l0YWRlbCBTdGF0aW9uIEEuSSBrbm93biBhcyBTLkguTy5ELkEuTiwgaW4gdGhlIFN5c3RlbSBTaG9jayBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "VGVycmkgQnJvc2l1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlBlcnNvbmEgNCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNhbm9uaWNhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "WXUgTmFydWthbWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIFN0cmVldCBGaWdodGVyIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFpIFNoaXJhbnVp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGVyayB0aGF0IHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiBtYXAsICJNb2IgT2YgVGhlIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWMgQ2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJSSIgWm9tYmllcywgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgYWxsIHRoZSBtYWluIGVhc3RlciBlZ2dzIHJld2FyZCB5b3Ugd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAwIFhQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBzdHJlYW1pbmcgcGxhdGZvcm0gVHdpdGNoVFYgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgbmFtZSBvZiBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhWPw==",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBWZXJzdXMgWElJSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgU2NvdXQncyBjaXR5IG9mIG9yaWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "Qm9zdG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdmFuaWxsYSBNaW5lY3JhZnQsIHlvdSBjYW4gbWFrZSBhcm1vciBvdXQgb2YgYWxsIEJVVCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "RW1lcmFsZHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0YXJ0aW5nIHBpc3RvbCBvZiB0aGUgVGVycm9yaXN0IHRlYW0gaW4gYSBjb21wZXRpdGl2ZSBtYXRjaCBvZiBDb3VudGVyIFN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZSBpcyB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "R2xvY2stMTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTGVmdCA0IERlYWQgMiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMTcsIDIwMDk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIFRvdWhvdSBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "WnVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkxlYWd1ZSBvZiBMZWdlbmRzIiwgdGhlcmUgZXhpc3RzIGZvdXIgZGlmZmVyZW50IHR5cGVzIG9mIERyYWdvbi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgdGVhbSBsZWFkZXIgaW4gUG9rw6ltb24gR08/",
            "answer": "TGVpZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRlRMOiBGYXN0ZXIgVGhhbiBMaWdodCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiBtYXAgdG8gaW50cm9kdWNlIHRoZSAiV3VuZGVyd2FmZmUgREctMiI/",
            "answer": "U2hpIE5vIE51bWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiRGVyIFJpZXNlIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgIlBhY2stQS1QdW5jaGVkIFBQU0gtNDEiPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJlYXBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUG9rw6ltb24gY2FuIGxlYXJuIHRoZSBtb3ZlICJTZWNyZXQgUG93ZXIiIGJ5IGxldmVsaW5nIHVwPw==",
            "answer": "QXVkaW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBoYXMgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgbWFwIHNpemU/",
            "answer": "SnVzdCBDYXVzZSAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVbHRpbWF0ZSBkb2VzIE1ha290byBOYWVnaSwgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2MsIGhhdmU/IA==",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hdGUgTHVja3kgU3R1ZGVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIFRvYnkgRm94LCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbWV0aG9kIHRvIGNyZWF0aW5nIHRoZSBpbml0aWFsIHR1bmUgZm9yIE1lZ2Fsb3ZhbmlhPw==",
            "answer": "U2luZ2luZyBpbnRvIGEgTWljcm9waG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyLCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiTW9yZW5hdHN1IiwgaGFzIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBvc3NpYmxlIGVuZGluZ3MgdG8gdGhlaXIgcm91dGUsIGF0IGEgdG90YWwgb2YgZm91ciBkaWZmZXJlbnQgZW5kaW5ncz8=",
            "answer": "U2hpbiBLdXJvaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBmYWN0aW9uIGluIFRvbSBDbGFuY3kncyBUaGUgRGl2aXNpb24/",
            "answer": "Q0RD"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGF2aWQgQmFzenVja2kgd2FzIGEgY28tZm91bmRlciBvZiBST0JMT1ggQ29ycG9yYXRpb24u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgMzogU25ha2UgRWF0ZXIiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDA0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU2FtYW50aGEgTWF4aXMnIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "Rmx1ZmZ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgdGFrZXMgcGxhY2UgaW4gdGhlIElyaXNoIHRvd24gb2YgRG9vbGluLCB3aXRoIHRoZSBvcHRpb24gdG8gcGxheSBhcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMsIEVsbGVuIGFuZCBLZWF0cz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9sa2xvcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICc2NCcgaW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvLTY0IGNvbnNvbGUgcmVmZXJzIHRvIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIGJpdHMgaW4gdGhlIENQVSBhcmNoaXRlY3R1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R29sZGVuRXllIDAwNyBvbiB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gNjQgd2FzIHBsYW5uZWQgdG8gYWxsb3cgeW91IHRvIHBsYXkgYXMgYWxsIHByZXZpb3VzIEJvbmQgYWN0b3JzLCB3aXRoIHRoZSBleGNlcHRpb24gb2Ygd2hvPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIExhemVuYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgdGVhbSBhdmFpbGFibGUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gR28/",
            "answer": "VGVhbSBSb2NrZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmluYWwgYm9zcyBpbiBUdXJvazogRGlub3NhdXIgSHVudGVyPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIENhbXBhaWduZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIEFkdmVudHVyZSIsIHlvdSBhcmUgYWJsZSB0byB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBTdXBlciBTb25pYyBhdCB3aWxsIGFmdGVyIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgdGhlIG1haW4gc3Rvcnku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGFyayBTb3Vscywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcmVnaW9uIHlvdSdyZSBpbiBmb3IgdGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TG9yZHJhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiB0aGUgdmlkZW9nYW1lICJEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2h1Y2sgR3JlZW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbGYtTGlmZSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgImdyYXZpdHkgZ3VuIj8=",
            "answer": "WmVyby1Qb2ludCBFbmVyZ3kgRmllbGQgTWFuaXB1bGF0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nOiBOZXcgTGVhZiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGFpbnRpbmdzIGZyb20gUmVkZCdzIEFydCBHYWxsZXJ5IGlzIGFsd2F5cyBnZW51aW5lPw==",
            "answer": "V2FybSBQYWludGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2YXVsdCBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiRmFsbG91dCAzIiBpcyB0aGUgaG9tZSBvZiBtdWx0aXBsZSBjbG9uZXMgbmFtZWQgR2FyeT8=",
            "answer": "VmF1bHQgMTA4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBEZXN0aW55Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2F5ZGUtNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNsYXNoIFJveWFsZSIgd2hhdCBpcyBBcmVuYSA0IGNhbGxlZD8=",
            "answer": "UC5FLksuSy5BJ3MgUGxheWhvdXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlBvcnRhbCAyIiwgQ2F2ZSBKb2huc29uIHN0YXJ0ZWQgb3V0IEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2UgYXMgYSBzaG93ZXIgY3VydGFpbiBjb21wYW55Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2FwY29tJ3Mgc3Vydml2YWwgaG9ycm9yIHRpdGxlIERlYWQgUmlzaW5nLCBjYW5vbmljYWxseSBzdGFydHMgb24gd2hhdCBkYXkgb2YgU2VwdGVtYmVyIDIwMDY/",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDE5dGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJEYXkgb2YgRGVmZWF0IiBzZXJpZXMgb2YgZ2FtZXMgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBkdXJpbmcgd2hpY2ggd2FyPw==",
            "answer": "V29ybGQgV2FyIElJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzb25nIGlzIHBsYXllZCBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIGVuZGluZyBjcmVkaXRzIG9mIEd1aXRhciBIZXJvOiBXb3JsZCBUb3VyPw==",
            "answer": "RHJlYW0gVGhlYXRlciAtIFB1bGwgTWUgVW5kZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9wdWxhciBGaXJzdCBQZXJzb24gU2hvb3RlciAoRlBTKSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIGdvdCBhIFJlYWwgVGltZSBTdHJhdGVneSAoUlRTKSBnYW1lIGRldmVsb3BlZCBiYXNlZCBvbiBpdHMgdW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "SGFsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29waWVzIG9mIHRoZSBub3RvcmlvdXMgRS5ULiBnYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgQXRhcmkgMjYwMCBkaWQgQXRhcmkgZW5kIHVwIHNlbGxpbmc/",
            "answer": "MS41IE1pbGxpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgTnVjbGVhciBUaHJvbmUsIHdoYXQgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIG9ubHkgdXNhYmxlIGluIGEgcGxheSB0aHJvdWdoIHdpdGggTWVsdGluZz8=",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgY3JlYXRlZCBieSBNYXNhaGlybyBTYWt1cmFpIGFuZCBTYXRvcnUgSXdhdGEgdGhhdCB3b3VsZCBldmVudHVhbGx5IGV2b2x2ZSBpbnRvICJTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiI/",
            "answer": "RHJhZ29uIEtpbmc6IFRoZSBGaWdodGluZyBHYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBDUzpHTyBjYXNlIGNvbnRhaW5zIHRoZSBCdXR0ZXJmbHkgS25pZmU/",
            "answer": "QnJlYWtvdXQgQ2FzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBnYW1lIHdhcyB1c2VkIHRvIGFkdmVydGlzZSBTdGVhbT8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgMS42"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGdhbWVzIGNhbWUgb3V0IGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGVycmFyaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgTGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hhdCBtaXNzaW9uIGFyZSBEb25hbGQgYW5kIEdvb2Z5IGFzc2lnbmVkIGJ5IEtpbmcgTWlja2V5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG8gZmluZCB0aGUgS2V5IGJlYXJlciBhbmQgc3RpY2sgd2l0aCBoaW0h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEFSUEcgIlBhdGggb2YgRXhpbGUsIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGFtb3VudCBvZiBzb2NrZXRzIHRoYXQgYW4gaXRlbSBjYW4gaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhcnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIHRvIGNvbGxlY3QgaW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gNjQ/",
            "answer": "MTIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggT3ZlcndhdGNoIGNoYXJhY3RlciBzYXlzIHRoZSBsaW5lICJIZXJvZXMgbmV2ZXIgZGllISI/",
            "answer": "TWVyY3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IG51bWJlcmVkIHBvd2VyIGdlbmVyYXRvcnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2V2ZXJhbCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGluICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyA2NCIgYmxpbmsgdGhlaXIgZXllcywgaW5jbHVkaW5nIE1hcmlvIGhpbXNlbGYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBQb2vDqW1vbidzIEJhc2UgU3RhdCBUb3RhbCBkb2VzIG5vdCBjaGFuZ2Ugd2hlbiBpdCBldm9sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2N5dGhlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGFyZGVzdCBwb3NzaWJsZSBkaWZmaWN1bHR5IGluICJEZXVzIEV4OiBNYW5raW5kIERpdmlkZWQiPw==",
            "answer": "SSBOZXZlciBBc2tlZCBGb3IgVGhpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UG9rw6ltb24gR28gaXMgYSBsb2NhdGlvbi1iYXNlZCBhdWdtZW50ZWQgcmVhbGl0eSBnYW1lIGRldmVsb3BlZCBhbmQgcHVibGlzaGVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbXBhbnk/",
            "answer": "TmlhbnRpYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdmFuaWxsYSBNaW5lY3JhZnQsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgY2Fubm90IGJlIG1hZGUgaW50byBhIGJsb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmNvYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F2ZSBHYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiAiR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBJViI/",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjksIDIwMDg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgbm90IGRldmVsb3BlZCBieSBCZXRoZXNkYT8=",
            "answer": "RmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSAgRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTb2Z0d2FyZSBSYXRpbmdzIEJvYXJkIChFU1JCKSBpcyBvZnRlbiBhc3NvY2lhdGVkIHdpdGggTW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCBhbmQgd2hhdCBGTVYgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "TmlnaHQgVHJhcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkZpcmUgRW1ibGVtOiBTaGFkb3cgRHJhZ29uIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2VudHJhbCBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCdzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "TWFydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIHRvIHRoZSBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zIGZyYW5jaGlzZSBpbiBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zIE1lbGVlPw==",
            "answer": "U2hlaWs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW5nbGlzaCBuZXcgd2F2ZSBtdXNpY2lhbiBHYXJ5IE51bWFuIGZvdW5kZWQgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgY29tcGFueSBGYWNlcHVuY2ggU3R1ZGlvcyBpbiBNYXJjaCAyMDA5Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB2aWxsYWluIGNvbXBhbnkgaW4gIlN0YXJkZXcgVmFsbGV5Ij8=",
            "answer": "Sm9qYSBDbyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGV0cmlzIGlzIHRoZSAjMSBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBvZiBhbGwtdGltZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkNhdmUgU3RvcnksIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgQmFscm9nJ3MgY2F0Y2hwaHJhc2U/",
            "answer": "SHV6emFoIQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYSBmcmFuY2hpc2Ugd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIE5vcnRoIEFtZXJpY2EgYmVmb3JlIEphcGFuPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVHdpbGlnaHQgUHJpbmNlc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYWNlcyBjYW4gYmUgc2hvdCBkb3duIHRocm91Z2ggdGhlIGVudGlyZXR5IG9mICJBY2UgQ29tYmF0IFplcm86IFRoZSBCZWxrYW4gV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "MTY5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlJlZCBEZWFkIFJlZGVtcHRpb24iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEpvaG4gTWFyc3RvbidzIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "UnVmdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hvIGFiZHVjdHMgSmFzbWluZSBpbiB0aGUgTGFtcCBDaGFtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "UmlrdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbmdyZWRpZW50IGlzIE5PVCB1c2VkIHRvIGNyYWZ0IGEgY2FrZSBpbiBNaW5lY3JhZnQ/",
            "answer": "QnJlYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIHB1bXAgIkYuTC5VLkQuRC4iIE1hcmlvIHVzZXMgaW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gU3Vuc2hpbmU/",
            "answer": "RWx2aW4gR2FkZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIExlZ28gSXNsYW5kIHRyaWxvZ3ksIHdobyB0YXVnaHQgUGVwcGVyIFJvbmkgaG93IHRvIHJlYWQ/",
            "answer": "T2ZmaWNlciBMYXVyYSBCcmljaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIHdlYXBvbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBkZWFsIGFueSBkYW1hZ2U/",
            "answer": "MzEtNzkgSkdiMjE1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG1haW4gY3VycmVuY3kgaW4gQ2x1YiBQZW5ndWluPw==",
            "answer": "Q29pbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpZ2h0aW5nIGdhbWUgIlNrdWxsZ2lybHMsIiB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgdXRpbGl6ZXMgYSBmb2xkaW5nIGNoYWlyIGNhbGxlZCB0aGUgIkh1cnRpbmciIGFzIGEgd2VhcG9uPw==",
            "answer": "QmVvd3VsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBGb3IgU3BlZWQgTW9zdCBXYW50ZWQgKDIwMDUpLCB3aGF0IGRvIHlvdSBkcml2ZSBhdCB0aGUgYmVnaW5uaW5nIG9mIHRoZSBjYXJlZXIgbW9kZT8=",
            "answer": "Qk1XIE0zIEdUUg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIHRoZSBXb3JsZCBSZWNvcmQgU3BlZWQgUnVuIG9mIFZhbHZlIFNvZnR3YXJlJ3MgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSIgdGhhdCB3YXMgZG9uZSBpbiAyMDE0Lg==",
            "answer": "MjAgTWludXRlcywgNDEgU2Vjb25kcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBhbnRhZ29uaXN0IG9mIE1heCBQYXluZSAzICgyMDEyKT8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yIEJyYW5jbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmViZWNjYSBDaGFtYmVycyBkb2VzIG5vdCBhcHBlYXIgaW4gYW55IFJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgZXhjZXB0IGZvciB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgUmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCBhbmQgdGhlIEdhbWVjdWJlIHJlbWFrZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIlBlcmstQS1Db2xhIiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiB3YXMgInJld29ya2VkIiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUkiPw==",
            "answer": "RG91YmxlIFRhcCBSb290IEJlZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdob3N0cyBpbiAiUGFjLU1hbiIgYW5kICJNcy4gUGFjLU1hbiIgaGF2ZSBjb21wbGV0ZWx5IGRpZmZlcmVudCBiZWhhdmlvci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgYm9zcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGVuY291bnRlcnMgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTcgZ2FtZSwgIkxpdHRsZSBOaWdodG1hcmVzIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEphbml0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGF0IGlzIE1hZSBCb3Jvd3NraSBtb3RoZXIncyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuZHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgR2FycnkncyBNb2Qgb3JpZ2luYWxseSB0b29rIGFzc2V0cyBhbmQgY29kZXMgZnJvbSB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBIYWxmIExpZmUgMiBtb2QgSkJtb2Qu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBQb3RhdG8gU2FjayIgd2FzIGEgY29sbGVjdGlvbiBvZiBpbmRpZSBnYW1lcyByZWxlYXNlZCBvbiBTdGVhbSBpbiAyMDExIGFzIGEgcHJvbW90aW9uIGZvciB3aGljaCBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UG9ydGFsIDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBDYWxsIG9mIER1dHkgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIGEgUFMzIGxhdW5jaCB0aXRsZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5IDM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gY2FyZWVyIG1vZGUgb2YgIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkOiBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZCAyIiwgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNhciB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGNhbiBkcml2ZSBpcyB0aGUgQk1XIE0zIEdUUi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBUaGUgSGVhdnkncyB2b2ljZSBhY3RvciwgR2FyeSBTY2h3YXJ0eiwgdm9pY2VzIHRoZSBEZW1vbWFuIGFzIHdlbGwg",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgRnJhbmsgV2VzdCdzIGpvYiBpbiAiRGVhZCBSaXNpbmciPw==",
            "answer": "UGhvdG9qb3VybmFsaXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBaZWxkYSBnYW1lcyBkaWQgbm90IGZlYXR1cmUgR2Fub24gYXMgYSBmaW5hbCBib3NzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFqb3JhJ3MgTWFzaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBoYWxmLWRlbW9uIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBEaXZpbml0eTogT3JpZ2luYWwgU2luIDIgd2hvIHlvdSB0YWxrIHRvIHRvIHRyYW5zaXRpb24gYmV0d2VlbiBhY3RzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFsYWR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBOYXRpb25hbGl0eSBpcyBELlZhIGZyb20gT3ZlcndhdGNoPw==",
            "answer": "S29yZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgRExDIHZlaGljbGUgaW4gIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgOCI/",
            "answer": "V2lsZCBXaWdnbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIHdoZXJlIGlzICJTdGFtaW4tVXAiIGxvY2F0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "R2VuZXJhdG9yIDU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlRoZSBTaW1zIiwgaG93IG1hbnkgU2ltb2xlb25zIGRvZXMgZWFjaCBmYW1pbHkgc3RhcnQgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "MjAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVuZCBjcmVkaXRzIHNlcXVlbmNlIGluIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gNSBpcyBvdmVyIGhhbGYgYW4gaG91ciBsb25nLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gQ29ucXVlc3QsIHdoaWNoIHdhcmxvcmQgaXMgYWJsZSB0byBib25kIHdpdGggWmVrcm9tIGFuZCBhIHNoaW55IFJheXF1YXp6YT8=",
            "answer": "Tm9idW5hZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmluY2V3aW5kIGZyb20gdGhlIDE5OTUgRGlzY3dvcmxkIGdhbWUgd2FzIHZvaWNlZCBieSB3aGljaCBtZW1iZXIgb2YgTW9udHkgUHl0aG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBJZGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEludGVybmV0IE1lbWUgIkFsbCB5b3VyIGJhc2UgYXJlIGJlbG9uZyB0byB1cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb24gdGhlIHBvb3JseSB0cmFuc2xhdGVkIEVuZ2xpc2ggVmVyc2lvbiBvZiB3aGljaCBWaWRlbyBHYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "WmVybyBXaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIDY0IiwgY29sbGVjdGluZyAxMDAgY29pbnMgb24gYSBsZXZlbCB3aWxsIGdpdmUgeW91IGEgMS1VUC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgZG8geW91IGZpZ2h0IEdpbGdhbWVzaCBpbiAiRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSA1Ij8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEdhbWVjdWJlIFZlcnNpb24gb2YgIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwiIHdoYXQgdGV4dCBkb2N1bWVudCBpcyBvcGVuIG9uIHRoZSBtb25pdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBjb21wdXRlciBpbiB0aGUgVmlzdWFsIERhdGEgUm9vbT8=",
            "answer": "QSBHREMgRG9jdW1lbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkxlYWd1ZSBvZiBMZWdlbmRzIiB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMga25vd24gYXMgIlRoZSBTaW5pc3RlciBCbGFkZSI/",
            "answer": "S2F0YXJpbmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBBWURBWSAyIiwgd2hhdCB3ZWFwb24gaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGJhc2Ugd2VhcG9uIGRhbWFnZSBvbiBhIHBlci1zaG90IGJhc2lzPw==",
            "answer": "SFJMLTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwZW9wbGUgY2FuIE5PVCB3aWVsZCBhIGtleWJsYWRlPw==",
            "answer": "TGFyeGVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiBjYW5vbiwgd2hhdCBkaWQgU2hha2VzcGVhcmljbGVzIE5PVCBpbnZlbnQ/",
            "answer": "U3RhaXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxvbmcgd2l0aCBHYWJlIE5ld2VsbCwgd2hvIGNvLWZvdW5kZWQgVmFsdmU/",
            "answer": "TWlrZSBIYXJyaW5ndG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIFRvbSBOb29rJ3MgY291c2lucyBpbiB0aGUgQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIGZyYW5jaGlzZSBhcmUgbmFtZWQgIlRpbW15IiBhbmQgIkppbW15Ii4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcHJvdmlkZWQgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGZvciB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBmYXRoZXIgaW4gRmFsbG91dCAzPw==",
            "answer": "TGlhbSBOZWVzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSdzIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgSGFsZi1MaWZlIGFyZSB0aGUgSEVDVSBNYXJpbmVzIHJlcGxhY2VkIHdpdGggcm9ib3RzPw==",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gQnJvcy4sIHdobyBpbmZvcm1zIE1hcmlvIHRoYXQgdGhlIHByaW5jZXNzIGlzIGluIGFub3RoZXIgY2FzdGxlPw==",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBsb3JlIG9mICJTdGFyYm91bmQiLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgdGhlICJDb2xvbnkgRGVlZCIgZG8gd2hlbiBpdCBpcyBwbGFjZWQgZG93bj8=",
            "answer": "U2VuZHMgb3V0IGFuIGFkdmVydGlzZW1lbnQgZm9yIHNvbWVvbmUgdG8gbW92ZSBpbi4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGlhYmxvIGxvcmUsIHRoaXMgbGVzc2VyIGV2aWwgc3Bhd25lZCBmcm9tIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgc2V2ZW4gaGVhZHMgb2YgVGF0aGFtZXQsIGFuZCB3YXMga25vd24gYXMgdGhlIE1haWRlbiBvZiBBbmd1aXNoLg==",
            "answer": "QW5kYXJpZWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgSGFsZi1MaWZlLCB3aGljaCBlbmVteSBpcyBzaG93Y2FzZWQgYXMgdGhlIGZpbmFsIGJvc3M/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5paGlsYW50aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgJ1BvcnRhbCAyJyByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFRvdWhvdSBQcm9qZWN0IHNlcmllcyBvZiBnYW1lcyBpcyBvZnRlbiBhc3NvY2lhdGVkIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggZ2VucmU/",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ2VtIHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggZGlkIHRoZSBpbmRpZSBnYW1lICJDYXZlIFN0b3J5IiBjb3N0IHdoZW4gaXQgd2FzIGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDIwMDQ/",
            "answer": "JDAgVVNE"
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9hcmQgR2FtZXM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiBKYXBhbj8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyOSwgMTk4OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGV0ZXIgTW9seW5ldXggd2FzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mIEJ1bGxmcm9nIFByb2R1Y3Rpb25zLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBTaW1zIiBzZXJpZXMsIHRoZSBtb3N0IG1lbWJlcnMgaW4gYSBob3VzZWhvbGQgeW91IGNhbiBoYXZlIGlzIDgu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkdhbGFnYSIgd2FzIGEgc2VxdWVsIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "R2FsYXhpYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBmYW1vdXMgbGluZSBWYWFzIHNheXMgaW4gIkZhciBDcnkgMyI/",
            "answer": "RGlkIEkgZXZlciB0ZWxsIHlvdSB0aGUgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiBvZiBJbnNhbml0eT8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIncyBIZWF2eSBXZWFwb25zIEd1eSdzIG1pbmlndW4/",
            "answer": "U2FzaGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBleHBlbnNpdmUgd2VhcG9uIGluIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "U2Nhci0yMC9HM1NHMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIGRvZXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0dXJlICJTbG93cG9rZSIgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "UG9rZW1vbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHJpZ2h0cyB0byB0aGUgIlJheW1hbiIgc2VyaWVzIGFyZSBvd25lZCBieSB3aGljaCBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "VWJpc29mdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiAiTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCAzIj8=",
            "answer": "TmFrZWQgU25ha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnQgc2VyaWVzIHdobyBwcm92aWRlcyB0aGUgZW5nbGlzaCB2b2ljZSBmb3IgTWFzdGVyIEVyYXF1cz8=",
            "answer": "TWFyayBIYW1pbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkZXZpY2UgYWxsb3dzIFRyYWNlciB0byBtYW5pcHVsYXRlIGhlciBvd24gdGltZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyb25hbCBBY2NlbGVyYXRvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUGFwZXIgTWFyaW8gZm9yIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyA2NCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcGFydG5lciB5b3UgbWVldCBpcyBhIEdvb21iYSwgd2hhdCBpcyBpdHMgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "R29vbWJhcmlv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgZ2FtZSB1bmRlciB0aGUgV29ybXMgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFqb3IgTWFsZnVuY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbXVzaWNhbCBhcnRpc3Qgd2FzIE5PVCBmZWF0dXJlZCBhcyBwbGF5YWJsZSBhdmF0YXJzIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJESiBIZXJvIj8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIERyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdmFuaWxsYSBNaW5lY3JhZnQsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgY2Fubm90IGJlIG1hZGUgaW50byBhIGJsb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmNvYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlN1Ym5hdXRpY2EiLCBhICJDYXZlIENyYXdsZXIiIHdpbGwgYXR0YWNrIHlvdS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgc3VwcG9zZWQgdG8gYmUgcGFja2FnZWQgd2l0aCBTb25pYyAzLCBidXQgd2FzIGN1dCBpbiBoYWxmIGR1ZSB0byB0aW1lIGNvbnN0cmFpbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgJiBLbnVja2xlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSGFsbyAyLCBob3cgbWFueSByb3VuZHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTTZDIGhvbGQgaW4gYSBzaW5nbGUgbWFnYXppbmU/",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGF5IGluICJQYXBlcnMsIFBsZWFzZSIgZG9lcyB0aGUgbWFuIGluIHJlZCBhcHBlYXI/",
            "answer": "RGF5IDIz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIGRldmVsb3BtZW50IG9mICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBXb3JsZCIsIFlvc2hpJ3MgaGFyZCBzYWRkbGUgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2U/",
            "answer": "QSBzaGVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmFsdmUncyAiUG9ydGFsIiBhbmQgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSIgZnJhbmNoaXNlcyBleGlzdCB3aXRoaW4gdGhlIHNhbWUgaW4tZ2FtZSB1bml2ZXJzZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgRWxpemEgIkFzaCIgQ29oZW4gZnJvbSAiVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgU2l4IFNpZWdlIiBib3JuIGluPw==",
            "answer": "SXNyYWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlRyYW5zaXN0b3IiLCAiUmVkIiBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBtb3N0IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgWVMgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QWRvbCBDaHJpc3RpbiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlJlZCBEZWFkIFJlZGVtcHRpb24iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEpvaG4gTWFyc3RvbidzIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "UnVmdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiBtYXAgdG8gaW50cm9kdWNlIHRoZSAiV3VuZGVyd2FmZmUgREctMiI/",
            "answer": "U2hpIE5vIE51bWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSIgZ2FtZSBhcmUgdGhlICJBcG90aGljb25zIiBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSBab21iaWVzIG1vZGU/",
            "answer": "Q2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUlJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGVyayB0aGF0IHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiBtYXAsICJNb2IgT2YgVGhlIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWMgQ2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1hY2hpbmUgdGhhdCB1cGdyYWRlcyB3ZWFwb25zPw==",
            "answer": "UGFjay1BLVB1bmNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBBWURBWSAyIiwgd2hhdCB3ZWFwb24gaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGJhc2Ugd2VhcG9uIGRhbWFnZSBvbiBhIHBlci1zaG90IGJhc2lzPw==",
            "answer": "SFJMLTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hZ2lja2EiLCB3aGljaCB0d28gZWxlbWVudHMgYXJlIGNvbWJpbmVkIHRvIGNhc3QgdGhlIHNwZWxsLCAiTnVsbGlmeSI/",
            "answer": "QXJjYW5lICsgU2hpZWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBQb2vDqW1vbiBEaWFtb25kICYgUGVhcmwgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkV4aWxlIiBhbmQgIlJldmVsYXRpb25zIiB3ZXJlIHRoZSB0aGlyZCBhbmQgZm91cnRoIGluc3RhbGxtZW50cyBvZiB3aGljaCBQQyBnYW1lIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TXlzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBOaW50ZW5kbyBnYW1lIGNvbnNvbGU/",
            "answer": "RHJlYW1jYXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkIElJSTogSG90IFB1cnN1aXQiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBmaWN0aW9uYWwgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "RWwgTmnDsW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQaWttaW4iIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBwaWttaW4gdHlwZSB0byBwb3NzZXNzIHZpc2libGUgZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQaWttaW4iIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHBpa21pbiBjb2xvcnMgbGFja3MgaXQncyBvd24gIk9uaW9uIiBuZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hhdCBtaXNzaW9uIGFyZSBEb25hbGQgYW5kIEdvb2Z5IGFzc2lnbmVkIGJ5IEtpbmcgTWlja2V5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG8gZmluZCB0aGUgS2V5IGJlYXJlciBhbmQgc3RpY2sgd2l0aCBoaW0h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmUsIHdoYXQncyB0aGUgcmFyaXR5IG9mIGRpc2NvbnRpbnVlZCBza2lucyBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "Q29udHJhYmFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWxsaWdhdG9yIGluIFdoZXJlJ3MgTXkgV2F0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3dhbXB5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBnYW1lIGNvbnNpc3RlZCBvZiBhIGZlbWFsZS1vbmx5IGNhc3Qgb2YgcGFydHkgbWVtYmVycz8=",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYLTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBoZW9uaXggV3JpZ2h0OiBBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHdoaWNoIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyB0aGUgRGlzdHJpY3QgQ2hpZWYgb2YgUG9saWNlPw==",
            "answer": "RGFtb24gR2FudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBWZWx2ZXQgUm9vbSBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gUGVyc29uYSA0IEFyZW5hIFVsdGltYXg/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZHJpdmUgZm9ybSB3YXMgYWRkZWQgaW50byBLaW5nZG9tIEhlYXJ0cyBJSSBGaW5hbCBNaXg/",
            "answer": "TGltaXQgRm9ybQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIkpldHBhY2sgSm95cmlkZSIgd2FzIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgIlJlZGJyaWNrIFN0dWRpb3MiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY292ZXJ0IGdyb3VwcyBlbXBsb3lzIFNhbSBGaXNoZXIgdG8gd29yayBhcyBhIFNwbGludGVyIENlbGw/",
            "answer": "VGhpcmQgRWNoZWxvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29jY2VyIHBsYXllciBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBvbiB0aGUgY292ZXIgb2YgRUEgU3BvcnQncyBGSUZBIDE4Pw==",
            "answer": "Q3Jpc3RpYW5vIFJvbmFsZG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHN5Y2hvcGF0aChzKSBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAxIGdhdmUgeW91IHRoZSBzbWFsbCBjaGFpbnNhdz8=",
            "answer": "QWRhbSB0aGUgQ2xvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgMiIsIHdoaWNoIHZpcnVzIHdhcyBXaWxsaWFtIEJpcmtpbiBtdXRhdGVkIGJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "Ry1WaXJ1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkJvcmRlcmxhbmRzIj8=",
            "answer": "R2VhcmJveCBTb2Z0d2FyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9wdWxhciBGaXJzdCBQZXJzb24gU2hvb3RlciAoRlBTKSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIGdvdCBhIFJlYWwgVGltZSBTdHJhdGVneSAoUlRTKSBnYW1lIGRldmVsb3BlZCBiYXNlZCBvbiBpdHMgdW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "SGFsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SnVzdCBDYXVzZSAyIHdhcyBtYWlubHkgc2V0IGluIHdoYXQgZmljdGlvbmFsIFNvdXRoZWFzdCBBc2lhbiBpc2xhbmQgY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuYXU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIHRoZSBlYXJsaWVzdCBrbm93biBmaXJzdC1wZXJzb24gc2hvb3RlciB3aXRoIGEga25vd24gdGltZSBvZiBwdWJsaWNhdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U3Bhc2lt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhbmNlbGxlZCBzZXF1ZWwgb2YgVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "VGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyOiBCcm90aGVyaG9vZCBvZiBBcm1z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSdzIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgSGFsZi1MaWZlIGFyZSB0aGUgSEVDVSBNYXJpbmVzIHJlcGxhY2VkIHdpdGggcm9ib3RzPw==",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIG1hZGUgR2FycnkncyBNb2Q/",
            "answer": "R2FycnkgTmV3bWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGVubmlzIGZvciBUd28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb21tZXJjaWFsIHZlaGljbGVzIGZyb20gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBJViBkaWQgTk9UIHJlYXBwZWFyIGluIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gVj8=",
            "answer": "U3RlZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYWN0b3JzIGRpZCBub3Qgdm9pY2UgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIlNhaW50cyBSb3c6IFRoZSBUaGlyZCI/",
            "answer": "Um9uIEplcmVteQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "THVpZ2kgaXMgdGFsbGVyIHRoYW4gTWFyaW8/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbmdyZWRpZW50IGlzIE5PVCB1c2VkIHRvIGNyYWZ0IGEgY2FrZSBpbiBNaW5lY3JhZnQ/",
            "answer": "QnJlYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIElXSEJZRCBzdGFuZCBmb3Igb24gdGhlIHNrdWxsIGluIHRoZSBIYWxvIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJlZW4gWW91ciBEYWRkeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNseSBDb29wZXIgZnJhbmNoaXNlLCB3aGF0IGZhbWlseSBoZWlybG9vbSBkaWQgU2x5IENvb3BlciB3YW50IHRvIHN0ZWFsIGJhY2s/",
            "answer": "VGhpZXZpdXMgUmFjY29vbnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hvIG9yZ2FuaXplZCB0aGUgY3JlYXRpb24gb2YgdGhlIFBhbGFkaW5zPw==",
            "answer": "QWxvbnN1cyBGYW9s"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoaWNoIHF1b3RlIGRvZXMgdGhlIGhlcm8gIk1jQ3JlZSIgTk9UIHNheSB1cG9uIHVzaW5nIGhpcyBmbGFzaGJhbmcgYWJpbGl0eT8=",
            "answer": "IllvdSBkb25lPyI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAoMjAwNik/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMDUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5IDI6IEJpZyBSZWQgT25lIiBpcyBub3QgYXZhaWxhYmxlIG9uIFBDLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFRvdWhvdSBQcm9qZWN0IHNlcmllcyBvZiBnYW1lcyBpcyBvZnRlbiBhc3NvY2lhdGVkIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggZ2VucmU/",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ2VtIHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBJbnN0aW5jdCBpbiBQb2vDqW1vbiBHbz8=",
            "answer": "U3Bhcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJDYXZlIFN0b3J5IiBpcyBuYW1lZA==",
            "answer": "UXVvdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgbW9uc3RlcnMgYXJlIGEgcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgIkZhdGVkIEZvdXIiPw==",
            "answer": "QXN0YWxvcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBoYWxsb3dlZW4tcmVsYXRlZCBTaW1zIDQgU3R1ZmYgUGFjayByZWxlYXNlZCBTZXB0ZW1iZXIgMjl0aCwgMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "U3Bvb2t5IFN0dWZm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIERPT00gZ2FtZXMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgZGVtb25zIGlzIGEgcmVjb2xvciBvZiB0aGUgQmFyb24gb2YgSGVsbCwgYnV0IGlzIHdlYWtlciB0aGFuIHRoZSBCYXJvbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVsbCBLbmlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgY3JlYXRlZCBieSBNYXNhaGlybyBTYWt1cmFpIGFuZCBTYXRvcnUgSXdhdGEgdGhhdCB3b3VsZCBldmVudHVhbGx5IGV2b2x2ZSBpbnRvICJTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiI/",
            "answer": "RHJhZ29uIEtpbmc6IFRoZSBGaWdodGluZyBHYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXMgTk9UIHBsYW5uZWQgdG8gYmUgcGxheWFibGUgZm9yIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIDY0Pw==",
            "answer": "UGVhY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSByZWFsIFBva8OpbW9uPw==",
            "answer": "THVtaW5pZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGZyb20gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIgd2FzIHJldmVhbGVkIHRvIGJlIGhvbW9zZXh1YWwgaW4gRGVjZW1iZXIgb2YgMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "VHJhY2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTGVmdCA0IERlYWQgMiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMTcsIDIwMDk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYSBmcmFuY2hpc2Ugd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIEphcGFuIGJlZm9yZSBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVGhlIE1pbmlzaCBDYXA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYWNlcyBjYW4gYmUgc2hvdCBkb3duIHRocm91Z2ggdGhlIGVudGlyZXR5IG9mICJBY2UgQ29tYmF0IFplcm86IFRoZSBCZWxrYW4gV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "MTY5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdW5pcXVlIGl0ZW1zIGRvZXMgIkJvcmRlcmxhbmRzIDIiIGNsYWltIHRvIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "ODcgQmF6aWxsaW9uIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIlBlcmstQS1Db2xhIiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIiB3YXMgInJld29ya2VkIiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUkiPw==",
            "answer": "RG91YmxlIFRhcCBSb290IEJlZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU2FtYW50aGEgTWF4aXMnIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "Rmx1ZmZ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFBhY2stQS1QdW5jaGVkIENyb3NzYm93Pw==",
            "answer": "QXdmdWwgTGF3dG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGZhc3Rlc3QgdGF1bnQga2lsbCB0aGF0IGNhbiBiZSBwdWxsZWQgb2ZmPw==",
            "answer": "U2hvd2Rvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbmFtZSBvZiBhIGNpdHkgaW4gdGhlIG1haW4gaXNsYW5kIG9mIFBMQVlFUlVOS05PV04nUyBCQVRUTEVHUk9VTkRTPw==",
            "answer": "QmVsdXNoeWEgR3ViYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29udHJvbGxlcnMgY291bGQgYSBOaW50ZW5kbyBHYW1lQ3ViZSBoYXZlIHBsdWdnZWQgaW4gYXQgb25lIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIGl0J3MgcmVkZXNpZ24gb2YgdGhlIGNvbXBhbnkgbG9nbyBpbiB0aGUgeWVhciAyMDAwLCB3aGljaCAzRCBzaGFwZSBpcyBOT1QgcmVwcmVzZW50ZWQgaW4gdGhlIEVsZWN0cm9uaWMgQXJ0cyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "Q3lsaW5kZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgbm90IGRldmVsb3BlZCBieSBCZXRoZXNkYT8=",
            "answer": "RmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBVQkFUVExFR1JPVU5EUyIgd2hpY2ggYW1tbyB0eXBlIGRvZXMgdGhlIE0yNCB1c2U/",
            "answer": "Ny42Mm1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2FzLCB3aGljaCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FzaW5vcyBjYW4geW91IG5vdCBwbGF5IGluPw==",
            "answer": "THVja3kgMzg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBCaWxsJ3MgbGFzdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "T3ZlcmJlY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmluY2V3aW5kIGZyb20gdGhlIDE5OTUgRGlzY3dvcmxkIGdhbWUgd2FzIHZvaWNlZCBieSB3aGljaCBtZW1iZXIgb2YgTW9udHkgUHl0aG9uPw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBJZGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGVyZSBkb2VzIEdyZWdnIHdvcms/",
            "answer": "U25hY2sgRmFsY29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICc2NCcgaW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvLTY0IGNvbnNvbGUgcmVmZXJzIHRvIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIGJpdHMgaW4gdGhlIENQVSBhcmNoaXRlY3R1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRpZCAiTWFyaW8iLCBmcm9tICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm90aGVycyIsIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "T3NzYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiAiVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIiB1cGRhdGUsIGluIHdoaWNoIGl0IGJlY2FtZSBGcmVlLXRvLXBsYXk/",
            "answer": "w5xiZXIgVXBkYXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW1hem9uIGFjcXVpcmVkIFR3aXRjaCBpbiBBdWd1c3QgMjAxNCBmb3IgJDk3MCBtaWxsaW9uIGRvbGxhcnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgb2YgTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCAyPw==",
            "answer": "UmFpZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlICJOaW50ZW5kbyBHYW1lY3ViZSI/",
            "answer": "RG9scGhpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlVuZGVydGFsZSIgaXMgYW4gUlBHIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgVG9ieSBGb3ggYW5kIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDIwMTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29waWVzIG9mIHRoZSBub3RvcmlvdXMgRS5ULiBnYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgQXRhcmkgMjYwMCBkaWQgQXRhcmkgZW5kIHVwIHNlbGxpbmc/",
            "answer": "MS41IE1pbGxpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RmF1c3QgaXMgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkd1aWx0eSBHZWFyIFhyZCBSZXZlbGF0b3IiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCIgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gTm9ydGggQW1lcmljYT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMiLCBob3cgbWFueSBwbGF5YWJsZSB3b3JsZHMgd2VyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGV0cmlzIGlzIHRoZSAjMSBiZXN0LXNlbGxpbmcgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBvZiBhbGwtdGltZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHZpcnVzLCBhcyBkZXNpZ25hdGVkIGJ5IENFREEsIHRoYXQgY2F1c2VzIG1vc3QgaHVtYW5zIHRvIHR1cm4gaW50byB0aGUgSW5mZWN0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gRmx1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIHdlcmUgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBmb3IgaW5jbHVzaW9uIGluIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIE1lbGVlPw==",
            "answer": "THVjYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBGb3IgU3BlZWQgTW9zdCBXYW50ZWQgKDIwMDUpLCB3aGF0IGRvIHlvdSBkcml2ZSBhdCB0aGUgYmVnaW5uaW5nIG9mIHRoZSBjYXJlZXIgbW9kZT8=",
            "answer": "Qk1XIE0zIEdUUg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBzdW1tb24gaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlNvdXRoIFBhcms6IFRoZSBTdGljayBvZiBUcnV0aCI/",
            "answer": "VG93ZWxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgdGVhbSBsZWFkZXIgaW4gUG9rw6ltb24gR08/",
            "answer": "TGVpZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBHYXJyeSdzIE1vZCByZWxlYXNlZCBhcyBhIHN0YW5kYWxvbmUgdGl0bGUgb24gVmFsdmUncyBTdGVhbSBkaXN0cmlidXRpb24gc2VydmljZT8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyLCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiTW9yZW5hdHN1IiwgaGFzIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBvc3NpYmxlIGVuZGluZ3MgdG8gdGhlaXIgcm91dGUsIGF0IGEgdG90YWwgb2YgZm91ciBkaWZmZXJlbnQgZW5kaW5ncz8=",
            "answer": "U2hpbiBLdXJvaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHMgVjogU2t5cmltLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGplc3RlciBpbiB0aGUgZGFyayBicm90aGVyaG9vZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2ljZXJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIExlZ28gSXNsYW5kIHRyaWxvZ3ksIHdobyB0YXVnaHQgUGVwcGVyIFJvbmkgaG93IHRvIHJlYWQ/",
            "answer": "T2ZmaWNlciBMYXVyYSBCcmljaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24sIEFyYm9rIGV2b2x2ZXMgaW50byBTZXZpcGVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUnVuZVNjYXBlLCBvbmUgbXVzdCBjb21wbGV0ZSB0aGUgIkRyYWdvbiBTbGF5ZXIiIHF1ZXN0IGJlZm9yZSBlcXVpcHBpbmcgUnVuZSBQbGF0ZWxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGF2aWQgQmFzenVja2kgd2FzIGEgY28tZm91bmRlciBvZiBST0JMT1ggQ29ycG9yYXRpb24u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkdpbW1pY2shIiBpcyBhIEphcGFuZXNlIEZhbWljb20gZ2FtZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgYSBzb3VuZCBjaGlwIGV4cGFuc2lvbiBpbiB0aGUgY2FydHJpZGdlLiBXaGF0IGlzIGl0IGNhbGxlZD8=",
            "answer": "Rk1FLTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdEJyBpbiB0aGUgdGVybSAiRC1NYWlsIiBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lICJTdGVpbnM7IEdhdGUiIGlzIHNob3J0IGZvciB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGVMb3JlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIERhbmdhbnJvbnBhIDI6IEdvb2RieWUgRGVzcGFpcj8=",
            "answer": "SGFqaW1lIEhpbmF0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkVhcnRoYm91bmQiLCBob3cgZG9lcyBvbmUgZW50ZXIgIk1hc3RlciBCZWxjaCdzIiBmYWN0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "V2FpdCAzIE1pbnV0ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFN1bnNoaW5lIiwgaG93IGRvIHlvdSB1bmxvY2sgdGhlICJDb3JvbmEgTW91bnRhaW4iIGxldmVsPw==",
            "answer": "QnkgY2xlYXJpbmcgZXZlcnkgN3RoIGVwaXNvZGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZGlmZmVyZW50IG5vdGVzIGlzIHRoZSB0dW5lLCAiU29uZyBvZiBIZWFsaW5nIiwgY29tcHJpc2VkIG9mIGluICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhOiBNYWpvcmEncyBNYXNrIj8=",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIk1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIiBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgbW9uc3RlciAiR29idWwiPw==",
            "answer": "TW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgVHJp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVsYXRpb25zaGlwIGJldHdlZW4gQXBvbGxvIEp1c3RpY2UgYW5kIFRydWN5IFdyaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGhleSdyZSBoYWxmLXNpYmxpbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIHdlYXBvbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBkZWFsIGFueSBkYW1hZ2U/",
            "answer": "MzEtNzkgSkdiMjE1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSB0cmFkaXRpb25hbGx5IHJld2FyZCB5b3UgZm9yIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgYSBib3NzIHJvdW5kPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4IEFtbW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgMjAxNiBmYXJtaW5nIFJQRyAiU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXkiPw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBCYXJvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdob3N0cyBpbiAiUGFjLU1hbiIgYW5kICJNcy4gUGFjLU1hbiIgaGF2ZSBjb21wbGV0ZWx5IGRpZmZlcmVudCBiZWhhdmlvci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFZhbHZlIENvcnBvcmF0aW9uIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0IDI0LCAxOTk2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAiQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIiBzZXJpZXMgdXNlcyB0aGUgcGhyYXNlICJ6aXAgem9vbSIgd2hlbiB0YWxraW5nIHRvIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXI/",
            "answer": "U2Nvb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIGhvdyBtdWNoIGhlYWx0aCBkb2VzIGEgc2NvdXQgaGF2ZSB3aGVuIG92ZXJoZWFsZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTg1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJQb3J0YWwiIHNlcmllcywgd2hvIHdhcyBDYXZlIEpvaG5zb24ncyBwZXJzb25hbCBhc3Npc3RhbnQ/",
            "answer": "Q2Fyb2xpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZG9lcyAiVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogTWFqb3JhJ3MgTWFzayIgdGFrZSBwbGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "VGVybWluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGlhYmxvIGxvcmUsIHRoaXMgbGVzc2VyIGV2aWwgc3Bhd25lZCBmcm9tIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgc2V2ZW4gaGVhZHMgb2YgVGF0aGFtZXQsIGFuZCB3YXMga25vd24gYXMgdGhlIE1haWRlbiBvZiBBbmd1aXNoLg==",
            "answer": "QW5kYXJpZWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIE5PVCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiAiTmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IEhvdCBQdXJzdWl0IDIiPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIE1SMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFNweXJvIGdhbWUgd2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB2aWxsYWluPw==",
            "answer": "R25hc3R5IEdub3Jj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWxpZW4gc3BlY2llcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIFNoYWRvdyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2cgKDIwMDUpPw==",
            "answer": "QmxhY2sgQXJtcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gT3ZlcndhdGNoLCB3aGF0IGlzIEzDumNpbydzIGZ1bGwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TMO6Y2lvIENvcnJlaWEgRG9zIFNhbnRvcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3b24gdGhlICJHYW1lcyBmb3IgSW1wYWN0IiBhd2FyZCBpbiBUaGUgR2FtZSBBd2FyZHMgMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "TGlmZSBpcyBTdHJhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIFRlcnJvciBGaWVuZHMgbW9yZSBjb21tb25seSBmb3VuZCBpbiB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gZ2FtZSBNaWl0b3BpYT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IEx1bW9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgR2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd29yayBhdCBiZWZvcmUgZm91bmRpbmcgVmFsdmUgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIGZyb20gIlNwbGF0b29uIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNvbXBvc2VkIHRoZSBzb3VuZHRyYWNrIGZvciB0aGUgZ2FtZSBWVlZWVlY/",
            "answer": "TWFnbnVzIFDDpWxzc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDNEIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "T2NhcmluYSBvZiBUaW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIkdhcnJ5J3MgTW9kIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVjZW1iZXIgMjQsIDIwMDQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRmFsbG91dCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgJ1BvcnRhbCAyJyByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgU3RhcmJvdW5kIHJhY2VzIGhhcyBhIFdpbGQgV2VzdCBjdWx0dXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Tm92YWtpZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hvIHdhcyBmaXJzdCB0byBoYXZlIHRoZSB0aXRsZSAiVGhlIEFzaGJyaW5nZXIiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxleGFuZHJvcyBNb2dyYWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWluZWNyYWZ0IGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIHRvIHRoZSBwdWJsaWM/",
            "answer": "TWF5IDE3dGgsIDIwMDk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U29saWQgU25ha2UgaXMgYWN0dWFsbHkgYSBjbG9uZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBETkEgb2YgQmlnIEJvc3MgaW4gdGhlIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgc2VyaWVzJyBoaXN0b3J5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgSHVtb25nb3VzIEVudGVydGFpbm1lbnQgZ2FtZSBmcmFuY2hpc2U/",
            "answer": "Q29tbWFuZGVyIEtlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluICJMZWZ0IDQgRGVhZCI/",
            "answer": "Tmljaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgaXMgb24gTGluaydzIHBhamFtYXMgaW4gVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVGhlIFdpbmQgV2FrZXI/",
            "answer": "Q3Jhd2Zpc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVuZCBjcmVkaXRzIHNlcXVlbmNlIGluIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gNSBpcyBvdmVyIGhhbGYgYW4gaG91ciBsb25nLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2FtZSBEZXZlbG9wbWVudCBjb21wYW55IG1hZGUgTm8gTWFuJ3MgU2t5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGVsbG8gR2FtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIFJveGFzJ3MgS2V5YmxhZGVzIGluIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIGFyZSAiT2F0aGtlZXBlciIgYW5kICJPYmxpdmlvbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBmYWN0aW9uIGluIFRvbSBDbGFuY3kncyBUaGUgRGl2aXNpb24/",
            "answer": "Q0RD"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCB3YXMgYWxtb3N0IGJhc2VkIG9uIEplYW4tQ2xhdWRlIFZhbiBEYW1tZSBtb3ZpZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBsZXZlbCBkbyB5b3UgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSB0byBnZXQgYSBzZXJ2aWNlIG1lZGFsIG9uIENTOkdPPw==",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMsIGd1aWxkIHN0eWxlIGlzIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBodW50aW5nIHN0eWxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3b24gdGhlICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIEludml0YXRpb25hbCBFdmVudCBGZWJydWFyeSAyMDE3IGluIHRoZSBQQyBDYXRlZ29yeT8=",
            "answer": "Q29udGludXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggS2lyYnkgZ2FtZSBmaXJzdCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIENvcHkgQWJpbGl0aWVzPw==",
            "answer": "S2lyYnkncyBBZHZlbnR1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYnJvd3NlciBnYW1lIEthbnRhaSBDb2xsZWN0aW9uIGhlYXZpbHkgaW5zcGlyZWQgYnk/",
            "answer": "U2Vjb25kIFdvcmxkIFdhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIGFjY29yZGluZyB0byB0aGUgYXNzZXQgZmlsZXMsIHRoZSBkZXNjcmlwdGlvbiBvZiB0aGUgIkVyY2hpdXMgR2hvc3QiIGlzIHRoZSBzYW1lIGFzIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIGFzc2V0cz8=",
            "answer": "U3Bvb2tpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIFRvdWhvdSBwcm9qZWN0Pw==",
            "answer": "WnVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlJldHVybiB0byBDYXN0bGUgV29sZmVuc3RlaW4iIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBXb2xmZW5zdGVpbiBzZXJpZXMgd2hlcmUgeW91IGRvbid0IHBsYXkgYXMgV2lsbGlhbSAiQi5KLiIgQmxhemtvd2ljei4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtaWxpdGFyeSByYW5rIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCAiTm9tYWQiIGluICJDcnlzaXMiPw==",
            "answer": "Rmlyc3QgTGlldXRlbmFudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogViwgd2hhdCB3YW50ZWQgbGV2ZWwgZG9lcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIHJlY2VpdmUgaWYgdGhleSBlbnRlciBaYW5jdWRvIEFybXkgQmFzZSBub3J0aCBvZiBMb3MgU2FudG9zPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFua3ksIEZ1bmt5LCBhbmQgQ2h1bmt5IGFyZSBhbGwgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBzZXJpZXMgb3duZWQgYnkgTmludGVuZG8/",
            "answer": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgQWdlbnQgNDcgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzICJIaXRtYW4iPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuIE90dG8gV29sZmdhbmcgT3J0LU1leWVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBQb2vDqW1vbidzIEJhc2UgU3RhdCBUb3RhbCBkb2VzIG5vdCBjaGFuZ2Ugd2hlbiBpdCBldm9sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2N5dGhlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIGNsYXNzIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lICJIZWFydGhzdG9uZSI/",
            "answer": "UHJpZXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgaW4gdGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGljaCBpbnN0cnVtZW50IGRpZCBDYXNleSBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1bXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU29uaWMgRm9yY2VzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIHdhcyBub3QgZnJvbSBhIHByZXZpb3VzIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "SW5maW5pdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtYWlubHkgZmF2b3JlZCByaWZsZSBpcyB1c2VkIGJ5IHRoZSBUZXJyb3Jpc3RzIGluIENvdW50ZXIgU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QUstNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVbHRpbWF0ZSBkb2VzIE1ha290byBOYWVnaSwgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2MsIGhhdmU/IA==",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hdGUgTHVja3kgU3R1ZGVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhIFRldHJpcyBwaWVjZSBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGV0cm9taW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBUZXRyaXMgY3JlYXRlZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QWxleGV5IFBhaml0bm92"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgYSBtYXAgdGhhdCB3YXMgaW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIGF0IGxhdW5jaD8=",
            "answer": "R3JhdmVsIFBpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1lbWJlcnMgZG9lcyBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gWElJSSBoYXZlIGluIHRvdGFsPw==",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmVzIHdhcyBtYWRlIGJ5IHRoZSBjb21wYW55IEVwaWMgR2FtZXM/",
            "answer": "VW5yZWFs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBtb2RlbCBmb3IgSGFsZi1MaWZlJ3MgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QgR29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4/",
            "answer": "SXZhbiB0aGUgU3BhY2UgQmlrZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgdGVhbSBhdmFpbGFibGUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gR28/",
            "answer": "VGVhbSBSb2NrZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0ICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIiBnYW1lIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBmb3IgdGhlIFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uIDEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgdGhlIFBhb3B1IGZydWl0IGlzIHNhaWQgdG8gaW50ZXJ0d2luZSB0aGUgZGVzdGluaWVzIGZvciB0d28gcGVvcGxlIGZvcmV2ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJXb3JtcyIgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHZpZGVvIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB3ZWFwb25zIGlzIGFmZmVjdGVkIGJ5IHdpbmQ/",
            "answer": "QmF6b29rYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgTnVjbGVhciBUaHJvbmUsIHdoYXQgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uIGNoYXNlcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGNoYXJhY3RlciB0aHJvdWdob3V0IHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEkuRC5QLkQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIiByZXZlYWxlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWluZWNyYWZ0IGNhbiBiZSBwbGF5ZWQgd2l0aCBhIHZpcnR1YWwgcmVhbGl0eSBoZWFkc2V0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdlcmUgYWNoaXZlbWVudHMgYWRkZWQgdG8gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBGb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KSwgaG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSB0aGVyZSB0byBkZWZlYXQgb24gdGhlIGJsYWNrbGlzdD8=",
            "answer": "MTU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBWYWxvciBpbiBQb2vDqW1vbiBHbz8=",
            "answer": "Q2FuZGVsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYViByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMjl0aCwgMjAxNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV2FyaW9XYXJlOiBTbW9vdGggTW92ZXMsIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBOT1QgYSBGb3JtPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhvdHNob3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gWGVub2JsYWRlIENocm9uaWNsZXMgWCwgd2hpY2ggY2xhc3MgaGFzIGEgc25pcGVyIHJpZmxlIGFzIGl0J3MgcHJpbWFyeSB3ZWFwb24/",
            "answer": "UGFydGlzYW4gRWFnbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgbG9yZSwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyB0aGUgR29kIG9mIFNwaWRlcnMgaW4gdGhlIHRyb2xsJ3MgbG9hIGJlbGllZnM/",
            "answer": "RWxvcnRoYSBubyBTaGFkcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIGhhZCBhIHNwZWNpYWwgZXZlbnQgaG9zdGVkIGluIHRoZSBwb3B1bGFyIE1NT1JQRyBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhJVjogQSBSZWFsbSBSZWJvcm4/",
            "answer": "WW8ta2FpIFdhdGNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGlzdG9ucyB3ZXJlIGFkZGVkIHRvIE1pbmVjcmFmdCBpbiBCZXRhIDEuNS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0b3IgcHJvdmlkZWQgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGZvciB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBmYXRoZXIgaW4gRmFsbG91dCAzPw==",
            "answer": "TGlhbSBOZWVzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZXNlIG1hcHMgd2VyZSBpbiAiVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgU2l4IFNpZWdlIiBvbiBpdHMgaW5pdGlhbCByZWxlYXNlOiBIb3VzZSwgQ2x1YmhvdXNlLCBCb3JkZXIsIENvbnN1bGF0ZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhlYXJ0aHN0b25lIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmVzdCByYW5rIHBvc3NpYmxlPw==",
            "answer": "UmFuayAxIExlZ2VuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxvIiBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHJhY2Ugb2YgYWxpZW5zIGh1bWFucyByZWZlciB0byBhcyAiR3J1bnRzIj8=",
            "answer": "VW5nZ295"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgbGV2ZWwgaW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogV29ybGQgYXQgV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "U2VtcGVyIEZp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZXIgd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyI/",
            "answer": "VHJleWFyY2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IHN0ZXBzIGFyZSB0aGVyZSB0byB1cGdyYWRlIGEgU3RhZmY/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYm9zcyByb3VuZCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIgbWFwICJGaXZlIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBlbnRhZ29uIFRoaWVm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGdhbWVzIGNhbWUgb3V0IGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGVycmFyaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZpYXQgTXVsdGlwbGEgaXMgYSBkcml2YWJsZSBjYXIgaW4gIkZvcnphIEhvcml6b24gMyIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2V2ZXJhbCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGluICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyA2NCIgYmxpbmsgdGhlaXIgZXllcywgaW5jbHVkaW5nIE1hcmlvIGhpbXNlbGYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgOHRoIGluc3RhbGxtZW50IGluIHRoZSBGaXJlIEVtYmxlbSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNhY3JlZCBTdG9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBpc2xhbmQgaW4gUExBWUVSVU5LTk9XTidTIEJBVFRMRUdST1VORFM/",
            "answer": "RXJhbmdlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QncyBmaXJzdCBQZXJzb25hIGluICJQZXJzb25hIDUiPw==",
            "answer": "QXJzZW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIiBTZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "SGlkZW8gS29qaW1h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsLCB3aGF0IGNvbG9yIGlzIHRoZSBJbnRlbGxpZ2VuY2UgQ29yZT8=",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgVG9tIENsYW5jeSdzIFJhaW5ib3cgNiBTaWVnZSwgd2hhdCBvcmdhbml6YXRpb24gaXMgVmFsa3lyaWUgZnJvbT8=",
            "answer": "TmF2eSBTZWFscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkOiBQb3JzY2hlIFVubGVhc2hlZCIsIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXIgY2FuIG9ubHkgZHJpdmUgY2FycyBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZWQgYnkgUG9yc2NoZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzb25nIGlzIHBsYXllZCBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIGVuZGluZyBjcmVkaXRzIG9mIEd1aXRhciBIZXJvOiBXb3JsZCBUb3VyPw==",
            "answer": "RHJlYW0gVGhlYXRlciAtIFB1bGwgTWUgVW5kZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwZW9wbGUgY2FuIE5PVCB3aWVsZCBhIGtleWJsYWRlPw==",
            "answer": "TGFyeGVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGluZGllIGZhcm1pbmcgZ2FtZSAiU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXkiLCB3aGljaCBOUEMgaGF0ZXMgdGhlICJwcmlzbWF0aWMgc2hhcmQiIGl0ZW0gd2hlbiByZWNlaXZlZCBhcyBhIGdpZnQ/",
            "answer": "SGFsZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9kICJDcnkgb2YgRmVhciIgYmFzZWQgb2ZmIG9mPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZi1MaWZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgQUstNDcncyBuYW1lIGluIENvdW50ZXIgU3RyaWtlOiBTb3VyY2U/",
            "answer": "Q1YtNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIExpZmUgaXMgU3RyYW5nZTogQmVmb3JlIFRoZSBTdG9ybT8=",
            "answer": "Q2hsb2UgUHJpY2Ug"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgRE9UQSAyLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBOT1QgYSBoZXJvPw==",
            "answer": "RHJhZ29uIENoYW1waW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW5nbGlzaCBuZXcgd2F2ZSBtdXNpY2lhbiBHYXJ5IE51bWFuIGZvdW5kZWQgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgY29tcGFueSBGYWNlcHVuY2ggU3R1ZGlvcyBpbiBNYXJjaCAyMDA5Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIFNvbmljJ3Mgc2lkZWtpY2s/",
            "answer": "VGFpbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBlYXJuZWQgbXVzaWMgY29tcG9zZXIgTWlrZSBNb3Jhc2t5IHRoZSBtb3N0IGF3YXJkcyBmb3IgaGlzIHdvcms/",
            "answer": "UG9ydGFsIDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBmaXJzdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNvbnNvbGU/",
            "answer": "TWFnbmF2b3ggT2R5c3NleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpbiAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIiBjYW4gdGhlIHBsYXllciBOT1QgZ28gb24gYSBkYXRlIHdpdGg/",
            "answer": "VG9yaWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk1lbHR5IEJsb29kIEFjdHJlc3MgQWdhaW4gQ3VycmVudCBDb2RlIiwgeW91IGNhbiBlbnRlciBCbG9vZCBIZWF0IG1vZGUgaW4gSGFsZiBNb29uIHN0eWxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9vdGJhbGwgcGxheWVyIGlzIGZlYXR1cmVkIG9uIHRoZSBpbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsIGNvdmVyIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgRklGQSAxNj8=",
            "answer": "TGlvbmVsIE1lc3Np"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgMzogU25ha2UgRWF0ZXIiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIG9uIFNoYWRvdyBNb3NlcyBJc2xhbmQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFjLU1hbiB3YXMgaW52ZW50ZWQgYnkgdGhlIGRlc2lnbmVyIFRvcnUgSXdhdGFuaSB3aGlsZSBoZSB3YXMgZWF0aW5nIHBpenphLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCBGUFMgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZXMgc3VjaCBhcyBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZSwgc2hvb3Rpbmcgd2hpY2ggcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgYm9keSBkb2VzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGRhbWFnZT8=",
            "answer": "SGVhZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTWFyaW8gc3Bpbi1vZmYgZ2FtZSBkaWQgV2FsdWlnaSBtYWtlIGhpcyBkZWJ1dD8=",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8gVGVubmlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgTnVjbGVhciBUaHJvbmUsIHdoYXQgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIG9ubHkgdXNhYmxlIGluIGEgcGxheSB0aHJvdWdoIHdpdGggTWVsdGluZz8=",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgY2l0eSBpbiB0aGUgR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "U2FuIEFuZHJlYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiBSZWQgJiBCbHVlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEhNMDU/",
            "answer": "Rmxhc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIE1ldHJvaWQgc2VyaWVzIGNvbWVzIGZyb20gd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QW4gZW5lbXkgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzOiBCaXJ0aCBieSBTbGVlcD8=",
            "answer": "SWduaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRWxpdGUgRm91ciBtZW1iZXIgZnJvbSB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBvZiBQb2vDqW1vbiBiZWNhbWUgdGhlIGNoYW1waW9uIGluIHRoZSBuZXh0IGdlbmVyYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "TGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IHZlcnNpb24gb2YgQmxvY2tsYW5kIGNhbWUgb3V0IGluIHdoaWNoIHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHlvdSBjYW4gY3JhZnQgdGhlIENlbGwgUGhvbmUgcHJlLWhhcmRtb2RlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IExlZnQgNCBEZWFkLCB5b3UgY2FuIHBsYXkgYXMgZWl0aGVyIG9mIHRoZXNlIGZvdXIgY2hhcmFjdGVycy4=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNpcywgQmlsbCwgWm9leSwgYW5kIExvdWlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHN0YXJzIGluIEJydXRhbCBMZWdlbmQ/",
            "answer": "SmFjayBCbGFjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZhbGxvdXQgNCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGRvZyB5b3UgZmluZCBhdCBSZWQgUm9ja2V0IHRydWNrIHN0b3A/",
            "answer": "RG9nbWVhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHdlYXBvbiBwYWNrIGZvciAiUEFZREFZIDIiPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdhZ2UgV2VhcG9uIFBhY2sgIzE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGEgQW5vdGhlciBFcGlzb2RlOiBVbHRyYSBEZXNwYWlyIEdpcmxzIGlzIHNldCBhZnRlciB3aGljaCBEYW5nYW5yb25wYSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBnYW1lIHdhcyB1c2VkIHRvIGFkdmVydGlzZSBTdGVhbT8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgMS42"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYmxvY2tzIGluICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiIGhhcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IGJsYXN0IHJlc2lzdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "U2FuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlAuQS5NLkUuTC5BLiIgcmVsZWFzZWQgb24gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggOSwgMjAxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIlBvY2tldCBNb3J0eSIgaGFzIGEgTW9ydHkgY2FsbGVkICJQb2NrZXQgTW9ydHlzIE1vcnR5Ij8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciB0aGF0IHdvdWxkIGV2ZW50dWFsbHkgYmVjb21lIERyLiBFZ2dtYW4gd2FzIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgZm9yIHRoZSByb2xlIG9mIFNlZ2EncyBuZXcgZmxhZ3NoaXAgbWFzY290IGJlZm9yZSBTb25pYyB3YXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBWYW1waXJlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiAiU2hpbmluZyBTb3VsIDIiLg==",
            "answer": "Qmxvb2RzdGFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBBWURBWSBzZXJpZXMsIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgaWNvbmljIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgUEFZREFZIGdhbmc/",
            "answer": "RGFsbGFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBVQkFUVExFR1JPVU5EUyIgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgTWlsaXRhcnkgQmFzZSBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "U29zbm92a2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tIEZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgVklJSSBwcmltYXJpbHkgc3Bva2UgaW4gb25lIHdvcmQgc2VudGVuY2VzPw==",
            "answer": "RnVqaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgUG9rZW1vbiBHTyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "SnVseSA2dGgsIDIwMTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBYSVYsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIERlZXAgRHVuZ2VvbiB0aGF0IHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSBleHBhbnNpb24gcGFjaywgSGVhdmVuc3dhcmQ/",
            "answer": "UGFsYWNlIG9mIHRoZSBEZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCA0LCB0aGUgQ2hpY2FnbyBUeXBld3JpdGVyIGhhcyBpbmZpbml0ZSBhbW1vLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSB0eXBlIG9mIG1vbnN0ZXIgZm91bmQgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWVyIGNsYXNzIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMj8=",
            "answer": "SGVhbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWFpbiBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gViI/",
            "answer": "TGFtYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmluYWwgZ2FtZSBvZiB0aGUgIlplcm8gRXNjYXBlIiBzZXJpZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "WmVybyBFc2NhcGUgWmVybyBUaW1lIERpbGVtbWEg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdm9pY2UgYWN0b3IgZm9yIFNuYWtlIGluIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgVjogVGhlIFBoYW50b20gUGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "S2llZmVyIFN1dGhlcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZVNwb3J0cyB0ZWFtIGNhbWUgZmlyc3QgcGxhY2UgaW4gVGhlIEludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgRG90YSAyIENoYW1waW9uc2hpcCAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "V2luZ3MgR2FtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGl0bGUgb2Ygc29uZyBvbiB0aGUgbWFpbiBtZW51IGluIEhhbG8/",
            "answer": "SGFsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBzZXJpZXMsIEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2Ugd2FzIGZvdW5kZWQgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGluIHRoZSBlYXJseSAxOTQwcz8=",
            "answer": "QXBlcnR1cmUgRml4dHVyZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiBTZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "TWFzYWhpcm8gU2FrdXJhaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2FtZSBCb3kgZnJvbSB0aGUgR2FtZSBCb3kgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHBvcnRhYmxlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgY29uc29sZXMgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "R2FtZSBCb3kgQ29sb3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgZmFjdGlvbiBpbmNsdWRlZCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Qk9QRQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvZ2FtZSBCdWxseSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3QncyBsYXN0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "SG9wa2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAyMDA1IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgS2lsbGVyNz8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgU21pdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlN1Ym5hdXRpY2EiLCB3aGljaCBmZWF0dXJlIHdhcyByZW1vdmVkIGR1ZSB0byBwZXJmb3JtYW5jZSBpc3N1ZXMgaW4gMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "VGVycmFmb3JtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24gU3VuIGFuZCBNb29uLCBhIG1hbGUgU2FsYW5kaXQgY2FuIGV2b2x2ZSB0byBhIFNhbGF6emxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIE1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgVjogVGhlIFBoYW50b20gUGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "UHVuaXNoZWQgIlZlbm9tIiBTbmFrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWVwZXIgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0IHdhcyB0aGUgcmVzdWx0IG9mIGEgYnVnIHdoaWxlIGltcGxlbWVudGluZyB3aGljaCBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "UGln"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hcmlvICYgU29uaWMgYXQgdGhlIE9seW1waWMgR2FtZXMiLCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGFyZSBzcGxpdCBpbnRvIGhvdyBtYW55IHR5cGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgd29ybGQgdGhhdCB0aGUgTU1PICJSdW5lU2NhcGUiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "R2llbGlub3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhhbG8gMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1vbml0b3Igb2YgSW5zdGFsbGF0aW9uIDA1Pw==",
            "answer": "MjQwMSBQZW5pdGVudCBUYW5nZW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGl0ZW1zIGlzIE5PVCBjcmFmdGVkIGF0IGEgTXl0aHJpbCBBbnZpbD8=",
            "answer": "QW5raCBDaGFybQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRG90YSAyLCB3aGF0IGlzIEVhcnRoc2hha2VyJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UmFpZ29yIFN0b25laG9vZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2l0aG91dCBlbmNoYW50bWVudHMsIHdoaWNoIHBpY2theGUgaW4gbWluZWNyYWZ0IG1pbmVzIGJsb2NrcyB0aGUgcXVpY2tlc3Qu",
            "answer": "R29sZGVuIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHlvdSBjYW4gdXBncmFkZSB0aGUgIkFwb3RoaWNvbiBTZXJ2YW50IiBpbiB0aGUgIlNoYWRvd3MgT2YgRXZpbCIgbWFwLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZ2FtZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSAiQ29sb255IFdhcnMiIHNlcmllcyBmb3IgdGhlIFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5ODBzLCBhIHNlcnZpY2UgY2FsbGVkIEdhbWVsaW5lIGFsbG93ZWQgdXNlcnMgdG8gZG93bmxvYWQgZ2FtZXMgdG8gd2hhdCBjb25zb2xlPw==",
            "answer": "QXRhcmkgMjYwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTLlQuQS5MLksuRS5SLiIgc2VyaWVzLCB0aGUgRnJlZWRvbSBmYWN0aW9uIHdpc2hlcyB0byBkZXN0cm95IHRoZSBzdXBlcm5hdHVyYWwgYXJlYSBrbm93biBhcyAgInRoZSBab25lIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGlueSBUaHdvbXBzIGNhbGxlZCBpbiBTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBXb3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "VGh3aW1wcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBW4oCZcyBzdG9yeSBtb2RlPw==",
            "answer": "VG9tbXkgVmVyY2V0dGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBoYXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "VGltZXNwbGl0dGVyczogRnV0dXJlIFBlcmZlY3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3ZWFwb25zIGluICJDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZSIgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBhIHJpZ2h0LWNsaWNrIGZ1bmN0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "WE0xMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29kZW1hc3RlcnMgaXMgdGhlIGRldmVsb3BlciBvZiB0aGUgR3JhbiBUdXJpc21vIHNlcmllcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRG90YSAxIGhlcm8gY2hhbmdlZCBnZW5kZXIgd2hlbiBwb3J0ZWQgdG8gRG90YSAyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVnaW9uIENvbW1hbmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR2VvbWV0cnkgRGFzaCwgd2hhdCBpcyBsZXZlbCAxMz8=",
            "answer": "RWxlY3Ryb21hbiBBZHZlbnR1cmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBoYWxmLWRlbW9uIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBEaXZpbml0eTogT3JpZ2luYWwgU2luIDIgd2hvIHlvdSB0YWxrIHRvIHRvIHRyYW5zaXRpb24gYmV0d2VlbiBhY3RzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFsYWR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTQgUG9rZW1vbiBWR0MgRmluYWxzLCB3aGljaCBQb2tlbW9uIHdhcyBmYW1vdXMgZm9yIGJyaW5naW5nIHRoZSB3aW5uZXIgdG8gdmljdG9yeT8=",
            "answer": "UGFjaGlyaXN1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgbGV0dGVyIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlICJIYWxmLUxpZmUiIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "TGFtYmRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgamVkaSB0aGF0IFN0YXJraWxsZXIgaGFkIHRvIGtpbGwgaW4gU3RhciBXYXJzOiBUaGUgRm9yY2UgVW5sZWFzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "UmFobSBLb3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiVGhlIFdhbGtpbmcgRGVhZDogU2Vhc29uIE9uZSI/",
            "answer": "TGVlIEV2ZXJldHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHRvIGJlIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IGRldmVsb3BtZW50IGNvbXBhbnkgUmFyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2xhbG9t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSB3YXMgcmVjYWxsZWQgZm9yIGNvbnRhaW5pbmcgYSBoaWRkZW4sIHBsYXlhYmxlIFNvdXRoIFBhcmsgZXBpc29kZT8=",
            "answer": "VGlnZXIgV29vZHMgOTkgUEdBIFRvdXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiB0aGVtZSBzb25nIG9mICJTb25pYyBBZHZlbnR1cmUgMiI/",
            "answer": "TGl2ZSBhbmQgTGVhcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCBWOiBUaGUgUGhhbnRvbSBQYWluIHJ1bnMgb24gdGhlIEZveCBFbmdpbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNwZWNpYWwgSW5mZWN0ZWQgdGhhdCBpcyB1bnBsYXlhYmxlIGluIFZlcnN1cyBtb2RlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdpdGNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsIDIsIGhvdyBkaWQgQ0VPIG9mIEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2UsIENhdmUgSm9obnNvbiwgcHJlc3VtYWJseSBkaWU/",
            "answer": "TW9vbiBSb2NrIFBvaXNvbmluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgU2NvdXQncyBjaXR5IG9mIG9yaWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "Qm9zdG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnkgaG93IG1hbnkgbWludXRlcyBhcmUgeW91IGxhdGUgdG8gd29yayBpbiAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIj8=",
            "answer": "MzA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBVbml0ZWQgT2ZmZW5zaXZlLCB3aGF0IHR3byBzb2xkaWVycyBzaGFyZSBhIG5hbWUgb2YgYSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uICYgRnJlZW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyLCBiZWluZyBkaXNndWlzZWQgYXMgYSBzY291dCBvciBtZWRpYyByZXN1bHRzIGluIGEgc3BlZWQgYm9vc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbmdyZWRpZW50cyBhcmUgcmVxdWlyZWQgdG8gbWFrZSBhIGNha2UgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "TWlsaywgU3VnYXIsIEVnZywgYW5kIFdoZWF0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGRvZXMgdGhlIGxpdHRsZSBoZWFkY3JhYiBpbiAiSGFsZiBMaWZlIDIiIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "TGFtYXJy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIk1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQiLCB3aGF0IGRpZCBSZXZvbHZlciBPY2Vsb3QgY29uc2lkZXIgdGhlIGdyZWF0ZXN0IGhhbmRndW4gZXZlciBtYWRlPw==",
            "answer": "Q29sdCBTaW5nbGUgQWN0aW9uIEFybXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ291bnRlciBTdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmUsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgaW1wbGFudGVkIG9udG8gdGhlIEM0IGFzIHRoZSBUZXJyb3Jpc3RzIHBsYW50IHRoZSBib21iPw==",
            "answer": "NzM1NTYwOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVEYyIExvcmUsIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgSGVhdnkncyB5b3VuZ2VyIHNpc3RlcnM/",
            "answer": "WWFuYSBhbmQgQnJvbmlzbGF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSGl0bWFuOiBCbG9vZCBNb25leSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGFyZ2V0IGluIHRoZSBtaXNzaW9uICJEZWF0aCBvZiBhIFNob3dtYW4iPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9zZXBoIENsYXJlbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyB0aGUgV2FsbCBvZiBGbGVzaCBub3QgZHJvcCB1cG9uIGRlZmVhdD8=",
            "answer": "UGlja3Nhdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9ja2V0IExlYWd1ZSwgeW91IGNhbiBwbGF5IEJhc2tldGJhbGwu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Ik1pbmVjcmFmdCIgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGZyb20gYmV0YSBpbiAyMDExIGR1cmluZyBhIGNvbnZlbnRpb24gaGVsZCBpbiB3aGljaCBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "TGFzIFZlZ2Fz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsLCB0aGUgQ29tcGFuaW9uIEN1YmUncyBBUkUgc2VudGllbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29tbW9uLCBndW4tdG90aW5nIGVuZW1pZXMgb2YgdGhlICJPZGR3b3JsZCIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "U2xpZ3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCB0byBiZSBkaXJlY3RlZCBieSBKYXNvbiBCbHVuZGVsbD8=",
            "answer": "TW9iIE9mIFRoZSBEZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJlZ2lubmluZyBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU29uaWMgQWR2ZW50dXJlIiwgd2hhdCBjb2xvciBDaGFvcyBFbWVyYWxkIGRvZXMgVGFpbHMgb3duPw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lLCAiTGV0aGFsIExlYWd1ZSI/",
            "answer": "UmV4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBXaXRuZXNzIiwgaG93IG1hbnkgbGFzZXJzIG11c3QgYmUgYWN0aXZhdGVkIHRvIGdldCBpbnRvIHRoZSBtb3VudGFpbiBhcmVhPw==",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbG8gc2VyaWVzLCB3aGljaCBlcmEgb2YgU1BBUlRBTiBpcyBNYXN0ZXIgQ2hpZWY/IA==",
            "answer": "U1BBUlRBTi1JSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlICJCYXR0bGVmaWVsZCIgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QmF0dGxlZmllbGQgMTk0Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmb3VyIHRpdGxlcyBvZiB0aGUgIkdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8iIGZyYW5jaGlzZSBzdGFydGVkIHRoZSBzZXJpZXMgb2YgaWNvbmljIGltYWdlIGdyaWQgY292ZXIgYXJ0cz8=",
            "answer": "R3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYW1waW9ucyBmcm9tIHRoZSBNT0JBICdMZWFndWUgb2YgTGVnZW5kcycgaXMgTk9UIGEgWW9yZGxlPw==",
            "answer": "QW5uaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzLCB3aGF0IGlzIE1hZSBCb3Jvd3NraSBtb3RoZXIncyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuZHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFZpZGVvIEdhbWUsIEhhbGYtbGlmZSwgd2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIFVTIG1pbGl0YXJ5IGZvcmNlIHN0YXJ0cyBjbGVhcmluZyBvdXQgdGhlIEJsYWNrIE1lc2EgUmVzZWFyY2ggRmFjaWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEhFQ1U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2V0cyBvZiBncmFuZG1hc3RlciB3aXRjaGVyIGdlYXIgYXJlIGluIFRoZSBXaXRjaGVyIDMncyBCbG9vZCBhbmQgV2luZSBETEM/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEluZGllIEdhbWUgRGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgU3R1ZGlvIENpbmcsIGRldmVsb3BlcnMgb2YgSG90ZWwgRHVzayBhbmQgTGFzdCBXaW5kb3csIHdlbnQgYmFua3J1cHQgb24gTWFyY2ggMXN0LCAyMDEwLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgd2FzIFRpdGFuZmFsbCBtYWRlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "U291cmNlIEVuZ2luZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFBsYW5ldHNpZGUgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIE5vcnRoIEFtZXJpY2Egb24uLi4=",
            "answer": "TWF5IDIwLCAyMDAz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiAiQXJraGFtIiBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "QXJraGFtIEFzeWx1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNpdHkgb2YgUm9ja3BvcnQgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2aWRlbyBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "TmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZmVtYWxlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIGEgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "U2FtdXMgQXJhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgIldvcm1zIiBnYW1lcyBmZWF0dXJlZCAzRCBnYW1lcGxheT8=",
            "answer": "V29ybXMgNDogTWF5aGVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBjaXR5IGluIHRoZSBkeXN0b3BpYSBhbHRlcm5hdGUgZnV0dXJlIG9mIEhhbGYtTGlmZSAyIGRvIHlvdSBmaXJzdCBzdGFydCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2l0eSAxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBoYXBwZW5lZCB0byBIYWxmLUxpZmUgMiBwcmlvciB0byBpdHMgcmVsZWFzZSwgd2hpY2ggcmVzdWx0ZWQgaW4gVmFsdmUgc3RhcnRpbmcgb3ZlciB0aGUgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIHNvdXJjZSBjb2RlIGdvdCBsZWFrZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcG9zc2libGUgZHJpbmsgdG8gYmUgbWFkZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiVkEtMTEgSEFMTC1BOiBDeWJlcnB1bmsgQmFydGVuZGVyIEFjdGlvbiI/",
            "answer": "U291ciBBcHBsZXRpbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE1IFJQRyAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIiBpcyBhIG1vbnN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgZG8geW91IGZpZ2h0IHRoZSBJbXByaXNvbmVkIGluIFRoZSBMZWdlbmQgb2YgWmVsZGE6IFNreXdhcmQgU3dvcmQ/",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIHB1bXAgIkYuTC5VLkQuRC4iIE1hcmlvIHVzZXMgaW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gU3Vuc2hpbmU/",
            "answer": "RWx2aW4gR2FkZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIHVuaXZlcnNlLCBUYWlscycgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIE1pbGVzIFByb3dlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBsYXN0IGxldmVsIHdoZXJlIHlvdSBwbGF5IGFzIGFuIEFtZXJpY2FuIHNvbGRpZXI/",
            "answer": "RmVzdHVuZyBSZWNvZ25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTmludGVuZG8ncyBWaXJ0dWFsIEJveSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE92ZXJ3YXRjaCdzIGxvcmUsIHdobyB3YXMgb25jZSBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgRGVhZGxvY2sgR2FuZz8=",
            "answer": "TWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdm9pY2UgY2hhbm5lbHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTeXN0ZW0gc3VwcG9ydCBuYXRpdmVseT8=",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXBlcnR1cmUgU2NpZW5jZSBDRU8gQ2F2ZSBKb2huc29uIGlzIHZvaWNlZCBieSB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBhY3Rvcj8=",
            "answer": "Si5LLiBTaW1tb25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHdhcyBub3QgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgdGhlIEZpZW5kaXNoIEZpdmUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU2x5IENvb3BlciBhbmQgdGhlIFRoaWV2aXVzIFJhY2Nvb251cz8=",
            "answer": "RGltaXRyaSBMb3VzdGVhdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBDb3B5IEFiaWxpdGllcyB3YXMgb25seSBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiAiS2lyYnkgJiBUaGUgQW1hemluZyBNaXJyb3IiPw==",
            "answer": "TWluaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiRGVyIFJpZXNlIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgIlBhY2stQS1QdW5jaGVkIFBQU0gtNDEiPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJlYXBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBmb3JtZXIgTU9CQSwgY3JlYXRlZCBieSBXYXlzdG9uZSBHYW1lcyBhbmQgcHVibGlzaGVkIGJ5IEVBLCB3YXMgc2h1dCBkb3duIGluIDIwMTQ/",
            "answer": "RGF3bmdhdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3b24gdGhlIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIEZpZ2h0ZXIgQmFsbG90IGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "QmF5b25ldHRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtaW5nIHNlcmllcyBpbmNsdWRlcyAiVGhlIERpYWJvbGljYWwgQm94IiBhbmQgIlRoZSBDdXJpb3VzIFZpbGxhZ2UiPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIExheXRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBJY2UgQ2xpbWJlcnMgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgSWNlIENsaW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "UG9wbyBhbmQgTmFuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2YXVsdCBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiRmFsbG91dCAzIiBpcyB0aGUgaG9tZSBvZiBtdWx0aXBsZSBjbG9uZXMgbmFtZWQgR2FyeT8=",
            "answer": "VmF1bHQgMTA4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUG9rw6ltb24gY2FuIGxlYXJuIHRoZSBtb3ZlICJTZWNyZXQgUG93ZXIiIGJ5IGxldmVsaW5nIHVwPw==",
            "answer": "QXVkaW5v"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTb3JhJ3MgaG9tZSB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVzdGlueSBJc2xhbmRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUsIEhhbGYtbGlmZSwgd2hhdCBldmVudCBzdGFydGVkIHRoZSBIYWxmLWxpZmUgdW5pdmVyc2UgYXMgd2Uga25vdyB0b2RheT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJlc29uYW5jZSBDYXNjYWRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgdGhlIEJyb3RoZXJob29kIG9mIE5vZCBpbiB0aGUgQ29tbWFuZCBhbmQgQ29ucXVlciBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "S2FuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWluZWNyYWZ0IHdhc27igJl0IHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBuYW1lIHRvIE1pbmVjcmFmdC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2lsbGluZyBGbG9vciBzdGFydGVkIGFzIGEgbW9kIGZvciB3aGljaCBVbnJlYWwgRW5naW5lIDIgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "VW5yZWFsIFRvdXJuYW1lbnQgMjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjcmVhdGVkIGFuZCBkaXJlY3RlZCB0aGUgS2F0YW1hcmkgRGFtYWN5IHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "S2VpdGEgVGFrYWhhc2hp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB5b3VyIHRlYW0gaW4gU3RhciBXYXJzOiBSZXB1YmxpYyBDb21tYW5kbz8=",
            "answer": "RGVsdGEgU3F1YWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZmVhdHVyZXMgd2FzIGFkZGVkIGluIHRoZSAxOTk0IGdhbWUgIkhlcmV0aWMiIHRoYXQgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsICJET09NIiBjb3VsZCBub3QgYWRkIGR1ZSB0byBsaW1pdGF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "TG9va2luZyB1cCBhbmQgZG93bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggZG9lcyB0aGUgJ0FXUCcgY29zdCBpbiBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZT8=",
            "answer": "JDQ3NTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGFyayBTb3Vscywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcmVnaW9uIHlvdSdyZSBpbiBmb3IgdGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TG9yZHJhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlBvcnRhbCAyIiwgQ2F2ZSBKb2huc29uIHN0YXJ0ZWQgb3V0IEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2UgYXMgYSBzaG93ZXIgY3VydGFpbiBjb21wYW55Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGV1cyBFeCAoMjAwMCkgZG9lcyBub3QgZmVhdHVyZSB0aGUgV29ybGQgVHJhZGUgQ2VudGVyIGJlY2F1c2UgaXQgd2FzIGRlc3Ryb3llZCBieSB0ZXJyb3Jpc3QgYXR0YWNrcyBhY2NvcmRpbmcgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUncyBwbG90Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbGYtTGlmZSBzZXJpZXMsIEdvcmRvbiBGcmVlbWFuJ3Mgc2lnbmF0dXJlIHdlYXBvbiBpcyBhOg==",
            "answer": "Q3Jvd2Jhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGdlbnJlIGlzIHRoZSBjb250cm92ZXJzaWFsIDIwMTUgZ2FtZSAiSGF0cmVkIj8=",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ0VtIFVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHNwYXJrZWQgY29udHJvdmVyc3kgYmVjYXVzZSBvZiBpdHMgaGlkZGVuICJIb3QgQ29mZmVlIiBtaW5pZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogU2FuIEFuZHJlYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgQmV0aGVzZGEgcHVyY2hhc2UgdGhlIEZhbGxvdXQgU2VyaWVzIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "SW50ZXJwbGF5IEVudGVydGFpbm1lbnQg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBnYW1lJ3MgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBldmVyIGNyZWF0ZWQgUG9rw6ltb24/",
            "answer": "Umh5aG9ybg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIkxpZmUgaXMgU3RyYW5nZSI/",
            "answer": "TWF4aW5lIENhdWxmaWVsZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBwbGFuZXQgaW4gS2VyYmFsIFNwYWNlIFByb2dyYW0/",
            "answer": "Sm9vbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHR1cm5zIG91dCB0byBiZSB0aGUgdHJ1ZSB2aWN0b3IgaW4gdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBBcm1hZ2VkZG9uIGluIE1vcnRhbCBLb21iYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2hhbyBLYWhu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IHRyaWxvZ3ksIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBwcm90YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "U2hlcGFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdm9pY2UgY2hhbm5lbHMgZG9lcyB0aGUgU3VwZXIgTmludGVuZG8gRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTeXN0ZW0gc3VwcG9ydD8=",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk4NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIHdhcyBOT1QgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiTGVnbyBEaW1lbnNpb25zIj8=",
            "answer": "QnJlYWtpbmcgQmFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcmVndWxhciBTdW5rZW4gU2VhIFNjcm9sbHMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluICJTcGxhdG9vbiI/",
            "answer": "Mjc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gQ29ucXVlc3QsIGhvdyBtYW55IGtpbmdkb21zIG1ha2UgdXAgdGhlIHJlZ2lvbiBvZiBSYW5zZWk/",
            "answer": "MTc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCA0IHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IG1lYW50IHRvIGJlIGEgTmludGVuZG8gR2FtZUN1YmUgZXhjbHVzaXZlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgcHVibGlzaGVyICJVYmlzb2Z0IiBmb3VuZGVkID8=",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggMTk4Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIHRoZSBwZXJrICJQaEQgRmxvcHBlciI/",
            "answer": "QXNjZW5zaW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgaXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gIkJsb29ucyBURCBCYXR0bGVzIj8=",
            "answer": "TW9ua2V5cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyB3YXMgTk9UIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIFZhbHZlJ3MgT3JhbmdlIEJveD8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIaXRtYW4iIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "QWdlbnQgNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGlzIE5PVCBhbiBvZmZpY2lhbCBtYXAgaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmU/",
            "answer": "ZGVfc2Vhc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNYXJpbyBLYXJ0IDggRGVsdXhlIGl0ZW1zIHdpbGwgTk9UIG1ha2UgeW91IGludmluY2libGU/",
            "answer": "R29sZGVuIE11c2hyb29t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMgTk9UIGFwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBHcmFuZCBUaGVmdCBBdXRvIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBDYXJkZW5hcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBaZWxkYSBnYW1lcyBkaWQgbm90IGZlYXR1cmUgR2Fub24gYXMgYSBmaW5hbCBib3NzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFqb3JhJ3MgTWFzaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvLW9wIHNob290ZXIgUGF5ZGF5IDIsIHdoaWNoIGNvbnRhY3QgaGVscHMgeW91IGJyZWFrIG91dCBIb3h0b24/",
            "answer": "VGhlIERlbnRpc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIEdhbWUgU3BsYXRvb24gMiwgd2hhdCBpcyBNYXJpbmEncyBzY3JlZW4gbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "REpfSHlwZXJmcmVzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvJ3MgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBUaHJhbGwgaW4gdGhlIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgTWV0emVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgdGVycm9yaXN0IGZhY3Rpb24gaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgKDIwMDApPw==",
            "answer": "TWlkd2VzdCBNaWxpdGlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBQaWthY2h1J3MgTmF0aW9uYWwgUG9rw6lEZXggTnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "IzAyNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYW4gb2ZmaWNpYWwgZ2FtZSBpbiBOaW50ZW5kbydzIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "U3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gQ3J1c2FkZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIHRoZSBTbmlwZXIgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBOYXRpb25hbGl0eSBpcyBELlZhIGZyb20gT3ZlcndhdGNoPw==",
            "answer": "S29yZWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugb25saW5lIGdhbWVzIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IG5hbWVkIExpbmRlbldvcmxkIGluIGl0J3MgZWFybHkgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "U2Vjb25kTGlmZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgVkEtMTEgSEFMTC1BOiBDeWJlcnB1bmsgQmFydGVuZGVyIEFjdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "SmlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgdHdvIEF1c3RyYWxpYW4gY3JpbWluYWxzIGZyb20gdGhlIEp1bmtlcnMgZmFjdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVua3JhdCBhbmQgUm9hZGhvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIFRvbSBOb29rJ3MgY291c2lucyBpbiB0aGUgQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIGZyYW5jaGlzZSBhcmUgbmFtZWQgIlRpbW15IiBhbmQgIkppbW15Ii4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEtvbmFtaSBDb2RlIGlzIGtub3duIGFzIFVwLCBVcCwgRG93biwgRG93biwgTGVmdCwgUmlnaHQsIFJpZ2h0LCBMZWZ0LCBCLCBBLCBTdGFydC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBuYW1lcyBpcyB0aGUgIk1lZ2EgTWFuIiBGcmFuY2hpc2Uga25vd24gYXMgaW4gSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "Um9ja21hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RWxsZW4gTWNMYWluLCB0aGUgdm9pY2Ugb2YgR0xhRE9TIGluIHRoZSBQb3J0YWwgZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXMsIGlzIG1hcnJpZWQgdG8gdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciB3aGljaCBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "U25pcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNha2UgZGVwaWN0ZWQgaW4gVmFsdmUncyAiUG9ydGFsIiBmcmFuY2hpc2UgbW9zdCBjbG9zZWx5IHJlc2VtYmxlcyB3aGljaCByZWFsLXdvcmxkIHR5cGUgb2YgY2FrZT8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2sgRm9yZXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgVGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYSBmcmFuY2hpc2Ugd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIE5vcnRoIEFtZXJpY2EgYmVmb3JlIEphcGFuPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlZ2VuZCBvZiBaZWxkYTogVHdpbGlnaHQgUHJpbmNlc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFdvcmxkIiwgdGhlIHJoaW5vIG1pbmktYm9zcywgUmV6bm9yLCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgbGVhZCBzaW5nZXIgb2YgdGhlIGJhbmQgIk5pbmUgSW5jaCBOYWlscyIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIHRoZSB0cmFjayBwbGF5ZWQgYnkgdGhlIERlY29yYXRlZCBNdXNpYyBCb3ggaXMgbmFtZWQgIkF0bGFzIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCdzIG9wZW5pbmcgY3V0c2NlbmUgc2hvd3MgIlJpY2h0b2ZlbiIga2lsbGluZyBhbm90aGVyIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgaGltc2VsZj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEdpYW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIG1hcCBmZWF0dXJlcyB0aGUgIkZseSBUcmFwIiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnPw==",
            "answer": "RGVyIFJpZXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3ZXJlIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB0d28gYmxvY2tzIGluICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiPw==",
            "answer": "R3Jhc3MgYW5kIENvYmJsZXN0b25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiBHcmFuZCBUaGVmdCBBdXRvIFY/",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDE3LCAyMDEz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgNHRoIGJvc3MgaW4gdGhlIDE5OTcgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ3Jhc2ggQmFuZGljb290IDI6IENvcnRleCBTdHJpa2VzIEJhY2siPw==",
            "answer": "RHIuIE4uIEdpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ3J5cHQgb2YgdGhlIE5lY3JvRGFuY2VyICgyMDE1KSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGFzIGEgc291bmR0cmFjayBieSBKYWtlICJWaXJ0IiBLYXVmbWFuPw==",
            "answer": "VW5jbGUgRWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgaW50cm91ZGNlZCBLbnVja2xlcyB0aGUgRWNoaWRuYT8=",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIDM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyBOT1QgYSBib3NzIGluIENyYXNoIEJhc2g/",
            "answer": "UmlwcGVyIFJvbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgb2YgZXhpc3RlbmNlIGluIE1pY3JvUHJvc2UncyAxOTk3ICJNYWdpYyB0aGUgR2F0aGVyaW5nIj8=",
            "answer": "U2hhbmRhbGFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBoYXMgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgbWFwIHNpemU/",
            "answer": "SnVzdCBDYXVzZSAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmludGVuZG8gNjQgZ2FtZSBkaWQgTk9UIGhhdmUgTHVpZ2kgaW4gaXQ/",
            "answer": "U3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gNjQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBUb3Vob3UgUHJvamVjdCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBmaXJzdCBldmVyIGFwcGVhcmFuY2Ugd2FzIGFzIGEgbWlkYm9zcyBpbiB0aGUgZWlnaHRoIGdhbWUsIEltcGVyaXNoYWJsZSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGV3aSBJbmFiYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlBvc3RhbCAyIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBQb3N0YWwgRHVkZSdzIGRvZz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbXA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vc3QgZ3JhcGhpY2FsbHkgdmlvbGVudCBnYW1lIHRvIHByZWNlZGUgdGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBFU1JCIChFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IFNvZnR3YXJlIFJhdGluZyBCb2FyZCkgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "TW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxvbmcgd2l0aCBHYWJlIE5ld2VsbCwgd2hvIGNvLWZvdW5kZWQgVmFsdmU/",
            "answer": "TWlrZSBIYXJyaW5ndG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hbm4gQ28uIFN0b3JlIGZyb20gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIGhhcyB0aGUgc2xvZ2FuICJXZSBoaXJlIG1lcmNlbmFyaWVzIGFuZCBnZXQgaW4gZmlnaHRzIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB3cml0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSI/",
            "answer": "TWFyYyBMYWlkbGF3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3YXMgZXhjbHVzaXZlIHRvIERyZWFtY2FzdD8=",
            "answer": "UGVuIFBlbiBUcmlJY2Vsb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIDNEIFdvcmxkIiwgdGhlIERvdWJsZSBDaGVycnkgcG93ZXItdXAgb3JpZ2luYXRlZCBmcm9tIGEgZGV2ZWxvcGVyIGFjY2lkZW50YWxseSBtYWtpbmcgdHdvIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgY29udHJvbGxhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHVsdGltYXRlIHBocmFzZSB1c2VkIGJ5IFBoYXJhaCBmcm9tIE92ZXJ3YXRjaCBpczogIkp1c3RpY2UgcmFpbnMgZnJvbSBhYm92ZSEi",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUFJPVE9UWVBFIDIuIHdobyBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBhcyAiVGFuZ28gUHJpbWFyeSI/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSGVsbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IE1vc3QgV2FudGVkICgyMDA1KSwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gYW50YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmVuY2UgIlJhem9yIiBDYWxsYWhhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBIZWFydGhzdG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IE1NT1JQRyB0byBwb3B1bGFyaXplIHRoZSBnZW5yZT8=",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hIE9ubGluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcHJpbWFyeSB3ZWFwb24gdGhlIHBsYXllciBnZXRzIGluICJQQVlEQVk6IFRoZSBIZWlzdCI/",
            "answer": "QU1DQVItNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBDUzpHTyBjYXNlIGNvbnRhaW5zIHRoZSBCdXR0ZXJmbHkgS25pZmU/",
            "answer": "QnJlYWtvdXQgQ2FzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIGdhbWUgZ2V0IHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJXYXJoZWFkIiBpbiB0aGUgU2VnYSBHZW5lc2lzIGdhbWUgIlZlY3Rvcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "UmFzdGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3VidGl0bGUgZm9yIEdyYW4gVHVyaXNtbyAzPw==",
            "answer": "QS1TcGVj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQ2l0eSBpbiBTYWludHMgUm93IFRoZSBUaGlyZD8=",
            "answer": "U3RlZWxwb3J0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGFsa2luZyBjYXQgaW4gUGVyc29uYSA1Pw==",
            "answer": "TW9yZ2FuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG91aG91IDEyOiBVbmRlZmluZWQgRmFudGFzdGljIE9iamVjdCwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "SXpheW9pIFNha3V5YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgR2FycnkncyBNb2Qgb3JpZ2luYWxseSB0b29rIGFzc2V0cyBhbmQgY29kZXMgZnJvbSB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBIYWxmIExpZmUgMiBtb2QgSkJtb2Qu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGl2aW5pdHk6IE9yaWdpbmFsIFNpbiBJSSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc2tlbGV0YWwgb3JpZ2luIGNoYXJhY3Rlcj8=",
            "answer": "RmFuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBudW1iZXJzIGRpZCBTYXlha2EgTWFpem9ubyB3cml0ZSBvbiB0aGUgd2FsbCBpbiBEYW5nYW4gUm9ucGEgVHJpZ2dlciBIYXBweSBIYXZvYz8=",
            "answer": "MTEwMzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vYmlsZSBnYW1lICJKZXRwYWNrIEpveXJpZGUiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/IA==",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxvIiBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIGluIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSBpcyBOZXcgTW9tYmFzYT8=",
            "answer": "S2VueWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MuIFNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBZb3NoaSdzIHNjaWVudGlmaWMgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VC4gWW9zaGlzYXVyIE11bmNoYWtvb3Bhcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHJhZ29uRm9yY2UncyAnVGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgRmlyZSBhbmQgRmxhbWVzJyBpcyB3aWRlbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSB0aGUgaGFyZGVzdCBzb25nIGluIHRoZSBHdWl0YXIgSGVybyBzZXJpZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEludGVybmV0IE1lbWUgIkFsbCB5b3VyIGJhc2UgYXJlIGJlbG9uZyB0byB1cyIgaXMgYmFzZWQgb24gdGhlIHBvb3JseSB0cmFuc2xhdGVkIEVuZ2xpc2ggVmVyc2lvbiBvZiB3aGljaCBWaWRlbyBHYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "WmVybyBXaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG1hc2NvdCBvZiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBOaW50ZW5kbyBnYW1lLCAiU3BsYXRvb24iIHdhcyBnb2luZyB0byBiZS4uLg==",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IE1heGlzIGdhbWUgdG8gZmVhdHVyZSB0aGUgZmljdGlvbmFsIGxhbmd1YWdlICJTaW1saXNoIiB3YXMgVGhlIFNpbXMgKDIwMDApLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpZ2h0aW5nIGdhbWUgIlNrdWxsZ2lybHMsIiB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgdXRpbGl6ZXMgYSBmb2xkaW5nIGNoYWlyIGNhbGxlZCB0aGUgIkh1cnRpbmciIGFzIGEgd2VhcG9uPw==",
            "answer": "QmVvd3VsZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmcgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgc2V0IHRvIGJlIGEgUG9wZXllIGFyY2FkZSBnYW1lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgcml2YWwgZ2FuZyBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBTYWludCdzIFJvdyAyPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFppbiBFbXBpcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIEFkdmVudHVyZSIsIHlvdSBhcmUgYWJsZSB0byB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBTdXBlciBTb25pYyBhdCB3aWxsIGFmdGVyIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgdGhlIG1haW4gc3Rvcnku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyLCB3aGljaCBjbGFzcyB3aWVsZHMgYSBzaG90Z3VuPw==",
            "answer": "RXZlcnlvbmUgTGlzdGVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgRnJhbmsgV2VzdCdzIGpvYiBpbiAiRGVhZCBSaXNpbmciPw==",
            "answer": "UGhvdG9qb3VybmFsaXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkb2VzIGEgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHNheSwgIlNvbWV0aW1lcywgSSBkcmVhbSBhYm91dCBjaGVlc2UiPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZiBMaWZlIDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlN1Ym5hdXRpY2EiLCBhICJTcGFkZWZpc2giIHdpbGwgYXR0YWNrIHlvdS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGh1bnRlciBhcnRzIGFyZSBleGNsdXNpdmUgdG8gdGhlIExvbmdzd29yZD8=",
            "answer": "VW5oaW5nZWQgU3Bpcml0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3Vydml2b3IgaW4gTGVmdCA0IERlYWQgc2FjcmlmaWNlZCB0aGVtc2VsZiB0byBzYXZlIHRoZSBvdGhlciBzdXJ2aXZvcnM/",
            "answer": "QmlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRlRMOiBGYXN0ZXIgVGhhbiBMaWdodCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugb3BlcmF0b3JzIGZyb20gIlRvbSBDbGFuY3kncyBSYWluYm93IFNpeCBTaWVnZSIgaGFzIHRoZSBhYmlsaXR5IHRvIGRhbWFnZSByZWluZm9yY2VkIHdhbGxzPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9yZGFuICJUaGVybWl0ZSIgVHJhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgRExDIHZlaGljbGUgaW4gIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgOCI/",
            "answer": "V2lsZCBXaWdnbGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1ldGFsIEdlYXIgU29saWQgMzogU25ha2UgRWF0ZXIiIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDA0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2VhbiBCZWFuIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mICJNYXJ0aW4gU2VwdGltIiBpbiB3aGljaCBFbGRlciBTY3JvbGxzIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHMgSVY6IE9ibGl2aW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJSSIgWm9tYmllcywgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgYWxsIHRoZSBtYWluIGVhc3RlciBlZ2dzIHJld2FyZCB5b3Ugd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAwIFhQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgYm9zcyB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGVuY291bnRlcnMgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTcgZ2FtZSwgIkxpdHRsZSBOaWdodG1hcmVzIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEphbml0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciAiTWFyaW8iIG1ha2UgaGlzIGZpcnN0IGFwcGVhcmFuY2U/",
            "answer": "RG9ua2V5IEtvbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU2lkIE1laWVyJ3MgQ2l2aWxpemF0aW9uIFYsIHdoaWNoIFdvcmxkIFdvbmRlciBjYW4gb25seSBiZSBidWlsdCBpbiBjaXRpZXMgb24gb3IgbmV4dCB0byBhIGRlc2VydD8=",
            "answer": "UGV0cmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RWFjaCBwaWVjZSBpbiBUZXRyaXMgaXMgY2FsbGVkIGEgdGV0cmlzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhbmNlbGVkIHByb2plY3RlZCBieSBCbGl6emFyZCBFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IHRoYXQgd291bGQgYmUgbGF0ZXIgYmVjb21lIE92ZXJ3YXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "VGl0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q291bnRpbmcgdGhlIEJsb29kIGFuZCBXaW5lIERMQywgaG93IG1hbnkgSGVybyBDYXJkcyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gdG90YWwgaW4gVGhlIFdpdGNoZXIgMz8=",
            "answer": "MjU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNob3RndW4gYXBwZWFycyBpbiBldmVyeSBudW1iZXJlZCBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlRoZSBTaW1zIiwgaG93IG1hbnkgU2ltb2xlb25zIGRvZXMgZWFjaCBmYW1pbHkgc3RhcnQgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "MjAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB2aWxsYWluIGNvbXBhbnkgaW4gIlN0YXJkZXcgVmFsbGV5Ij8=",
            "answer": "Sm9qYSBDbyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlrbyBCZWxsaWMgaXMgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIEdyYW5kIFRoZWZ0IEF1dG8gSVYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQb2vDqW1vbiBnYW1lcyByZWxlYXNlZCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "UG9rw6ltb24gQ3J5c3RhbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkNhdmUgU3RvcnksIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgQmFscm9nJ3MgY2F0Y2hwaHJhc2U/",
            "answer": "SHV6emFoIQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWVyeWwgU2lsdmVyYnVyZ2gsIGEgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgZnJvbSB0aGUgTWV0YWwgR2VhciBzZXJpZXMsIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGEgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHdoaWNoIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "UG9saWNlbmF1dHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4sIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIiwgaXMgc2FpZCB0byBoYXZlIG9uY2UgaGFkIGEgcG9ueXRhaWwu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWVyY3kncyAidWx0aW1hdGUgYWJpbGl0eSI/",
            "answer": "VmFsa3lyaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBNeXN0aWMgaW4gUG9rw6ltb24gR28/",
            "answer": "QmxhbmNoZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUFJPVE9UWVBFIDIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYWJpbGl0aWVzL3dlYXBvbnMgaXMgTk9UIG9idGFpbmVkIGJ5IGFuIEV2b2x2ZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGVuZHJpbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGdhbWVzIHdhc24ndCByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "TWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCBW"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBva8OpbW9uIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggdHlwZSBpcyBTdWRvd29vZG8sIHRoZSBJbWl0YXRpb24gUG9rw6ltb24/",
            "answer": "Um9jaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdlcmUgc2NyZWVuc2hvdHMgYWRkZWQgdG8gU3RlYW0/",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSBnYW1lIHRvIGluY2x1ZGUgdGhlIFpvbWJpZXMgZ2FtZW1vZGU/",
            "answer": "Q2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBXb3JsZCBhdCBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIERPT00gKDE5OTMpIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2hlYXQgY29kZT8=",
            "answer": "SURDTElQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIE5pbnRlbmRvIFN3aXRjaCBsYXVuY2ggdGl0bGUgaW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/IA==",
            "answer": "Vm9leg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJEZXZpbCBNYXkgQ3J5IiBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIHdoaWNoIGdhbWUgaXMgY2hyb25vbG9naWNhbGx5IGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "RGV2aWwgTWF5IENyeSAzOiBEYW50ZSdzIEF3YWtlbmluZyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIHdoZXJlIGlzICJTdGFtaW4tVXAiIGxvY2F0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "R2VuZXJhdG9yIDU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFNlYXNvbiBPbmUgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwIG9mICJMZWFndWUgb2YgTGVnZW5kcyIsIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGFjaGlldmFibGUgcmFuayB3YXMgRGlhbW9uZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ29EOiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUlJLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSByb2d1ZSBBLkkuIGFudGFnb25pc3Q/",
            "answer": "Q29ydnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQb2tlbW9uIFR5cGVzIHdhcyBwcmVzZW50IGluIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBnYW1lcywgUmVkIGFuZCBCbHVlPw==",
            "answer": "SWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE1NTyBSUEcgIlJlYWxtIG9mIHRoZSBNYWQgR29kIiwgd2hhdCBjbGFzcyBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IHBvc3NpYmxlIGRlZmVuc2U/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtuaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBNb2Rlcm4gV2FyZmFyZSAyLCBob3cgbWFueSBjb25zZWN1dGl2ZSBraWxscyBkb2VzIGl0IHJlcXVpcmUgdG8gZWFybiB0aGUgIlRhY3RpY2FsIE51a2UiIGtpbGxzdHJlYWs/",
            "answer": "MjU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgV2FyZnJhbWUsIHdoYXQgTWFzdGVyeSBSYW5rIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgdG8gYnVpbGQgdGhlIFRpZ3JpcyBQcmltZT8=",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBEZXN0aW55Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2F5ZGUtNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJNZXRhbCBHZWFyIFNvbGlkIiBzZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQncyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTb2xpZCBTbmFrZSdzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "TGlxdWlkIFNuYWtl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwiLCBvbmx5IENocmlzIGhhcyBhY2Nlc3MgdG8gdGhlIGdyZW5hZGUgbGF1bmNoZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggTWFyaW8gZ2FtZSBkaWQgdGhlIE1lZ2EgTXVzaHJvb20gbWFrZSBpdHMgZGVidXQ/",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8gUGFydHkgNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiB0aGUgdmlkZW9nYW1lICJEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2h1Y2sgR3JlZW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFNuaXBlcidzIFNNRyBpbiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIsIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGludGVuZGVkIHRvIGJlIHRoZSBTY291dCdzIHByaW1hcnkgd2VhcG9uLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBTZW50cnkgcm9ja2V0IGRhbWFnZSBmYWxsb2ZmIGlzIGNhbGN1bGF0ZWQgYmFzZWQgb24gdGhlIGRpc3RhbmNlIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIHNlbnRyeSBhbmQgdGhlIGVuZW15LCBub3QgdGhlIGVuZ2luZWVyIGFuZCB0aGUgZW5lbXk=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdmFuaWxsYSBNaW5lY3JhZnQsIHlvdSBjYW4gbWFrZSBhcm1vciBvdXQgb2YgYWxsIEJVVCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "RW1lcmFsZHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCBhbGlhcyB0aGF0IFByaW5jZXNzIEdhcm5ldCBnb2VzIGJ5IGluIEZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgSVg/",
            "answer": "RGFnZ2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0YXJ0aW5nIHBpc3RvbCBvZiB0aGUgVGVycm9yaXN0IHRlYW0gaW4gYSBjb21wZXRpdGl2ZSBtYXRjaCBvZiBDb3VudGVyIFN0cmlrZTogR2xvYmFsIE9mZmVuc2l2ZSBpcyB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "R2xvY2stMTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5hdGlvbmFsIFBva2VkZXggd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgaXMgUG9yeWdvbi1aPw==",
            "answer": "NDc0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gQnJvcy4sIHdobyBpbmZvcm1zIE1hcmlvIHRoYXQgdGhlIHByaW5jZXNzIGlzIGluIGFub3RoZXIgY2FzdGxlPw==",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IEhhcHB5IFRyaWdnZXIgSGF2b2MsIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgQW9pIEFzYWhpbmEncyB1bHRpbWF0ZSBhYmlsaXR5IGlzIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hdGUgU3dpbW1lcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlRlcnJhcmlhIiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9zc2VzIGFyZSBwcmUtaGFyZG1vZGUgYm9zc2VzPw==",
            "answer": "RXllIG9mIEN0aHVsaHU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciB3aGljaCBQb3J0YWwgMiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgd2FzIG5vdCBhIFRWIG9yIGZpbG0gYWN0b3IgcHJpb3IgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "R0xhRE9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaXRlbSByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBzdW1tb24gdGhlIGJvc3MgRHVrZSBGaXNocm9uIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIFRlcnJhcmlhPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZmZsZSBXb3Jt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUmlvdCBHYW1lcyAiTGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMiIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEhhbGxvd2VlbiBldmVudCBpcyBjYWxsZWQgIlRoZSBSZWNrb25pbmciLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkZhbGxvdXQ6IE5ldyBWZWdhcyIgcXVlc3QgaXMgTk9UIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIGEgcmVhbC1saWZlIHNvbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhleSBXZW50IFRoYXQtYS1XYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFpvbWJpZXMgbW9kZSBvZiAiQ2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSAiUGFjay1BLVB1bmNoZWQiIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgdGhlICJHYWxpbCIgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGFtZW50YXRpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mICJBY2UgQ29tYmF0IFplcm86IFRoZSBCZWxrYW4gV2FyIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2lwaGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBY2UgQXR0b3JuZXkiIHNlcmllcywgd2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdHJ1bHkgcmVzcG9uc2libGUgb2YgdGhlIGZvcmdpbmcgb2YgdGhlIGF1dG9wc3kgcmVwb3J0IG9mIHRoZSBwaXZvdGFsIElTLTcgaW5jaWRlbnQ/",
            "answer": "QmFuc2FpIEljaGl5YW5hZ2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgb25lIHRvIHJldHVybiB0byB0aGUgc2VyaWVzIGFmdGVyIGJlaW5nIGFic2VudCBmcm9tIGEgcHJldmlvdXMgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "RHIuIE1hcmlv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGFyZGVzdCBwb3NzaWJsZSBkaWZmaWN1bHR5IGluICJEZXVzIEV4OiBNYW5raW5kIERpdmlkZWQiPw==",
            "answer": "SSBOZXZlciBBc2tlZCBGb3IgVGhpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugcm9sZXMgaW4gVG93biBvZiBTYWxlbSBpcyBtYWZpYT8=",
            "answer": "RGlzZ3Vpc2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkZpcmUgRW1ibGVtOiBTaGFkb3cgRHJhZ29uIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2VudHJhbCBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCdzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "TWFydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byAoR1RBKSBnYW1lcyBoYXZlIHRoZSBzYW1lIHNldHRpbmc/",
            "answer": "R1RBIFYgYW5kIEdUQSBTYW4gQW5kcmVhcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFBhcmFkb3ggSW50ZXJhY3RpdmUgZ2FtZSAiU3RlbGxhcmlzIiB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAxNi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXIgaXMgQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgYmFzZWQgb24/",
            "answer": "Q29sZCBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmludGVuZG8gc3RhcnRlZCBvdXQgYXMgYSBwbGF5aW5nIGNhcmQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGRpZ2l0YWwgZGlzdHJpYnV0aW9uIHBsYXRmb3JtIFN0ZWFtPw==",
            "answer": "VmFsdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIERTIGdhbWUgJ0dob3N0IFRyaWNrOiBQaGFudG9tIERldGVjdGl2ZScsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGhpdG1hbiBzZWVuIGF0IHRoZSBzdGFydCBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "TmVhcnNpZ2h0ZWQgSmVlZ28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGhlcm8gaW4gdGhlIDgwcyBhbmltYXRlZCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lICdEcmFnb24ncyBMYWlyJz8=",
            "answer": "RGlyayB0aGUgRGFyaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBzaGlwIHVzZWQgYnkgQ29tbWFuZGVyIFNoZXBhcmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IEZyYW5jaGlzZSBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "Tm9ybWFuZHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNsYXNoIFJveWFsZSIgd2hhdCBpcyBBcmVuYSA0IGNhbGxlZD8=",
            "answer": "UC5FLksuSy5BJ3MgUGxheWhvdXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MuIiwgdGhlIGNsb3VkcyBhbmQgYnVzaGVzIGhhdmUgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXJ0d29yayBhbmQgYXJlIGp1c3QgZGlmZmVyZW50IGNvbG9ycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ1M6R08gZVNwb3J0cyB0ZWFtIHdvbiB0aGUgbWFqb3IgZXZlbnQgRVNMIE9uZSBDb2xvZ25lIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "U0sgR2FtaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Um9ja2V0IExlYWd1ZSBpcyBhIGdhbWUgd2hpY2ggZmVhdHVyZXMuLg==",
            "answer": "Q2Fycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBWSSB3YXMgb3JpZ2luYWxseSByZWxlYXNlZCBvdXRzaWRlIEphcGFuIHVuZGVyIHdoYXQgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZSBmcmFuY2hpc2VzIHdlcmUgbWFkZSBieSBOYW1jbz8=",
            "answer": "VGVra2Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyB3ZWFwb24gaW4gQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IEdsb2JhbCBPZmZlbnNpdmUgZG9lcyBub3QgZXhpc3QgaW4gcmVhbCBsaWZlLg==",
            "answer": "TTRBNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGhpbCBGaXNoIHdhcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "RmV6"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBCaW5kaW5nIG9mIElzYWFjIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmluYWwgYm9zcyB0aGF0IHlvdSBmaWdodCBpbiBUaGUgVm9pZD8=",
            "answer": "RGVsaXJpdW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHRvcC1kb3duIG9ubGluZSBSUEcgIlNwYWNlIFN0YXRpb24gMTMiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9wIHNpbmdlciB3YXMgYnJvdWdodCBpbiBieSBTRUdBIHRvIHByb2R1Y2UgdGhlIG11c2ljIGZvciAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIDMiPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwcm9zZWN1dG9yIGluIHRoZSAiQWNlIEF0dG9ybmV5IiB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SmFrZSBNYXJzaGFsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIktpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIiwgd2hvIGFiZHVjdHMgSmFzbWluZSBpbiB0aGUgTGFtcCBDaGFtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "UmlrdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkZ1ZWwiIGhhcyBhbiBvcGVuIHdvcmxkIHRoYXQgaXMgNSw1NjAgc3F1YXJlIG1pbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW50aWwgRGF3biwgYm90aCBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIFNhbSBhbmQgTWlrZSBjYW5ub3QgYmUga2lsbGVkIHVuZGVyIGFueSBtZWFucyB1bnRpbCB0aGUgZmluYWwgY2hhcHRlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9raSBEb2tpIExpdGVyYXR1cmUgQ2x1YiB3YXMgZGV2ZWxvcGVkIGluIEphcGFuLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlNwbGF0b29uIiwgdGhlIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgd2VyZSBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGdvaW5nIHRvIGJlIHJhYmJpdHMgaW5zdGVhZCBvZiBzcXVpZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHVuaXNobWVudCBmb3IgcGxheWluZyBQb3N0YWwgMiBpbiBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "MTAgeWVhcnMgaW4gcHJpc29uIGFuZCBhIGZpbmUgb2YgJDUwLDAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBTb2xpZCBTbmFrZSdzIHJlYWwgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgIk1lZ2Fsb3ZhbmlhIiBieSBUb2J5IEZveCBtYWRlIGl0cyB0aGlyZCBhcHBlYXJlbmNlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE1IFJQRyAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgNjQiLCBXYWx1aWdpIGlzIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgT3ZlcndhdGNoPw==",
            "answer": "SW52b2tlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0d28gY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lIFVuZGVydGFsZSBhcmUgbmV2ZXIgaW4gYSByZWxhdGlvbnNoaXAgb3Igbm90IHJlbGF0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "RnJpc2sgJiBDaGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyB0aGUgbWFzY290IG9mIHRoZSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNvbXBhbnkgU0VHQT8=",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZGlmZmVyZW50bHkgc2hhcGVkIFRldHJpcyBwaWVjZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEZhbGxvdXQgc2VyaWVzLCBvbiB3aGljaCBkYXRlIGRpZCBUaGUgR3JlYXQgV2FyIGhhcHBlbj8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyM3JkLCAyMDc3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUG9rZW1vbiBnZW5lcmF0aW9uIGRpZCB0aGUgZmFuLW5hbWVkICJNYXN1ZGEgTWV0aG9kIiBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXIgaW4/IA==",
            "answer": "RGlhbW9uZC9QZWFybA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWF4aW11bSBIUCBpbiBUZXJyYXJpYT8=",
            "answer": "NTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IC5oYWNrIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "LmhhY2svL0luZmVjdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBibG9jayBpbiBNaW5lY3JhZnQgaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGJsYXN0IHJlc2lzdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "QmFycmllcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0LCB3aGljaCB0d28gaXRlbXMgbXVzdCBiZSBjb21iaW5lZCB0byBjcmFmdCBhIHRvcmNoPw==",
            "answer": "U3RpY2sgYW5kIENvYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG9ieSBGb3gncyAiTWVnYWxvdmFuaWEiIHdhcyBmaXJzdCB1c2VkIHdoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "UmFkaWF0aW9uJ3MgRWFydGhib3VuZCBIYWxsb3dlZW4gSGFjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgbWFpbiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnIHdpbGwgcmV3YXJkIHlvdSB3aXRoIHRoZSBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCwgIkxpdHRsZSBMb3N0IEdpcmwiPw==",
            "answer": "T3JpZ2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgbWFpbiBlYXN0ZXIgZWdnIHdpbGwgcmV3YXJkIHlvdSB3aXRoIHRoZSBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCwgIkhpZ2ggTWFpbnRlbmFuY2UiPw==",
            "answer": "RGllIFJpc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgU2FucyBhbmQgUGFweXJ1cyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciBpbiAiVW5kZXJ0YWxlIj8=",
            "answer": "Rm9udHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbGYtTGlmZSB1bml2ZXJzZSwgdGhlIEJsYWNrIE1lc2EgUmVzZWFyY2ggRmFjaWxpdHkgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBVUyBzdGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IE1leGljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgRG9raSBEb2tpIExpdGVyYXR1cmUgQ2x1Yj8=",
            "answer": "Tmljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHBvcHVsYXIgZnJhbmNoaXNlIHRoYXQgaW5jbHVkZXMgcGxhY2luZyBibG9ja3MgZG93biBhbmQgc3Vydml2aW5nIGluIGFuIG9wZW4gd29ybGQ/IA==",
            "answer": "TWluZWNyYWZ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHJldGFpbCBkaXNjIG9mIFRvbnkgSGF3aydzIFBybyBTa2F0ZXIgNSBvbmx5IGNvbWVzIHdpdGggdGhlIHR1dG9yaWFsLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMsIERPVEEgMiwgU21pdGUgYW5kIEhlcm9lcyBvZiB0aGUgU3Rvcm0gYXJlIGFsbCBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGdhbWUgZ2VucmU/",
            "answer": "TXVsdGlwbGF5ZXIgT25saW5lIEJhdHRsZSBBcmVuYSAoTU9CQSk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGFudGFnb25pc3QgaW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBmcmFuY2hpc2U/",
            "answer": "R0xhRE9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgZGlkIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIiBydW4gb24/",
            "answer": "R29sZFNyYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkhhbGYtTGlmZSAyIiBydW5zIG9uIHRoZSBTb3VyY2UgRW5naW5lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIDIwMTEgVmlkZW8gR2FtZSAiTWluZWNyYWZ0Ij8=",
            "answer": "TWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdG90YWwgbW9uc3RlcnMgYXBwZWFyIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIEdlbmVyYXRpb25zPw==",
            "answer": "MTA1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2VhcG9uIGNsYXNzZXMgRE8gTk9UIGFwcGVhciBpbiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "Qm93IA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhhbG8iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwbGFuZXQgd2hpY2ggSW5zdGFsbGF0aW9uIDA0IG9yYml0cz8=",
            "answer": "VGhyZXNob2xk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBmcm9tIHRoZSBpbmRpZSBhZHZlbnR1cmUgZ2FtZSAiTmlnaHQgaW4gdGhlIFdvb2RzIj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyZ2FyZXQgQm9yb3dza2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogV29ybGQgQXQgV2FyIiwgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGFwcGVhcmFuY2Ugb2YgdGhlICJQUFNILTQxIiBpbiAiWm9tYmllcyIgd2FzIGluIHRoZSBtYXAgIkRlciBSaWVzZSIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXNuJ3QgYSB2aWxsaWFuIGluIENsdWIgUGVuZ3Vpbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIERpcmVjdG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBva8OpbW9uIFN1biBhbmQgTW9vbiIsIFRlYW0gU2t1bGwgdG9vayBvdmVyIHdoaWNoIHRvd24/",
            "answer": "UG8gVG93bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nJ3Mgb3JpZ2luYWwgaHVtYW4gZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "TWFkb25uYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAwNCwgd2hpY2ggcGVyc29uKHMpIGNyZWF0ZWQgIlJvYmxveCI/",
            "answer": "RGF2aWQgQmFzenVja2kgYW5kIEVyaWsgQ2Fzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgdGhlIGRlZmF1bHQgVUkgY29sb3IgdGhhdCBzaWduaWZpZXMgRHJ1aWQgaXMgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "T3Jhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEFSUEcgIlBhdGggb2YgRXhpbGUsIiB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGFtb3VudCBvZiBzb2NrZXRzIHRoYXQgYW4gaXRlbSBjYW4gaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiBjYW5vbiwgd2hhdCBkaWQgU2hha2VzcGVhcmljbGVzIE5PVCBpbnZlbnQ/",
            "answer": "U3RhaXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBob3N0ZWQgdGhlIENTOkdPIERyZWFtaGFjayBPcGVuIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "Q2x1ai1OYXBvY2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRW50ZXIgdGhlIEd1bmdlb24sIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVzZSBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdpemFyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSB0aXRsZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyOSwgMjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggc2VyaWVzIG9mIGdhbWVzIGRvIHlvdSBjb2xsZWN0IHNvdWxzIHRvIGVtcG93ZXIgeW91IGFuZCBidXkgd2VhcG9ucnkgYW5kIGFybW9yIHdpdGg/",
            "answer": "U291bHMg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qmxpbmt5LCBQaW5reSwgSW5reSBhbmQgQ2x5ZGUgYXJlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBjbGFzc2ljIHZpZGVvIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "UGFjLU1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW50dXJuZWQgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBzdGFydGVkIGFzIGEgUm9ibG94IGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgYSAiMzYwIG5vLXNjb3BlIiBpcyBvbmUgZnVsbCByb3RhdGlvbiBiZWZvcmUgc2hvb3RpbmcsIGhvdyBtYW55IHJvdGF0aW9ucyB3b3VsZCBhICIxMDgwIG5vLXNjb3BlIiBiZT8=",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1haW4gZW5kaW5ncyBhcmUgdGhlcmU/",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSB0aGUgbG9jYXRpb24tYmFzZWQgYXVnbWVudGVkIHJlYWxpdHkgZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgTmlhbnRpYyBiZWZvcmUgUG9rw6ltb24gR08/",
            "answer": "SW5ncmVzcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc291bHMgZ2FtZSB3YXMgbm90IGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IEhpZGV0YWthIE1peWF6YWtpPw==",
            "answer": "RGFyayBTb3VscyAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSGFsZi1MaWZlIDIsIGlmIHlvdSBwbGF5IHRoZSB6b21iaWVzJyBzcGVlY2ggaW4gcmV2ZXJzZSwgdGhleSBhY3R1YWxseSBzcGVhayBjb2hlcmVudCBFbmdsaXNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBmcm9tIHRoZSBTTkVTIGdhbWUgQ2xvY2sgVG93ZXI/",
            "answer": "SmVubmlmZXIgU2ltcHNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGFuZ2Fucm9ucGE6IFRyaWdnZXIgSGFwcHkgSGF2b2MsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0J3MgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrb3RvIE5hZWdp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGVzdGlueSwgd2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBQZXRlciBEaW5rbGFnZSBpbiB2b2ljaW5nIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCdzICJHaG9zdCI/",
            "answer": "Tm9sYW4gTm9ydGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhhbGYtTGlmZSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgImdyYXZpdHkgZ3VuIj8=",
            "answer": "WmVyby1Qb2ludCBFbmVyZ3kgRmllbGQgTWFuaXB1bGF0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBub3QgYSBkZWZhdWx0IGdhbWUgbW9kZSBpbiBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZSAoMjAwMCk/",
            "answer": "QXJtcyBSYWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBpcyBTYW5zLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSB3YXMgdXNlZCB0byBjcmVhdGUgdGhlIGdhbWUgIk1pbmVjcmFmdCI/",
            "answer": "SmF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgTGVhZ3VlIG9mIExlZ2VuZHMgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHNjcmFwcGVkIFNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIGxldmVsICJIaWRkZW4gUGFsYWNlIFpvbmUiIHdhcyBsYXRlciByZXVzZWQgaW4gdGhlIGlPUyBwb3J0IG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lLiA=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dDogTmV3IFZlZ2FzLCB1cG9uIHN0YXJ0aW5nIGVhY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb3VyIGNhbXBhaWduIERMQ3MsIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVtIGRvZXMgbm90IGhhdmUgYSB3YXJuaW5nIHNjcmVlbi9yZWNvbW1lbmRlZCBsZXZlbD8g",
            "answer": "SG9uZXN0IEhlYXJ0cyA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFydG5lcnMgY2FuIHlvdSBvYnRhaW4gaW4gUGFwZXIgTWFyaW86IFRoZSBUaG91c2FuZC1ZZWFyIERvb3I/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlVuZGVydGFsZSIsIHdobyB3YXMgTWV0dGF0b24ncyBjcmVhdG9yPw==",
            "answer": "QWxwaHlz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFjY2VsZXJhdGlvbiBvZiBNYXJpbyBpZiBoZSB3YXMgaW4gZnJlZSBmYWxsPw==",
            "answer": "OTEuMjggbS9zXjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIGFuIGFsbGllZCBNY0NyZWUgd2lsbCBzYXkgIlN0ZXAgcmlnaHQgdXAiIHVwb24gdXNpbmcgaGlzIHVsdGltYXRlIGFiaWxpdHkgRGVhZGV5ZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCB3aGF0J3MgdGhlIHByaXplIGZvciBhbnN3ZXJpbmcgY29ycmVjdGx5Pw==",
            "answer": "TW9yZSBxdWVzdGlvbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IG9mIERlYWQgU3BhY2U/",
            "answer": "SXNhYWMgQ2xhcmtl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG91aG91OiBFbWJvZGltZW50IG9mIFNjYXJsZXQgRGV2aWwsIHdoYXQgc29uZyBwbGF5cyBkdXJpbmcgRmxhbmRyZSBTY2FybGV0J3MgYm9zcyBmaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VS5OLiBPd2VuIFdhcyBIZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWlycm9yJ3MgRWRnZSBDYXRhbHlzdCB0YWtlcyBwbGFjZSBpbiB0aGUgQ2l0eSBvZi4uLj8=",
            "answer": "R2xhc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2hhcHRlciAxIG9mIHRoZSBTb3VyY2UgRW5naW5lIG1vZCAiVW5kZXJoZWxsIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDFzdCwgMjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgRGVhZCBieSBEYXlsaWdodCwgdGhlIGtpbGxlciBNaWNoYWVsIE15ZXJzIGlzIHJlZmVyZWQgdG8gYXMgIlRoZSBTaGFwZSIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nIGdhbWUgd2FzIGZvciB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gV2lpPw==",
            "answer": "QW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nOiBDaXR5IEZvbGs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIG1hbmFnZXIgb2YgdGhlIHRvd24gc2hvcD8=",
            "answer": "VG9tIE5vb2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24sIEJ1bGJhc2F1ciBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBzdGFydGVyIHBva2Vtb24gdGhhdCBpcyBhIEdyYXNzL1BvaXNvbiB0eXBlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBob3VzZWhvbGQgaXRlbSBtYWtlIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIG9mICJTdGVpbnM7IEdhdGUiIHRyYXZlbCB0aHJvdWdoIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "TWljcm93YXZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgTWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24/",
            "answer": "RHdhcmYgRm9ydHJlc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBCaW5kaW5nIG9mIElzYWFjIiwgd2hpY2ggaXRlbSBpbnN0YW50bHkga2lsbHMgTW9tIGFuZCBNb20ncyBIZWFydD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJpYmxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgZmlnaHRlciBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gTWVsZWUiIGNhcGFibGUgb2YgZGVhbGluZyBkYW1hZ2Ugd2l0aCB0aGVpciB0YXVudCBhbmltYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "THVpZ2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBKb2VsJ3MgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUsICJUaGUgTGFzdCBvZiBVcyI/IA==",
            "answer": "U2FyYWg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgdGFrZXMgcGxhY2UgaW4gdGhlIElyaXNoIHRvd24gb2YgRG9vbGluLCB3aXRoIHRoZSBvcHRpb24gdG8gcGxheSBhcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMsIEVsbGVuIGFuZCBLZWF0cz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9sa2xvcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24sIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFnZSB0aGF0IGlua2xpbmdzIGNhbiBmcmVlbHkgY2hhbmdlIGJldHdlZW4gc3F1aWQgYW5kIGh1bWFub2lkIGZvcm1zPw==",
            "answer": "MTQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgeW91IHBsYXkgYXMgaW4gWXVtZSBOaWtraT8=",
            "answer": "TWFkb3RzdWtp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSByYWNlIGluIHRoZSBNTU9SUEcgR3VpbGQgV2FycyAyPyA=",
            "answer": "VGVuZ3U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkxlYWd1ZSBvZiBMZWdlbmRzIiB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMga25vd24gYXMgIlRoZSBTaW5pc3RlciBCbGFkZSI/",
            "answer": "S2F0YXJpbmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIFN0cmVldCBGaWdodGVyIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFpIFNoaXJhbnVp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkJyYXdsaGFsbGEiLCB3aGF0IHNwZWNpZXMgaXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBCw7ZkdmFyIGlzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsZiBIdW1hbiAvIEhhbGYgQmVhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlN0YXJib3VuZCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG1heCBIUCBvZiB0aGUgbW9uc3RlciAiUHVuY2h5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NTAsMDAwIEhQ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQsIHdoaWNoIHJhaWQgaW5zdGFuY2UgZmVhdHVyZXMgYSBjaGVzcyBldmVudD8=",
            "answer": "S2FyYXpoYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTmVlZCBmb3IgU3BlZWQ6IFVuZGVyZ3JvdW5kLCB3aGF0IGNhciBkb2VzIEVkZGllIGRyaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Tmlzc2FuIFNreWxpbmUgR1QtUiAoUjM0KQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB2aWN0aW0gbWVudGlvbmVkIGluIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgS0ctOCBpbmNpZGVudCwgaW4gQWNlIGF0dG9ybmV5IEludmVzdGlnYXRpb25zLCBDYXNlIDQ/",
            "answer": "RGVpZCBNYW5u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2ZWhpY2xlIGluIFBVQkcgaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IHRvcCBzcGVlZD8=",
            "answer": "TW90b3JjeWNsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIFNvcmEncyBOb2JvZHkgaW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHM/",
            "answer": "Um94YXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IGFtb3VudCBvZiBtYXggaGVhbHRoIHlvdSBjYW4gaGF2ZSBpbiBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDI/",
            "answer": "NzA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvJ3MgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgR2VvbWV0cnkgRGFzaD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IFRvcGFsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGludGVyYWN0aXZlIG1vdmllIHZpZGVvIGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "QXN0cm9uIEJlbHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIEZJUlNUIFZhbHZlIGdhbWUgdG8gaGF2ZSBWUj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExhYg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgaGFuZGhlbGQgZ2FtZSBkZXZpY2U/",
            "answer": "TWF0dGVsIEF1dG8gUmFjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2F0Y2hfRG9ncyAyIGlzIGEgcHJlcXVlbC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlICMxIHNlbGxpbmcgZ2FtZSBvbiBTdGVhbSBieSByZXZlbnVlIGluIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "U2lkIE1laWVyJ3MgQ2l2aWxpemF0aW9uIFZJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY3JlYXR1cmUgdGhhdCB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgYmVmcmllbmRzIGluICJUaGUgTGFzdCBHdWFyZGlhbiI/",
            "answer": "VHJpY28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIkRhcmsgU291bHMiIHNlcmllcyBkb2VzIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXIgcGxheSBhcyB0aGUgIkFzaGVuIE9uZSI/",
            "answer": "RGFyayBTb3VscyBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBDYWxsIG9mIER1dHkgZ2FtZXMgd2FzIGEgUFMzIGxhdW5jaCB0aXRsZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5IDM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYWR2ZW50dXJlciB5b3UgbWVldCBhdCB0aGUgbWluZXMgaW4gU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXk/",
            "answer": "TWFybG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHN1cnZpdmFsIGhvcnJvciBnYW1lLCAiQ3J5IG9mIEZlYXIsIiB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTaW1vbidzIGNsb3NlIGZyaWVuZC9wb3RlbnRpYWwgbG92ZSBpbnRlcmVzdD8=",
            "answer": "U29waGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UHN5Y2gtSG9ycm9yICJFdGVybmFsIERhcmtuZXNzOiBTYW5pdHkncyBSZXF1aWVtIiwgZGV2ZWxvcGVkIGJ5IFNpbGljb24gS25pZ2h0cyBpbiAyMDAyLCB3YXMgcHVibGlzaGVkIGJ5IHdobyBhbmQgb24gd2hhdCBwbGF0Zm9ybT8=",
            "answer": "TmludGVuZG/CriBDby4gTHRkLiB8IEdhbWVDdWJl4oSi"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgU3RhciBTcGlyaXRzIGRvIHlvdSByZXNjdWUgaW4gdGhlIE5pbnRlbmRvIDY0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlBhcGVyIE1hcmlvIj8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdhbWUgIkJhdHRsZWZpZWxkIDEiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMidzIGZpY3Rpb25hbCBjb21wYW55ICJNYW5uIENvIj8=",
            "answer": "WmVwaGVuaWFoIE1hbm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGhlcm8gTWNDcmVlJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmVzc2UgTWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gT3ZlcndhdGNoLCBob3cgb2xkIGlzIFJlaW5oYXJkdCBXaWxoZWxtPw==",
            "answer": "NjE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdG93biB3YXMgU2VhbXVzICJTbGVkZ2UiIENvd2RlbiBmcm9tICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIGJvcm4gaW4/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBPJ0dyb2F0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lcyBvZiB0aGVzZSBNYXJpbyBLYXJ0IGdhbWVzIHdhcyBtYWRlIGZvciB0aGUgR2FtZWJveSBBZHZhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWFyaW8gS2FydDogU3VwZXIgQ2lyY3VpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIGNvbXBsZXRpbmcgd2hpY2ggbWFwJ3MgZWFzdGVyIGVnZyB3aWxsIHJld2FyZCB5b3Ugd2l0aCB0aGUgYWNoaWV2ZW1lbnQsICJUaW1lIFRyYXZlbCBXaWxsIFRlbGwiPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhbmdyaS1MYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG1haW4gY3VycmVuY3kgaW4gQ2x1YiBQZW5ndWluPw==",
            "answer": "Q29pbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggcGxhbmV0IGRvZXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgRnJlZWRvbSBQbGFuZXQgKDIwMTQpIHRha2UgcGxhY2U/",
            "answer": "QXZhbGljZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2h5IHdlcmUgb25seSBvbmx5IDMwMCwwMDAgY29waWVzIG9mIFVuaXJhY2VycyB3ZXJlIHByb2R1Y2VkPw==",
            "answer": "RE1BIERlc2lnbnMgd2FzIHN1ZWQgYnkgUGl4YXIsIHByZXZlbnRpbmcgbW9yZSBjb3BpZXMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBwcm9kdWNlZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGludHJvZHVjZWQgaW4gU29uaWMgQm9vbTogUmlzZSBvZiBMeXJpYz8=",
            "answer": "U3RpY2tzIHRoZSBCYWRnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAzIiBmb3IgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sb3Igb2YgdGhlIHNlY29uZCBDaGFvcyBFbWVyYWxkIHlvdSBjYW4gZ2V0IGZyb20gU3BlY2lhbCBTdGFnZXM/",
            "answer": "T3Jhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgYXJlIGFsbCB0aGUgY3V0c2NlbmVzIGZyb20gTWV0YWwgR2VhciBTb2xpZCA0IChQUzMsIDIwMDgpIGNvbWJpbmVkPw==",
            "answer": "OCBob3Vycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG9ueSBIYXdrJ3MgUHJvIFNrYXRlciB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMTk5OS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIHRoZSBlYXJseSBwcm90b3R5cGVzIG9mIHRoZSBTZWdhIERyZWFtY2FzdCBjb250cm9sbGVyIHJlc2VtYmxlZCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "VGVsZXZpc2lvbiBSZW1vdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIFN1cGVyIFNtYXNoIEJyb3MuIGNvbnRhaW5lZCBOaW50ZW5kbyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzLCB3aGF0IHdhcyBpdCBrbm93biBhcyBpbnRlcm5hbGx5Pw==",
            "answer": "RHJhZ29uIEtpbmc6IFRoZSBGaWdodGluZyBHYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgd2VhcG9uIHlvdSBhY3F1aXJlIGluIEhhbGYtTGlmZT8=",
            "answer": "QSBjcm93YmFy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRmFsbG91dCA0LCB3aGljaCB0eXBlIG9mIHBvd2VyIGFybW9yIGlzIGZpcnN0IGVuY291bnRlcmVkIGluIHRoZSBlYXJseSBtaXNzaW9uICJXaGVuIEZyZWVkb20gQ2FsbHMiIGluIGEgY3Jhc2hlZCBWZXJ0aWJpcmQ/",
            "answer": "VC00NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBvcnRhbCBzZXJpZXMgb2YgZ2FtZXMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGZvdW5kZXIgb2YgQXBlcnR1cmUgU2NpZW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2F2ZSBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBoYXMgSmVubmlmZXIgVGF5bG9yIE5PVCB2b2ljZWQ/",
            "answer": "U2FyYWggS2VycmlnYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCBob3cgbXVjaCBkbyBTcGlkZXIgRG9udXRzIGNvc3QgaW4gSG90bGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "OTk5OUc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyBFbnRlcnRhaW5tZW50IFN5c3RlbSB2b2ljZSBjaGFubmVscyBzdXBwb3J0cyBwbGF5YmFjayBvZiBzb3VuZCBzYW1wbGVzLiBXaGljaCBvbmU/",
            "answer": "RE1D"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgICJNaW5lY3JhZnQiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F2ZSBHYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFbmdsaXNoIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBTb3JhIGZyb20gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "SGFsZXkgSm9lbCBPc21lbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgUG9rw6ltb24gQ29ucXVlc3QsIHdoaWNoIHdhcmxvcmQgaXMgYWJsZSB0byBib25kIHdpdGggWmVrcm9tIGFuZCBhIHNoaW55IFJheXF1YXp6YT8=",
            "answer": "Tm9idW5hZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBsb3JlIG9mICJTdGFyYm91bmQiLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgdGhlICJDb2xvbnkgRGVlZCIgZG8gd2hlbiBpdCBpcyBwbGFjZWQgZG93bj8=",
            "answer": "U2VuZHMgb3V0IGFuIGFkdmVydGlzZW1lbnQgZm9yIHNvbWVvbmUgdG8gbW92ZSBpbi4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xvcnMgZG9lcyB0aGUgWm9tYmllIGV5ZXMgZ2xvdyBpbiB0aGUgIk51a2V0b3duIiBtYXAgaW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJIiBab21iaWVzIG1vZGU/",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93IGFuZCBCbHVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgR2VuZXJhdGlvbiAxIFBva2Vtb24gZGlkIE5PVCBoYXZlIGFuIGV2b2x1dGlvbiBpbiBHZW5lcmF0aW9uIDQ/",
            "answer": "SnlueA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2hhbmcgVHN1bmcgaXMgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gTW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCBYTC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiBEaWFtb25kLCBQZWFybCBhbmQgUGxhdGludW0sIHdoZXJlIGNhbiBhIE11bmNobGF4IGJlIGZvdW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SG9uZXkgVHJlZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyIG9mIHRoZSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiwgaXMgWmVsZGEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgTk9UIGdldCBmaW5hbmNlZCB2aWEgQ3Jvd2RmdW5kaW5nPw==",
            "answer": "RW50ZXIgdGhlIEd1bmdlb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBIYWxmLUxpZmU6IE9wcG9zaW5nIEZvcmNlPw==",
            "answer": "QWRyaWFuIFNoZXBoYXJk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgQ2hhb3MgRW1lcmFsZHMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiB1bml2ZXJzZT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgU3RlYW0gZmlyc3QgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBzcGVlZCBwb3NzaWJsZSBpbiBUcmFja21hbmlhwrI6IFN0YWRpdW0/",
            "answer": "MTAwMCAga20vaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGlzIE5PVCBhIGZlbWFsZSBtYXJyaWFnZSBjYW5kaWRhdGUgaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgU3RhcmRldyBWYWxsZXk/",
            "answer": "Q2Fyb2xpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXMgYWxtb3N0IGFkZGVkIGludG8gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gTWVsZWUsIGJ1dCBub3QgaW5jbHVkZWQgYXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgd2FzIHRvbyBmYXIgaW4gZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "U29saWQgU25ha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyB3YXMgY29uc2lkZXJlZCwgYnV0IHVsdGltYXRlbHkgbm90IGluY2x1ZGVkLCBmb3IgU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gTWVsZWU/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgQm9uZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBva8OpbW9uIHNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBQYWxraWEncyBoaWRkZW4gYWJpbGl0eT8=",
            "answer": "VGVsZXBhdGh5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdHJvcGhpZXMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluICJTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zLiBmb3IgTmludGVuZG8gM0RTIj8=",
            "answer": "Njg1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGVuZ2luZSBkb2VzIHRoZSB2aWRlb2dhbWUgUXVha2UgMiBydW4gaW4/",
            "answer": "aUQgVGVjaCAy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBDb0QgIkRlYXRoc3RyZWFrIiBpcyBvbmx5IGZlYXR1cmVkIGluIENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSA6IE1vZGVybiBXYXJmYXJlIDI/",
            "answer": "Q29weWNhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggVS5TLiBzdGF0ZSBpcyBGYXIgQ3J5IDUncyBmaWN0aW9uYWwgc2V0dGluZyAnSG9wZSBDb3VudHknIGxvY2F0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "TW9udGFuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgdGl0bGVzIGJ5IFZhbHZlIGlzIG5vdCBiYXNlZCBvbiBhIENvbW11bml0eSBNb2Q/",
            "answer": "Umljb2NoZXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIGdhbWUgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgZG8geW91IGZpZ2h0IEdpbGdhbWVzaCBpbiAiRmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSA1Ij8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIDYgbGVnZW5kYXJ5IGNhcmRzIGluICJDbGFzaCBSb3lhbGUiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBEaXNob25vcmVkIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgQmF0dGxlYmxvY2sgVGhlYXRlciwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIHdobyB2b2ljZWQgdGhlIG5hcnJhdG9yPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbCBTdGFtcGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIk1hc3MgRWZmZWN0IiBnYW1lIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgIlJvYmxveCIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJMaXR0bGUgTG9zdCBHaXJsIiBFYXN0ZXIgRWdnIGluIENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogQmxhY2sgT3BzIElJLCB3aGF0J3MgdGhlIGxhc3Qgc3RlcCByZXF1aXJlZCBmb3IgdGhlIGFjaGlldmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "UmFpc2UgSGVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgMiIsIHdoYXQgaXMgTGVvbiBLZW5uZWR5J3MgbWlkZGxlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "U2NvdHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzeXN0ZW0gd2FzICJUb3Vob3U6IEhpZ2hseSBSZXNwb25zaXZlIHRvIFByYXllcnMiIHJlbGVhc2VkIG9uPw==",
            "answer": "UEMtOTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5sb2NrYWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gRm9yIFdpaSBVIGFuZCAzRFMgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSBmb3VnaHQgdG8gYmUgdW5sb2NrZWQ/",
            "answer": "TWlpIEZpZ2h0ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBnaXZlbiB0byBTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2cgNCBkdXJpbmcgaXRzIGRldmVsb3BtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "UHJvamVjdCBOZWVkbGVtb3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgb2YgV2FyY3JhZnQgTG9yZSwgZm91ciBPbGQgR29kcyBjcmVhdGVkIGEgZ2lhbnQgYW5kIHBvd2VyZnVsIGNyZWF0dXJlLiBXaGF0IHdhcyBpdCBjYWxsZWQ/IA==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuY2llbnQgT25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY3VycmVuY3kgaW4gdGhlICJBbmltYWwgQ3Jvc3NpbmciIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "QmVsbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2h5IHdhcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIFRyZXZvciBQaGlsaXBzIGRpc2NoYXJnZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgQWlyIEZvcmNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWVudGFsIEhlYWx0aCBJc3N1ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2VhcG9ucyBpcyBOT1QgYXZhaWxhYmxlIHRvIHRoZSBUZXJyb3Jpc3QgdGVhbSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSwgIkNvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlIj8=",
            "answer": "U0NBUi0yMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHYWJlIE5ld2VsbCdzIGZhdm9yaXRlIGNsYXNzIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMj8=",
            "answer": "U3B5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJEYXkgb2YgRGVmZWF0IiBzZXJpZXMgb2YgZ2FtZXMgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBkdXJpbmcgd2hpY2ggd2FyPw==",
            "answer": "V29ybGQgV2FyIElJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmViZWNjYSBDaGFtYmVycyBkb2VzIG5vdCBhcHBlYXIgaW4gYW55IFJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgZXhjZXB0IGZvciB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgUmVzaWRlbnQgRXZpbCBhbmQgdGhlIEdhbWVjdWJlIHJlbWFrZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGRpZCBub3QgYXBwZWFyIGluIHRoZSAyMDAyIExlZ28gR2FtZTogRHJvbWUgUmFjZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "V2FzcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGFyZSB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgY3JlYXRvcnMgb2YgUmFjaGV0ICYgQ2xhbms/",
            "answer": "SW5zb21uaWFjIEdhbWVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiQW50aWNoYW1iZXIiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIHdoaWNoIGhlcm8gaXMgYWJsZSB0byB3YWxscmlkZT8=",
            "answer": "THVjaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVybWFuZW50IGNvbXBhbmlvbnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSBiYXNlIGdhbWUgdmVyc2lvbiBvZiBGYWxsb3V0OiBOZXcgVmVnYXM/",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbWFzY290IG9mIFNFR0EgYmVmb3JlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciPw==",
            "answer": "QWxleCBLaWRk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBNLXJhdGVkIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZGV2ZWxvcGVkIGJ5IFNxdWFyZXNvZnQvU3F1YXJlIEVuaXg/",
            "answer": "UGFyYXNpdGUgRXZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaG9tZXdvcmxkIG9mIHRoZSBFbGl0ZXMgZnJvbSBIYWxvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FuZ2hlbGlvcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBFbGl0ZSBGb3VyIG1lbWJlcnMgZnJvbSB0aGUgNnRoIEdlbmVyYXRpb24gb2YgUG9rw6ltb24gd2FzIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIFRlYW0gRmxhcmU/",
            "answer": "TWFsdmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFEQU0gY29sbGVjdGVycyBpbiB0aGUgQmlvc2hvY2sgc2VyaWVzIGFyZSBrbm93biBhcyBMaXR0bGUgU2lzdGVycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2VucmUgaXMgdGhlIFRvdWhvdSBQcm9qZWN0IGFzc29jaWF0ZWQgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "U2hvb3QgJ2VtIHVwIChidWxsZXQtaGVsbCkgJiBGaWdodGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIDIgcGxheWVyIHJvbGVzIGluIFRyb3VibGUgaW4gVGVycm9yaXN0IFRvd24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIDY0IiwgY29sbGVjdGluZyAxMDAgY29pbnMgb24gYSBsZXZlbCB3aWxsIGdpdmUgeW91IGEgMS1VUC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlnIHRoZSBDYXQgaXMgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gIlNvbmljIEdlbmVyYXRpb25zIi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdmFyaWFudCBvZiB0aGUgTVA1IGlzIGRlcGljdGVkIGluIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlIDEuNj8=",
            "answer": "TVA1Tg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBldmVudHMgb2YgSGFsZi1MaWZlOiBPcHBvc2luZyBGb3JjZSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWdlIG9mIEFkcmlhbiBTaGVwaGFyZCwgdGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgZnJhbmNoaXNlICJIYWxvIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgVU5TQydzIG1haW4gb3Bwb3NpbmcgZmFjdGlvbiBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIENvdmVuYW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiAiVGhlIFN0YW5sZXkgUGFyYWJsZSI/",
            "answer": "U3RhbmxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIiBmb3IgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcywgd2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgaW5wdXQgaW4gdGhlIHNvdW5kIHRlc3Qgc2NyZWVuIHRvIGFjY2VzcyB0aGUgc2VjcmV0IGxldmVsIHNlbGVjdD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExlYWQgUHJvZ3JhbW1lcidzIGJpcnRoZGF5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY2xhc3NlcyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIYWxmLUxpZmUgZXhwYW5zaW9uIGNhbiB5b3UgZmluZCBHb3Jkb24ncyBwaWN0dXJlIGluIGFuICJFbXBsb3llZSBvZiB0aGUgTW9udGgiIHBpY3R1cmUgZnJhbWU/",
            "answer": "SGFsZi1MaWZlOiBPcHBvc2luZyBGb3JjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgem9tYmllcyBuZWVkIHRvIGJlIGtpbGxlZCB0byBnZXQgdGhlICJab21iaWUgR2Vub2NpZGVyIiBhY2hpZXZlbWVudCBpbiBEZWFkIFJpc2luZyAoMjAwNik/",
            "answer": "NTMsNTk0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCBoYXZpbmcgYSAiRnVuIFZhbHVlIiBzZXQgdG8gNTYtNTcgd2lsbCBwbGF5IHRoZSAiV3JvbmcgTnVtYmVyIFNvbmcgQ2FsbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgaW5mYW1vdXMgQ2l0YWRlbCBTdGF0aW9uIEEuSSBrbm93biBhcyBTLkguTy5ELkEuTiwgaW4gdGhlIFN5c3RlbSBTaG9jayBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "VGVycmkgQnJvc2l1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggT3ZlcndhdGNoIGNoYXJhY3RlciBzYXlzIHRoZSBsaW5lICJIZXJvZXMgbmV2ZXIgZGllISI/",
            "answer": "TWVyY3k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJDYWxsIE9mIER1dHk6IFpvbWJpZXMiIG1hcCAiT3JpZ2lucyIsIGhvdyBtYW55IG51bWJlcmVkIHBvd2VyIGdlbmVyYXRvcnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24gMiwgd2hvIGFyZSB0aGUgbWVtYmVycyBvZiBPZmYgVGhlIEhvb2s/",
            "answer": "UGVhcmwgJiBNYXJpbmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIHRvIHRoZSBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zIGZyYW5jaGlzZSBpbiBTdXBlciBTbWFzaCBCcm9zIE1lbGVlPw==",
            "answer": "U2hlaWs="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFsZi1MaWZlIGJ5IFZhbHZlIHVzZXMgdGhlIEdvbGRTcmMgZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmUsIHdoaWNoIGlzIGEgaGlnaGx5IG1vZGlmaWVkIHZlcnNpb24gb2Ygd2hhdCBlbmdpbmU/",
            "answer": "UXVha2UgRW5naW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UG9rw6ltb24gR28gaXMgYSBsb2NhdGlvbi1iYXNlZCBhdWdtZW50ZWQgcmVhbGl0eSBnYW1lIGRldmVsb3BlZCBhbmQgcHVibGlzaGVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbXBhbnk/",
            "answer": "TmlhbnRpYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlJvbGxlcmNvYXN0ZXIgVHljb29uIiB3YXMgcHJvZ3JhbW1lZCBtb3N0bHkgZW50aXJlbHkgaW4uLi4=",
            "answer": "eDg2IEFzc2VtYmx5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJIYWxmLUxpZmUiIHNlcmllcywgIkguRS5WIiBzdGFuZHMgZm9yICJIYXphcmRvdXMgRXZhc2l2ZW5lc3MgVmVzdCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHdoaWNoIGNsYXNzIGlzIGFibGUgdG8gZG91YmxlIGp1bXA/",
            "answer": "U2NvdXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUnVzdCwgaG93IG1hbnkgVGltZWQgRXhwbG9zaXZlIENoYXJnZXMgZG9lcyBpdCB0YWtlIHRvIGRlc3Ryb3kgYSBMYWRkZXIgSGF0Y2g/",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBDcmVhbSB0aGUgUmFiYml0J3MgbW9tIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "VmFuaWxsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbWFsbCBkb2VzICJEZWFkIFJpc2luZyIgdGFrZSBwbGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGFtZXR0ZSBQYXJrdmlldyBNYWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlkZGVuIGluIHRoZSBmaWxlcyBmb3IgIk1hcmlvIEthcnQgQXJjYWRlIEdQIiBpcyBhIHBpY3R1cmUgb2YgdGhlIEJlc2xhbiBzY2hvb2wgaG9zdGFnZSBjcmlzaXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsLCB3aGF0IGNvbG9yIGlzIHRoZSBNb3JhbGl0eSBDb3JlPw==",
            "answer": "UHVycGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdhbGxzIG9mIHRoZSBHb2xkZW5yb2QgQ2l0eSBHeW0gaW4gIlBva8OpbW9uIEdvbGQgYW5kIFNpbHZlciIgYXJlIGFycmFuZ2VkIGluIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBQb2vDqW1vbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2xlZmFpcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDAgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiQ3JpbXNvbiBTa2llcywiIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdHMnIHplcHBlbGluPw==",
            "answer": "UGFuZG9yYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBCbGFjayBPcHMgSUksIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBhbnRhZ29uaXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "UmF1bCBNZW7DqW5kZXog"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbGVtZW50IGRvZXMgdGhlIFppbm9ncmUgdXNlIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyPw==",
            "answer": "VGh1bmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSGVyb2VzIG9mIHRoZSBTdG9ybSwgdGhlIEN1cnNlZCBIb2xsb3cgbWFwIGdpbW1pY2sgcmVxdWlyZXMgcGxheWVycyB0byBraWxsIHRoZSB1bmRlYWQgdG8gY3Vyc2UgdGhlIGVuZW15IHRlYW0u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIGhvdyBtdWNoIGhlYWx0aCBkb2VzIFJvYWRob2cncyAiVGFrZSBhIEJyZWF0aGVyIiBhYmlsaXR5IHJlY292ZXI/",
            "answer": "MzAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJWZXJub24gQ2hlcnJ5IiBpbiAiUmVkIERlYWQgUmVkZW1wdGlvbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2FzZXkgTW9uZ2lsbG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgd29uZGVyIHdlYXBvbiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIj8=",
            "answer": "UjExNSBSZXNvbmF0b3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHZpbGxhaW4gb2YgdGhlIENyYXNoIEJhbmRpY29vdCBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "RHIuIE5lbyBDb3J0ZXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlN0cmFuZ2VyZWFsIiBpcyBhIGZpY3RpdGlvdXMgRWFydGgtbGlrZSB3b3JsZCBmb3Igd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBzZXJpZXM/",
            "answer": "QWNlIENvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIFdpdGNoZXIgMywgdGhlIFpvbHRhbiBDaGl2YXkgR3dlbnQgY2FyZCBjYW4gYmUgZm91bmQgdW5kZXIgdGhlIEhhbmdlZCBNYW4ncyBUcmVlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlhlbm9ibGFkZSBDaHJvbmljbGVzIDIiLCBXaGljaCBwYXJ0eSBtZW1iZXIgY2Fubm90IHVzZSBub3JtYWwgYmxhZGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG9yYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWFwIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "T2lscmln"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IHBsYXkgdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIFJQRyBhbmQgbmFwIGluIGEgcmVudGVkIGhvdGVsIHJvb20sIHlvdSB3aWxsIHdha2UgdXAgbmV4dCB0byB3aGF0IGZhbWlsaWFyIGxvb2tpbmcgY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "TGluaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGdlbnJlIHdlcmUgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UlRTIChSZWFsIFRpbWUgU3RyYXRlZ3kp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIDZ0aCBvZiBKdW5lIDIwMDYsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBpbmZhbW91cyBnbGl0Y2ggdGhhdCBvY2N1cnJlZCBpbiB0aGUgTU1PIFJ1bmVTY2FwZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZhbGFkb3IgTWFzc2FjcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlBhcGVyIE1hcmlvOiBUaGUgVGhvdXNhbmQgWWVhciBEb29yIiwgd2hhdCBpcyBIb29rdGFpbCdzIHdlYWtuZXNzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNvdW5kIG9mIENyaWNrZXRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYW5kIHB1Ymxpc2hlZCBHYW1lIERldiBUeWNvb24/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW5oZWFydCBHYW1lcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgc2VyaWVzLCBMZW9uIFMuIEtlbm5lZHkgaXMgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgU1RBUlMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RXhjbHVkaW5nIHRoZWlyIGluc3RydWN0b3IsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1lbWJlcnMgb2YgQ2xhc3MgVklJIGFyZSB0aGVyZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiTGVnZW5kIG9mIEhlcm9lczogVHJhaWxzIG9mIENvbGQgU3RlZWwiPw==",
            "answer": "OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNlY3JldCBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gaW4gdGhlIEhvdGxpbmUgTWlhbWkgc2VyaWVzPyA=",
            "answer": "NTAgQmxlc3Npbmdz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXRlbXMgZG9lcyB0aGUgTWFydGlhbiBTYXVjZXIgbWluaS1ib3NzIE5PVCBkcm9wPw==",
            "answer": "RHJpbGwgQ29udGFpbm1lbnQgVW5pdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMiIsIHRoZSAiQmlsbCdzIEhhdCIgaXMgYSByZWZlcmVuY2UgdG8gdGhlIGdhbWUgIkRvdGEgMiIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW5hIHdhcyBhZGRlZCBhcyBhIG5ldyBoZXJvIGZvciB0aGUgZ2FtZSBPdmVyd2F0Y2ggb24gSnVseSAxOXRoLCAyMDE2Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gU3Vuc2hpbmUiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmV0cm8gdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgZmlyc3Q/",
            "answer": "U3BhY2UgSW52YWRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbGV2ZWxzIGRvZXMgTk9UIGFwcGVhciBpbiB0aGUgY29uc29sZS9QQyB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiU29uaWMgR2VuZXJhdGlvbnMiPw==",
            "answer": "TXVzaHJvb20gSGlsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJIYWxmLUxpZmUiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgUlBHICJVbmRlcnRhbGUiLCB3aGljaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgZG8geW91IGZpcnN0IGVuY291bnRlciBhZnRlciBmYWxsaW5nIGRvd24gaW50byB0aGUgdW5kZXJncm91bmQ/",
            "answer": "Rmxvd2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2F0ZXItdHlwZSBQb2vDqW1vbiBzdGFydGVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSA0dGggZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBvZiB0aGUgc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGlwbHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgNC1hcm1lZCBDaGFvcyBXaXRjaCBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDE2IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkJhdHRsZWJvcm4iPw==",
            "answer": "T3JlbmRp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW9uc3RlciBpbiAiTW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgVHJpIiB3YXMgY2F1c2luZyBlYXJ0aHF1YWtlcyBpbiBNb2dhIFZpbGxhZ2U/",
            "answer": "Q2VhZGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIlN5c3RlbSBTaG9jayIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGVycmFyaWEsIHdoaWNoIGRlYnVmZiBkb2VzIHRoZSBhbmtoIGNoYXJtIG5vdCBwcm92aWRlIGltbXVuaXR5IHRvPw==",
            "answer": "VmVub20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEFuaW1hbCBDcm9zc2luZyBzZXJpZXMsIHdoaWNoIGZsb3dlciBpcyBlcnJvbmVvdXNseSBjYWxsZWQgdGhlICJKYWNvYidzIExhZGRlciI/",
            "answer": "TGlseSBvZiB0aGUgVmFsbGV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgd2FzIHRoZSBXb3JsZCBSZWNvcmQgU3BlZWQgUnVuIG9mIFZhbHZlIFNvZnR3YXJlJ3MgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSIgdGhhdCB3YXMgZG9uZSBpbiAyMDE0Lg==",
            "answer": "MjAgTWludXRlcywgNDEgU2Vjb25kcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gU3BsYXRvb24sIHRoZSBTcXVpZCBTaXN0ZXJzIGFyZSBuYW1lZCBUYWtvIGFuZCBZYWtpLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiRWxpbWluYXRvciIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIHRoZSBnYW1lICJMdWlnaSdzIE1hbnNpb24iLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IGxldHRlciB0byBub3QgYXBwZWFyIHdpdGggYSBwYWlyIG9mIGV5ZXMgaW4gaXQ/",
            "answer": "cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbG9jYXRpb24gZG9lcyBEYXJrIFN1biBHd3luZG9saW4gcmVzaWRlIGluICJEYXJrIFNvdWxzIj8=",
            "answer": "QW5vciBMb25kbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSAgRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTb2Z0d2FyZSBSYXRpbmdzIEJvYXJkIChFU1JCKSBpcyBvZnRlbiBhc3NvY2lhdGVkIHdpdGggTW9ydGFsIEtvbWJhdCBhbmQgd2hhdCBGTVYgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "TmlnaHQgVHJhcA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlVudGlsIERhd24iIEVtaWx5IGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlciB3aG8gY2FuIGJlIGtpbGxlZCBieSBhbm90aGVyIHBsYXlhYmxlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBkaXJlY3RseS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcmltYXJ5IGZlbWFsZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBvZiBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFZJSUk/",
            "answer": "SGVhcnRpbGx5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gY2FyZWVyIG1vZGUgb2YgIk5lZWQgZm9yIFNwZWVkOiBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZCAyIiwgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNhciB0aGUgcGxheWVyIGNhbiBkcml2ZSBpcyB0aGUgQk1XIE0zIEdUUi4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHZpbGxhaW4gb2YgS2lyYnkncyBSZXR1cm4gdG8gRHJlYW1sYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "TWFnb2xvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlJlc2lkZW50IEV2aWwgNyIgaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZpcnN0LXBlcnNvbiBSZXNpZGVudCBFdmlsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9ydGFsIDIsIHRoZSBpY29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdMYURPUyBpcyB0dXJuZWQgaW50bzo=",
            "answer": "QSBwb3RhdG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb3JkZXIgZG8geW91IG5lZWQgdG8gaGl0IHNvbWUgRGVrdSBTY3J1YnMgdG8gb3BlbiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgYm9zcyBkb29yIGluICJPY2FyaW5hIG9mIFRpbWUiPw==",
            "answer": "MiwgMywgMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIFRvYnkgRm94LCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbWV0aG9kIHRvIGNyZWF0aW5nIHRoZSBpbml0aWFsIHR1bmUgZm9yIE1lZ2Fsb3ZhbmlhPw==",
            "answer": "U2luZ2luZyBpbnRvIGEgTWljcm9waG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcGFjZSBzaG9vdGVyIGdhbWVzLCB3aGljaCBjYW1lIG91dCBmaXJzdD8=",
            "answer": "U3BhY2UgSW52YWRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBQb3RhdG8gU2FjayIgd2FzIGEgY29sbGVjdGlvbiBvZiBpbmRpZSBnYW1lcyByZWxlYXNlZCBvbiBTdGVhbSBpbiAyMDExIGFzIGEgcHJvbW90aW9uIGZvciB3aGljaCBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UG9ydGFsIDI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiAiR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBJViI/",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjksIDIwMDg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBHZW5lcmF0aW9uIElJSSBQb2tlbW9uIHdob3NlIG5hbWUgYmVnaW5zIHdpdGggdGhlIGxldHRlciBJPw==",
            "answer": "SWxsdW1pc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIllvISBOb2lkIDIsIiBUaGUgTm9pZCBjYW4gcGVyZm9ybSB3aGF0IHNwZWNpYWwgbW92ZT8=",
            "answer": "RGFi"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpbiB0aGUgIk1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIiBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgIkluc2VjdCBHbGFpdmUiIHdlYXBvbj8=",
            "answer": "TW9uc3RlciBIdW50ZXIgNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBub3QgYSBwbGF5YWJsZSByYWNlIGluICJGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhJVjogQSBSZWFsbSBSZWJvcm4iPw==",
            "answer": "SHVtZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3RhZ2Ugd2FzIHBsYW5uZWQgdG8gYmUgYSBwYXJ0IG9mICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2cgMiIsIGJ1dCB3YXMgc2NyYXBwZWQgZHVyaW5nIGRldmVsb3BtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "R2Vub2NpZGUgQ2l0eSBab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBUaGUgTWVkaWMgd2lsbCBiZSBjcmVkaXRlZCBmb3IgYW4gYXNzaXN0IGlmIGhlIGhlYWxzIGEgU3B5IHRoYXQgc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bGx5IHNhcHMgYSBidWlsZGluZy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgdGhlIFRvdWhvdSBQcm9qZWN0IHNlcmllcyBpczo=",
            "answer": "WlVO"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU2t5bGFuZGVycyBHaWFudHMsIHdoeSB3YXMgWmFwcycgV293IFBvdyBuYW1lZCAiRm9yIFJpbGV5IiA/",
            "answer": "QXMgYSB0cmlidXRlIHRvIGEgZmFuIHdobyBwYXNzZWQgYXdheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGJldGEgdmVyc2lvbiBvZiB0aGUgMTk4NiBnYW1lICJUaGUgTGVnZW5kIG9mIFplbGRhIiwgcGxheWVycyBoYXZlIHRoZSBjaG9pY2UgYmV0d2VlbiBhIHN3b3JkIGFuZCB3aGF0IG90aGVyIGl0ZW0/",
            "answer": "Qm9vbWVyYW5nIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSBjdXQgZW5lbXkgZnJvbSAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIDIiPw==",
            "answer": "SHlkcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VEYyOiBUaGUgSGVhdnkncyB2b2ljZSBhY3RvciwgR2FyeSBTY2h3YXJ0eiwgdm9pY2VzIHRoZSBEZW1vbWFuIGFzIHdlbGwg",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZhbGxvdXQgNCIgd2hpY2ggZmFjdGlvbiBpcyBub3QgcHJlc2VudCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVuY2xhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmFsdmUgQ29ycG9yYXRpb24gaXMgYW4gQW1lcmljYW4gdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZXIgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "QmVsbGV2dWUsIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGZyb20gdGhlIE1lZ2EgTWFuIHNlcmllcyBtYWRlIGEgc21hbGwgY2FtZW8gb24gVm9sdCBDYXRmaXNoJ3MgaW50cm9kdWN0aW9uIHNjZW5lIGluIENEIHZlcnNpb25zIG9mIE1lZ2EgTWFuIFgzPw==",
            "answer": "QXV0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWN0aXZpc2lvbiBjcmVhdGVkIEJhdHRsZWZpZWxkIDEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBBY2UgQ29tYmF0IDU6IFRoZSBVbnN1bmcgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "T3NlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R29sZGVuRXllIDAwNyBvbiB0aGUgTmludGVuZG8gNjQgd2FzIHBsYW5uZWQgdG8gYWxsb3cgeW91IHRvIHBsYXkgYXMgYWxsIHByZXZpb3VzIEJvbmQgYWN0b3JzLCB3aXRoIHRoZSBleGNlcHRpb24gb2Ygd2hvPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIExhemVuYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQ291bnRlci1TdHJpa2UgbWFwcyBpcyBhIGJvbWIgZGVmdXNlIHNjZW5hcmlvPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZGlneQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgZXZlciByZWxlYXNlZCB0aGF0IHJhbiBvbiB0aGUgU291cmNlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q291bnRlci1TdHJpa2U6IFNvdXJjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBnYW1lcyBpbiB0aGUgQW5ubyBzZXJpZXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgIkVjbyBCYWxhbmNlIiBnYW1lcGxheSBtZWNoYW5pYz8=",
            "answer": "QW5ubyAyMDcw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2NjdXBhdGlvbiBkaWQgSm9obiBUYW5uZXIsIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGZvciBEcml2ZXIgYW5kIERyaXZlciAyLCBoYWQgYmVmb3JlIHR1cm5pbmcgaW50byBhbiB1bmRlcmNvdmVyIGNvcD8=",
            "answer": "UmFjaW5nIERyaXZlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgb2JzaWRpYW4gYmxvY2tzIGFyZSByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBidWlsZCBhIG5ldGhlciBwb3J0YWwgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdmlydXMgdGhhdCBpbmZlY3RlZCBOZXcgWW9yayBpbiBUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgVGhlIERpdmlzaW9uPw==",
            "answer": "RG9sbGFyIEZsdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgSGFsZi1MaWZlLCB3aGljaCBlbmVteSBpcyBzaG93Y2FzZWQgYXMgdGhlIGZpbmFsIGJvc3M/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5paGlsYW50aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBtYWRlIHRoZSBKYXBhbmVzZSBSUEcgIkRyYWdvbiBRdWVzdCI/",
            "answer": "U3F1YXJlIEVuaXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRG90YSAyLCBXcmFpdGggS2luZyB3YXMgcHJldmlvdXNseSBrbm93biBhcy4uLg==",
            "answer": "U2tlbGV0b24gS2luZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ29vaywgU2VydmUsIERlbGljaW91cyEsIHdoaWNoIGZvb2QgaXMgTk9UIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "UGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZmxhZ3NoaXAgbW9uc3RlcnMgYXBwZWFyIGluIE1vbnN0ZXIgSHVudGVyIEdlcm5lcmF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgVGhlIFdvcmxkIEVuZHMgV2l0aCBZb3UsIGFsbCBvZiB0aGVzZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXJzIGFjdCBhcyBhIGdhbWUgcGFydG5lciB3aXRoIE5la3UgZm9yIGEgd2VlayBleGNlcHQ6",
            "answer": "Umh5bWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFNvbGlkIFNuYWtlIHVzZSB0byBoaWRlIGhpbXNlbGYgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "Q2FyZGJvYXJkIEJveA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3RhZ2VzIGlzIG5vdCBwbGF5YWJsZSBpbiAiU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gZm9yIFdpaSBVIj8=",
            "answer": "Rm91bnRhaW4gb2YgRHJlYW1z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIgbWFwIGludHJvZHVjZWQgdGhlICJTdGFmZnMgT2YgVGhlIEFuY2llbnRzIj8=",
            "answer": "T3JpZ2lucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IGNvbXBvc2VkIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBzb3VuZHRyYWNrIGZvciAiV2F0Y2ggRG9ncyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "SHVkc29uIE1vaGF3a2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBUZXJyYW4gdW5pdHMgZnJvbSB0aGUgUlRTIGdhbWUgU3RhcmNyYWZ0IHdhcyBmaXJzdCBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSBleHBhbnNpb24gQnJvb2QgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVkaWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBoZWFsaW5nIGl0ZW0gaW4gRGFyayBTb3Vscz8=",
            "answer": "RXN0dXMgRmxhc2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3R1ZGVudCBpbiBZYW5kZXJlIFNpbXVsYXRvciBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgYXNraW5nIGlycml0YXRpbmcgYW5kIHN0dXBpZCBxdWVzdGlvbnM/",
            "answer": "TWlkb3JpIEd1cmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlZmF1bHQgcGxheWVybW9kZWwgb2YgR2FycnkncyBNb2QgaXMgdGhpcyBIYWxmIExpZmUgMiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIu",
            "answer": "SXNhYWMgS2xlaW5lcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZXMgTm8gTWFu4oCZcyBTa3kgYW5kIE1pZ2h0eSBOby4gOSBoYXZlIGluIGNvbW1vbj8=",
            "answer": "Qm90aCB3ZXJlIGFubm91bmNlZCBpbiAyMDEzLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggZGlkIHRoZSBpbmRpZSBnYW1lICJDYXZlIFN0b3J5IiBjb3N0IHdoZW4gaXQgd2FzIGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDIwMDQ/",
            "answer": "JDAgVVNE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rZW1vbiwgdGhlIGFiaWxpdHkgV29uZGVyIEd1YXJkIGlzIGV4Y2x1c2l2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBQb2tlbW9uPyA=",
            "answer": "U2hlZGluamEg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBTY291dCBpbiAiVGVhbSBGb3J0cmVzcyAyIj8=",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTLlQuQS5MLksuRS5SLiIgc2VyaWVzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBpdGVtcyBjYW4ndCBiZSB1c2VkIHRvIGxvd2VyIHRoZSBwbGF5ZXIncyBhY2N1bXVsYXRlZCByYWRpYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "UmFkaW9wcm90ZWN0YW50"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHByZS1wcm9kdWN0aW9uIG9mICJTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiIsIE1hcmlvIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgd2FzIG1lYW50IHRvIHNob290IGJ1bGxldHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhcnMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIHRvIGNvbGxlY3QgaW4gU3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gNjQ/",
            "answer": "MTIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyIGluIHRoZSAiSGFsZi1MaWZlIiBmcmFuY2hpc2UgaXMgbmFtZWQgTW9yZ2FuIEZyZWVtYW4u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIiBlbnRlciBjbG9zZWQgYmV0YT8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgT3ZlcndhdGNoLCB3aGljaCBwbGF5YWJsZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMgaW5mYW1vdXMgZm9yIHNheWluZyAiSXQncyBoaWdoIG5vb24uIj8=",
            "answer": "TWNDcmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gQnJvcy4gd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDE5OTAu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIlN0YXJib3VuZCI/",
            "answer": "RmVuZXJveA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RGFuZ2Fucm9ucGEgMjogR29vZGJ5ZSBEZXNwYWlyIGZlYXR1cmVkIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgc3Vydml2aW5nIHN0dWRlbnRzIGZyb20gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbm9ybWFsIGVuZGluZ3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIENyeSBPZiBGZWFyJ3MgY2FtcGFpZ24gbW9kZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMgZ2FtZSBmZWF0dXJlZCB0aGUgY2FzdCBvZiAiVGhlIFdvcmxkIEVuZHMgV2l0aCBZb3UiPw==",
            "answer": "RHJlYW0gRHJvcCBEaXN0YW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb3BlcmF0aW9uIGluICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIGludHJvZHVjZWQgdGhlICJTa3lzY3JhcGVyIiBtYXA/",
            "answer": "UmVkIENyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIncyBuYW1lIGluICJCcmFpZCI/",
            "answer": "VGlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIiIHVwZGF0ZSB0byBpbmNsdWRlIGEgd2FyPw==",
            "answer": "U25pcGVyIHZzLiBTcHkgVXBkYXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBhbnRhZ29uaXN0IG9mIE1heCBQYXluZSAzICgyMDEyKT8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yIEJyYW5jbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBpcyBOT1QgcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgU2NpZW5jZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUgc2VyaWVzIGJ5IDVwYi4gYW5kIE5pdHJvcGx1cz8=",
            "answer": "T2NjdWx0aWM7IE5pbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggd2VhcG9uIHRoYXQgd2FzIGN1dCBmcm9tIHRoZSBnYW1lICJIYWxmIExpZmUgMiIgd2FzIGdvaW5nIHRvIHJlcGxhY2UgdGhlIGNyb3diYXI/",
            "answer": "SWNlIEF4ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGlzbmV5J3MgIlRvb250b3duIE9ubGluZSIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNwZWNpZXMgd2Fzbid0IGF2YWlsYWJsZSBhcyBhIFRvb24/",
            "answer": "Q293"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgQ2hhb3MgRW1lcmFsZHMgY2FuIHlvdSBjb2xsZWN0IGluIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBTb25pYyBUaGUgSGVkZ2Vob2c/",
            "answer": "U2l4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1hcCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBBcm1hIDMgbmFtZWQgIkFsdGlzIiBpcyBiYXNlZCBvZmYgb2Ygd2hhdCBHcmVlayBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "TGVtbm9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3MgZG9lcyBOT1QgcGxheSBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIFJ1aW5zIHNlZ21lbnRzIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE1IGdhbWUgIlVuZGVydGFsZSI/",
            "answer": "QW5vdGhlciBNZWRpdW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlBlcnNvbmEgNCIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNhbm9uaWNhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdD8=",
            "answer": "WXUgTmFydWthbWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZpbmFsIEZhbnRhc3kgVkkiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIChzdW1tb25lZCkgR2lsZ2FtZXNoJ3Mgd2Vha2VzdCBhdHRhY2s/",
            "answer": "RXhjYWxpcG9vcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgb2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgZ3JvdXAgZG9lcyBEb2N0b3IgTWF4aXMgd29yayBmb3I/",
            "answer": "R3JvdXAgOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsYXN0IGJvc3MgaW4gTmlnaHQgSW4gVGhlIFdvb2RzJyBEZW1vbnRvd2VyIG1pbmlnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsb29kIFRoaWVm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBLaXJieSBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGdvaW5nIHRvIGJlIG5hbWVkPw==",
            "answer": "UG9wb3Bv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGNhbiB5b3UgcmVjcnVpdCBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBTdWlrb2RlbiBpbiBhIHNpbmdsZSBwbGF5dGhyb3VnaD8=",
            "answer": "MTA3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgdGhlIEtvbmFtaSBDb2RlIG1ha2UgaXRzIGZpcnN0IGFwcGVhcmFuY2U/",
            "answer": "R3JhZGl1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBIYWxvIDM6IE9EU1Qgd2FzIHVudmVpbGVkIGluIDIwMDgsIGl0IGhhZCBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCB0aXRsZS4gV2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGdhbWUgZm9ybWFsbHkgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "SGFsbyAzOiBSZWNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzbm93eSBtb2Igd2FzIGFkZGVkIGluIE1pbmVjcmFmdCAxLjEwPw==",
            "answer": "UG9sYXIgYmVhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VEYyOiBXaGF0IGNvZGUgZG9lcyBTb2xkaWVyIHB1dCBpbnRvIHRoZSBkb29yIGtleXBhZCBpbiAiTWVldCB0aGUgU3B5Ij8=",
            "answer": "MTExMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsICJSaWNodG9mZW4iIGlzIGluIHBvc3Nlc3Npb24gb2YgdHdvIGZpbGxlZCBibG9vZCB2aWFscyBiZWxvbmdpbmcgdG8gd2hvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsIERlTHVjYSBhbmQgRmlubiBPJ0xlYXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFBsYXlTdGF0aW9uIGdhbWUgdG8gcmVxdWlyZSB0aGUgdXNlIG9mIHRoZSBEdWFsU2hvY2sgY29udHJvbGxlcj8=",
            "answer": "QXBlIEVzY2FwZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIGNpdHkgZG9lcyB0aGUgbWFwICJDbHViaG91c2UiIGluICJUb20gQ2xhbmN5J3MgUmFpbmJvdyBTaXggU2llZ2UiIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "SGFubm92ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBzdHJlYW1pbmcgcGxhdGZvcm0gVHdpdGNoVFYgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEFjZSBBdHRvcm5leSB0cmlsb2d5IHdhcyBzdXBwb3NlIHRvIGVuZCB3aXRoICJQaG9lbml4IFdyaWdodDogQWNlIEF0dG9ybmV5IOKIkiBUcmlhbHMgYW5kIFRyaWJ1bGF0aW9ucyIgYXMgaXRzIGZpbmFsIGdhbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21wYW55IGRldmVsb3BzIHRoZSBSb2NrIEJhbmQgc2VyaWVzIG9mIHJoeXRobSBnYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "SGFybW9uaXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUG9rw6ltb24gY2Fubm90IGxlYXJuIFN1cmY/",
            "answer": "QXJib2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxheWFibGUgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgaW4gU3VwZXIgU21hc2ggQnJvcy4gZm9yIE5pbnRlbmRvIDNEUyBhbmQgV2lpIFU/",
            "answer": "NTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGNyZWRpdGVkIHdpdGggaGF2aW5nIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBFYXN0ZXIgRWdnPw==",
            "answer": "V2FycmVuIFJvYmluZXR0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBWLCB3aGF0IHdhcyBNaWNoYWVsIERlIFNhbnRhJ3MgZm9ybWVyIHN1cm5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VG93bmxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21wYW55IGNyZWF0ZWQgYW5kIGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "QmxpenphcmQgRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGluZGllIGFkdmVudHVyZSBnYW1lICJOaWdodCBpbiB0aGUgV29vZHMiPw==",
            "answer": "QWxlYyBIb2xvd2th"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIkx1aWdpJ3MgTWFuc2lvbiAzIiByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAzMXN0LCAyMDE5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgbmFtZSBvZiBGaW5hbCBGYW50YXN5IFhWPw==",
            "answer": "RmluYWwgRmFudGFzeSBWZXJzdXMgWElJSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMDIgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMiLCBob3cgbWFueSBLZXlibGFkZXMgYXJlIHVzYWJsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgQ3Jhc2ggQmFuZGljb290Pw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGllIFdvbWJhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFN0YXIgV2FyczogQmF0dGxlZnJvbnQgSUkgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAzMSwgMjAwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R29yZG9uIEZyZWVtYW4gaXMgc2FpZCB0byBoYXZlIGJ1cm50IGFuZCBkZXN0cm95ZWQgd2hhdCBmb29kIGluIHRoZSBicmVhayByb29tIG1pY3Jvd2F2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Fzc2Vyb2xl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSB3aGVyZSBkb2VzIHRoZSBOaW50ZW5kbyB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNoYXJhY3RlciBNYXJpbyBkZXJpdmUgaGlzIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VGhlIGxhbmRsb3JkIG9mIHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtoYWppaXQgYXJlIGEgcmFjZSBvZiBjYXQtbGlrZSBjcmVhdHVyZXMgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBlcGljIHNlcmllcyBvZiByb2xlLXBsYXlpbmcgZ2FtZXMsIHNldCBhY3Jvc3MgdGhlIGxhbmQgb2YgVGFtcmllbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVsZGVyIFNjcm9sbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEtpbmdkb20gSGVhcnRzIHNlcmllcywgd2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGFuIG9wdGlvbmFsIGJvc3MgeW91IGNhbiBmaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "TWFzdGVyIFllbiBTaWQ="
        }
    ],
    "U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIHRoZSByYXJpc3QgZm9ybSBvZiBjb2xvciBibGluZG5lc3M/",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIERvcHBsZXIgZWZmZWN0IGFwcGxpZXMgdG8gbGlnaHQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sb3VyIG9mIHVub3hpZGl6ZWQgYmxvb2Q/",
            "answer": "UmVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBhbmltYWwgY3VycmVudGx5IG9uIEVhcnRoPw==",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZSBXaGFsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGNoZW1pY2FsIG5hbWUgb2YgSDJPPw==",
            "answer": "RGloeWRyb2dlbiBNb25veGlkZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgb2JqZWN0cyBhcmUgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byBvbmUgbW9sZT8=",
            "answer": "Ni4wMjIgeCAxMF4yMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBsZXR0ZXIgJ1MnIHN0YW5kIGZvciBpbiAnTkFTQSc/",
            "answer": "U3BhY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIGdpdmVuIHRvIGFsbCBiYWJ5IG1hcnN1cGlhbHM/",
            "answer": "Sm9leQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGh1bWVydXMsIHBhaXJlZCByYWRpdXMsIGFuZCB1bG5hIGNvbWUgdG9nZXRoZXIgdG8gZm9ybSB3aGF0IGpvaW50Pw==",
            "answer": "RWxib3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxhbmV0cyBhcmUgaW4gb3VyIFNvbGFyIFN5c3RlbT8=",
            "answer": "RWlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb21tb24gbmFtZSBpcyBnaXZlbiB0byB0aGUgbWVkaWFsIGNvbmRpdGlvbiwgdGliaWFsIHN0cmVzcyBzeW5kcm9tZSAoTVRTUyk/",
            "answer": "U2hpbiBTcGxpbnRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ2FzIGZvcm1zIGFib3V0IDc4JSBvZiB0aGUgRWFydGjigJlzIGF0bW9zcGhlcmU/",
            "answer": "Tml0cm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3QgbWludXRlLCBob3cgbG9uZyBkb2VzIGl0IHRha2UgZm9yIGxpZ2h0IHRvIHRyYXZlbCBmcm9tIHRoZSBTdW4gdG8gdGhlIEVhcnRoPw==",
            "answer": "OCBNaW51dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9sZWN1bGFyIGZvcm11bGEgb2YgR2x1Y29zZT8=",
            "answer": "QzZIMTJPNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb3JnYW5pYyBjb21wb3VuZCBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGFuIGFsY29ob2wgaWYgaXQgaGFzIHdoYXQgZnVuY3Rpb25hbCBncm91cD8=",
            "answer": "SHlkcm94eWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGxhbmV0cyBtYWtlIHVwIG91ciBTb2xhciBTeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgb2ZmaWNpYWxseSByZWNvZ25pemVkIGR3YXJmIHBsYW5ldHMgaW4gdGhlIHNvbGFyIHN5c3RlbSBhcmUgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgUG9seW5lc2lhbiBkZWl0aWVzPw==",
            "answer": "Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VHlwZSAxIGRpYWJldGVzIGlzIGEgcmVzdWx0IG9mIHRoZSBsaXZlciB3b3JraW5nIGltcHJvcGVybHku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SXQgd2FzIG9uY2UgYmVsaWV2ZWQgdGhhdCBpbmplY3Rpbmcgc2hhcmsgY2FydGlsYWdlIGludG8gcGVvcGxlIHdvdWxkIHByZXZlbnQgdGhlbSBmcm9tIGNvbnRyYWN0aW5nIGNhbmNlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWx6aGVpbWVyJ3MgZGlzZWFzZSBwcmltYXJpbHkgYWZmZWN0cyB3aGljaCBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBodW1hbiBib2R5Pw==",
            "answer": "QnJhaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSByZWQgZm94Pw==",
            "answer": "VnVscGVzIFZ1bHBlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIEROQSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "RGVveHlyaWJvbnVjbGVpYyBBY2lk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW5hdG9teSBjb25zaWRlcnMgdGhlIGZvcm1zIG9mIG1hY3Jvc2NvcGljIHN0cnVjdHVyZXMgc3VjaCBhcyBvcmdhbnMgYW5kIG9yZ2FuIHN5c3RlbXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2FsdCBpcyAxMDAlIGNvbXBvc2VkIG9mIFNvZGl1bS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlRoZSBCaWcgQmFuZyBUaGVvcnkiIHdhcyBmaXJzdCB0aGVvcml6ZWQgYnkgYSBwcmllc3Qgb2Ygd2hhdCByZWxpZ2lvdXMgaWRlb2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Q2F0aG9saWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGh1bWFuIGhlYXJ0IGhhcyBob3cgbWFueSBjaGFtYmVycz8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW9vbiBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBzYXRlbGxpdGUgaW4gb3VyIHNvbGFyIHN5c3RlbSB0byBwb3NzZXNzIGEgZGVuc2UgYXRtb3NwaGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGl0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGh1bWFuIHJpZ2h0IGx1bmcgaGFzIGhvdyBtYW55IGxvYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGFzdGVyb2lkIGJlbHQgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBiZXR3ZWVuIHdoaWNoIHR3byBwbGFuZXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWFycyBhbmQgSnVwaXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1lZGljYWwgdGVybSBmb3IgdGhlIGJlbGx5IGJ1dHRvbiBpcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "VW1iaWxpY3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvcmUgb2YgdGhlIFN1biBjYW4gcmVhY2ggd2hpY2ggdGVtcGVyYXR1cmU/",
            "answer": "MjfCsCBNaWxsaW9uIEYgKDE1wrAgTWlsbGlvbiBDKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgYXRvbWljIHdlaWdodCBvZiBhIFBsdXRvbml1bSBudWNsZXVzPw==",
            "answer": "MjQ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbGVtZW50IG9uIHRoZSBwZXJpb2RpYyB0YWJsZSBoYXMgOTIgZWxlY3Ryb25zPw==",
            "answer": "VXJhbml1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWJvdXQgaG93IG9sZCBpcyBFYXJ0aD8=",
            "answer": "NC41IEJpbGxpb24gWWVhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBnZW5ldGljIGRpc2Vhc2UgaXMgY2F1c2VkIGJ5IGhhdmluZyBhbiBleHRyYSBZIGNocm9tb3NvbWUgKFhZWSk/",
            "answer": "SmFjb2IncyBTeW5kcm9tZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2FtZSBpbiBDZWxzaXVzIGFuZCBGYWhyZW5oZWl0Pw==",
            "answer": "LTQw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIExBU0VSIHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "answer": "TGlnaHQgYW1wbGlmaWNhdGlvbiBieSBzdGltdWxhdGVkIGVtaXNzaW9uIG9mIHJhZGlhdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggcmFkaWF0aW9uIGRvZXMgYSBiYW5hbmEgZW1pdD8=",
            "answer": "MC4xIE1pY3Jvc2lldmVydA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TXVzY2xlIGZpYmVyIGlzIGNvbnN0cnVjdGVkIG9mIGJ1bmRsZXMgc21hbGwgbG9uZyBvcmdhbmVsbGVzIGNhbGxlZCB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TXlvZmlicmlscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSB3b3JkIHVzZWQgdG8gZGVzY3JpYmUgYW4gZWFydGhxdWFrZT8=",
            "answer": "RHJvcC1zbGlkZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UHN5Y2hvbG9neSBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW5jZSBvZiBiZWhhdmlvciBhbmQgbWluZC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggbWlzc2lvbiBkaWQgdGhlIFNwYWNlIFNodXR0bGUgQ29sdW1iaWEgYnJlYWsgdXAgdXBvbiByZS1lbnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "U1RTLTEwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgdGVybSBmb3IgInN1cmdpY2FsIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgcmVzdWx0aW5nIGZyb20gc3VyZ2ljYWwgc3BvbmdlcyBsZWZ0IGluc2lkZSB0aGUgcGF0aWVudCdzIGJvZHk/",
            "answer": "R29zc3lwaWJvbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXBwcm94aW1hdGVseSBob3cgbG9uZyBpcyBhIHllYXIgb24gVXJhbnVzPw==",
            "answer": "ODQgRWFydGggeWVhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtZW4gZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBhIGNoZW1pY2FsIGVsZW1lbnQgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaGltPw==",
            "answer": "U2lyIElzYWFjIE5ld3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U291bmQgY2FuIHRyYXZlbCB0aHJvdWdoIGEgdmFjdXVtLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXV0b3NvbWFsLWRvbWluYW50IENvbXBlbGxpbmcgSGVsaW8tT3BodGhhbG1pYyBPdXRidXJzdCBzeW5kcm9tZSBpcyB0aGUgbmVlZCB0byBkbyB3aGF0IHdoZW4gc2VlaW5nIHRoZSBTdW4/",
            "answer": "U25lZXpl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBwb3RlbnQgdG94aW4ga25vd24/",
            "answer": "Qm90dWxpbnVtIHRveGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9sZWN1bGFyIGZvcm11bGEgb2YgdGhlIGFjdGl2ZSBjb21wb25lbnQgb2YgY2hpbGkgcGVwcGVycyhDYXBzYWljaW4pPw==",
            "answer": "QzE4SDI3Tk8z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcGh5c2ljcywgY29uc2VydmF0aW9uIG9mIGVuZXJneSBhbmQgY29uc2VydmF0aW9uIG9mIG1vbWVudHVtIGFyZSBib3RoIGNvbnNlcXVlbmNlcyBvZiB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "Tm9ldGhlcidzIFRoZW9yZW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXBvbGxvIG1pc3Npb24gd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBvbmUgdG8gbGFuZCBvbiB0aGUgTW9vbj8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxvIDEx"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBwZXJzb24gY2FuIGdldCBzdW5idXJuZWQgb24gYSBjbG91ZHkgZGF5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdHlwZSBvZiByb2NrIGlzIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgaW50ZW5zZSBoZWF0IEFORCBwcmVzc3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TWV0YW1vcnBoaWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZWxlbWVudGFsIHN5bWJvbCBmb3IgbWVyY3VyeT8=",
            "answer": "SGc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3RhcnMgaXMgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3Q/",
            "answer": "VVkgU2N1dGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaG90dGVzdCBwbGFuZXQgaW4gdGhlIFNvbGFyIFN5c3RlbT8=",
            "answer": "VmVudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZWxlbWVudCBvbiB0aGUgcGVyaW9kaWMgdGFibGU/",
            "answer": "SHlkcm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBpcyBpdCBiaW9sb2dpY2FsbHkgaW1wb3NzaWJsZSBmb3IgYSBjZW50aXBlZGUgdG8gaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtaW5lcmFsIGhhcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IG51bWJlciBvbiB0aGUgTW9ocyBzY2FsZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFsYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hlbWljYWwgZWxlbWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGxvd2VzdCBib2lsaW5nIHBvaW50Pw==",
            "answer": "SGVsaXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBibG9vZCB2ZXNzZWxzIGNhcnJpZXMgZGVveHlnZW5hdGVkIGJsb29kPw==",
            "answer": "UHVsbW9uYXJ5IEFydGVyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hlbWljYWwgY29tcG91bmRzIGlzIE5PVCBmb3VuZCBpbiBnYXN0cmljIGFjaWQ/",
            "answer": "U3VsZnVyaWMgYWNpZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9saWMgYWNpZCBpcyB0aGUgc3ludGhldGljIGZvcm0gb2Ygd2hpY2ggdml0YW1pbj8=",
            "answer": "Vml0YW1pbiBC"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gYXRvbSBjb250YWlucyBhIG51Y2xldXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2VudHJpcGVkYWwgZm9yY2UgaXMgYW4gYXBwYXJlbnQgZm9yY2UgdGhhdCBhY3RzIG91dHdhcmQgb24gYSBib2R5IG1vdmluZyBhcm91bmQgYSBjZW50ZXIsIGFyaXNpbmcgZnJvbSB0aGUgYm9keSdzIGluZXJ0aWEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSB5ZWxsb3cgZGlhbW9uZCBvbiB0aGUgTkZQQSA3MDQgZmlyZSBkaWFtb25kIHJlcHJlc2VudD8=",
            "answer": "UmVhY3Rpdml0eQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgYWJ1bmRhbnQgZWxlbWVudCBpbiB0aGUgdW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "SHlkcm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2hlbWlzdHJ5LCBob3cgbWFueSBpc29tZXJzIGRvZXMgQnV0YW5vbCAoQzRIOU9IKSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qm90YW5pY2FsbHkgc3BlYWtpbmcsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGZydWl0cyBpcyBOT1QgYSBiZXJyeT8=",
            "answer": "U3RyYXdiZXJyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoZW1pY2FsIGVsZW1lbnQgTGl0aGl1bSBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgY291bnRyeSBvZiBMaXRodWFuaWEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSB0ZXJtICJpc29sYXRpb24iIHJlZmVyIHRvIGluIG1pY3JvYmlvbG9neT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIHNlcGFyYXRpb24gb2YgYSBzdHJhaW4gZnJvbSBhIG5hdHVyYWwsIG1peGVkIHBvcHVsYXRpb24gb2YgbGl2aW5nIG1pY3JvYmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3VnYXIgY29udGFpbnMgZmF0Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gYXZlcmFnZSBodW1hbiBjYW4gZ28gdHdvIHdlZWtzIHdpdGhvdXQgd2F0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdW5pdCBvZiBlbGVjdHJpY2FsIGluZHVjdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "SGVucnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHZhbHVlIG9mIG9uZSBDYWxvcmllIGlzIGRpZmZlcmVudCB0aGFuIHRoZSB2YWx1ZSBvZiBvbmUgY2Fsb3JpZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgaHVtYW4gbmFpbHMgbWFkZSBvZj8=",
            "answer": "S2VyYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGxhbmV0IGRpZCB0aGUgIlZpa2luZyAxIiBzcGFjZWNyYWZ0IHNlbmQgc3VyZmFjZSBpbWFnZXMgb2YsIHN0YXJ0aW5nIGluIDE5NzY/",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gTG93bGFuZCBHb3JpbGxhIGlzIHNjaWVudGlmaWNhbGx5IGtub3cgYXM/",
            "answer": "R29yaWxsYSBHb3JpbGxhIEdvcmlsbGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3BlZWQgb2YgbGlnaHQgaW4gYSB2YWN1dW0/",
            "answer": "Mjk5LDc5Miw0NTggbS9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIHBlcmlvZGljIHRhYmxlIG9mIGVsZW1lbnRzLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBzeW1ib2wgZm9yIFRpbj8=",
            "answer": "U24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc3RhciBsb2NhdGVkIGNsb3Nlc3QgdG8gdGhlIE5vcnRoIENlbGVzdGlhbCBQb2xlPw==",
            "answer": "UG9sYXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlRhY2h5Y2FyZGlhIiBvciAiVGFjaHlhcnJoeXRobWlhIiByZWZlcnMgdG8gYSByZXN0aW5nIGhlYXJ0LXJhdGUgbmVhciBvciBvdmVyIDEwMCBCUE0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHdvcmQgInNjaWVuY2UiIHN0ZW1zIGZyb20gdGhlIHdvcmQgInNjaXJlIiBtZWFuaW5nIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "VG8ga25vdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVpb25pemVkIHdhdGVyIGlzIHdhdGVyIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByZW1vdmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hvaWNlcyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBwaGFzZXMgb2YgbWl0b3Npcz8=",
            "answer": "RGlwbG9waGFzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlIGF1ZGl0b3J5IGlsbHVzaW9uIG9mIGEgbm90ZSB0aGF0IHNlZW1zIHRvIGJlIHJpc2luZyBpbmZpbml0ZWx5Pw==",
            "answer": "U2hlcGFyZCBUb25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBwYXNzaXZlIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgY29tcG9uZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "VHJhbnNpc3Rvcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIG1ham9yIG11c2NsZSBvZiB0aGUgYmFjaz8=",
            "answer": "VHJhcGV6aXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhcmUgY2VsbHMgb2YgdGhlIGFkYXB0aXZlIGltbXVuZSBzeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "Q3l0b3RveGljIFQgY2VsbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZXMgdGhlIHNvdW5kIG9mIGEgaGVhcnRiZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2xvc3VyZSBvZiB0aGUgaGVhcnQgdmFsdmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCBpcyB0aGUgdW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "MTMuOCBCaWxsaW9uIFllYXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vb25zLCBNaXJhbmRhLCBBcmllbCwgVW1icmllbCwgVGl0YW5pYSBhbmQgT2Jlcm9uIG9yYml0IHdoaWNoIHBsYW5ldD8=",
            "answer": "VXJhbnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYWVyb25hdXRpY3MsIGZsYXBzIGFuZCBzbGF0cyBhcmUgdXNlZCB0byBjb250cm9sIHdoYXQgb24gYW4gYWlyY3JhZnQ/",
            "answer": "TGlmdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBlbGVtZW50LCB3aGVuIG92ZXJjb21lIHdpdGggZXh0cmVtZSBoZWF0IGFuZCBwcmVzc3VyZSwgY3JlYXRlcyBkaWFtb25kcy4=",
            "answer": "Q2FyYm9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaHVtYW4gZ2VuZXRpYyBoYXBsb2dyb3VwIG5hbWVzIGFyZSBzaGFyZWQgYmV0d2VlbiBZLWNocm9tb3NvbWUgYW5kIG1pdG9jaG9uZHJpYWwgRE5BIGhhcGxvZ3JvdXBzIEVYQ0VQVDo=",
            "answer": "SGFwbG9ncm91cCBV"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEF4aW9tIG9mIFByZXZlbnRpdmUgTWVkaWNpbmUgc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgcGVvcGxlIHdpdGggX19fIHJpc2sgZm9yIGEgZGlzZWFzZSBzaG91bGQgYmUgc2NyZWVuZWQgYW5kIHdlIHNob3VsZCB0cmVhdCBfX18gb2YgdGhvc2UgcGVvcGxlLg==",
            "answer": "bG93LCBhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2hyaW1wIGNhbiBzd2ltIGJhY2t3YXJkcy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHN5Y2hvbG9naWNhbCB0ZXJtIHJlZmVycyB0byB0aGUgc3RyZXNzIG9mIGhvbGRpbmcgY29udHJhc3RpbmcgYmVsaWVmcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29nbml0aXZlIERpc3NvbmFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb2x5bWVyIGlzIHVzZWQgdG8gbWFrZSBDRHMsIHNhZmV0eSBnb2dnbGVzIGFuZCByaW90IHNoaWVsZHM/",
            "answer": "UG9seWNhcmJvbmF0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1lZGljYWwgY29uZGl0aW9uIG9zdGVvcG9yb3NpcyBhZmZlY3RzIHdoaWNoIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIGJvZHk/",
            "answer": "Qm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGlzIHNjaWVudGlmaWMgdGVybSBmb3IgIkJyYWluIEZyZWV6ZSI/",
            "answer": "U3BoZW5vcGFsYXRpbmUgR2FuZ2xpb25ldXJhbGdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TXlvcGlhIGlzIHRoZSBzY2llbnRpZmljIHRlcm0gZm9yIHdoaWNoIGNvbmRpdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2hvcnRzaWdodGVkbmVzcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzdGFnZSBvZiBkZXZlbG9wbWVudCBkbyB0aGUgbWFqb3JpdHkgb2YgZXVrYXJ5b3RpYyBjZWxscyByZW1haW4gaW4gZm9yIG1vc3Qgb2YgdGhlaXIgbGlmZT8=",
            "answer": "SW50ZXJwaGFzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXQgd2hhdCB0ZW1wZXJhdHVyZSBkb2VzIHdhdGVyIGJvaWw/",
            "answer": "MjEywrBG"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gQXN0cm9ub21pY2FsIFVuaXQgaXMgdGhlIGRpc3RhbmNlIGJldHdlZW4gRWFydGggYW5kIHRoZSBNb29uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBudWNsZW90aWRlIHBhaXJzIHdpdGggZ3VhbmluZT8=",
            "answer": "Q3l0b3NpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVybmluZyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBtZXRhbHMgd2lsbCBwcm9kdWNlIGEgYnJpZ2h0IHdoaXRlIGZsYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TWFnbmVzaXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgdGFrZXMgcGFydCBpbiBTY2hyw7ZkaW5nZXIncyBtb3N0IGZhbW91cyB0aG91Z2h0IGV4cGVyaW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "Q2F0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UG5ldW1vbm91bHRyYW1pY3Jvc2NvcGljc2lsaWNvdm9sY2Fub2Nvbmlvc2lzIGlzIGEgc3lub255bSBmb3IgdGhlIGRpc2Vhc2Uga25vd24gYXMgc2lsaWNvc2lzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG93biBTeW5kcm9tZSBpcyB1c3VhbGx5IGNhdXNlZCBieSBhbiBleHRyYSBjb3B5IG9mIHdoaWNoIGNocm9tb3NvbWU/",
            "answer": "MjE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2F0ZXIgYWx3YXlzIGJvaWxzIGF0IDEwMMKwQywgMjEywrBGLCAzNzMuMTVLLCBubyBtYXR0ZXIgd2hlcmUgeW91IGFyZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbm9ibGUgZ2FzIGhhcyB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IGF0b21pYyBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "SGVsaXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyAiU3Rlbm9tYSI/",
            "answer": "QSBnZW51cyBvZiBtb3Rocw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBsaWVzIGF0IHRoZSBjZW50ZXIgb2Ygb3VyIGdhbGF4eT8=",
            "answer": "QSBibGFjayBob2xl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBiZWxvbmdzIGluIGNsYXNzIENob25kcmljaHRoeWVzPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlYXQgd2hpdGUgc2hhcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIHNtYWxsZXN0IGJsb29kIHZlc3NlbHMgaW4gdGhlIGh1bWFuIGJvZHk/",
            "answer": "Q2FwaWxsYXJpZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGNsYXNzaWNhbCBjb25kaXRpb25pbmc/",
            "answer": "UGF2bG92J3MgZG9nIGV4cGVyaW1lbnRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1hbW1hbCBzdWNjZXNzZnVsbHkgY2xvbmVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxvbmcgd2l0aCBPeHlnZW4sIHdoaWNoIGVsZW1lbnQgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciB0aGUgc2t5IGFwcGVhcmluZyBibHVlPw==",
            "answer": "Tml0cm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlICJHeW1waWUgU3RpbmdlciIgaXMgdGhlIGRlYWRsaWVzdCBwbGFudCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcG93ZXJob3VzZSBvZiB0aGUgY2VsbD8=",
            "answer": "TWl0b2Nob25kcmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3RlZWwgaXMgYW4gYWxsb3kgb2YgSXJvbiBhbmQgQ2FyYm9uLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJUaWJpYSIgaXMgZm91bmQgaW4gd2hpY2ggcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgYm9keT8=",
            "answer": "TGVn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcHJpbWFyeSBhZGRpY3RpdmUgc3Vic3RhbmNlIGZvdW5kIGluIHRvYmFjY28/",
            "answer": "Tmljb3RpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2hlbWljYWwgZm9ybXVsYSBmb3IgYW1tb25pYT8=",
            "answer": "Tkgz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSByZWFsIGVsZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "Vml0cmFpbml1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0ZXJtIGlzIGJlc3QgYXNzb2NpYXRlZCB3aXRoIFNpZ211bmQgRnJldWQ/",
            "answer": "UHN5Y2hvYW5hbHlzaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9sZWN1bGFyIGZvcm11bGEgb2YgT3pvbmU/",
            "answer": "TzM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyByYWRpYXRpb24gbWVhc3VyZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "R3JheSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdW5pdCBvZiBlbGVjdHJpY2FsIHJlc2lzdGFuY2U/",
            "answer": "T2ht"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN1biBjb25zaXN0cyBvZiBtb3N0bHkgd2hpY2ggdHdvIGVsZW1lbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "SHlkcm9nZW4gJiBIZWxpdW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgaXMgYSBsaWdodC15ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "OS40NjEgVHJpbGxpb24gS2lsb21ldHJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBicmFpbiB0YWtlcyBpdHMgbmFtZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBHcmVlayBmb3Igc2VhaG9yc2U/",
            "answer": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGFsZi1saWZlIG9mIFVyYW5pdW0tMjM1Pw==",
            "answer": "NzAzLDgwMCwwMDAgeWVhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gaHVtYW4gYmlvbG9neSwgYSBjaXJjYWRpdW0gcmh5dGhtIHJlbGF0ZXMgdG8gYSBwZXJpb2Qgb2Ygcm91Z2hseSBob3cgbWFueSBob3Vycz8=",
            "answer": "MjQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb3JnYW5pc20gZGVzY3JpYmVkIGFzICJoZWxpb3Ryb3BpYyIgaGFzIGEgdGVuZGFuY3kgdG8gbW92ZSB0b3dhcmRzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIHRoaW5ncz8=",
            "answer": "TGlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29sb3IgY2Fubm90IGJlIHByb2R1Y2VkIGluIFJvc2VzLCBldmVuIHRocm91Z2ggZ2VuZXRpYyBhbHRlcmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Qmx1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHJ5IGljZSBpcyB0aGUgc29saWQgZm9ybSBvZiB3aGF0IHN1YnN0YW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FyYm9uIGRpb3hpZGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIeXBlcm5hdHJlbWlhPw==",
            "answer": "SW5jcmVhc2UgaW4gYmxvb2Qgc29kaXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgRWxlbWVudHMgaXMgYSBtZXRhbGxvaWQ/",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdHlwZXMgb2YgcXVhcmtzIGFyZSB0aGVyZSBpbiB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgbW9kZWwgb2YgcGh5c2ljcz8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2FubnltZWRlIGlzIHRoZSBsYXJnZXN0IG1vb24gb2Ygd2hpY2ggcGxhbmV0Pw==",
            "answer": "SnVwaXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXUgb24gdGhlIFBlcmlvZGljIFRhYmxlIHJlZmVycyB0byB3aGljaCBlbGVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgbWV0YWwgZWxlbWVudHMgYXJlIGxpcXVpZHMgYXQgb3IgbmVhciByb29tIHRlbXBlcmF0dXJlIEVYQ0VQVDo=",
            "answer": "QmVyeWxsaXVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBrbmVlIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "UGF0ZWxsYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgc3RydWN0dXJlIG9mIGEgdHlwaWNhbCBuZXVyb24/",
            "answer": "SXNsZXRzIG9mIExhbmdlcmhhbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgYm9keSBkb2VzIGdsYXVjb21hIGFmZmVjdD8=",
            "answer": "RXllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2NpZW50aXN0cyBhY2NpZGVudGFsbHkga2lsbGVkIHRoZSBvbmNlIGtub3duIHdvcmxkJ3Mgb2xkZXN0IGxpdmluZyBjcmVhdHVyZSwgYSBtb2xsdXNjLCBrbm93biB0byBiZSBhZ2VkIGFzIDUwNyB5ZWFycyBvbGQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNjaWVudGlzdHMgY29uZHVjdGVkIHRoZSBHb2xkIEZvaWwgRXhwZXJpbWVudCB3aGljaCBjb25jbHVkZWQgdGhhdCBhdG9tcyBhcmUgbW9zdGx5IG1hZGUgb2YgZW1wdHkgc3BhY2U/",
            "answer": "RXJuZXN0IFJ1dGhlcmZvcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIG1hZGUgdGhlIGRpc2NvdmVyeSBvZiBYLXJheXM/",
            "answer": "V2lsaGVsbSBDb25yYWQgUsO2bnRnZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW4gZXhvdGhlcm1pYyByZWFjdGlvbiBpcyBhIGNoZW1pY2FsIHJlYWN0aW9uIHRoYXQgcmVsZWFzZXMgZW5lcmd5IGJ5IHJhZGlhdGluZyBlbGVjdHJpY2l0eS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "NzElIG9mIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCdzIHN1cmZhY2UgaXMgbWFkZSB1cCBvZg==",
            "answer": "V2F0ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2VsaWFjIERpc2Vhc2UgaXMgYSBkaXNlYXNlIHRoYXQgZWZmZWN0cyB0aGUgaGVhcnQsIGNhdXNpbmcgdGhvc2UgZWZmZWN0ZWQgdG8gYmUgdW5hYmxlIHRvIGVhdCBtZWF0Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgZXh0aW5jdCBob21pbmluIGtub3duIGFzICJMdWN5Ij8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJhbG9waXRoZWN1cyBBZmFyZW5zaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyB0ZXJtIGZvciAndGFzdGUnPw==",
            "answer": "R3VzdGF0b3J5IFBlcmNlcHRpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1lZGlhbCBtZW5pc2N1cyBmb3JtcyB3aGljaCBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoYXQgam9pbnQgaW4gdGhlIGh1bWFuIGJvZHk/",
            "answer": "S25lZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwaHlzaWNzIHByaW5jaXBsZSByZWxhdGVzIHRoZSBuZXQgZWxlY3RyaWMgZmx1eCBvdXQgb2YgYSBjbG9zZWQgc3VyZmFjZSB0byB0aGUgY2hhcmdlIGVuY2xvc2VkIGJ5IHRoYXQgc3VyZmFjZT8=",
            "answer": "R2F1c3MncyBMYXc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3R1ZHkgb2YgdGhlIGNlbGxzIGFuZCB0aXNzdWVzIG9mIHBsYW50cyBhbmQgYW5pbWFscz8=",
            "answer": "SGlzdG9sb2d5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBhbiBhbHRlcm5hdGl2ZSBuYW1lIGZvciBtdWx0aXBsZSBwZXJzb25hbGl0eSBkaXNvcmRlcj8=",
            "answer": "RGlzc29jaWF0aXZlIGlkZW50aXR5IGRpc29yZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB0aGUgRmFsY29uIEhlYXZ5IHdhcyBsYXVuY2hlZCBvbiBpdCdzIHRlc3QgZmxpZ2h0LCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBvcGVyYXRpb24gdGhhdCBmYWlsZWQ/",
            "answer": "Q2VudGVyIENvcmUgTGFuZGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWduZW91cyByb2NrcyBhcmUgZm9ybWVkIGJ5IGV4Y2Vzc2l2ZSBoZWF0IGFuZCBwcmVzc3VyZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGxpdmluZyBjcmVhdHVyZSBpbiBzcGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "RnJ1aXQgRmxpZXMg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGF0b21pYyBudW1iZXIgb2YgNz8=",
            "answer": "Tml0cm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRldmVsb3BlZCB0aGUgZmlyc3Qgc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bCBwb2xpbyB2YWNjaW5lIGluIHRoZSAxOTUwcz8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uYXMgU2Fsaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZGlkIHRoZSBkb2cgYnJlZWQgIkNoaWh1YWh1YSIgb3JpZ2luYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TWV4aWNv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSB0eXBlIG9mIHN0cmV0Y2gvZGVlcCB0ZW5kb24gcmVmbGV4Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5rbGUgamVyayByZWZsZXg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGVsZW1lbnQgaW52b2x2ZWQgaW4gbWFraW5nIGh1bWFuIGJsb29kIHJlZCBpcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "SXJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjb21ldCdzIGdhc2VvdXMgZW52ZWxvcGUgKHdoaWNoIGNyZWF0ZXMgdGhlIHRhaWwpIGlzIGNhbGxlZCB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIGNvbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY2hyb21vc29tZXMgYXJlIGluIHlvdXIgYm9keSBjZWxscz8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB5b3Ugc3R1ZHkgaWYgeW91IGFyZSBzdHVkeWluZyBlbnRvbW9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5zZWN0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2NpZW50aWZpYyB1bml0IGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIGFuIEl0YWxpYW4gbm9ibGVtYW4/",
            "answer": "Vm9sdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgTGlubmVhbiBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBkb21lc3RpYyBhcHBsZSB0cmVlPw==",
            "answer": "TWFsdXMgcHVtaWxh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBlbGVtZW50cyBpcyB0eXBpY2FsbHkgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgZG9waW5nIG9mIHRoZSBzZW1pY29uZHVjdG9yIHNpbGljb24/",
            "answer": "Qm9yb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsaXF1aWRzIGlzIGxlYXN0IHZpc2NvdXM/IEFzc3VtZSB0ZW1wZXJhdHVyZSBpcyAyNcKwQy4=",
            "answer": "QWNldG9uZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGNoZW1pY2FsIHN5bWJvbCAnRmUnPw==",
            "answer": "SXJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgInBvd2VyaG91c2UiIG9mIHRoZSBFdWthcnlvdGljIGFuaW1hbCBjZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "TWl0b2Nob25kcmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gdGhlIEJlYXVmb3J0IFNjYWxlIG9mIHdpbmQgZm9yY2UsIHdoYXQgd2luZCBuYW1lIGlzIGdpdmVuIHRvIG51bWJlciA4Pw==",
            "answer": "R2FsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGFydGlmaWNpYWwgRWFydGggc2F0ZWxsaXRlLCBsYXVuY2hlZCBieSB0aGUgU292aWV0IFVuaW9uIGluIDE5NTc/",
            "answer": "U3B1dG5payAx"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9uZXMgYXJlIGluIHRoZSBodW1hbiBib2R5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXRvbWljIG51bWJlciBvZiB0aGUgZWxlbWVudCBTdHJvbnRpdW0/",
            "answer": "Mzg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZWxlbWVudHMgb24gdGhlIFBlcmlvZGljIFRhYmxlIGlzIGEgTm9ibGUgR2FzPw==",
            "answer": "TmVvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdW5pdCBvZiBlbGVjdHJpY2FsIGNhcGFjaXRhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "RmFyYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGVzZXJ0IGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IGRlc2VydCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQgd2hlcmUgdGhlICJTYWd1YXJvIiBjYWN0dXMgZ3Jvd3MgaW5kaWdlbm91c2x5Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNvbm9yYW4gRGVzZXJ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWFqb3IgZXh0aW5jdGlvbiBldmVudCB3YXMgY2F1c2VkIGJ5IGFuIGFzdGVyb2lkIGNvbGxpc2lvbiBhbmQgZWxpbWluYXRlZCB0aGUgbWFqb3JpdHkgb2Ygbm9uLWF2aWFuIGRpbm9zYXVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q3JldGFjZW91cy1QYWxlb2dlbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9uZXMgaXMgaGFyZGVzdCB0byBicmVhaz8=",
            "answer": "RmVtdXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdJc2xldHMgb2YgTGFuZ2VyaGFucycgaXMgZm91bmQgaW4gd2hpY2ggaHVtYW4gb3JnYW4/",
            "answer": "UGFuY3JlYXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBsYW5ldCBNYXJzIGhhcyB0d28gbW9vbnMgb3JiaXRpbmcgaXQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBkZWZpYnJpbGxhdG9yIGlzIHVzZWQgdG8gc3RhcnQgdXAgYSBoZWFydGJlYXQgb25jZSBhIGhlYXJ0IGhhcyBzdG9wcGVkIGJlYXRpbmcu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IHBsYW50ZWQgdGhlIHNlZWRzIG9mIFF1ZXJjdXMgcm9idXIgd2hhdCB3b3VsZCBncm93Pw==",
            "answer": "VHJlZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpZ2dlc3QgZGlzdGluY3Rpb24gYmV0d2VlbiBhIGV1a2FyeW90aWMgY2VsbCBhbmQgYSBwcm9rYXJ5b3RpYyBjZWxsIGlzOg==",
            "answer": "VGhlIHByZXNlbmNlIG9yIGFic2VuY2Ugb2YgYSBudWNsZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tm90IGluY2x1ZGluZyBmYWxzZSB0ZWV0aDsgQSBodW1hbiBoYXMgdHdvIHNldHMgb2YgdGVldGggaW4gdGhlaXIgbGlmZXRpbWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBwbGFudCB0aGF0IGhhcyBhIGxpZmUgY3ljbGUgZm9yIG1vcmUgdGhhbiBhIHllYXIgaXMga25vd24gYXMgYW4gYW5udWFsLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBib25lcyBpcyBub3QgaW4gdGhlIGxlZz8=",
            "answer": "UmFkaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZGVncmVlcyBGYWhyZW5oZWl0IGlzIDEwMCBkZWdyZWVzIENlbHNpdXM/IA==",
            "answer": "MjEy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGEgdHlwZSBvZiBuZXVyb24/",
            "answer": "UGVyY2VwdHVhbCBOZXVyb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgd2hpY2ggRGFuaXNoIGNpdHkgaXMgdGhlIDcydGggZWxlbWVudCBvbiB0aGUgcGVyaW9kaWMgdGFibGUgbmFtZWQ/",
            "answer": "Q29wZW5oYWdlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBwb3NpdHJvbiBpcyBhbiBhbnRpcGFydGljbGUgb2YgYSB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "RWxlY3Ryb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcGFjZWNyYWZ0IG5ldmVyIHRvdWNoZWQgdGhlIG1vb24/",
            "answer": "TWFyaW5lciA0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29nbml0aXZlIGJpYXMgd2hlcmVpbiBhIHBlcnNvbiB3aXRoIGxvdyBhYmlsaXR5IGluIGEgcGFydGljdWxhciBza2lsbCBtaXN0YWtlIHRoZW1zZWx2ZXMgYXMgYmVpbmcgc3VwZXJpb3I/",
            "answer": "RHVubmluZy1LcnVnZXIgZWZmZWN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcXVhbnR1bSBwaHlzaWNzLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB0aGVvcmlzZWQgc3ViLWF0b21pYyBwYXJ0aWNsZXMgaGFzIHlldCB0byBiZSBvYnNlcnZlZD8=",
            "answer": "R3Jhdml0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9wb3RvbW9uc3Ryb3Nlc3F1aXBwZWRhbGlvcGhvYmlhIGlzIHRoZSBpcnJhdGlvbmFsIGZlYXIgb2YgbG9uZyB3b3Jkcy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGlrZSB3aXRoIHRoZSBOZWFuZGVydGhhbHMsIEhvbW8gc2FwaWVucyBzYXBpZW5zIGFsc28gaW50ZXJicmVkIHdpdGggdGhlIERlbmlzb3ZhbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjaGVtaWNhbCBlbGVtZW50IEN1cml1bSBuYW1lZCBhZnRlcj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyaWUgJiBQaWVycmUgQ3VyaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGhpZ2hlc3QgbWVsdGluZyBwb2ludD8=",
            "answer": "Q2FyYm9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHBlcmlvZGljIHRhYmxlLCBQb3Rhc3NpdW0ncyBzeW1ib2wgaXMgdGhlIGxldHRlciBLLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2hlbWljYWwgZWxlbWVudCB3YXMgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBrbm93biBhcyBBbGFiYW1pbmU/",
            "answer": "QXN0YXRpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9ydGlvbiBvZiB0aGUgTWFyaWp1YW5hIHBsYW50IHByb2R1Y2VzIHRoZSBwc3ljaG9hY3RpdmUgc3Vic3RhbmNlIGtub3duIGFzIFRIQz8=",
            "answer": "RmVtYWxlIEZsb3dlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGxvbmdlc3QgYm9uZSBpbiB0aGUgaHVtYW4gYm9keT8g",
            "answer": "RmVtdXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlIEdsdXRldXMgTWF4aW11cyBtdXNjbGUgbG9jYXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "QnV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcHJvdG9ucyBhcmUgaW4gYW4gb3h5Z2VuIGF0b20/",
            "answer": "RWlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgZGlkIHRoZSBHcmVhdCBTdG9ybSBvZiAxOTg3IG1ha2UgbGFuZGZhbGwgYXQsIGZpcnN0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q29ybndhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG9yZ2FuaWMgY29tcG91bmQgdG8gYmUgc3ludGhlc2l6ZWQgZnJvbSBpbm9yZ2FuaWMgY29tcG91bmRzPw==",
            "answer": "VXJlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFNjb3ZpbGxlIHNjYWxlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBob3R0ZXN0IGNoZW1pY2FsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVzaW5pZmVyYXRveGlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBzdG9wIGNvZG9uIGluIEROQT8=",
            "answer": "VEFB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBsaXZpbmcgb3JnYW5pc20gY3VycmVudGx5IGtub3duIHRvIG1hbj8=",
            "answer": "SG9uZXkgRnVuZ3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q291bHJvcGhvYmlhIGlzIHRoZSBpcnJhdGlvbmFsIGZlYXIgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "Q2xvd25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5lYW5kZXJ0aGFscyB3ZXJlIGEgZGlyZWN0IGFuY2VzdG9yIG9mIG1vZGVybiBodW1hbnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2hlbWljYWwgbWFrZXVwIG9mIHdhdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "SDIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SHVtYW4gY2VsbHMgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGhhdmUgaG93IG1hbnkgY29waWVzIG9mIGVhY2ggZ2VuZT8=",
            "answer": "Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgU0kgdW5pdCBmb3IgdGVtcGVyYXR1cmU/",
            "answer": "S2Vsdmlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwbGFzdGljIGlzIGNvbW1vbmx5IHVzZWQgZm9yIHdpbmRvdyBmcmFtZXMsIGd1dHRlcnMgYW5kIGRyYWluIHBpcGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UG9seXZpbnlsY2hsb3JpZGUgKFBWQykg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUHN5Y2hvbG9neSwgd2hpY2ggbmVlZCBhcHBlYXJzIGhpZ2hlc3QgaW4gdGhlICJNYXNsb3cncyBoaWVyYXJjaHkgb2YgbmVlZHMiIHB5cmFtaWQ/",
            "answer": "RXN0ZWVt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaG9yaXpvbiBpbiBhIHNvaWwgcHJvZmlsZSBjb25zaXN0cyBvZiBiZWRyb2NrPw==",
            "answer": "Ug=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGV1dGVyaXVtIGlzIGFuIGlzb3RvcGUgb2Ygd2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "SHlkcm9nZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Umhpbm9wbGFzdHkgaXMgYSBzdXJnaWNhbCBwcm9jZWR1cmUgb24gd2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBodW1hbiBib2R5Pw==",
            "answer": "Tm9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBpc29idXR5bHBoZW55bHByb3Bhbm9pYyBhY2lkIG1vcmUgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXM/",
            "answer": "SWJ1cHJvZmVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vc3QgZnJlcXVlbnQgc3ViY29uc2Npb3VzIGFjdGl2aXR5IHJlcGVhdGVkIGJ5IHRoZSBodW1hbiBib2R5IGlzIGJsaW5raW5nLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        }
    ],
    "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhcnZhcmQgYXJjaGl0ZWN0dXJlIGZvciBtaWNyby1jb250cm9sbGVycyBhZGRlZCB3aGljaCBhZGRpdGlvbmFsIGJ1cz8=",
            "answer": "SW5zdHJ1Y3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYW55IHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiB3YXkgdG8gaXRlcmF0ZSB0aHJvdWdoIGFuIGFycmF5Pw==",
            "answer": "J0ZvcicgbG9vcHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW1vbiBzb2Z0d2FyZS1wcm9ncmFtbWluZyBhY3JvbnltICJJMThOIiBjb21lcyBmcm9tIHRoZSB0ZXJtICJJbnRlcmxvY2FsaXphdGlvbiIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaW50ZXJuZXQgY29tcGFueSBiZWdhbiBsaWZlIGFzIGFuIG9ubGluZSBib29rc3RvcmUgY2FsbGVkICdDYWRhYnJhJz8=",
            "answer": "QW1hem9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvbXB1dGVyIGJ1ZyB3YXMgZm9ybWVkIGJ5IGZhdWx0eSB3aXJlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpc3RsZXIgd2FzIHRoZSBjb2RlbmFtZSBvZiB0aGlzIE1pY3Jvc29mdCBPcGVyYXRpbmcgU3lzdGVtLg==",
            "answer": "V2luZG93cyBYUA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TW9vcmUncyBsYXcgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBzdGF0ZWQgdGhhdCB0aGUgbnVtYmVyIG9mIHRyYW5zaXN0b3JzIG9uIGEgbWljcm9wcm9jZXNzb3IgY2hpcCB3b3VsZCBkb3VibGUgZXZlcnkuLi4=",
            "answer": "WWVhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHZlcnkgZmlyc3QgcmVjb3JkZWQgY29tcHV0ZXIgImJ1ZyIgd2FzIGEgbW90aCBmb3VuZCBpbnNpZGUgYSBIYXJ2YXJkIE1hcmsgSUkgY29tcHV0ZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggY29tcHV0ZXIgaGFyZHdhcmUgZGV2aWNlIGlzIHRoZSBCSU9TIGNoaXAgbG9jYXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "TW90aGVyYm9hcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlIEphdmEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGtleXdvcmRzIHdvdWxkIHlvdSBwdXQgb24gYSB2YXJpYWJsZSB0byBtYWtlIHN1cmUgaXQgZG9lc24ndCBnZXQgbW9kaWZpZWQ/",
            "answer": "RmluYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsYW5ndWFnZXMgaXMgdXNlZCBhcyBhIHNjcmlwdGluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdHkgM0QgZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmU/",
            "answer": "QyM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlICJQeXRob24iIGlzIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBhIG1vZGlmaWVkIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgIkphdmFTY3JpcHQiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UG9pbnRlcnMgd2VyZSBub3QgdXNlZCBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgQyBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZTsgdGhleSB3ZXJlIGFkZGVkIGxhdGVyIG9uIGluIEMrKy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgcHJvZ3JhbXMgYXJlIGNsYXNzaWZpZWQgYXMgcmFzdGVyIGdyYXBoaWNzIGVkaXRvcnMgRVhDRVBUOg==",
            "answer": "SW5rc2NhcGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbXB1dGVyIE9FTSBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgQ2xldm8sIGtub3duIGZvciBpdHMgU2FnZXIgbm90ZWJvb2sgbGluZSwgaXMgYmFzZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "VGFpd2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TnZpZGlhJ3MgaGVhZHF1YXJ0ZXJzIGFyZSBiYXNlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBTaWxpY29uIFZhbGxleSBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "U2FudGEgQ2xhcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFRvciBBbm9ueW1pdHkgTmV0d29yayBvcmlnbmlhbGx5IHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE9uaW9uIFJvdXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQW5kcm9pZCA0LjM/",
            "answer": "SmVsbHkgQmVhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gYnlwYXNzIFVTIE11bml0aW9ucyBFeHBvcnQgTGF3cywgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgdGhlIFBHUCBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYWxsIHRoZSBzb3VyY2UgY29kZSBpbiBib29rIGZvcm0uIA==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCB0aGUgV29ybGQgV2lkZSBXZWIgZ28gb25saW5lPw==",
            "answer": "RGVjZW1iZXIgMjAsIDE5OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGRvbWFpbiAuZm0gaXMgdGhlIGNvdW50cnktY29kZSB0b3AtbGV2ZWwgZG9tYWluIGZvciB3aGljaCBQYWNpZmljIE9jZWFuIGlzbGFuZCBuYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "TWljcm9uZXNpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29yZXMgZG9lcyB0aGUgSW50ZWwgaTctNjk1MFggaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGlzIG5vdCBhbiBvZmZpY2lhbCBkZXZlbG9wbWVudCBuYW1lIGZvciBhIFVidW50dSByZWxlYXNlPw==",
            "answer": "TXlzdGljIE1hbnNpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNlcnZlciBob3N0aW5nIGluZHVzdHJ5IElhYVMgc3RhbmRzIGZvci4uLg==",
            "answer": "SW5mcmFzdHJ1Y3R1cmUgYXMgYSBTZXJ2aWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QU1EIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvbnN1bWVyIDY0LWJpdCBwcm9jZXNzb3Iu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbmFtZXMgd2FzIGFuIGFjdHVhbCBjb2RlbmFtZSBmb3IgYSBjYW5jZWxsZWQgTWljcm9zb2Z0IHByb2plY3Q/",
            "answer": "TmVwdHVuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCB0aGVtZSB0aGF0IGlzIGluc3RhbGxlZCB3aXRoIFdpbmRvd3MgWFA/",
            "answer": "THVuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSFRNTCwgd2hpY2ggbm9uLXN0YW5kYXJkIHRhZyB1c2VkIHRvIGJlIGJlIHVzZWQgdG8gbWFrZSBlbGVtZW50cyBzY3JvbGwgYWNyb3NzIHRoZSB2aWV3cG9ydD8=",
            "answer": "PG1hcnF1ZWU+PC9tYXJxdWVlPg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIElCTSBQQyB1c2VkIGFuIEludGVsIDgwMDggbWljcm9wcm9jZXNzb3IgY2xvY2tlZCBhdCA0Ljc3IE1IeiBhbmQgOCBraWxvYnl0ZXMgb2YgbWVtb3J5Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gY29tcHV0aW5nIHRlcm1zLCB0eXBpY2FsbHkgd2hhdCBkb2VzIENMSSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "Q29tbWFuZCBMaW5lIEludGVyZmFjZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5WaWRpYSBHVFggMTA4MCBnZXRzIGl0cyBuYW1lIGJlY2F1c2UgaXQgY2FuIG9ubHkgcmVuZGVyIGF0IGEgMTkyMHgxMDgwIHNjcmVlbiByZXNvbHV0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvcmlnaW5hbCBhdXRob3Igb2YgdGhlIHJlYWx0aW1lIHBoeXNpY3MgZW5naW5lIGNhbGxlZCBQaHlzWD8=",
            "answer": "Tm92b2RlWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SXQncyBub3QgcG9zc2libGUgdG8gZm9ybWF0IGEgd3JpdGUtcHJvdGVjdGVkIERWRC1SIEhhcmQgRGlzay4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG51bWJlcmluZyBzeXN0ZW0gd2l0aCBhIHJhZGl4IG9mIDE2IGlzIG1vcmUgY29tbW9ubHkgcmVmZXJyZWQgdG8gYXMg",
            "answer": "SGV4aWRlY2ltYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvY2VzcyB0aGF0IHNlbmRzIG9uZSBxdWJpdCBvZiBpbmZvcm1hdGlvbiB1c2luZyB0d28gYml0cyBvZiBjbGFzc2ljYWwgaW5mb3JtYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "UXVhbnR1bSBUZWxlcG9ydGF0aW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEFuZHJvaWQgdmVyc2lvbiBzcGVjaWZpY2FsbHkgb3B0aW1pemVkIGZvciB0YWJsZXRzPw==",
            "answer": "SG9uZXljb21i"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUkFJRCBhcnJheSB0eXBlIGlzIGFzc29jaWF0ZWQgd2l0aCBkYXRhIG1pcnJvcmluZz8=",
            "answer": "UkFJRCAx"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFzZXJqZXQgYW5kIGlua2pldCBwcmludGVycyBhcmUgYm90aCBleGFtcGxlcyBvZiB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgcHJpbnRlcj8=",
            "answer": "Tm9uLWltcGFjdCBwcmludGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGludmVudGVkIHRoZSAiU3Bhbm5pbmcgVHJlZSBQcm90b2NvbCI/",
            "answer": "UmFkaWEgUGVybG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXBwcm94aW1hdGVseSBob3cgbWFueSBBcHBsZSBJIHBlcnNvbmFsIGNvbXB1dGVycyB3ZXJlIGNyZWF0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugc2hhcmVzIGl0cyBuYW1lIHdpdGggYW4gaXNsYW5kIGluIEluZG9uZXNpYT8=",
            "answer": "SmF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFJBSUQgc3RhbmQgZm9yPw==",
            "answer": "UmVkdW5kYW50IEFycmF5IG9mIEluZGVwZW5kZW50IERpc2tz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgaXMgYW4gSVB2NiBhZGRyZXNzPw==",
            "answer": "MTI4IGJpdHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBCb29sZWFuIHZhbHVlIG9mICIwIiByZXByZXNlbnRzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIHdvcmRzPw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGFjcm9ueW0gIlJJUCIgc3RhbmRzIGZvciB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Um91dGluZyBJbmZvcm1hdGlvbiBQcm90b2NvbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgbGF5ZXIgaW4gdGhlIE9TSSBtb2RlbCBmb3IgZGF0YSBjb21tdW5pY2F0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "Q29ubmVjdGlvbiBMYXllcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbnVtYmVyIG9mIGtleXMgb24gYSBzdGFuZGFyZCBXaW5kb3dzIEtleWJvYXJkPw==",
            "answer": "MTA0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIHNvdW5kIGNoaXAgZG9lcyB0aGUgU3VwZXIgTmludGVuZG8gRW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudCBTeXN0ZW0gKFNORVMpIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "QURQQ00gU2FtcGxlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VW5peCBUaW1lIGlzIGRlZmluZWQgYXMgdGhlIG51bWJlciBvZiBzZWNvbmRzIHRoYXQgaGF2ZSBlbGFwc2VkIHNpbmNlIHdoZW4/",
            "answer": "TWlkbmlnaHQsIEphbnVhcnkgMSwgMTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2gga2luZCBvZiBhbGdvcml0aG0gaXMgUm9uIFJpdmVzdCBub3QgZmFtb3VzIGZvciBjcmVhdGluZz8=",
            "answer": "U2VjcmV0IHNoYXJpbmcgc2NoZW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIENQVSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "Q2VudHJhbCBQcm9jZXNzaW5nIFVuaXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RkxBQyBzdGFuZHMgZm9yICJGcmVlIExvc3NsZXNzIEF1ZGlvIENvbmRlbnNlciIn",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIEFEIHN0YW5kIGZvciBpbiByZWxhdGlvbiB0byBXaW5kb3dzIE9wZXJhdGluZyBTeXN0ZW1zPyA=",
            "answer": "QWN0aXZlIERpcmVjdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SFRNTCBpcyB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgbGFuZ3VhZ2U/",
            "answer": "TWFya3VwIExhbmd1YWdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbW91bnQgb2YgYml0cyBjb21tb25seSBlcXVhbHMgb25lIGJ5dGU/",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxsIHByb2dyYW0gY29kZXMgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSBjb21waWxlZCBpbnRvIGFuIGV4ZWN1dGFibGUgZmlsZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byBiZSBydW4uIFRoaXMgZmlsZSBjYW4gdGhlbiBiZSBleGVjdXRlZCBvbiBhbnkgbWFjaGluZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgSHogZG9lcyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gc3RhbmRhcmQgUEFMIHN1cHBvcnQ/",
            "answer": "NTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxvZ28gZm9yIFNuYXBjaGF0IGlzIGEgQmVsbC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IHdlcmUgdG8gY29kZSBzb2Z0d2FyZSBpbiB0aGlzIGxhbmd1YWdlIHlvdSdkIG9ubHkgYmUgYWJsZSB0byB0eXBlIDAncyBhbmQgMSdzLg==",
            "answer": "QmluYXJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvbW1lcmljYWxseSBhdmFpbGFibGUgY29tcHV0ZXIgcHJvY2Vzc29yPw==",
            "answer": "SW50ZWwgNDAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpbGUgQXBwbGUgd2FzIGZvcm1lZCBpbiBDYWxpZm9ybmlhLCBpbiB3aGljaCB3ZXN0ZXJuIHN0YXRlIHdhcyBNaWNyb3NvZnQgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IE1leGljbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga2lsb2J5dGVzIGluIG9uZSBnaWdhYnl0ZSAoaW4gZGVjaW1hbCk/",
            "answer": "MTAwMDAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWFjT1MgaXMgYmFzZWQgb24gTGludXgu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG9wZW4gc291cmNlIHByb2dyYW0gUmVkaXMgaXMgYSByZWxhdGlvbmFsIGRhdGFiYXNlIHNlcnZlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gVHdpdHRlciwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIGNoYXJhY3RlciBsaW1pdCBmb3IgYSBUd2VldD8=",
            "answer": "MTQw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwb3J0IGRvZXMgSFRUUCBydW4gb24/",
            "answer": "ODA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "REhDUCBzdGFuZHMgZm9yIER5bmFtaWMgSG9zdCBDb25maWd1cmF0aW9uIFBvcnQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCB0ZXJtIGZvciB0aGUgbWV0YWwgb2JqZWN0IGluIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIENQVSBhbmQgdGhlIENQVSBmYW4gd2l0aGluIGEgY29tcHV0ZXIgc3lzdGVtPw==",
            "answer": "SGVhdCBTaW5r"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzIGlzIGEgbG93LWxldmVsIGxhbmd1YWdlPw==",
            "answer": "QXNzZW1ibHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RWFybHkgUkFNIHdhcyBkaXJlY3RseSBzZWF0ZWQgb250byB0aGUgbW90aGVyYm9hcmQgYW5kIGNvdWxkIG5vdCBiZSBlYXNpbHkgcmVtb3ZlZC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIExUUyBzdGFuZCBmb3IgaW4gdGhlIHNvZnR3YXJlIG1hcmtldD8=",
            "answer": "TG9uZyBUZXJtIFN1cHBvcnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IGR1YWwtY29yZSBDUFUgd2FzIHRoZSBJbnRlbCBQZW50aXVtIEQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhc3QgV2luZG93cyBvcGVyYXRpbmcgc3lzdGVtIHRvIGJlIGJhc2VkIG9uIHRoZSBXaW5kb3dzIDl4IGtlcm5lbCB3YXMgV2luZG93cyA5OC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgb2xkZXN0IG9mIHRoZXNlIGNvbXB1dGVycyBieSByZWxlYXNlIGRhdGU/",
            "answer": "VFJTLTgw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW1lcmljYSBPbmxpbmUgKEFPTCkgc3RhcnRlZCBvdXQgYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugb25saW5lIHNlcnZpY2UgcHJvdmlkZXJzPw==",
            "answer": "UXVhbnR1bSBMaW5r"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBtb2JpbGUgT1MgaGVsZCB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBtYXJrZXQgc2hhcmUgaW4gMjAxMi4=",
            "answer": "aU9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBJbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsIFN5c3RlbSBvZiBRdWFudGl0aWVzIHJlZmVyIDEwMjQgYnl0ZXMgYXM/",
            "answer": "S2liaWJ5dGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIG9ubGluZSBzdHJlYW1pbmcgc2VydmljZSAiTWl4ZXIiIGxhdW5jaD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHV0Y2ggY29tcHV0ZXIgc2NpZW50aXN0IE1hcmsgT3Zlcm1hcnMgaXMga25vd24gZm9yIGNyZWF0aW5nIHdoaWNoIGdhbWUgZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "R2FtZSBNYWtlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEMgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugd2FzIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgdGhpcyBBbWVyaWNhbiBjb21wdXRlciBzY2llbnRpc3QuIA==",
            "answer": "RGVubmlzIFJpdGNoaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gY29tcHV0aW5nLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgTUlESSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "TXVzaWNhbCBJbnN0cnVtZW50IERpZ2l0YWwgSW50ZXJmYWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYnl0ZXMgYXJlIGluIGEgc2luZ2xlIEtpYmlieXRlPw==",
            "answer": "MTAyNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYml0cyBtYWtlIHVwIHRoZSBzaWduaWZpY2FuZCBwb3J0aW9uIG9mIGEgc2luZ2xlIHByZWNpc2lvbiBmbG9hdGluZyBwb2ludCBudW1iZXI/",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhUTUw1IHN0YW5kYXJkIHdhcyBwdWJsaXNoZWQgaW4gMjAxNC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBQcnQgU2MgYnV0dG9uIGRvPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FwdHVyZXMgd2hhdCdzIG9uIHRoZSBzY3JlZW4gYW5kIGNvcGllcyBpdCB0byB5b3VyIGNsaXBib2FyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBwcmVmZXJyZWQgaW1hZ2UgZm9ybWF0IHVzZWQgZm9yIGxvZ29zIGluIHRoZSBXaWtpbWVkaWEgZGF0YWJhc2U/",
            "answer": "LnN2Zw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29kZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgbW9iaWxlIG9wZXJhdGluZyBzeXN0ZW0gQW5kcm9pZCA3LjA/",
            "answer": "Tm91Z2F0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZG9tYWluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSBjb3VudHJ5IFR1dmFsdT8=",
            "answer": "LnR2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UkFNIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgUmFuZG9tIEFjY2VzcyBNZW1vcnku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VuZXJhbGx5LCB3aGljaCBjb21wb25lbnQgb2YgYSBjb21wdXRlciBkcmF3cyB0aGUgbW9zdCBwb3dlcj8=",
            "answer": "VmlkZW8gQ2FyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdpbmRvd3MgNyBvcGVyYXRpbmcgc3lzdGVtIGhhcyBzaXggbWFpbiBlZGl0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdpbmRvd3MgTUUgb3BlcmF0aW5nIHN5c3RlbSB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gdGhlIHllYXIgMjAwMC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGZhc3QgaXMgVVNCIDMuMSBHZW4gMiB0aGVvcmV0aWNhbGx5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTAgR2Ivcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "LmF0IGlzIHRoZSB0b3AtbGV2ZWwgZG9tYWluIGZvciB3aGF0IGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEga2V5IHZhbHVlIG9mIEFnaWxlIHNvZnR3YXJlIGRldmVsb3BtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Q29tcHJlaGVuc2l2ZSBkb2N1bWVudGF0aW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW5kcm9pZCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBhcmUgbmFtZWQgaW4gYWxwaGFiZXRpY2FsIG9yZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvbXBhbnkgdG8gdXNlIHRoZSB0ZXJtICJHb2xkZW4gTWFzdGVyIj8=",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGludXMgU2ViYXN0aWFuIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBMaW51eCBrZXJuZWwsIHdoaWNoIHdlbnQgb24gdG8gYmUgdXNlZCBpbiBMaW51eCwgQW5kcm9pZCwgYW5kIENocm9tZSBPUy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGVjaG5vbG9neSBjb21wYW55IEhQIHN0YW5kcyBmb3Igd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "SGV3bGV0dC1QYWNrYXJk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gY29tcHV0aW5nLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgTEFOIHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "answer": "TG9jYWwgQXJlYSBOZXR3b3Jr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtYWpvciBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSBkb2VzIFVucmVhbCBFbmdpbmUgNCB1c2U/",
            "answer": "Qysr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlYXBvdCBvZnRlbiBzZWVuIGluIG1hbnkgM0QgbW9kZWxpbmcgYXBwbGljYXRpb25zIGlzIGNhbGxlZCB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VXRhaCBUZWFwb3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEJ1bGdhcmlhbiBwZXJzb25hbCBjb21wdXRlcj8=",
            "answer": "SU1LTy0x"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29kZW5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGVpZ2h0aCBnZW5lcmF0aW9uIEludGVsIENvcmUgbWljcm8tYXJjaGl0ZWN0dXJlIGxhdW5jaGVkIGluIE9jdG9iZXIgMjAxNz8=",
            "answer": "Q29mZmVlIExha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVub3ZvIGFjcXVpcmVkIElCTSdzIHBlcnNvbmFsIGNvbXB1dGVyIGRpdmlzaW9uLCBpbmNsdWRpbmcgdGhlIFRoaW5rUGFkIGxpbmUgb2YgbGFwdG9wcyBhbmQgdGFibGV0cywgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQ2hlcnJ5IE1YIG1lY2hhbmljYWwga2V5Ym9hcmQgc3dpdGNoZXMgaXMgYm90aCB0YWN0aWxlIGFuZCBjbGlja3k/",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5IE1YIEJsdWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAiTVAiIHN0YW5kIGZvciBpbiBNUDM/",
            "answer": "TW92aW5nIFBpY3R1cmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBJbnRlcm5hdGlvbmFsIFN5c3RlbSBvZiBVbml0cywgaG93IG1hbnkgYnl0ZXMgYXJlIGluIGEga2lsb2J5dGUgb2YgUkFNPw==",
            "answer": "MTAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIEdIeiBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "R2lnYWhlcnR6"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlICJDIyIgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlICdTd2lmdCcgd2FzIGNyZWF0ZWQgdG8gcmVwbGFjZSB3aGF0IG90aGVyIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlPw==",
            "answer": "T2JqZWN0aXZlLUM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBmaXZlIGxldHRlciB3b3JkIGlzIHRoZSBtb3R0byBvZiB0aGUgSUJNIENvbXB1dGVyIGNvbXBhbnk/",
            "answer": "VGhpbms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSBmYWlsZWQga2V5IGVzY3JvdyBkZXZpY2UgaW50cm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgTmF0aW9uYWwgU2VjdXJpdHkgQWdlbmN5IGluIDE5OTM/",
            "answer": "Q2xpcHBlciBDaGlw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBhY3JvbnltIENETiBzdGFuZCBmb3IgaW4gdGVybXMgb2YgbmV0d29ya2luZz8=",
            "answer": "Q29udGVudCBEZWxpdmVyeSBOZXR3b3Jr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29kaW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlIHdhcyB0aGUgIzEgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2UgaW4gdGVybXMgb2YgdXNhZ2Ugb24gR2l0SHViIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "SmF2YVNjcmlwdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkhUTUwiIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgSHlwZXJ0ZXh0IE1hcmt1cCBMYW5ndWFnZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhleGFkZWNpbWFsIiwgd2hhdCBjb2xvciB3b3VsZCBiZSBkaXNwbGF5ZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgY29sb3IgY29kZT8gIiMwMEZGMDAiPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbnRlcm5ldCBwcm90b2NvbCB3YXMgZG9jdW1lbnRlZCBpbiBSRkMgMTQ1OT8=",
            "answer": "SVJD"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGludXggd2FzIGZpcnN0IGNyZWF0ZWQgYXMgYW4gYWx0ZXJuYXRpdmUgdG8gV2luZG93cyBYUC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBDUFUgaXMgdGhlIFNlZ2EgTWVnYSBEcml2ZSAvIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcz8=",
            "answer": "TW90b3JvbGEgNjgwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugd2FzIGRldmVsb3BlZCBieSBTdW4gTWljcm9zeXN0ZW1zIGluIDE5OTU/",
            "answer": "SmF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhvbiBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSBnZXRzIGl0cyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggY29tZWR5IGdyb3VwICJNb250eSBQeXRob24uIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAnUycgaW4gdGhlIFJTQSBlbmNyeXB0aW9uIGFsZ29yaXRobSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "U2hhbWly"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb21wdXRlciBjb21wb25lbnRzIGNhbiBiZSBidWlsdCB1c2luZyBvbmx5IE5BTkQgZ2F0ZXM/",
            "answer": "QUxV"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNlcmllcyBvZiB0aGUgSW50ZWwgSEQgZ3JhcGhpY3MgZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBzdWNjZWVkaW5nIHRoYXQgb2YgdGhlIDUwMDAgYW5kIDYwMDAgc2VyaWVzIChCcm9hZHdlbGwpIGlzIGNhbGxlZDo=",
            "answer": "SEQgR3JhcGhpY3MgNTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IldpbmRvd3MgTlQiIGlzIGEgbW9ub2xpdGhpYyBrZXJuZWwu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ1NTLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB2YWx1ZXMgQ0FOTk9UIGJlIHVzZWQgd2l0aCB0aGUgInBvc2l0aW9uIiBwcm9wZXJ0eT8=",
            "answer": "Y2VudGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgYnVnIGZvdW5kIGluIEFwcmlsIDIwMTQgaW4gdGhlIHB1YmxpY2x5IGF2YWlsYWJsZSBPcGVuU1NMIGNyeXB0b2dyYXBoeSBsaWJyYXJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SGVhcnRibGVlZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCBwcm9ncmFtbWluZyBsYW5ndWFnZXMsIHRoZSBvcGVyYXRvciArKyBpcyBlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIHRoZSBzdGF0ZW1lbnQgIis9IDEiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhIHBlcnNvbmFsIGNvbXB1dGVyIG1hZGUgYnkgdGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGNvbXBhbnkgRnVqaXRzdT8=",
            "answer": "Rk0tNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBrbm93biBhcyAidGhlIGJyYWluIiBvZiB0aGUgQ29tcHV0ZXI/",
            "answer": "Q2VudHJhbCBQcm9jZXNzaW5nIFVuaXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSB0ZXJtIEdQVSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "R3JhcGhpY3MgUHJvY2Vzc2luZyBVbml0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIERlTW9yZ2FuJ3MgVGhlb3JlbSwgdGhlIEJvb2xlYW4gZXhwcmVzc2lvbiAoQUIpJyBpcyBlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvOg==",
            "answer": "QScgKyBCJw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBsYW5ndWFnZSBkb2VzIE5vZGUuanMgdXNlPw==",
            "answer": "SmF2YVNjcmlwdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFQtTW9iaWxlIFNpZGVraWNrIHNtYXJ0cGhvbmUgaXMgYSByZS1icmFuZGVkIHZlcnNpb24gb2YgdGhlIERhbmdlciBIaXB0b3Au",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBjb21wdXRlciBzb2Z0d2FyZSBhY3JvbnltIEpWTSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "SmF2YSBWaXJ0dWFsIE1hY2hpbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBHbWFpbCBmaXJzdCBsYXVuY2hlZCwgaG93IG11Y2ggc3RvcmFnZSBkaWQgaXQgcHJvdmlkZSBmb3IgeW91ciBlbWFpbD8=",
            "answer": "MUdC"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcHV0ZXIgaGFyZHdhcmUgZGV2aWNlIHByb3ZpZGVzIGFuIGludGVyZmFjZSBmb3IgYWxsIG90aGVyIGNvbm5lY3RlZCBkZXZpY2VzIHRvIGNvbW11bmljYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TW90aGVyYm9hcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGludXMgVG9ydmFsZHMgY3JlYXRlZCBMaW51eCBhbmQgR2l0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcsIHRoZSB0ZXJuYXJ5IG9wZXJhdG9yIGlzIG1vc3RseSBkZWZpbmVkIHdpdGggd2hhdCBzeW1ib2wocyk/",
            "answer": "Pzo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "LnJzIGlzIHRoZSB0b3AtbGV2ZWwgZG9tYWluIGZvciB3aGF0IGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "U2VyYmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGF0YSBzdHJ1Y3R1cmUgZG9lcyBGSUxPIGFwcGx5IHRvPw==",
            "answer": "U3RhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIHdhcyBOT1QgYSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mIEFwcGxlIEluYz8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uYXRoYW4gSXZl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSB0ZXJtIE1JTUUgc3RhbmQgZm9yLCBpbiByZWdhcmRzIHRvIGNvbXB1dGluZz8=",
            "answer": "TXVsdGlwdXJwb3NlIEludGVybmV0IE1haWwgRXh0ZW5zaW9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gMjAwMSwgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGVkaXRpb24gb2YgQXBwbGUncyBNYWMgT1MgWCBvcGVyYXRpbmcgc3lzdGVtICh2ZXJzaW9uIDEwLjApIHdhcyBnaXZlbiB3aGF0IGFuaW1hbCBjb2RlIG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "Q2hlZXRhaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcsIHdoYXQgZG8geW91IGNhbGwgZnVuY3Rpb25zIHdpdGggdGhlIHNhbWUgbmFtZSBidXQgZGlmZmVyZW50IGltcGxlbWVudGF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "T3ZlcmxvYWRpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIG9mIFBhbGFudGlyPw==",
            "answer": "UGV0ZXIgVGhpZWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSB3YXMgZXN0YWJsaXNoZWQgb24gQXByaWwgMXN0LCAxOTc2IGJ5IFN0ZXZlIEpvYnMsIFN0ZXZlIFdvem5pYWsgYW5kIFJvbmFsZCBXYXluZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNlY3VyaXR5IHZ1bG5lcmFiaWxpdHkgZm91bmQgaW4gQmFzaCBpbiAyMDE0Pw==",
            "answer": "U2hlbGxzaG9jaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlICJQeXRob24iLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSBzdGF0ZW1lbnRzIHdvdWxkIGRpc3BsYXkgdGhlIHN0cmluZyAiSGVsbG8gV29ybGQiIGNvcnJlY3RseT8=",
            "answer": "cHJpbnQoIkhlbGxvIFdvcmxkIik="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGltZSBvbiBDb21wdXRlcnMgaXMgbWVhc3VyZWQgdmlhIHRoZSBFUE9YIFN5c3RlbS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb3BlcmF0aW5nIHN5c3RlbSB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgZmlyc3Q/",
            "answer": "TWFjIE9T"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdmFsdWVzIGNhbiBhIHNpbmdsZSBieXRlIHJlcHJlc2VudD8=",
            "answer": "MjU2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2ViIGRlc2lnbiwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIENTUyBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "answer": "Q2FzY2FkaW5nIFN0eWxlIFNoZWV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWRhIExvdmVsYWNlIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvbXB1dGVyIHByb2dyYW1tZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzICJMQ0QiIHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "answer": "TGlxdWlkIENyeXN0YWwgRGlzcGxheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBnaXZlbiB0byBsYXllciA0IG9mIHRoZSBPcGVuIFN5c3RlbXMgSW50ZXJjb25uZWN0aW9uIChJU08pIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "VHJhbnNwb3J0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcHV0ZXIgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugd291bGQgeW91IGFzc29jaWF0ZSBEamFuZ28gZnJhbWV3b3JrIHdpdGg/",
            "answer": "UHl0aG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB2dWxuZXJhYmlsaXR5IHJhbmtlZCAjMSBvbiB0aGUgT1dBU1AgVG9wIDEwIGluIDIwMTM/",
            "answer": "SW5qZWN0aW9uIA=="
        }
    ],
    "U2NpZW5jZTogTWF0aGVtYXRpY3M=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDYgZGlnaXRzIG9mIHRoZSBudW1iZXIgIlBpIj8=",
            "answer": "My4xNDE1OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbnVtYmVycyBpcyBjbG9zZXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0b3RhbCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcG9zc2libGUgc3RhdGVzIGZvciBhbiBhcm15IHN0YW5kYXJkIEVuaWdtYSBNYWNoaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "MS41OCB4IDEwXjIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDYgZGlnaXRzIG9mIHRoZSBudW1iZXIgIlBpIj8=",
            "answer": "My4xNDE1OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTWVyc2VubmUgcHJpbWUgZXhwb25lbnQgb3ZlciAxMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MTI3OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDYgZGlnaXRzIG9mIHRoZSBudW1iZXIgIlBpIj8=",
            "answer": "My4xNDE1OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTWVyc2VubmUgcHJpbWUgZXhwb25lbnQgb3ZlciAxMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MTI3OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDYgZGlnaXRzIG9mIHRoZSBudW1iZXIgIlBpIj8=",
            "answer": "My4xNDE1OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbnVtYmVycyBpcyBjbG9zZXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0b3RhbCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcG9zc2libGUgc3RhdGVzIGZvciBhbiBhcm15IHN0YW5kYXJkIEVuaWdtYSBNYWNoaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "MS41OCB4IDEwXjIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTWVyc2VubmUgcHJpbWUgZXhwb25lbnQgb3ZlciAxMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MTI3OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbnVtYmVycyBpcyBjbG9zZXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0b3RhbCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcG9zc2libGUgc3RhdGVzIGZvciBhbiBhcm15IHN0YW5kYXJkIEVuaWdtYSBNYWNoaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "MS41OCB4IDEwXjIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc2V0LCBvciBhIHNldCB0aGF0IGNvbnRhaW5zIGFsbCBzZXRzLCBleGlzdHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3ltYm9sIGZvciBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "zpRy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbnVtYmVycyBpcyBjbG9zZXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0b3RhbCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcG9zc2libGUgc3RhdGVzIGZvciBhbiBhcm15IHN0YW5kYXJkIEVuaWdtYSBNYWNoaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "MS41OCB4IDEwXjIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHN5c3RlbSwgd2hhdCBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgYWZ0ZXIgOT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIExldHRlciBB"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZSBvZiBBY2NlbGVyYXRpb24gd2l0aCByZXNwZWN0IHRvIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "SmVyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU/",
            "answer": "Mi43Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVyb3MgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIGEgZ29vZ29sPw==",
            "answer": "MTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBhIGNpcmNsZSB3aXRoIGEgZGlhbWV0ZXIgb2YgMjAgaW5jaGVzIGlmIM+APSAzLjE0MTU/",
            "answer": "MzE0LjE1IEluY2hlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5dGhhZ29yZWFuIHRoZW9yZW0gc3RhdGVzIHRoYXQgdGhlIHNxdWFyZSBvZiB0aGUgaHlwb3RlbnVzZSBpcyBlcXVhbCB0byB0aGUgcHJvZHVjdCBvZiB0aGUgc3F1YXJlcyBvZiB0aGUgb3RoZXIgdHdvIHNpZGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IDYgZGlnaXRzIG9mIHRoZSBudW1iZXIgIlBpIj8=",
            "answer": "My4xNDE1OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUm9tYW4gTnVtZXJhbHMsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyBYTCBlcXVhdGUgdG8/",
            "answer": "NDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCBmb3IgNTAwPw==",
            "answer": "RA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBvZiA0OT8=",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgemVwdG9tZXRyZXMgYXJlIGluc2lkZSBvbmUgZmVtdG9tZXRyZT8=",
            "answer": "MSwwMDAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgTWVyc2VubmUgcHJpbWUgZXhwb25lbnQgb3ZlciAxMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MTI3OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb29mIGZvciB0aGUgQ2hpbmVzZSBSZW1haW5kZXIgVGhlb3JlbSB1c2VkIGluIE51bWJlciBUaGVvcnkgd2FzIE5PVCBkZXZlbG9wZWQgYnkgaXRzIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlciwgU3VuIFR6dS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "MTExLDExMSwxMTEgeCAxMTEsMTExLDExMSA9IDEyLDM0NSw2NzgsOTg3LDY1NCwzMjE=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICdTcXVhcmluZyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlJyBwcm9ibGVtIGlzIHNvbHZhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgIjEwMTAwMTEwMSIgaXMgZXF1aXZhbGVudCB0byB0aGUgRGVjaW1hbCBudW1iZXIgIjMzNCI=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwcmltZSBudW1iZXIgY29tZXMgbmV4dCBhZnRlciAxOT8=",
            "answer": "MjM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGNvdWxkIGZvbGQgYSBwaWVjZSBvZiBwYXBlciBpbiBoYWxmIDUwIHRpbWVzLCBpdHMnIHRoaWNrbmVzcyB3aWxsIGJlIDMvNHRoIHRoZSBkaXN0YW5jZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCB0byB0aGUgU3VuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWxwaGFudW1lcmljIHJlcHJlc2VudGF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBpbWFnaW5hcnkgbnVtYmVyPw==",
            "answer": "aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gdGhlIG5lYXJlc3Qgd2hvbGUgbnVtYmVyLCBob3cgbWFueSByYWRpYW5zIGFyZSBpbiBhIHdob2xlIGNpcmNsZT8=",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBHcmVlayBsZXR0ZXIgaXMgdXNlZCB0byBzaWduaWZ5IHN1bW1hdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "U2lnbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlY2ltYWwgbnVtYmVyIDMxIGluIGhleGFkZWNpbWFsIHdvdWxkIGJlIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "MUY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RSA9IE1DMw==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WmVybyBmYWN0b3JpYWwgaXMgZXF1YWwgdG8gemVyby4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ldHJpYyBwcmVmaXggImF0dG8tIiBtYWtlcyBhIG1lYXN1cmVtZW50IGhvdyBtdWNoIHNtYWxsZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgYmFzZSB1bml0Pw==",
            "answer": "T25lIFF1aW50aWxsaW9udGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSAnTWlsbGluaWxsaW9uJyBpcyBhIHJlYWwgbnVtYmVyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIGhlcHRhZ29uIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGxhbmUgY3VydmUgcHJvcG9zZWQgYnkgRGVzY2FydGVzIHRvIGNoYWxsZW5nZSBGZXJtYXQncyBleHRyZW11bS1maW5kaW5nIHRlY2huaXF1ZXMgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9saXVtIG9mIERlc2NhcnRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVG9wb2xvZ3ksIHRoZSBjb21wbGVtZW50IG9mIGFuIG9wZW4gc2V0IGlzIGEgY2xvc2VkIHNldC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFuIMOJdmFyaXN0ZSBHYWxvaXMgaXMgcHJpbWFyaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBoaXMgd29yayBpbiB3aGljaD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lzIFRoZW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNldCBvZiBhbGwgYWxnZWJyYWljIG51bWJlcnMgaXMgY291bnRhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TCdIw7RwaXRhbCB3YXMgdGhlIG1hdGhlbWF0aWNpYW4gd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIGhvbW9ueW1vdXMgcnVsZSB0aGF0IHVzZXMgZGVyaXZhdGl2ZXMgdG8gZXZhbHVhdGUgbGltaXRzIHdpdGggaW5kZXRlcm1pbmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1bSBvZiBhbnkgdHdvIG9kZCBpbnRlZ2VycyBpcyBvZGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiBzcXVhcmUgcm9vdCBhIG5lZ2F0aXZlIG51bWJlciB3aXRoIGFuIGltYWdpbmFyeSBudW1iZXIgImkiLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gaXNvc2NlbGVzIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoIGFzIG9wcG9zZWQgdG8gdGhyZWUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzY2FsZW5lIHRyaWFuZ2xlIGhhcyB0d28gc2lkZXMgb2YgZXF1YWwgbGVuZ3RoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gZXF1aWxhdGVyYWwgdHJpYW5nbGUgYWx3YXlzIGhhcyBldmVyeSBhbmdsZSBtZWFzdXJpbmcgNjDCsC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2lkZXMgZG9lcyBhIHRyYXBleml1bSBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbnVtYmVycyBpcyBjbG9zZXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0b3RhbCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcG9zc2libGUgc3RhdGVzIGZvciBhbiBhcm15IHN0YW5kYXJkIEVuaWdtYSBNYWNoaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "MS41OCB4IDEwXjIw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByYW4gdGhyb3VnaCB0aGUgc3RyZWV0cyBvZiBTeXJhY3VzZSBuYWtlZCB3aGlsZSBzaG91dGluZyAiRXVyZWthIiBhZnRlciBkaXNjb3ZlcmluZyB0aGUgcHJpbmNpcGxlIG9mIGRpc3BsYWNlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "QXJjaGltZWRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmYW1vdXMgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbnMgZGllZCBpbiBhIGR1ZWwgYXQgdGhlIGFnZSBvZiAyMD8=",
            "answer": "R2Fsb2lz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgYm9va3MgYXJlIGluIEV1Y2xpZCdzIEVsZW1lbnRzIG9mIEdlb21ldHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWNlIGlzIG5vdCBhIHBsYXRvbmljIHNvbGlkPw==",
            "answer": "MTAtc2lkZWQgZGll"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYXRoZW1hdGljaWFucyBtYWRlIG1ham9yIGNvbnRyaWJ1dGlvbnMgdG8gZ2FtZSB0aGVvcnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBWb24gTmV1bWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdGlvbiBvZiBhICJzZXQgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyBhbGwgc2V0cyB3aGljaCBkbyBub3QgY29udGFpbiB0aGVtc2VsdmVzIiBpcyBhIHBhcmFkb3hpY2FsIGlkZWEgYXR0cmlidXRlZCB0byB3aGljaCBFbmdsaXNoIHBoaWxvc3BoZXI/",
            "answer": "QmVydHJhbmQgUnVzc2Vs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWF0aGVtYXRpY2lhbiByZWZ1c2VkIHRoZSBGaWVsZHMgTWVkYWw/",
            "answer": "R3JpZ29yaSBQZXJlbG1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgbnVtYmVyIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyB0aGUgc3VtIG9mIHR3byBwb3NpdGl2ZSBjdWJlcyBpbiB0d28gZGlmZmVyZW50IHdheXM/",
            "answer": "MTcyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZm91cnRoIGRpZ2l0IG9mIM+APw==",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbXBsZXggcGxhbmUsIG11bHRpcGx5aW5nIGEgZ2l2ZW4gZnVuY3Rpb24gYnkgaSByb3RhdGVzIGl0IGFudGktY2xvY2t3aXNlIGJ5IGhvdyBtYW55IGRlZ3JlZXM/",
            "answer": "OTA="
        }
    ],
    "TXl0aG9sb2d5": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIGZpcmU/",
            "answer": "VnVsY2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVwdHVuZSdzIGdyZWVrIG5hbWUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "UG9zZWlkb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdyZWVrIGdvZCBQb3NlaWRvbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBIZXJhIGlzIHRoZSBnb2RkZXNzIG9mIGhhcnZlc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIGJsYWNrc21pdGhzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVwaGFlc3R1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "Q2VudGF1cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEphcGFuZXNlIGZvbGtsb3JlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kIG9mIHRoZSBLYXBwYS4=",
            "answer": "Q3VjdW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgaHVtYW4gYmVpbmcgaW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIGZpcmU/",
            "answer": "VnVsY2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBzZXJwZW50IHdoaWNoIGVhdHMgdGhlIHJvb3RzIG9mIHRoZSBhc2ggdHJlZSBZZ2dkcmFzaWw/",
            "answer": "TmlkaG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdyZWVrIGdvZCBQb3NlaWRvbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBIZXJhIGlzIHRoZSBnb2RkZXNzIG9mIGhhcnZlc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCB0cmFkaXRpb25zLCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSB3aWZlIG9mIFpldXM/",
            "answer": "SGVyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "Q2VudGF1cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEphcGFuZXNlIGZvbGtsb3JlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kIG9mIHRoZSBLYXBwYS4=",
            "answer": "Q3VjdW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgaHVtYW4gYmVpbmcgaW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIGZpcmU/",
            "answer": "VnVsY2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVwdHVuZSdzIGdyZWVrIG5hbWUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "UG9zZWlkb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdyZWVrIGdvZCBQb3NlaWRvbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBIZXJhIGlzIHRoZSBnb2RkZXNzIG9mIGhhcnZlc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aW5lPw==",
            "answer": "RGlvbnlzdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIGJsYWNrc21pdGhzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVwaGFlc3R1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "Q2VudGF1cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEphcGFuZXNlIGZvbGtsb3JlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kIG9mIHRoZSBLYXBwYS4=",
            "answer": "Q3VjdW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIGZpcmU/",
            "answer": "VnVsY2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVwdHVuZSdzIGdyZWVrIG5hbWUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "UG9zZWlkb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBzZXJwZW50IHdoaWNoIGVhdHMgdGhlIHJvb3RzIG9mIHRoZSBhc2ggdHJlZSBZZ2dkcmFzaWw/",
            "answer": "TmlkaG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBIZXJhIGlzIHRoZSBnb2RkZXNzIG9mIGhhcnZlc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aW5lPw==",
            "answer": "RGlvbnlzdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIGJsYWNrc21pdGhzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVwaGFlc3R1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "Q2VudGF1cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEphcGFuZXNlIGZvbGtsb3JlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kIG9mIHRoZSBLYXBwYS4=",
            "answer": "Q3VjdW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgaHVtYW4gYmVpbmcgaW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIGZpcmU/",
            "answer": "VnVsY2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVwdHVuZSdzIGdyZWVrIG5hbWUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "UG9zZWlkb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBzZXJwZW50IHdoaWNoIGVhdHMgdGhlIHJvb3RzIG9mIHRoZSBhc2ggdHJlZSBZZ2dkcmFzaWw/",
            "answer": "TmlkaG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGdyZWVrIGdvZCBQb3NlaWRvbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCB0cmFkaXRpb25zLCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSB3aWZlIG9mIFpldXM/",
            "answer": "SGVyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVwdHVuZSdzIGdyZWVrIG5hbWUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "UG9zZWlkb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBzZXJwZW50IHdoaWNoIGVhdHMgdGhlIHJvb3RzIG9mIHRoZSBhc2ggdHJlZSBZZ2dkcmFzaWw/",
            "answer": "TmlkaG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aW5lPw==",
            "answer": "RGlvbnlzdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCB0cmFkaXRpb25zLCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSB3aWZlIG9mIFpldXM/",
            "answer": "SGVyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIGJsYWNrc21pdGhzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVwaGFlc3R1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==",
            "answer": "Q2VudGF1cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpbW1lbnNlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBpcyByZWZlcnJlZCB0byBpbiBOb3JzZSBNeXRob2xvZ3kgYXMgdGhlIFlnZ2RyYXNpbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJlZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEphcGFuZXNlIGZvbGtsb3JlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kIG9mIHRoZSBLYXBwYS4=",
            "answer": "Q3VjdW1iZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgaHVtYW4gYmVpbmcgaW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGFsb3MsIHRoZSBteXRoaWNhbCBnaWFudCBicm9uemUgbWFuLCB3YXMgdGhlIHByb3RlY3RvciBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q3JldGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHB1bmlzaG1lbnQgZm9yIFN5c2lwaHVzJ3MgY3JhZnRpbmVzcz8=",
            "answer": "Q3Vyc2VkIHRvIHJvbGwgYSBib3VsZGVyIHVwIGEgaGlsbCBmb3IgZXRlcm5pdHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEFsZ29ucXVpYW4gZm9sa2xvcmUsIGhvdyBkb2VzIG9uZSB0cmFuc2Zvcm0gaW50byBhIFdlbmRpZ28/",
            "answer": "UGFydGljaXBhdGluZyBpbiBjYW5uaWJhbGlzbS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBnb2QgZnJvbSBHcmVlY2Ugd2hvIGRpZCBub3QgZ2V0IGEgbmFtZSBjaGFuZ2UgaW4gUm9tZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgUm9tYW4gZ29kIG9mIHdhciB3YXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZz8=",
            "answer": "TWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ2ljYWwgZmlndXJlIGlzIHRoZSBnb2QvZ29kZGVzcyBvZiBiYXR0bGUgc3RyYXRlZ3kgKGFtb25nIG90aGVyIHRoaW5ncyku",
            "answer": "QXRoZW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBUaG9yIG9uY2UgZHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIHdvbWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEhpcHBvZ3JpZmYsIG5vdCB0byBiZSBjb25mdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBHcmlmZm9uLCBpcyBhIG1hZ2ljYWwgY3JlYXR1cmUgd2l0aCB0aGUgZnJvbnQgaGFsZiBvZiBhbiBlYWdsZSwgYW5kIHRoZSBiYWNrIGhhbGYgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QSBIb3JzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGluIEdyZWVrIG15dGhvbG9neSwgd2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQXJnb25hdXRzIGluIHNlYXJjaCBvZiB0aGUgR29sZGVuIEZsZWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "SmFzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVyYSBpcyBnb2Qgb2YuLi4=",
            "answer": "TWFycmlhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBNZXNvcG90YW1pYW4gbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBhIGRlaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "RW5raWR1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBHb2RzIGluIEFuY2llbnQgR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "WmV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSBkYXVnaHRlciBvZiBLaW5nIE1pbm9zPw==",
            "answer": "QXJpYWRuZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgWmV1cyBjYW4gY29udHJvbCBsaWdodG5pbmcu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIE5vcnNlIG15dGhvbG9neSwgTG9raSBpcyBhIG1vdGhlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGdvZCBJemFuYWdpIHN1Y2Nlc3NmdWxseSByZXR1cm5lZCBoaXMgd2lmZSBJemFuYW1pIGZyb20gdGhlIFVuZGVyd29ybGQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBzZXJwZW50IHdoaWNoIGVhdHMgdGhlIHJvb3RzIG9mIHRoZSBhc2ggdHJlZSBZZ2dkcmFzaWw/",
            "answer": "TmlkaG9nZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUm9tYW4gZ29kcyBkb2Vzbid0IGhhdmUgYSBjb3VudGVycGFydCBpbiBHcmVlayBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "SmFudXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgJiBSb21hbiBnb2Qgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2YgbXVzaWMsIHRydXRoIGFuZCBwcm9waGVjeSwgaGVhbGluZywgdGhlIHN1biBhbmQgbGlnaHQsIHBsYWd1ZSwgcG9ldHJ5LCBhbmQgbW9yZT8=",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFubmFtYWFyaSB3YXMgYSBzZWEgZGVtb24gdGhhdCBoYXVudGVkIHRoZSBwZW9wbGUgb2YgdGhlIE1hbGRpdmVzIGFuZCBoYWQgdG8gYmUgYXBwZWFzZWQgbW9udGhseSB3aXRoIHRoZSBzYWNyaWZpY2Ugb2YgYSB2aXJnaW4gZ2lybC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgTXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8ga2lsbGVkIEFjaGlsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyaXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmlndXJlIGZyb20gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5IHRyYXZlbGVkIHRvIHRoZSB1bmRlcndvcmxkIHRvIHJldHVybiBoaXMgd2lmZSBFdXJ5ZGljZSB0byB0aGUgbGFuZCBvZiB0aGUgbGl2aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "T3JwaGV1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBnb2QgaW4gTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2d5Lg==",
            "answer": "SmVucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlkaG9nZyBpcyBhIG15dGhpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlIGZyb20gd2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "Tm9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCBIZXJhIGlzIHRoZSBnb2RkZXNzIG9mIGhhcnZlc3Qu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gR3JlZWsgbXl0aG9sb2d5LCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aW5lPw==",
            "answer": "RGlvbnlzdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBnb2Qgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGFuZCBsZXR0dWNlPw==",
            "answer": "TWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBtaW5vdGF1ciBpcyBoYWxmIGh1bWFuIGhhbGYgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gbW9zdCB0cmFkaXRpb25zLCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSB3aWZlIG9mIFpldXM/",
            "answer": "SGVyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIEdyZWVrIE15dGhvbG9neSwgQXRsYXMgd2FzIGFuIE9seW1waWFuIEdvZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIGJsYWNrc21pdGhzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVwaGFlc3R1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBFZ3lwdGlhbiBNeXRoIG9mIE9zaXJpcywgd2hvIG11cmRlcmVkIE9zaXJpcz8=",
            "answer": "U2V0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJvbWFuIGdvZCAiSnVwaXRlciIgd2FzIGZpcnN0IGtub3duIGFzICJaZXVzIiB0byB0aGUgR3JlZWtzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBHcmVlayBGYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmFyY2lzc3Vz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQWZyaWNhbiBteXRob2xvZ3ksIEFuYW5zaSBpcyBhIHRyaWNrc3RlciBhbmQgc3Rvcnl0ZWxsZXIgd2hvIHRha2VzIHRoZSBzaGFwZSBvZiB3aGljaCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "U3BpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hb3JpIGhvbGQgdGhhdCB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgbmF0aW9uIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGJ5IEt1cGUsIHdobyBkaXNjb3ZlcmVkIGl0IHVuZGVyIGEgbG9uZyB3aGl0ZSBjbG91ZD8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSB3eXZlcm4gaXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgYXMgYSBkcmFnb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBteXRvbG9naWNhbCBjcmVhdHVyZXMgaGF2ZSB3b21lbidzIGZhY2VzIGFuZCB2dWx0dXJlcycgYm9kaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGFycGllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmFudXMgd2FzIHRoZSBSb21hbiBnb2Qgb2YgZG9vcndheXMgYW5kIHBhc3NhZ2V3YXlzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBnb2Qgb2Ygd2FyIGluIFBvbHluZXNpYW4gbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "J09ybw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5pa2UgYXBwYXJlbCBhbmQgZm9vdHdlYXIgYnJhbmQgdGFrZXMgaXQncyBuYW1lIGZyb20gdGhlIEdyZWVrIGdvZGRlc3Mgb2Ygd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgR29kIGhhcyBhIGhvcnNlIG5hbWVkIFNsZWlwbmlyPw==",
            "answer": "T2Rpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE5vcnNlIGdvZCBPZGluIGhhcyB0d28gcGV0IGNyb3dzIG5hbWVkICJIdWdpbm4iIGFuZCAiTXVuaW5uIi4gIFdoYXQgZG8gdGhlaXIgbmFtZXMgbWVhbj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvdWdodCAmIE1lbW9yeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmlyc3QgaHVtYW4gYmVpbmcgaW4gTm9yc2UgbXl0aG9sb2d5Pw==",
            "answer": "QXNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZ3JlZWsgZ29kL2dvZGRlc3MgdG9zc2VkIGEgZ29sZGVuIGFwcGxlIHdpdGggdGhlIHdvcmRzICJmb3IgdGhlIGZhaXJlc3QiIGludG8gdGhlIG1pZGRsZSBvZiB0aGUgZmVhc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGdvZHM/",
            "answer": "RXJpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgR3JlZWsgZ29kIG9mIHBlYWNlZnVsIGRlYXRocz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhbmF0b3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGVsIHdhcyB0aGUgZGF1Z2h0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggTm9yc2UgTXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGZpZ3VyZT8=",
            "answer": "TG9raQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYWwgZGlkIFF1ZWVuIFBhc2lwYWhlIHNsZWVwIHdpdGggYmVmb3JlIHNoZSBnYXZlIGJpcnRoIHRvIHRoZSBNaW5vdGF1ciBpbiBHcmVlayBNeXRob2xvZ3k/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGEgbWlub3IgZ29kIHRoYXQgaXMgcHJvdGVjdG9yIGFuZCBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHZhcmlvdXMgYXJ0cywgc3VjaCBhcyBjaGVlc2UgbWFraW5nIGFuZCBiZWUga2VlcGluZy4=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RhZXVz"
        }
    ],
    "U3BvcnRz": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcG9ydHMgaXMgbm90IHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIHRyaWF0aGxvbj8=",
            "answer": "SG9yc2UtUmlkaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gZ29sZiwgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIGdpdmVuIHRvIGEgaG9sZSBzY29yZSBvZiB0d28gdW5kZXIgcGFyPw==",
            "answer": "RWFnbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgb2YgTm9ydGhhbXB0b24gdG93bidzIHJ1Z2J5IHVuaW9uIGNsdWI/",
            "answer": "U2FpbnRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBmb290YmFsbCBjbHViIGhhcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgJ1RoZSBGb3hlcyc/",
            "answer": "TGVpY2VzdGVyIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc29jY2VyIHBsYXllcnMgc2hvdWxkIGJlIG9uIHRoZSBmaWVsZCBhdCB0aGUgc2FtZSB0aW1lPw==",
            "answer": "MjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWFuY2hlc3RlciBVbml0ZWQgd29uIHRoZSAyMDEzLTE0IEVuZ2xpc2ggUHJlbWllciBMZWFndWUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYmFzZWJhbGwsIGhvdyBtYW55IGZvdWxzIGFyZSBhbiBvdXQ/",
            "answer": "MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbmF0aW9uIGhvc3RlZCB0aGUgRklGQSBXb3JsZCBDdXAgaW4gMjAwNj8=",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGV5dG9uIE1hbm5pbmcgcmV0aXJlZCBhZnRlciB3aW5uaW5nIFN1cGVyIEJvd2wgWExJWC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3aWxsIGhvc3QgdGhlIDIwMjAgU3VtbWVyIE9seW1waWNzPw==",
            "answer": "SmFwYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgaG9zdGVkIHRoZSAyMDE4IEZJRkEgV29ybGQgQ3VwPw==",
            "answer": "UnVzc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBob3N0aW5nIHRoZSAyMDIyIEZJRkEgV29ybGQgQ3VwPw==",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpbmFsIHNjb3JlIG9mIHRoZSBHZXJtYW55IHZzLiBCcmF6aWwgMjAxNCBGSUZBIFdvcmxkIEN1cCBtYXRjaD8=",
            "answer": "NyAtIDE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbWFsZSBwbGF5ZXIgd29uIHRoZSBnb2xkIG1lZGFsIG9mIHRhYmxlIHRlbm5pcyBzaW5nbGVzIGluIDIwMTYgT2x5bXBpY3MgR2FtZXM/",
            "answer": "TWEgTG9uZyAoQ2hpbmEp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29jY2VyIHRlYW0gd29uIHRoZSBDb3BhIEFtw6lyaWNhIDIwMTUgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwID8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29jY2VyIHRlYW0gd29uIHRoZSBDb3BhIEFtw6lyaWNhIENlbnRlbmFyaW8gMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcG9pbnRzIGRpZCBMZUJyb24gSmFtZXMgc2NvcmUgaW4gaGlzIGZpcnN0IE5CQSBnYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "MjU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbCB0ZWFtIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNiBlZGl0aW9uIG9mIFVFRkEgRXVyb3BlYW4gQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVnYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybXVsYSBFIGlzIGFuIGF1dG8gcmFjaW5nIHNlcmllcyB0aGF0IHVzZXMgaHlicmlkIGVsZWN0cmljIHJhY2UgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQmFzZWJhbGwsIGhvdyBtYW55IHRpbWVzIGRvZXMgdGhlIGJhbGwgaGF2ZSB0byBiZSBwaXRjaGVkIG91dHNpZGUgb2YgdGhlIHN0cmlrZSB6b25lIGJlZm9yZSB0aGUgYmF0dGVyIGlzIHdhbGtlZD8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2xkZXN0IHRlYW0gaW4gdGhlIE5GTD8=",
            "answer": "QXJpem9uYSBDYXJkaW5hbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZXhhY3QgbGVuZ3RoIG9mIG9uZSBub24tY3VydmVkIHBhcnQgaW4gTGFuZSAxIG9mIGFuIE9seW1waWMgVHJhY2s/",
            "answer": "ODQuMzlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcG9ydHVndWVzZSBpc2xhbmQgaXMgc29jY2VyIHBsYXllciBDcmlzdGlhbm8gUm9uYWxkbyBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkZWlyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUnVnYnkgTGVhZ3VlLCBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgIjQwLTIwIiBpcyBwdW5pc2hlZCBieSBhIGZyZWUga2ljayBmb3IgdGhlIG9wcG9zaW5nIHRlYW0u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2lsdCBDaGFtYmVybGFpbiBzY29yZWQgaGlzIGluZmFtb3VzIDEwMC1wb2ludC1nYW1lIGFnYWluc3QgdGhlIE5ldyBZb3JrIEtuaWNrcyBpbiAxOTYyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBmb290YmFsbGVyICJDcmlzdGlhbm8gUm9uYWxkbyI/",
            "answer": "Q3Jpc3RpYW5vIFJvbmFsZG8gZG9zIFNhbnRvcyBBdmVpcm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBob2NrZXkgbGVnZW5kIFdheW5lIEdyZXR6a3kgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BvcnQgaXMgTk9UIHRyYWRpdGlvbmFsbHkgcGxheWVkIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgTW9uZ29saWFuIE5hYWRhbSBmZXN0aXZhbD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gRm9vdGJhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTkJBIHBsYXllciB3b24gTW9zdCBWYWx1YWJsZSBQbGF5ZXIgZm9yIHRoZSAxOTk5LTIwMDAgc2Vhc29uPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhcXVpbGxlIE8nTmVhbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBzcG9ydCBkb2VzIEZhbm55IENobWVsYXIgY29tcGV0ZSBmb3IgR2VybWFueT8=",
            "answer": "U2tpaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0ZWFtIGRpZCBFbmdsYW5kIGJlYXQgdG8gd2luIGluIHRoZSAxOTY2IFdvcmxkIEN1cCBmaW5hbD8=",
            "answer": "V2VzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0ZWFtIGRpZCBFbmdsYW5kIGJlYXQgaW4gdGhlIHNlbWktZmluYWwgc3RhZ2UgdG8gd2luIGluIHRoZSAxOTY2IFdvcmxkIEN1cCBmaW5hbD8=",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVnYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYm93bGluZywgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGVybSB1c2VkIGZvciBnZXR0aW5nIHRocmVlIGNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHN0cmlrZXM/",
            "answer": "VHVya2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAidGhlIE1hZXN0cm8iIGluIHRoZSBtZW4ncyB0ZW5uaXMgY2lyY3VpdD8=",
            "answer": "Um9nZXIgRmVkZXJlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcHJlbWllciBsZWFndWUgdHJvcGhpZXMgZGlkIFNpciBBbGV4IEZlcmd1c29uIHdpbiBkdXJpbmcgaGlzIHRpbWUgYXQgTWFuY2hlc3RlciBVbml0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGxheWVyICJrdW5nLWZ1IGtpY2tlZCIgYSBDcnlzdGFsIFBhbGFjZSBmYW4gaW4gSmFudWFyeSAxOTk1Pw==",
            "answer": "RXJpYyBDYW50b25h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIE1hbmNoZXN0ZXIgVW5pdGVkJ3MgbGVhZGluZyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIG1ha2VyPw==",
            "answer": "UnlhbiBHaWdncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpZCBTdGV2ZW4gR2VycmFyZCB3aW4gdGhlIENoYW1waW9ucyBMZWFndWUgd2l0aD8=",
            "answer": "TGl2ZXJwb29s"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIExvcyBBbmdlbGVzIERvZGdlcnMgd2VyZSBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGZyb20gd2hhdCBVLlMuIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "QnJvb2tseW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlN0YWRpdW0gb2YgTGlnaHQiIGlzIHRoZSBob21lIHN0YWRpdW0gZm9yIHdoaWNoIHNvY2NlciB0ZWFtPw==",
            "answer": "U3VuZGVybGFuZCBGQw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRm9ybXVsYSAxIGRyaXZlciBzd2l0Y2hlZCB0ZWFtcyBpbiB0aGUgbWlkZGxlIG9mIHRoZSAyMDE3IHNlYXNvbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybG9zIFNhaW56IEpyLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBUaWdlciBXb29kcycgYWxsLXRpbWUgYmVzdCBjYXJlZXIgZ29sZi1zY29yZT8=",
            "answer": "NjE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgVUVGQSBDaGFtcGlvbnMgTGVhZ3VlIGluIDIwMTY/",
            "answer": "UmVhbCBNYWRyaWQgQy5GLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdHdvIHRlYW1zIHBsYXllZCBpbiBTdXBlciBCb3dsIFhMSUk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5ldyBZb3JrIEdpYW50cyAmIFRoZSBOZXcgRW5nbGFuZCBQYXRyaW90cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyDigJxUaGUgU3BvcnQgb2YgS2luZ3PigJ0/",
            "answer": "SG9yc2UgUmFjaW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTkJBIHBsYXllciBoYXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgZ2FtZXMgcGxheWVkIG92ZXIgdGhlIGNvdXJzZSBvZiB0aGVpciBjYXJlZXI/",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IFBhcmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkaWQgS2FiYWRkaSwgYSBjb250YWN0IHNwb3J0IGludm9sdmluZyB0YWNrbGluZywgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FuYWRpYW4gZm9vdGJhbGwsIHNjb3JpbmcgYSByb3VnZSBpcyB3b3J0aCBob3cgbWFueSBwb2ludHM/",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEFITCBhZmZpbGlhdGUgdGVhbSBvZiB0aGUgQm9zdG9uIEJydWlucyBpcyBuYW1lZCB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHJvdmlkZW5jZSBCcnVpbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBmb290YmFsbCB0ZWFtIGlzIG5pY2tuYW1lZCAnVGhlIFRpZ2Vycyc/",
            "answer": "SHVsbCBDaXR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXQgd2hpY2ggYnJpZGdlIGRvZXMgdGhlIGFubnVhbCBPeGZvcmQgYW5kIENhbWJyaWRnZSBib2F0IHJhY2Ugc3RhcnQ/",
            "answer": "UHV0bmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgZGlkIE1hcnRpbmEgTmF2cmF0aWxvdmEgd2luIHRoZSBXaW1ibGVkb24gU2luZ2xlcyBDaGFtcGlvbnNoaXA/",
            "answer": "TmluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0b29sIGxlbmRzIGl0J3MgbmFtZSB0byBhIGxhc3Qtc3RvbmUgYWR2YW50YWdlIGluIGFuIGVuZCBpbiBDdXJsaW5nPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtbWVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjcmlja2V0aW5nIHRlcm0gZGVub3RlcyBhIGJhdHNtYW4gYmVpbmcgZGlzbWlzc2VkIHdpdGggYSBzY29yZSBvZiB6ZXJvPw==",
            "answer": "RHVjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBzcG9ydCBpcyBhICJzaHV0dGxlY29jayIgdXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "QmFkbWludG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzdGltcG1ldGVyIG1lYXN1cmVzIHRoZSBzcGVlZCBvZiBhIGJhbGwgb3ZlciB3aGF0IHN1cmZhY2U/",
            "answer": "R29sZiBQdXR0aW5nIEdyZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRm9ybXVsYSBPbmUgZHJpdmVyIHdhcyBuaWNrbmFtZWQgJ1RoZSBQcm9mZXNzb3InPw==",
            "answer": "QWxhaW4gUHJvc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYSBnYW1lIG9mIHNub29rZXIsIHdoYXQgY29sb3VyIGJhbGwgaXMgd29ydGggMyBwb2ludHM/",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEYxIHNlYXNvbiBvZiAxOTk0IGlzIHJlbWVtYmVyZWQgZm9yIHdoYXQgdHJhZ2ljIGV2ZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "RGVhdGggb2YgQXlydG9uIFNlbm5hIChTYW4gTWFyaW5vKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciB3b24gdGhlIDIwMTYgMjQgSG91cnMgb2YgTGUgTWFucz8=",
            "answer": "UG9yc2NoZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSXRhbGlhbiBmb290YmFsbGVyIHRvbGQgTmV1ZXIgd2hlcmUgaGUncyBwdXR0aW5nIGhpcyBzaG90IGFuZCBkcmFnZ2luZyBpdCB3aWRlLCBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIG1hdGNoIEl0YWx5LUdlcm1hbnksIFVFRkEgRVVSTyAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "UGVsbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNiBGb3JtdWxhIDEgV29ybGQgRHJpdmVyJ3MgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "TmljbyBSb3NiZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2xkZXN0IHRlYW0gaW4gTWFqb3IgTGVhZ3VlIEJhc2ViYWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSBCcmF2ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRm9ybXVsYSAxLCB0aGUgVmlydHVhbCBTYWZldHkgQ2FyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGZvbGxvd2luZyB0aGUgZmF0YWwgY3Jhc2ggb2Ygd2hpY2ggZHJpdmVyPw==",
            "answer": "SnVsZXMgQmlhbmNoaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBHcmFuZCBTbGFtIHRlbm5pcyB0b3VybmFtZW50cyBvY2N1cnMgTEFTVD8=",
            "answer": "VVMgT3Blbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgTmV3IE9ybGVhbnMgU2FpbnRzIHdpbiB0aGUgU3VwZXIgQm93bD8=",
            "answer": "MjAxMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhpcyBDYW5hZGlhbiB0ZWxldmlzaW9uIHNwb3J0c2Nhc3RlciBpcyBrbm93biBmb3IgaGlzICJIb2NrZXkgTmlnaHQgaW4gQ2FuYWRhIiByb2xlLCBhIGNvbW1lbnRhcnkgc2hvdyBkdXJpbmcgaG9ja2V5IGdhbWVzLg==",
            "answer": "RG9uIENoZXJyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwaXRjaGVycyB3YXMgbmFtZWQgTmF0aW9uYWwgTGVhZ3VlIFJvb2tpZSBvZiB0aGUgWWVhciBmb3IgdGhlIDIwMTMgc2Vhc29uPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9zZSBGZXJuYW5kZXo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIFdpbWJsZWRvbiwgc3BlY3RhdG9ycyBpbiB0aGUgZ3JvdW5kcyBjYW4gYnV5IHRoZSB0ZW5uaXMgYmFsbHMgdGhhdCBoYXZlIGJlZW4gdXNlZCBpbiBtYXRjaGVzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb21tb24gdHlwZSBvZiBwaXRjaCB0aHJvd24gYnkgcGl0Y2hlcnMgaW4gYmFzZWJhbGw/",
            "answer": "RmFzdGJhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgRnJlbmNoIE9wZW4ncyBkaWQgQmrDtnJuIEJvcmcgd2luPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGxheWVyIGhvbGRzIHRoZSBOSEwgcmVjb3JkIG9mIDIsODU3IHBvaW50cz8=",
            "answer": "V2F5bmUgR3JldHpreQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBmZWF0dXJlcyBhbGwgb2YgdGhlaXIgcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsIHNwb3J0cyB0ZWFtcycgamVyc2V5J3Mgd2l0aCB0aGUgc2FtZSBjb2xvciBzY2hlbWU/",
            "answer": "UGl0dHNidXJnaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBNYW5jaGVzdGVyIFVuaXRlZCdzIGhvbWUgc3RhZGl1bT8=",
            "answer": "T2xkIFRyYWZmb3Jk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIE1hbmNoZXN0ZXIgVW5pdGVkJ3MgdG9wIHByZW1pZXIgbGVhZ3VlIGdvYWwgc2NvcmVyPw==",
            "answer": "V2F5bmUgUm9vbmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIGEgdG90YWwgb2YgMjAgcmFjZXMgaW4gRm9ybXVsYSBPbmUgMjAxNiBzZWFzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgSmVuc29uIEJ1dHRvbiB3b24gaGlzIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgRm9ybXVsYSBPbmUgV29ybGQgRHJpdmVycycgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdG9wc2NvcmVyIGZvciBFbmdsYW5kIG5hdGlvbmFsIGZvb3RiYWxsIHRlYW0/",
            "answer": "V2F5bmUgUm9vbmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBGb3JtdWxhIE9uZSBXb3JsZCBEcml2ZXJzJyBDaGFtcGlvbnNoaXA/",
            "answer": "TGV3aXMgSGFtaWx0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgVUVGQSBDaGFtcGlvbnMgTGVhZ3VlIGluIDIwMTc/",
            "answer": "UmVhbCBNYWRyaWQgQy5GLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGhvc3RlZCB0aGUgMjAxNCBXaW50ZXIgT2x5bXBpY3M/",
            "answer": "UnVzc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgUnVzc2lhbiBjaXRpZXMgZGlkIE5PVCBjb250YWluIGEgc3RhZGl1bSB0aGF0IHdhcyB1c2VkIGluIHRoZSAyMDE4IEZJRkEgV29ybGQgQ3VwPw==",
            "answer": "VmxhZGl2b3N0b2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxOCBNb25hY28gR3JhbmQgUHJpeD8=",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIFJpY2NpYXJkbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIHNwb3J0c3dlYXIgY29tcGFueSdzIGxvZ28gaXMgdGhlICdGb3Jtc3RyaXBlJz8=",
            "answer": "UHVtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdGVhbXMgaXNuJ3QgYSBtZW1iZXIgb2YgdGhlIE5ITCdzICJPcmlnaW5hbCBTaXgiIGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "UGhpbGFkZWxwaGlhIEZseWVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc2NvcmluZyB6b25lcyBhcmUgdGhlcmUgb24gYSBjb252ZW50aW9uYWwgZGFydCBib2FyZD8=",
            "answer": "ODI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2l0aCB3aGljaCBkb3VibGVzIHBhcnRuZXIgZGlkIEpvaG4gTWNFbnJvZSBoYXZlIG1vc3Qgc3VjY2Vzcz8=",
            "answer": "UGV0ZXIgRmxlbWluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFJpbyAyMDE2IFN1bW1lciBPbHltcGljcyBoZWxkIGl0J3MgY2xvc2luZyBjZXJlbW9ueSBvbiB3aGF0IGRhdGU/",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0IDIx"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2thdGVib2FyZGluZyB3aWxsIGJlIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSAyMDIwIFN1bW1lciBPbHltcGljcyBpbiBUb2t5by4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3YXMgdGhlIDIwMTUtMjAxNiBOQkEgQ2hhbXBpb25zPw==",
            "answer": "Q2xldmVsYW5kIENhdmFsaWVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIHRoZSBHYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgWFhJSSBPbHltcGlhZCBoZWxkPw==",
            "answer": "TW9zY293"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Um9nZXIgRmVkZXJlciBpcyBhIGZhbW91cyBzb2NjZXIgcGxheWVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgd2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgRm9ybXVsYSAxIFdvcmxkIENvbnN0cnVjdG9yJ3MgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwIGZvciB0aGUgdGhpcmQgdGltZSBpbiBhIHJvdz8=",
            "answer": "TWVyY2VkZXMtQU1HIFBldHJvbmFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSBoYXMgd29uIHRoZSBtb3N0IFN0YW5sZXkgQ3VwcyBpbiB0aGUgTkhMPw==",
            "answer": "TW9udHJlYWwgQ2FuYWRpYW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2h5IHdhcyBUaGUgR3JlZW4gTW9uc3RlciBhdCBGZW53YXkgUGFyayB3YXMgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBidWlsdD8=",
            "answer": "VG8gcHJldmVudCB2aWV3aW5nIGdhbWVzIGZyb20gb3V0c2lkZSB0aGUgcGFyay4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYm94ZXIgd2FzIGJhbm5lZCBmb3IgdGFraW5nIGEgYml0ZSBvdXQgb2YgRXZhbmRlciBIb2x5ZmllbGQncyBlYXIgaW4gMTk5Nz8=",
            "answer": "TWlrZSBUeXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QVRQIHRlbm5pcyBob3N0ZWQgc2V2ZXJhbCB0b3VybmFtZW50cyBvbiBjYXJwZXQgY291cnQgYmVmb3JlIGJlaW5nIHJlcGxhY2VkIHRvIHJlZHVjZSBpbmp1cmllcy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgcHJlbWllciBsZWFndWUgdGl0bGUgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTUtMjAxNiBzZWFzb24gZm9sbG93aW5nIGEgZmFpcnkgdGFsZSBydW4/",
            "answer": "TGVpY2VzdGVyIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwbGF5ZXIgc2NvcmVkIGEgaGF0LXRyaWNrIGR1cmluZyB0aGVpciBNYW5jaGVzdGVyIFVuaXRlZCBkZWJ1dD8=",
            "answer": "V2F5bmUgUm9vbmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3aWxsIGhvc3QgdGhlIDIwMjIgRklGQSBXb3JsZCBDdXA/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFza2V0YmFsbCB0ZWFtIGhhcyBhdHRlbmRlZCB0aGUgbW9zdCBOQkEgZ3JhbmQgZmluYWxzPw==",
            "answer": "TG9zIEFuZ2VsZXMgTGFrZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2l0aCB3aGljaCB0ZWFtIGRpZCBNaWNoYWVsIFNjaHVtYWNoZXIgbWFrZSBoaXMgRm9ybXVsYSBPbmUgZGVidXQgYXQgdGhlIDE5OTEgQmVsZ2lhbiBHcmFuZCBQcml4Pw==",
            "answer": "Sm9yZGFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U29jY2VyIHBsYXllciBDcmlzdGlhbm8gUm9uYWxkbyBvcGVuZWQgYSBtdXNldW0gZGVkaWNhdGVkIHRvIGhpbXNlbGYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBiZWx0IHlvdSBjYW4gZ2V0IGluIFRhZWt3b25kbz8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNSBGb3JtdWxhIDEgV29ybGQgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "TGV3aXMgSGFtaWx0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGNvbXBhbnkgaXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgSmFwYW5lc2UgY29tcGFueSB3aGljaCB3b24gdGhlIDI0IEhvdXJzIG9mIExlIE1hbnM/",
            "answer": "TWF6ZGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE9seW1waWNzIHRlbm5pcyBjb3VydCBpcyBhIGdpYW50IGdyZWVuIHNjcmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0ZWFtIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNiBNTFMgQ3VwPw==",
            "answer": "U2VhdHRsZSBTb3VuZGVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAwOCwgVXNhaW4gQm9sdCBzZXQgdGhlIHdvcmxkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgdGhlIDEwMCBtZXRlcnMgd2l0aCBvbmUgc2hvZWxhY2UgdW50aWVkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTQgRklGQSBXb3JsZCBDdXAsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBmaW5hbCBzY29yZSBpbiB0aGUgbWF0Y2ggQnJhemlsIC0gR2VybWFueT8=",
            "answer": "MS03"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxMSBTdGFubGV5IEN1cD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9zdG9uIEJydWlucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hemRhIDc4N0Igd29uIHRoZSAyNCBIb3VycyBvZiBMZSBNYW5zIGluIHdoYXQgeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk5MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzJyBuYXRpb25hbCB0ZWFtcyBxdWFsaWZpZWQgZm9yIHRoZSAyMDE4IEZJRkEgV29ybGQgQ3VwIGluIFJ1c3NpYT8=",
            "answer": "VHVuaXNpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGVubmlzIHdhcyBvbmNlIGtub3duIGFzIFJhY3F1ZXRiYWxsLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9zaCBNYW5zb3VyIGlzIHBhcnQgb2Ygd2hhdCBOUkwgdGVhbT8=",
            "answer": "UGVucml0aCBQYW50aGVycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3b24gMjAxNCBGSUZBIFdvcmxkIEN1cCBpbiBCcmF6aWw/",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBkaWQgdGhlIGZvcm1lciBOSEwgdGVhbSAiVGhlIE5vcmRpcXVlcyIgb3JpZ2luaWF0ZSBmcm9tPw==",
            "answer": "UXVlYmVjIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gYXNzb2NpYXRpb24gZm9vdGJhbGwsIG9yIHNvY2NlciwgYSBjb3JuZXIga2ljayBpcyB3aGVuIHRoZSBnYW1lIHJlc3RhcnRzIGFmdGVyIHNvbWVvbmUgc2NvcmVzIGEgZ29hbC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgdGhlIHRoaXJkIFN1cGVyIEJvd2wgaGVsZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk2OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdG9wIHNjb3JlciBvZiB0aGUgMjAxNCBGSUZBIFdvcmxkIEN1cD8=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgUm9kcsOtZ3Vleg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3b24gdGhlIDIwMTUtMTYgRW5nbGlzaCBQcmVtaWVyIExlYWd1ZT8=",
            "answer": "TGVpY2VzdGVyIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3YXMgdGhlIDIwMTQtMjAxNSBOQkEgQ2hhbXBpb25zPw==",
            "answer": "R29sZGVuIFN0YXRlIFdhcnJpb3Jz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgIkNoYW1waW9ucyBMZWFndWUiIGluIDE5OTk/",
            "answer": "TWFuY2hlc3RlciBVbml0ZWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG9mZmljaWFsIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgZ2FtZSBwbGF5ZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTg3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQWZyaWNhbiBBbWVyaWNhbiBpcyBpbiBwYXJ0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBpbnRlZ3JhdGluZyAgTWFqb3IgTGVhZ3VlIGJhc2ViYWxsPw==",
            "answer": "SmFja2llIFJvYmluc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBwcm9mZXNzaW9uYWwgd3Jlc3RsZXIgU2hpcmxleSBDcmFidHJlZSBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM/",
            "answer": "QmlnIERhZGR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZHJpdmVyIGhhcyBiZWVuIHRoZSBGb3JtdWxhIDEgd29ybGQgY2hhbXBpb24gZm9yIGEgcmVjb3JkIDcgdGltZXM/",
            "answer": "TWljaGFlbCBTY2h1bWFjaGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciB3b24gdGhlIDIwMTcgMjQgSG91cnMgb2YgTGUgTWFucz8=",
            "answer": "UG9yc2NoZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsIHdyZXN0bGVyIGZlbGwgZnJvbSB0aGUgcmFmdGVycyB0byBoaXMgZGVhdGggZHVyaW5nIGEgbGl2ZSBQYXktUGVyLVZpZXcgZXZlbnQgaW4gMTk5OT8=",
            "answer": "T3dlbiBIYXJ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQUhMIGFmZmlsaWF0ZSBvZiB0aGUgVG9yb250byBNYXBsZSBMZWFmcz8=",
            "answer": "VG9yb250byBNYXJsaWVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmVtYWxlIHBsYXllciB3b24gdGhlIGdvbGQgbWVkYWwgb2YgdGFibGUgdGVubmlzIHNpbmdsZXMgaW4gMjAxNiBPbHltcGljcyBHYW1lcz8=",
            "answer": "RElORyBOaW5nIChDaGluYSk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNSBDb2xsZWdlIEZvb3RiYWxsIFBsYXlvZmYgKENGUCkgTmF0aW9uYWwgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPyA=",
            "answer": "T2hpbyBTdGF0ZSBCdWNrZXllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEZDIFNjaGFsa2UgMDQgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwNA=="
        }
    ],
    "R2VvZ3JhcGh5": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBvZiBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "V2FzaGluZ3RvbiBELkM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY2l0eSwgaXMgdGhlIEJpZyBOaWNrZWwgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "U3VkYnVyeSwgT250YXJpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzICJkb3VibHkgbGFuZGxvY2tlZCIgKHN1cnJvdW5kZWQgZW50aXJlbHkgYnkgb25lIG9yIG1vcmUgbGFuZGxvY2tlZCBjb3VudHJpZXMpPw==",
            "answer": "VXpiZWtpc3Rhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGFuIEF1c3RyYWxpYW4gc3RhdGUgb3IgdGVycml0b3J5Pw==",
            "answer": "QWxiZXJ0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBBdXN0cmFsaWE/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYmVycmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBEZW5tYXJrPw==",
            "answer": "Q29wZW5oYWdlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUnVzc2lhbiBvYmxhc3QgZm9ybXMgYSBib3JkZXIgd2l0aCBQb2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "S2FsaW5pbmdyYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBzdGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyB0aGF0IGRvZXMgbm90IGhhdmUgYSBmbGFnIGluIGEgc2hhcGUgd2l0aCA0IGVkZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "T2hpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgZG9lcyBOT1QgcmVjb2duaXplIEFybWVuaWEgYXMgYW4gaW5kZXBlbmRlbnQgY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "UGFraXN0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgYmFubmVkIHRoZSB1c2Ugb2YgcGVyc29uYWwgZ2VuZXRpYyBhbmNlc3RyeSB0ZXN0cz8=",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgY291bnRyaWVzIGhhdmUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgY2xhaW1zIHRvIHRlcnJpdG9yeSBpbiBBbnRhcnRpY2EgRVhDRVBUOg==",
            "answer": "VW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBBZnJpY2FuIGNvdW50cnkgaGFzIFBvcnR1Z3Vlc2UgYXMgaXRzIG9mZmljaWFsIGxhbmd1YWdlPw==",
            "answer": "TW96YW1iaXF1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbmF0aW9uIGNsYWltcyBvd25lcnNoaXAgb2YgQW50YXJjdGljYT8=",
            "answer": "Tm8gb25lLCBidXQgdGhlcmUgYXJlIGNsYWltcy4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIHdhcyBoaXN0b3JpY2FsbHkgdXNlZCBmb3IgdGhlIFR1cmtpc2ggY2l0eSBjdXJyZW50bHkga25vd24gYXMgSXN0YW5idWw/",
            "answer": "Q29uc3RhbnRpbm9wbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2licmFsdGFyLCBsb2NhdGVkIGp1c3Qgc291dGggb2YgdGhlIEliZXJpYW4gcGVuaW5zdWxhLCBpcyBhIHRlcnJpdG9yeSBvZiB3aGljaCBXZXN0IEV1cm9wZSBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "VW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBsYWtlIGluIHRoZSBBZnJpY2FuIGNvbnRpbmVudD8=",
            "answer": "TGFrZSBWaWN0b3JpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3R0YXdhIGlzIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsIG9mIENhbmFkYS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGRvZXMgU3BhaW4gaGF2ZSBhIGxhbmQgYm9yZGVyIHdpdGg/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgZnJlc2h3YXRlciBsYWtlIGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "TGFrZSBTdXBlcmlvciA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Ik1vbmdvbGlhIiB3YXMgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBub3cgbm9uLWV4aXN0ZW50IFUuUy5TLlIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgQ2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "V2FzaGluZ3RvbiwgRC5DLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlIGZhc3QgZm9vZCBjaGFpbiAiUGFuZGEgRXhwcmVzcyIgaGVhZHF1YXJ0ZXJlZD8=",
            "answer": "Um9zZW1lYWQsIENhbGlmb3JuaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQWZyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJpZXMgbGlzdCAiU3BhbmlzaCIgYXMgYW4gb2ZmaWNpYWwgbGFuZ3VhZ2U/",
            "answer": "RXF1YXRvcmlhbCBHdWluZWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGxhbmZhaXLCrXB3bGxnd3luZ3lsbMKtZ29nZXJ5wq1jaHd5cm7CrWRyb2J3bGzCrWxsYW7CrXR5c2lsaW/CrWdvZ2/CrWdvY2ggaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBvbiB3aGljaCBXZWxzaCBpc2xhbmQ/",
            "answer": "QW5nbGVzZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG9yb250byBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBjaXR5IG9mIHRoZSBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJ5IG9mIENhbmFkYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXJlYSBvZiBWYXRpY2FuIENpdHk/",
            "answer": "MC40NGttXjI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgdGhlIFVTIFN0YXRlIE9oaW8gaXMgdGhlIGNpdHkgb2YgQ2hpbGxpY290aGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QW50YXJjdGljYSBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBkZXNlcnQgaW4gdGhlIHdvcmxkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3Mgb2xkZXN0IHN0aWxsIG9wZXJhdGlvbmFsIHNwYWNlIGxhdW5jaCBmYWNpbGl0eSBsb2NhdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "S2F6YWtoc3Rhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgVVMgU3RhdGUgb2YgTmV3IFlvcms/",
            "answer": "QWxiYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgY291bnRyeSBpbiBTb3V0aCBBbWVyaWNhIGJ5IGFyZWE/",
            "answer": "U3VyaW5hbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBNdXNsaW0gY291bnRyeSBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiByb2NreSByZWdpb24gdGhhdCBzcGFucyBtb3N0IG9mIGVhc3Rlcm4gQ2FuYWRhPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRpYW4gU2hpZWxk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgUG9saXNoIGNpdHkga25vd24gdG8gR2VybWFucyBhcyBEYW56aWc/",
            "answer": "R2RhxYRzaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNvdW50cmllcyBib3JkZXJzIHdpdGggUG9sYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "TGl0aHVhbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBKYXBhbmVzZSBpc2xhbmRzIGlzIHRoZSBiaWdnZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "SG9uc2h1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBCZWxhcnVzPw==",
            "answer": "TWluc2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTYgR2xvYmFsIFBlYWNlIEluZGV4IHBvbGwsIG91dCBvZiAxNjMgY291bnRyaWVzLCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBvZiBBbWVyaWNhIHJhbmtlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTAz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBjaXR5IG9mIEJlcm11ZGE/",
            "answer": "SGFtaWx0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb250aW5lbnQgaXMgdGhlIGNvdW50cnkgTGVzb3RobyBpbj8=",
            "answer": "QWZyaWNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHR3byBsYXJnZXN0IGV0aG5pYyBncm91cHMgb2YgQmVsZ2l1bSBhcmUgRmxlbWlzaCBhbmQgV2FsbG9vbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBjYXBpdGFsIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "U3lkbmV5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEFscHMgYXJlIGEgbW91bnRhaW4gcmFuZ2Ugb24gd2hpY2ggY29udGluZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "RXVyb3Bl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGVtYmxlbSBvbiB0aGUgZmxhZyBvZiB0aGUgUmVwdWJsaWMgb2YgVGFqaWtpc3RhbiBmZWF0dXJlcyBhIHN1bnJpc2Ugb3ZlciBtb3VudGFpbnMgYmVsb3cgd2hhdCBzeW1ib2w/",
            "answer": "Q3Jvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgaXMgYW4gaXNsYW5kIGluIEphcGFuIGNhbGxlZCDFjGt1bm9zaGltYSwgQS5LLkEuICJSYWJiaXQgSXNsYW5kIiwgc28gbmFtZWQgYmVjYXVzZSBvZiBpdCdzIGh1Z2UgcG9wdWxhdGlvbiBvZiByYWJiaXRzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhdGVzIGFyZSBpbiBBdXN0cmFsaWE/",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFB5cmVuZWVzIG1vdW50YWlucyBhcmUgbG9jYXRlZCBvbiB0aGUgYm9yZGVyIG9mIHdoaWNoIHR3byBjb3VudHJpZXM/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNlIGFuZCBTcGFpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SXMgVGFydHUgdGhlIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgRXN0b25pYT8=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBmcmVzaHdhdGVyIGxha2UgYnkgdm9sdW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFrZSBCYWlrYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBjb3VudHJ5IGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZCA/",
            "answer": "UnVzc2lhbiBGZWRlcmF0aW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBjaXR5IGFuZCBjb21tZXJjaWFsIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgU3JpIExhbmthPw==",
            "answer": "Q29sb21ibw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFByaW5jaXBhbGl0eSBvZiBTZWFsYW5kIGlzIGFuIHVucmVjb2duaXplZCBtaWNyb25hdGlvbiBvZmYgdGhlIGNvYXN0IG9mIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBub24tY29udGluZW50YWwgaXNsYW5kIGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "R3JlZW5sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXNsYW5kIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHRoZSBDYXJpYmJlYW4/",
            "answer": "QmFyYmFkb3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN1cmZhY2UgYXJlYSBvZiBSdXNzaWEgaXMgc2xpZ2h0bHkgbGFyZ2VyIHRoYW4gdGhhdCBvZiB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IFBsdXRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIG5vIHJvYWRzIGluL291dCBvZiBKdW5lYXUsIEFsYXNrYS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2FuIE1hcmlubyBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBjb3VudHJ5IGNvbXBsZXRlbHkgc3Vycm91bmRlZCBieSBhbm90aGVyIGNvdW50cnku",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBjb3VudHkgaXMgU3RvbmVoZW5nZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsdHNoaXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBjb21wbGV0ZWx5IGxhbmRsb2NrZWQgYnkgU291dGggQWZyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "TGVzb3Robw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhbmQgb2YgR290bGFuZCBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIEV1cm9wZWFuIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "U3dlZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzIGxvY2F0ZWQgdGhlIEZVUlRIRVNUIGF3YXkgZnJvbSB0aGUgU291dGggQ2hpbmEgU2VhPw==",
            "answer": "QmFuZ2xhZGVzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFNvdXRoZWFzdCBBc2lhbiBpc2xhbmQgb2YgQm9ybmVvIGlzIHBvbGl0aWNhbGx5IGRpdmlkZWQgYW1vbmcgMyBjb3VudHJpZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGFuIGlzbGFuZCB0aGF0IGlzIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIFBoaWxpcHBpbmVzPw==",
            "answer": "SmF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGRvZXMgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgc2hhcmUgYSBsYW5kIGJvcmRlciB3aXRoPw==",
            "answer": "Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugb2YgQ29zdGEgUmljYT8=",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmFiIGNvdW50cmllcyBkb2VzIE5PVCBoYXZlIGEgZmxhZyBjb250YWluaW5nIG9ubHkgUGFuLUFyYWIgY29sb3Vycz8=",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGhhcyBhIGhvcml6b250YWwgYmljb2xvciByZWQgYW5kIHdoaXRlIGZsYWc/",
            "answer": "TW9uYWNv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R290aGVuYnVyZyBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTd2VkZW4u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFNvbm9yYW4gRGVzZXJ0IGlzIGxvY2F0ZWQgaW4gZWFzdGVybiBBZnJpY2Eu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3QuIExvdWlzIGlzIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBTdGF0ZSBNaXNzb3VyaS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0aW55IHByaW5jaXBhbGl0eSBsaWVzIGJldHdlZW4gU3BhaW4gYW5kIEZyYW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "QW5kb3JyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FsaWZvcm5pYSBpcyBsYXJnZXIgdGhhbiBKYXBhbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyB0aGUgaG9tZSBvZiB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBKYXBhbmVzZSBwb3B1bGF0aW9uIG91dHNpZGUgb2YgSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "QnJhemls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBDYW5hZGEncyBzbWFsbGVzdCBwcm92aW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "UHJpbmNlIEVkd2FyZCBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGRvZXMgTWV4aWNvIGJvcmRlcj8=",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTZXljaGVsbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZCdzIGluZGlnZW5vdXMgcGVvcGxlPw==",
            "answer": "TWFvcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBJbmRpYT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IERlbGhp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzIHRoZSBzbWFsbGVzdCBieSBwb3B1bGF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Tm9yd2F5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBtb3VudGFpbiBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "TXQuIEV2ZXJlc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2NlYW4gYm9yZGVycyB0aGUgd2VzdCBjb2FzdCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "UGFjaWZpYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q29sY2hlc3RlciBPdmVycGFzcywgb3RoZXJ3aXNlIGtub3duIGFzICJCdW5ueSBNYW4gQnJpZGdlIiwgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCB3aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "RmFpcmZheCBDb3VudHksIFZpcmdpbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb21tb24gY2xpbWJpbmcgcm91dGUgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgaGlnaGVzdCBtb3VudGFpbiBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQsIEsyPw==",
            "answer": "QWJydXp6aSBTcHVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBMaXRodWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "Vmlsbml1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW50byB3aGljaCBiYXNpbiBkb2VzIHRoZSBKb3JkYW4gUml2ZXIgZmxvdyBpbnRvPw==",
            "answer": "RGVhZCBTZWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBjb3VudHkgd2lsbCB5b3UgZmluZCB0aGUgVW5pdmVyc2l0eSBvZiBFYXN0IEFuZ2xpYT8=",
            "answer": "Tm9yZm9saw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UmhvZGUgSXNsYW5kIGlzIGFjdHVhbGx5IGxvY2F0ZWQgb24gdGhlIFVTIG1haW5sYW5kLCBkZXNwaXRlIGl0cyBuYW1lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmF0aW9uYWwgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugb2YgUGFraXN0YW4/",
            "answer": "VXJkdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIE1hbHVrdSBpc2xhbmRzIChpbmZvcm1hbGx5IGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBTcGljZSBJc2xhbmRzKSBiZWxvbmcgdG8gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb3VudGFpbiByYW5nZSBsaW5lcyB0aGUgYm9yZGVyIGJldHdlZW4gU3BhaW4gYW5kIEZyYW5jZT8=",
            "answer": "UHlyZW5lZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgSmFwYW5lc2UgaXNsYW5kcyBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBieSBhcmVhPw==",
            "answer": "U2hpa29rdQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T25seSBvbmUgY291bnRyeSBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQgc3RhcnRzIHdpdGggdGhlIGxldHRlciBRLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R3JlZW5sYW5kIGlzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBraW5nZG9tPw==",
            "answer": "RGVubWFyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgbGFyZ2VzdCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQgYnkgYXJlYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2VvdWwgaXMgdGhlIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgTm9ydGggS29yZWEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZsYWcgb2YgU291dGggQWZyaWNhIGZlYXR1cmVzIDcgY29sb3Vycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2l0eSBpbiBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWE/",
            "answer": "RHViYWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SXNyYWVsIGlzIDcgaG91cnMgYWhlYWQgb2YgTmV3IFlvcmsu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGRlcmlzaXZlIGFjcm9ueW0gIlBJSUdTIiByZWZlcnMgdG8gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBFdXJvcGVhbiBjb3VudHJpZXMgYW5kIHRoZWlyIGVjb25vbWljIHN0YXR1c2VzPw==",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVnYWwsIElyZWxhbmQsIEl0YWx5LCBHcmVlY2UsIFNwYWlu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSBsYXJnZXIgdGhhbiBBdXN0cmFsaWE/",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBldmVudCBsZWQgdG8gTGllY2hlbnN0ZWluIGFkZGluZyBhIGNyb3duIHRvIGl0cyBmbGFnPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIDE5MzYgT2x5bXBpY3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEh1bnVhIFJhbmdlcyBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluLi4u",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "WW91IGNvdWxkIHdhbGsgZnJvbSBOb3J3YXkgdG8gTm9ydGggS29yZWEgd2hpbGUgb25seSBwYXNzaW5nIHRocm91Z2ggUnVzc2lhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgT25lIFdvcmxkIFRyYWRlIENlbnRlciBpbiBOZXcgWW9yayBDaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "MSw3NzYgZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TGllY2h0ZW5zdGVpbiBkb2VzIG5vdCBoYXZlIGFuIGFpcnBvcnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgRmlubmlzaCB3b3JkIGZvciAiRmlubGFuZCI/",
            "answer": "U3VvbWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhbiB0b3VyaXN0IGF0dHJhY3Rpb24gaXMgc2VydmVkIGJ5IHRoZSAiTWFpZCBvZiB0aGUgTWlzdCIgdG91ciBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "TmlhZ2FyYSBGYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhcnMgYXJlIGZlYXR1cmVkIG9uIE5ldyBaZWFsYW5kJ3MgZmxhZz8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG9reW8gaXMgdGhlIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgSmFwYW4u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG1vc3QgcG9wdWxvdXMgY2l0eSBpbiB0aGUgQW1lcmljYXMgaW4gMjAxNT8=",
            "answer": "U8OjbyBQYXVsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFuZCBjb25uZWN0aW5nIE5vcnRoIEFtZXJpY2EgYW5kIFNvdXRoIEFtZXJpY2E/",
            "answer": "SXN0aG11cyBvZiBQYW5hbWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyBUYWxsaW5uIGxvY2F0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "RXN0b25pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdCByaXZlciBpbiBFdXJvcGU/",
            "answer": "Vm9sZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTb3V0aCBLb3JlYT8=",
            "answer": "U2VvdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tm92YSBTY290aWEgaXMgb24gdGhlIGVhc3QgY29hc3Qgb2YgQ2FuYWRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgTk9UIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "Um9tYW5pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIHNoYXJlIGEgbGFuZCBib3JkZXIgd2l0aCBMdXhlbWJvdXJnPw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBjb3VudHkgaXMgdGhlIGNpdHkgb2YgUG9ydHNtb3V0aD8=",
            "answer": "SGFtcHNoaXJl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbCBtdXNldW0gd2lsbCB5b3UgZmluZCBpbiBDb29wZXJzdG93biwgTmV3IFlvcms/",
            "answer": "TmF0aW9uYWwgQmFzZWJhbGwgSGFsbCBvZiBGYW1l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcHJvdmluY2VzIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgTmV0aGVybGFuZHM/",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgSGFkcmlhbidzIFdhbGwgbG9jYXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2FybGlzbGUsIEVuZ2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmlyIFRhd2lsLCBhbiB1bmluaGFiaXRlZCB0cmFjayBvZiBsYW5kIGNsYWltZWQgYnkgbm8gY291bnRyeSwgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBhbG9uZyB0aGUgYm9yZGVyIG9mIHdoaWNoIHR3byBjb3VudHJpZXM/",
            "answer": "RWd5cHQgYW5kIFN1ZGFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgbm90IGEgY291bnRyeSBpbiBBZnJpY2E/",
            "answer": "R3V5YW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBtZWdhZGl2ZXJzZSBjb3VudHJ5IC0gb25lIHRoYXQgaGFyYm9ycyBhIGhpZ2ggbnVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBlYXJ0aCdzIGVuZGVtaWMgc3BlY2llcz8=",
            "answer": "VGhhaWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdHdvIG1vZGVybi1kYXkgY291bnRyaWVzIHVzZWQgdG8gYmUga25vd24gYXMgdGhlIHJlZ2lvbiBvZiBSaG9kZXNpYSBiZXR3ZWVuIHRoZSAxODkwcyBhbmQgMTk4MD8=",
            "answer": "WmFtYmlhICYgWmltYmFid2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3RhdGUgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgaXMgdGhlIHNtYWxsZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "UmhvZGUgSXNsYW5kIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGJvZHkgb2YgdGhlIEVneXB0aWFuIFNwaGlueCB3YXMgYmFzZWQgb24gd2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "TGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TW9udHJlYWwgaXMgaW4gd2hpY2ggQ2FuYWRpYW4gcHJvdmluY2U/",
            "answer": "UXVlYmVj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBjb3VudHJ5IGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZCB3aXRoIGEgZmxhZyB0aGF0IGRvZXNuJ3QgaGF2ZSBmb3VyIHJpZ2h0IGFuZ2xlcz8=",
            "answer": "TmVwYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSBpbnNpZGUgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tPw==",
            "answer": "Rm91cg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTd2l0emVybGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "QmVybg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmF0aWNhbiBDaXR5IGlzIGEgY291bnRyeS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRXVyb3BlYW4gY2l0eSBoYXMgdGhlIGhpZ2hlc3QgbWlsZWFnZSBvZiBjYW5hbHMgaW4gdGhlIHdvcmxkPw==",
            "answer": "QmlybWluZ2hhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBUdXJrZXk/",
            "answer": "QW5rYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWYgc29jY2VyIGlzIGNhbGxlZCBmb290YmFsbCBpbiBFbmdsYW5kLCB3aGF0IGlzIEFtZXJpY2FuIGZvb3RiYWxsIGNhbGxlZCBpbiBFbmdsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gZm9vdGJhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYXJlIHRvd25zL3ZpbGxhZ2VzIGluIHRoZSBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZCBuYXRpb24gb2YgS2lyaWJhdGkgRVhDRVBUOg==",
            "answer": "VXJ1dG9yYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggY29udGluZW50IGlzIHRoZSBjb3VudHJ5IG9mIEFuZ29sYSBsb2NhdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "QWZyaWNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBJbnVpdCBsYW5ndWFnZXMgd2FzIHRoZSBGSVJTVCB0byB1c2UgYSB1bmlxdWUgd3JpdGluZyBzeXN0ZW0gbm90IGJhc2VkIG9uIHRoZSBMYXRpbiBhbHBoYWJldD8=",
            "answer": "SW51a3RpdHV0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIGRpc3RyaWN0IEFraWhhYmFyYSBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIGJ5IHdoYXQgbmlja25hbWU/",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWMgVG93bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVUsgY291bnRyeSBmZWF0dXJlcyBhIGRyYWdvbiBvbiB0aGVpciBmbGFnPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGJvcmRlciBLeXJneXpzdGFuPw==",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGFydmFyZCBVbml2ZXJzaXR5IGlzIGxvY2F0ZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "Q2FtYnJpZGdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTbG92YWtpYT8=",
            "answer": "QnJhdGlzbGF2YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQ2FuYWRpYW4gcHJvdmluY2UgaGFzIENoYXJsb3R0ZXRvd24gYXMgaXRzIGNhcGl0YWw/",
            "answer": "UHJpbmNlIEVkd2FyZCBJc2xhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQ2FuYWRpYW4gbmF0aW9uYWwgYW50aGVtPw==",
            "answer": "TyBDYW5hZGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBCcml0aXNoIENvbHVtYmlhLCBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "VmljdG9yaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZm9ybWVybHkgcmljaCBmaXNoaW5nIGdyb3VuZHMgb2ZmIHRoZSBpc2xhbmQgb2YgTmV3Zm91bmRsYW5kLCBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "R3JhbmQgQmFua3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTcGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "TWFkcmlk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBOYXRpb25hbCBQYXJrIGRlc2lnbmF0ZWQgaW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93c3RvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlICJTb25vcmFuIERlc2VydCIgbG9jYXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "Tm9ydGggQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgaW5kZXBlbmRlbnQgY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB0aGVyZSB3aXRoaW4gdGhlIGNvbnRpbmVudCBvZiBTb3V0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "MTI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBXaXNjb25zaW4sIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "TWFkaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBjbGFpbXMgb3duZXJzaGlwIG9mIHRoZSBkaXNwdXRlZCBzdGF0ZSBLb3Nvdm8/",
            "answer": "U2VyYmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIG5vdCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgU2NhbmRpbmF2aWE/",
            "answer": "RmlubGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBFdXJvcGVhbiBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIG5vdCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEVVPw==",
            "answer": "Tm9yd2F5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gYSBMb25kb24gVW5kZXJncm91bmQgbWFwLCB3aGF0IGNvbG91ciBpcyB0aGUgQ2lyY2xlIExpbmU/",
            "answer": "WWVsbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2l0eSBpbiBJbmRpYT8=",
            "answer": "SXNsYW1hYmFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkb2VzIEF1c3RyaWEgbm90IGJvcmRlcj8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBKYW1haWNhPw==",
            "answer": "S2luZ3N0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHByZWZpeCBTaW5vLSAoQXMgaW4gU2luby1BbWVyaWNhbikgaXMgdXNlZCB0byByZWZlciB0byB3aGF0IG5hdGlvbmFsaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZvdXIgY29ybmVyIHN0YXRlcyBvZiB0aGUgVVM/",
            "answer": "VXRhaCwgQ29sb3JhZG8sIEFyaXpvbmEsIE5ldyBNZXhpY28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY2l0eSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgc3RhdGUgVGVubmVzc2VlPw==",
            "answer": "TWVtcGhpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgR2VybWFuIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFN3aXNzIEZlZGVyYWwgUmFpbHdheXM/",
            "answer": "U2Nod2VpemVyaXNjaGUgQnVuZGVzYmFobmVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRvd25zIG9mIEJydWdlbGV0dGUsIEFybG9uIGFuZCBBdGggYXJlIGxvY2F0ZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "QmVsZ2l1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFwYW4gaGFzIGxlZnQtaGFuZCBzaWRlIHRyYWZmaWMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhbmQgbWFzcyBvZiBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IFR1cmtleSBpcyBjYWxsZWQgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "QW5hdG9saWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEFuZGFtYW4gYW5kIE5pY29iYXIgSXNsYW5kcyBpbiBTb3V0aCBFYXN0IEFzaWEgYXJlIGNvbnRyb2xsZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "SW5kaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmV3IEhhdmVuIGlzIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsIGNpdHkgb2YgdGhlIHN0YXRlIG9mIENvbm5lY3RpY3V0IGluIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhdGlvbnMgZG9lcyB0aGUgQ2VudHJhbCBMaW5lIGhhdmUgb24gdGhlIExvbmRvbiBVbmRlcmdyb3VuZD8=",
            "answer": "NDk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmlmdGggbGFyZ2VzdCBjb3VudHJ5IGJ5IGFyZWE/",
            "answer": "QnJhemls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBNYXVyaXRpdXM/",
            "answer": "UG9ydCBMb3Vpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc21hbGwgY291bnRyeSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGJldHdlZW4gdGhlIGJvcmRlcnMgb2YgRnJhbmNlIGFuZCBTcGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "QW5kb3JyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgbG9uZ2VzdCByaXZlcj8=",
            "answer": "TmlsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd291bGQgeW91IGZpbmQgdGhlICJTcGFuaXNoIFN0ZXBzIj8=",
            "answer": "Um9tZSwgSXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdCByaXZlciBpbiBFdXJvcGU/",
            "answer": "Vm9sZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFrZSBUaXRpY2FjYSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGJldHdlZW4gd2hpY2ggdHdvIG5hdGlvbnM/",
            "answer": "UGVydSBhbmQgQm9saXZpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzdGF0ZSBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBzdGF0ZSBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBvZiBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "QWxhc2th"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZmVkZXJhbCBzdGF0ZXMgZG9lcyBHZXJtYW55IGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "MTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S3VhbGEgTHVtcHVyIGlzIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsIG9mIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "TWFsYXlzaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcHJvdmluY2UgaW4gQ2hpbmE/",
            "answer": "WWFuZ3R6ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1vdW50YWlub3VzIEtoeWJlciBQYXNzIGNvbm5lY3RzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gZm9sbG93aW5nIGNvdW50cmllcz8=",
            "answer": "QWZnaGFuaXN0YW4gYW5kIFBha2lzdGFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYXJlIGNsYXNzaWZpZWQgYXMgRmlubm8tVWdyaWMgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzIEVYQ0VQVDo=",
            "answer": "U2Ftb3llZGlj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxvbmdlc3QgcGxhY2UgbmFtZWQgaW4gdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgaXMgTGFrZSBDaGFyZ29nZ2Fnb2dnbWFuY2hhdWdnYWdvZ2djaGF1YnVuYWd1bmdhbWF1Z2csIGxvY2F0ZWQgbmVhciBXZWJzdGVyLCBNQS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxMiB0aGUgR2VybWFuLXNwZWFraW5nIG1pY3Jvc3RhdGUgIkxpZWNodGVuc3RlaW4iIGluIENlbnRyYWwgRXVyb3BlIGhhZCBhIHBvcHVsYXRpb24gb2YgaG93IG1hbnkgaW5oYWJpdGFudHM/",
            "answer": "MzYsNjAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBsb2NhdGVkIGluIEFmcmljYT8=",
            "answer": "U3VyaW5hbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgVVMgc3RhdGUgTmV2YWRhPw==",
            "answer": "Q2Fyc29uIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgV2FzaGluZ3RvbiwgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "T2x5bXBpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGFsbGVzdCBtb3VudGFpbiBpbiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "TW91bnQgTG9nYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkb2VzIEZpbmxhbmQgY2VsZWJyYXRlIHRoZWlyIGluZGVwZW5kZW5jZSBkYXk/",
            "answer": "RGVjZW1iZXIgNnRo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgY291bnRyeSBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "VmF0aWNhbiBDaXR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVnaW9uIGNvbmpvaW5pbmcgUGFraXN0YW4sIEluZGlhLCBhbmQgQ2hpbmEgd2l0aCB1bmtub3duIGxlYWRlcnNoaXAgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "S2FzaG1pcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaXR5ICBoYXMgdGhlIGJ1c2llc3QgYWlycG9ydCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYSBVU0E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTY290bGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "RWRpbmJ1cmdo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRpdGxlIG9mIHRoZSAxOTY5IGZpbG0gIktyYWthdG9hLCBFYXN0X29mIEphdmEiIGlzIGluY29ycmVjdCwgYXMgS3Jha2F0b2EgaXMgaW4gZmFjdCB3ZXN0IG9mIEphdmEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcmVhbCB0ZWN0b25pYyBwbGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50aWMgUGxhdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaXR5IGlzIHRoZSBUZXJyYWNvdHRhIEFybXkgbG9jYXRlZCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "WGknYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBJbmRvbmVzaWE/",
            "answer": "SmFrYXJ0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3JlZW5sYW5kIGlzIGNvdmVyZWQgd2l0aCBncmFzcyBhbmQgSWNlbGFuZCBjb3ZlcmVkIHdpdGggaWNlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY2l0eSBpbiBNb3JvY2NvPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FzYWJsYW5jYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIE5lby1BcmFtYWljIGxhbmd1YWdlcyBzcG9rZW4gYnkgdGhlIEpld2lzaCBwb3B1bGF0aW9uIGZyb20gTm9ydGh3ZXN0ZXJuIElyYXE/",
            "answer": "TGlzaGFuYSBEZW5p"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsYW5ndWFnZXMgZG9lcyBOT1QgdXNlIHRoZSBMYXRpbiBhbHBoYWJldD8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdpYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmlnaHQgd2F5IHRvIHNwZWxsIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsIG9mIEh1bmdhcnk/",
            "answer": "QnVkYXBlc3Q="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSBVUyBzdGF0ZSBEZWxhd2FyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZpcnN0IFN0YXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZvcm1lcmx5IEVhc3QtUHJ1c3NpYW4gY2l0eSBvZiBLw7ZuaWdzYmVyZyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyB3aGljaCBSdXNzaWFuIENpdHkgdG9kYXk/",
            "answer": "S2FsaW5pbmdyYWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZm9ybWVyIGNvdW50cnkgdGhhdCB3YXMgc3VjY2VlZGVkIGJ5IGNvdW50cmllcyBzdWNoIGFzIFNlcmJpYSwgQ3JvYXRpYSBhbmQgU2xvdmVuaWE/",
            "answer": "WXVnb3NsYXZpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3JlZW5sYW5kIGlzIGFsbW9zdCBhcyBiaWcgYXMgQWZyaWNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRpZXMgaW4gdGhlIFJlcHVibGljIG9mIElyZWxhbmQu",
            "answer": "MjY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGlzIG9uIHRoZSBmbGFnIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBzdGF0ZSBXaXNjb25zaW4/",
            "answer": "MTg0OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBTZW5lZ2FsPw==",
            "answer": "RGFrYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgTk9UIGZvcm1lcmx5IHBhcnQgb2YgWXVnb3NsYXZpYT8=",
            "answer": "QWxiYW5pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGFiYnJldmlhdGlvbiAiQ0giPw==",
            "answer": "U3dpdHplcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnJvb21lIGlzIGEgdG93biBpbiB3aGljaCBzdGF0ZSBvZiBBdXN0cmFsaWE/",
            "answer": "V2VzdGVybiBBdXN0cmFsaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyeSdzIGNhcGl0YWxzIHN0YXJ0cyB3aXRoIHRoZSBsZXR0ZXIgQj8=",
            "answer": "TGViYW5vbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbm9ydGhlcm5tb3N0IGh1bWFuIHNldHRsZW1lbnQgd2l0aCB5ZWFyIHJvdW5kIGluaGFiaXRhbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "QWxlcnQsIENhbmFkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBMYW9zPw==",
            "answer": "Q291bnRyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQW1lcmljYW4gY2l0aWVzIGhhcyBmZXdlciB0aGFuIDEsMDAwLDAwMCBwZW9wbGU/",
            "answer": "U2FuIEZyYW5jaXNjbywgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBQZXJ1Pw==",
            "answer": "TGltYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFJlcHVibGljIG9mIE1hbHRhIGlzIHRoZSBzbWFsbGVzdCBtaWNyb3N0YXRlIHdvcmxkd2lkZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgaXMgdGhlIGFyZWEgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMgdGhlIEJlcm11ZGEgVHJpYW5nbGU/",
            "answer": "Tm9ydGggQXRsYW50aWMgT2NlYW4sIGJldHdlZW4gRmxvcmlkYSBhbmQgUHVlcnRvIFJpY28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGhpc3RvcmljYWwgY2l0eSBUaW1idWt0dSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIFdlc3QgQWZyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "TWFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnVja2luZyBpcyBhIHZpbGxhZ2UgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcGVuaW5zdWxhIGNvbnRhaW5pbmcgU3BhaW4gYW5kIFBvcnR1Z2FsPw==",
            "answer": "SWJlcmlhbiBQZW5pbnN1bGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3dpdHplcmxhbmQgaGFzIGZvdXIgbmF0aW9uYWwgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzLCBFbmdsaXNoIGJlaW5nIG9uZSBvZiB0aGVtLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjaXR5IGlzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBSb3NlIENhcGl0YWwgb2YgdGhlIFdvcmxkPw==",
            "answer": "VHlsZXIsIFRleGFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2Vjb25kLWxhcmdlc3QgY2l0eSBpbiBMaXRodWFuaWE/",
            "answer": "S2F1bmFz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcml2ZXJzIGFyZSBpbiBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWE/",
            "answer": "MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBHcmVlbmxhbmQ/",
            "answer": "TnV1aw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2l0aWVzIGlzIE5PVCBpbiBFbmdsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "RWRpbmJ1cmdo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpc2xhbmQgaW4gdGhlIENhbmFyeSBJc2xhbmRzIHdhcyB0aGUgc2NlbmUgb2Ygb25lIG9mIHRoZSB3b3JzdCBhaXIgZGlzYXN0ZXJzIGluIGhpc3Rvcnkgd2l0aCB0aGUgY29sbGlzaW9uIG9mIHR3byBqdW1ibyBqZXRzPw==",
            "answer": "VGVuZXJpZmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBDaGlsZT8=",
            "answer": "U2FudGlhZ28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxhc2thIGlzIHRoZSBsYXJnZXN0IHN0YXRlIGluIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBwb3B1bG91cyBNdXNsaW0tbWFqb3JpdHkgbmF0aW9uIGluIDIwMTA/",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXpvbmVzIGRvZXMgUnVzc2lhIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "MTE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2l0aWVzIGhhcyBhIDTCsCBFYXN0IGxvbmdpdHVkZS4g",
            "answer": "QW1zdGVyZGFt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBjaXR5IG9mIE5ldyBaZWFsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "V2VsbGluZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgb25seSByZW1haW5pbmcgR3JhbmQgRHVjaHkgaW4gdGhlIHdvcmxkID8=",
            "answer": "THV4ZW1ib3VyZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGxvbmdlc3Qgc2hhcmVkIGJvcmRlciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQgY2FuIGJlIGZvdW5kIGJldHdlZW4gd2hpY2ggdHdvIG5hdGlvbnM/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRhIGFuZCB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgQW1lcmljYW4gc3RhdGUgb2YgQXJpem9uYT8=",
            "answer": "UGhvZW5peA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc292ZXJlaWduIHN0YXRlcyBhcmUgbWVtYmVycyBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIE5hdGlvbnM/",
            "answer": "MTk1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdvcmxkIEhlYWx0aCBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gaGVhZHF1YXJ0ZXJzIGlzIGxvY2F0ZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggRXVyb3BlYW4gY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "U3dpdHplcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgYXJlIG5vIGRlc2VydHMgaW4gRXVyb3BlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugb2YgQmh1dGFuPw==",
            "answer": "RHpvbmdraGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhyZWUgY2FwaXRhbCBjaXRpZXM/",
            "answer": "U291dGggQWZyaWNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBFc3RvbmlhPw==",
            "answer": "VGFsbGlubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJhbmtlbm11dGgsIGEgVVMgY2l0eSBuaWNrbmFtZWQgIkxpdHRsZSBCYXZhcmlhIiwgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGlnYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEFzaWFuIGNvbnRpbmVudD8=",
            "answer": "U3VyaW5hbWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmb3JtZXIgWXVnb3NsYXZpYW4gc3RhdGVzIGlzIGxhbmRsb2NrZWQ/",
            "answer": "U2VyYmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVVMgc3RhdGUgaGFzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IHBvcHVsYXRpb24/",
            "answer": "Q2FsaWZvcm5pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VmlldG5hbSBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBjb3VudHJ5IGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZCB0aGF0IHN0YXJ0cyB3aXRoIFYuIA==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBjaXR5IG9mIFNsb3ZlbmlhPw==",
            "answer": "TGp1YmxqYW5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnJpZGdldG93biBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB3aGljaCBpc2xhbmQgY291bnRyeSBpbiB0aGUgQ2FycmliZWFuPw==",
            "answer": "QmFyYmFkb3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBFdXJvcGVhbiBsYW5ndWFnZXMgaXMgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBhICJsYW5ndWFnZSBpc29sYXRlPyI=",
            "answer": "QmFzcXVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBTcGFuaXNoIHByb3ZpbmNlcyBhcmUgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiB0aGUgbm9ydGhlcm4gYXJlYSBvZiBTcGFpbiBleGNlcHQ6",
            "answer": "TXVyY2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBOYXpjYSBMaW5lcyBsb2NhdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "UGVydQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tm9yd2F5IGhhcyBhIGxhcmdlciBsYW5kIGFyZWEgdGhhbiBTd2VkZW4u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsYW5ndWFnZSBmYW1pbGllcyBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb250cm92ZXJzaWFsIGFtb25nc3QgbW9kZXJuIGxpbmd1aXN0cz8=",
            "answer": "QWx0YWlj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZSB6b25lcyBkb2VzIENoaW5hIGhhdmU/",
            "answer": "MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIGNpdHkgaXMgbG9jYXRlZCBvbiB0aGUgUml2ZXIgSXNhcj8=",
            "answer": "TXVuaWNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgZXhpc3RzIGFuIGlzbGFuZCBuYW1lZCAiSmF2YSIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SHVuZ2FyeSBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBjb3VudHJ5IGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZCBiZWdpbm5pbmcgd2l0aCBILg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaGFzIGEgZmxhZyBmZWF0dXJpbmcgYSB5ZWxsb3cgbGlvbiB3aWVsZGluZyBhIHN3b3JkIG9uIGEgZGFyayByZWQgYmFja2dyb3VuZD8=",
            "answer": "U3JpIExhbmth"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIGlzIG5vdCBhIFVuaXRlZCBOYXRpb25zIG1lbWJlciBzdGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "Tml1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpbnNpZGUgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIGRvZXMgTk9UIGFwcGVhciBvbiBpdHMgZmxhZywgdGhlIFVuaW9uIEphY2s/",
            "answer": "V2FsZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFNwYWNlIE5lZWRsZSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "U2VhdHRsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYnVzaWVzdCBwb3J0IGluIEV1cm9wZT8=",
            "answer": "UG9ydCBvZiBSb3R0ZXJkYW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBDYW5hZGEncyBsYXJnZXN0IGlzbGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "QmFmZmluIElzbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBpcyB0aGUgVGFlZG9uZyBSaXZlciBpbj8=",
            "answer": "Tm9ydGggS29yZWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZSB6b25lcyBhcmUgaW4gUnVzc2lhPw==",
            "answer": "MTE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvdXIgaXMgdGhlIGNpcmNsZSBvbiB0aGUgSmFwYW5lc2UgZmxhZz8=",
            "answer": "UmVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBjb3VudHJ5IGluIHRoZSB3b3JsZD8=",
            "answer": "UnVzc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBncm91cCBvZiBpc2xhbmRzIGlzIGNhbGxlZCBhbiAnYXJjaGlwZWxhZ28nLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaXMgd2l0aGluIHRoZSBFdXJvem9uZSBidXQgb3V0c2lkZSBvZiB0aGUgU2NoZW5nZW4gQXJlYT8=",
            "answer": "Q3lwcnVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgMTV0aCBsZXR0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIEdyZWVrIGFscGhhYmV0Pw==",
            "answer": "T21pY3JvbiAozp8p"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIEFmcmljYW4gbmF0aW9uIG9mIFppbWJhYndlIGZvcm1lcmx5IGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "UmhvZGVzaWE="
        }
    ],
    "SGlzdG9yeQ==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2l0aCB3aGljaCBHcmVlayBwaGlsb3NvcGhlciB3b3VsZCB5b3UgYXNzb2NpYXRlIHRoZSBwaHJhc2UsICJJIGtub3cgdGhhdCBJIGtub3cgbm90aGluZyI/",
            "answer": "U29jcmF0ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbmF2YWwgYmF0dGxlIHdhcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIHRoZSB0dXJuaW5nIHBvaW50IG9mIHRoZSBQYWNpZmljIE9jZWFuIFRoZWF0ZXIgZHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciAyPw==",
            "answer": "QmF0dGxlIG9mIE1pZHdheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBOZWlsIEFybXN0cm9uZyBhbmQgQnV6eiBBbGRyaW4gbGFuZCBvbiB0aGUgbW9vbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IFdoYXQgUnVzc2lhbiBhdXRvbWF0aWMgZ2FzLW9wZXJhdGVkIGFzc2F1bHQgcmlmbGUgd2FzIGRldmVsb3BlZCBpbiB0aGUgU292aWV0IFVuaW9uIGluIDE5NDcsIGFuZCBpcyBzdGlsbCBwb3B1bGFybHkgdXNlZCB0b2RheT8=",
            "answer": "QUstNDc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U3BhaW4gd2FzIGZvcm1lZCBpbiAxNDY5IHdpdGggdGhlIG1hcnJpYWdlIG9mIElzYWJlbGxhIEkgb2YgQ2FzdGlsZSBhbmQgRmVyZGluYW5kIElJIG9mIHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgSWJlcmlhbiBraW5nZG9tPw==",
            "answer": "QXJhZ29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBudW1iZXIgZG9lcyB0aGUgUm9tYW4gbnVtZXJhbCAiRCIgc3RhbmQgZm9yPw==",
            "answer": "NTAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNweSByaW5nIHRoYXQgaGVscGVkIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHdpbiB0aGUgUmV2b2x1dGlvbmFyeSBXYXI/",
            "answer": "Q3VscGVyIFJpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyb3duIG9mIHRoZSBFbXBpcmUgU3RhdGUgQnVpbGRpbmcgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgYnVpbHQgZm9yIHdoYXQgcHVycG9zZT8=",
            "answer": "QWlyc2hpcCBEb2Nr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hhdCBkYXkgZGlkIEdlcm1hbnkgaW52YWRlIFBvbGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDEsIDE5Mzk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGljdGF0b3Iga2lsbGVkIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBlb3BsZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFvIFplZG9uZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgSmFtYWljYSByZWNpZXZlIGl0cyBpbmRlcGVuZGVuY2UgZnJvbSBFbmdsYW5kPyA=",
            "answer": "MTk2Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBDYW5hZGEgZm91bmRlZCBpbj8=",
            "answer": "MTg2Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHdvcmxkIGxlYWRlciBpcyBmYW1lZCBmb3IgdGhlIHNheWluZywgIkxldCB0aGVtIGVhdCBjYWtlIiwgeWV0IGlzIHJ1bW9yZWQgdGhhdCBoZS9zaGUgbmV2ZXIgc2FpZCBpdCBhdCBhbGw/",
            "answer": "TWFyaWUgQW50b2luZXR0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFJvbWFuIGFscGhhYmV0IGxhY2tlZCB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIGxldHRlcnMgRVhDRVBUOg==",
            "answer": "WA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgIlRoZSBHYWRnZXQiLCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgbnVjbGVhciBkZXZpY2UgdG8gYmUgZGV0b25hdGVkLCB0ZXN0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "SnVseSAxNiwgMTk0NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQmF0dGxlIG9mIEFnaW5jb3VydCB0YWtlIHBsYWNlPw==",
            "answer": "MTQxNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIEZpcnN0IFdvcmxkIFdhciBiZWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "MTkxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgSm9obiBGLiBLZW5uZWR5IHdhcyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0ZWQgZHVyaW5nIGhpcyBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgbW90b3JjYWRlIGluIEF0bGFudGEsIEdlb3JnaWEgb24gTm92ZW1iZXIgMjJuZCwgMTk2My4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTcyMCwgRW5nbGFuZCB3YXMgaW4gbWFzc2l2ZSBkZWJ0LCBhbmQgYmVjYW1lIGluIGludm9sdmVkIGluIHRoZSBTb3V0aCBTZWEgQnViYmxlLiBXaG8gd2FzIHRoZSBtYWluIG1hc3Rlcm1pbmQgYmVoaW5kIGl0Pw==",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBCbHVudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdlcmUgdGhlIE1hcmlhbiBSZWZvcm1zIGluc3RpdHV0ZWQgaW4gdGhlIFJvbWFuIFJlcHVibGljPw==",
            "answer": "MTA3IEJDRQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIFRva3lvIFN1YndheSBTYXJpbiBBdHRhY2sgb2NjdXI/",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGludmVudGVkIHRoZSAiRmx5aW5nIFNodXR0bGUiIGluIDE3Mzg7IG9uZSBvZiB0aGUga2V5IGRldmVsb3BtZW50cyBpbiB0aGUgaW5kdXN0cmlhbGl6YXRpb24gb2Ygd2VhdmluZz8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBLYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggV1dJSSB0YW5rIGFjZSBpcyBjcmVkaXRlZCB3aXRoIGhhdmluZyBkZXN0cm95ZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgdGFua3M/",
            "answer": "S3VydCBLbmlzcGVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBEZWNsYXJhdGlvbiBvZiBJbmRlcGVuZGVuY2Ugc2lnbmVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTc3Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgUm9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBhcHBvaW50IGEgd29tYW4gdG8gdGhlIFN1cHJlbWUgQ291cnQuIA==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTmFwb2xlb24gQm9uYXBhcnRlJ3MgbmFtZSBiZWZvcmUgaGUgY2hhbmdlZCBpdD8=",
            "answer": "TmFwb2xlb25lIGRpIEJ1b25hcGFydGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aW9uIERJRCBOT1QgaGF2ZSBhIENvbG9ueSBpbiBNb2Rlcm4tZGF5IEFtZXJpY2E/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVnYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgTm9yd2F5IGJlY29tZSBmcmVlIGZyb20gU3dlZGVuPw==",
            "answer": "MTkwNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzbmlwZXJzIGhhcyB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBhbW91bnQgb2YgY29uZmlybWVkIGtpbGxzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltbyBIw6R5aMOk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGJsb29kaWVzdCBzaW5nbGUtZGF5IGJhdHRsZSBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIEFtZXJpY2FuIENpdmlsIFdhcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBBbnRpZXRhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaGlzdG9yaWNhbCBjb25mbGljdCBraWxsZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgcGVvcGxlPw==",
            "answer": "V29ybGQgV2FyIElJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgRmlyc3QgV29ybGQgV2FyIGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkxOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgV2FyIGxsLCBHcmVhdCBCcml0aWFuIHVzZWQgaW5mbGF0YWJsZSB0YW5rcyBvbiB0aGUgcG9ydHMgb2YgR3JlYXQgQnJpdGFpbiB0byBkaXZlcnQgSGl0bGVyIGF3YXkgZnJvbSBOb3JtYW5keS9ELWRheSBsYW5kaW5nLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlIEFsbGllZCBpbnZhc2lvbiBvZiBTb3V0aGVybiBGcmFuY2Ugb24gQXVndXN0IDE1dGgsIDE5NDQ/",
            "answer": "T3BlcmF0aW9uIERyYWdvb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEZhbGxpbmd3YXRlciBIb3VzZSwgbG9jYXRlZCBpbiBQZW5uc3lsdmFuaWEsIHdhcyBkZXNpZ25lZCBieSB3aGljaCBhcmNoaXRlY3Q/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmsgTGxveWQgV3JpZ2h0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG8gd2hhdCBwb2xpdGljYWwgcGFydHkgZGlkIEFicmFoYW0gTGluY29sbiBiZWxvbmcgd2hlbiBlbGVjdGVkIFBPVFVTPw==",
            "answer": "UmVwdWJsaWNhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlc2UgdHdvIGNvdW50cmllcyBoZWxkIGEgY29tbW9ud2VhbHRoIGZyb20gdGhlIDE2dGggdG8gMTh0aCBjZW50dXJ5Lg==",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5kIGFuZCBMaXRodWFuaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQmVybGluIFdhbGwgZmFsbD8=",
            "answer": "MTk4OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgVmlldG5hbSBXYXIgZW5kPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiBjb2xvbmllcyBzd2l0Y2hlZCB0byB0aGUgR3JlZ29yaWFuIGNhbGVuZGFyIGluIDE3NTIsIG9uIHdoYXQgZGF0ZSBkaWQgdGhlaXIgbmV3IHllYXIgc3RhcnQ/",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggMjV0aA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBVUyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gYmUgZWxlY3RlZCBmb3VyIHRpbWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtsaW4gUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggS2luZyBvZiBFbmdsYW5kIHdhcyBmYWNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBQZWFzYW50cycgUmV2b2x0IGluIDEzODE/",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBJSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hhdCBzdHJlZXQgZGlkIHRoZSAxNjY2IEdyZWF0IEZpcmUgb2YgTG9uZG9uIHN0YXJ0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVkZGluZyBMYW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1hbiB0aGF0IHNob3QgQWxleGFuZGVyIEhhbWlsdG9uIHdhcyBuYW1lZCBBYXJvbiBCdXJyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQ2hhbmNlbGxvciBvZiBhIHVuaXRlZCBHZXJtYW55IGluIDE4NzE/IA==",
            "answer": "T3R0byBWb24gQmlzbWFyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJLCB3aGljaCBuYXRpb24ncyBtb25hcmNocyB3ZXJlIGJsb29kIHJlbGF0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "RW5nbGFuZCwgR2VybWFueSwgUnVzc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGFzc2Fzc2luYXRlZCBBcmNoZHVrZSBGcmFueiBGZXJkaW5hbmQ/",
            "answer": "R2F2cmlsbyBQcmluY2lw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgaGlzIGxvc3MgYXQgdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBXYXRlcmxvbywgTmFwb2xlb24gQm9uYXBhcnRlIHdhcyBleGlsZWQgdG8gd2hpY2ggaXNsYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "U3QuIEhlbGVuYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZyYXVkZWxlbnQgZG9jdG9yIEpvaG4gUi4gQnJpbmtsZXkgYWN1bW11bGF0ZWQgZ3JlYXQgZmFtZSBhbmQgd2VhbHRoIGluIHRoZSBlYXJseSAxOTAwcyBvZmZlcmluZyB3aGF0IHNlcnZpY2U/",
            "answer": "R29hdCB0ZXN0aWNsZXMgdHJhbnNwbGFudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIG1pbGl0YXJ5IGNvbW1hbmRlciBtYXJjaGVkIGFuIGFybXksIHdoaWNoIGluY2x1ZGVkIHdhciBlbGVwaGFudHMsIG92ZXIgdGhlIEFscHMgZHVyaW5nIHRoZSBTZWNvbmQgUHVuaWMgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "SGFubmliYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgV2lsbGlhbSBGcmVkZXJpY2sgQ29keSBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM/",
            "answer": "QnVmZmFsbyBCaWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFwYW4gd2FzIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEFsbGllZCBQb3dlcnMgZHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiB0aGUgU29tbWUgaW4gV29ybGQgV2FyIEkgdG9vayBwbGFjZSBpbiB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBZnJpY2FuIGNvdW50cmllcyB3YXMgbW9zdCBzdWNjZXNzZnVsIGluIHJlc2lzdGluZyBjb2xvbml6YXRpb24/",
            "answer": "RXRoaW9waWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBiYXR0bGVzIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgYXMgbWFya2luZyB0aGUgYmVnaW5uaW5nIG9mIHRoZSBmYWxsIG9mIHRoZSBXZXN0ZXJuIFJvbWFuIEVtcGlyZT8=",
            "answer": "QmF0dGxlIG9mIEFkcmlhbm9wbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXNzeXJpYW4ga2luZyBTZW5uYWNoZXJpYidzIGRlc3RydWN0aW9uIG9mIEJhYnlsb24gaW4gNjg5IEJDRSB3YXMgdmlld2VkIGFzIGEgdHJpdW1waCBieSBvdGhlciBBc3N5cmlhbiBjaXRpemVucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiB0aGUgU29tbWUgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "SnVseSAxc3QsIDE5MTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgTm9ydGggQW1lcmljYW4gVmlkZW8gR2FtZSBDcmFzaCBvY2N1cj8=",
            "answer": "MTk4Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZvdXJ0aCBmdW5uZWwgb2YgdGhlIFJNUyBUaXRhbmljIHdhcyBmYWtlIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRvIG1ha2UgdGhlIHNoaXAgbG9vayBtb3JlIHBvd2VyZnVsIGFuZCBzeW1tZXRyaWNhbC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGltZXMgd2FzIEFsYmVydCBFaW5zdGVpbiBtYXJyaWVkIGluIGhpcyBsaWZldGltZT8=",
            "answer": "VHdpY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk2NywgYSBtYWdhemluZSBwdWJsaXNoZWQgYSBzdG9yeSBhYm91dCBleHRyYWN0aW5nIGhhbGx1Y2lub2dlbmljIGNoZW1pY2FscyBmcm9tIGJhbmFuYXMgdG8gcmFpc2UgbW9yYWwgcXVlc3Rpb25zIGFib3V0IGJhbm5pbmcgZHJ1Z3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9zZXBoIFN0YWxpbiBoYWQgYSBjcmltaW5hbCBwYXN0IGRvaW5nIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "Um9iYmluZyBUcmFpbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUHJpbWUgTWluaXN0ZXIgb2YgSmFwYW4gd2hlbiBKYXBhbiBkZWNsYXJlZCB3YXIgb24gdGhlIFVTPw==",
            "answer": "SGlkZWtpIFRvam8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3ZXJlIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBzdGF0ZXMgdG8gYnJlYWsgYXdheSBmcm9tIFl1Z29zbGF2aWE/",
            "answer": "U2xvdmVuaWEsIENyb2F0aWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWJyYWhhbSBMaW5jb2xuIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgVS5TLiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gYmUgYm9ybiBvdXRzaWRlIHRoZSBib3JkZXJzIG9mIHRoZSB0aGlydGVlbiBvcmlnaW5hbCBzdGF0ZXMuIA==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW5lbW9uaWMgZGV2aWNlIGZvciByZW1lbWJlcmluZyB0aGUgZmF0ZXMgb2YgdGhlIHdpdmVzIG9mIEhlbnJ5IFZJSUk/",
            "answer": "RGl2b3JjZWQsIEJlaGVhZGVkLCBEaWVkLCBEaXZvcmNlZCwgQmVoZWFkZWQsIFN1cnZpdmVk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2l2aWxpemF0aW9uIGlzIHRoZSBzb3VyY2Ugb2YgdGhlIGJlbGllZiB0aGF0IHRoZSB3b3JsZCB3b3VsZCBlbmQgb3IgZHJhc3RpY2FsbHkgY2hhbmdlIG9uIERlY2VtYmVyIDIxc3QsIDIwMTI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE1heWFucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgZm9ybWFsbHkgZGVjbGFyZSB3YXIgb24gSmFwYW4sIGVudGVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "RGVjZW1iZXIgOCwgMTk0MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcHJlc2lkZW50IGJvcm4gaW4gdGhlIGluZGVwZW5kZW50IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFZhbiBCdXJlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdhcyBhY2NlcHRlZCBpbnRvIHRoZSBWaWVubmEgQWNhZGVteSBvZiBGaW5lIEFydHMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJUcmFpbCBvZiBUZWFycyIgd2FzIGEgcmVzdWx0IG9mIHdoaWNoIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50J3MgSW5kaWFuIFJlbW92YWwgUG9saWN5Pw==",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgQXJteSBBaXIgQ29ycHMgYmVjYW1lIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIEFpciBGb3JjZSBvbiB3aGF0IGRhdGU/",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDE4LCAxOTQ3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBLZW50dWNreSBiZWNvbWUgdGhlIDE1dGggc3RhdGUgdG8gam9pbiB0aGUgdW5pb24/",
            "answer": "MTc5Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCB0byBzZW5kIGFuIG9iamVjdCBpbnRvIHNwYWNlPw==",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGFpbSBvZiB0aGUgIlVtYnJlbGxhIFJldm9sdXRpb24iIGluIEhvbmcgS29uZyBpbiAyMDE0Pw==",
            "answer": "R2VudWluZSB1bml2ZXJzYWwgc3VmZnJhZ2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTk2MSwgYW4gQW1lcmljYW4gQi01MiBhaXJjcmFmdCBjcmFzaGVkIGFuZCBuZWFybHkgZGV0b25hdGVkIHR3byA0bXQgbnVjbGVhciBib21icyBvdmVyIHdoaWNoIFVTIGNpdHk/",
            "answer": "R29sZHNib3JvLCBOb3J0aCBDYXJvbGluYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBTa29hbCwgYSBzbW9rZWxlc3MgVG9iYWNjbyBjb21wYW55LCByZWxlYXNlIHRoZWlyIGZpcnN0IGxpbmUgb2YgUG91Y2hlcywga25vd24gYXMgIlNrb2FsIEJhbmRpdHMiPw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGxlZCB0aGUgQ29tbXVuaXN0IFJldm9sdXRpb24gb2YgUnVzc2lhPw==",
            "answer": "VmxhZGltaXIgTGVuaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG91c3NhaW50IExvdXZlcnR1cmUgbGVkIGEgc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bCBzbGF2ZSByZXZvbHQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "SGFpdGk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgTywgQ2FuYWRhIG9mZmljaWFsbHkgYmVjb21lIHRoZSBuYXRpb25hbCBhbnRoZW0/",
            "answer": "MTk4MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHdoaWNoIEFtZXJpY2FuIENpdmlsIFdhciBjYW1wYWlnbiBkaWQgVW5pb24gdHJvb3BzIGRpZyBhIHR1bm5lbCBiZW5lYXRoIENvbmZlZGVyYXRlIHRyb29wcyB0byBkZXRvbmF0ZSBleHBsb3NpdmVzIHVuZGVybmVhdGggdGhlbT8=",
            "answer": "U2llZ2Ugb2YgUGV0ZXJzYnVyZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvYXQgb2YgYXJtcyBvZiB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBTcGFpbiBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgYXJtcyBmcm9tIHRoZSBtb25hcmNocyBvZiBDYXN0aWxsZSwgTGVvbiwgQXJhZ29uIGFuZCB3aGljaCBvdGhlciBmb3JtZXIgSWJlcmlhbiBraW5nZG9tPw==",
            "answer": "TmF2YXJyZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFRoaXJ0eSBZZWFycyBXYXIgZW5kZWQgd2l0aCB3aGljaCB0cmVhdHk/",
            "answer": "UGVhY2Ugb2YgV2VzdHBoYWxpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwaHlzaWNpc3RzIGRpZCBOT1Qgd29yayBvbiB0aGUgTWFuaGF0dGFuIHByb2plY3Q/",
            "answer": "TXVycmF5IEdlbGwtTWFubg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIE90dG9tYW4gRW1waXJlIHdhcyBkaXNzb2x2ZWQgYWZ0ZXIgdGhlaXIgbG9zcyBpbiB3aGljaCB3YXI/",
            "answer": "V29ybGQgV2FyIEk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RnJhbnogSm9zZXBoIEkgd2FzIHRoZSBsYXN0IGVtcGVyb3Igb2YgQXVzdHJpYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGh1bGwgTk8uIG9mIHRoZSBGbGV0Y2hlciBjbGFzcyBkZXN0cm95ZXIgRmxldGNoZXI/",
            "answer": "REQtNDQ1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZm91bmRpbmcgZmF0aGVycyBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBvZiBBbWVyaWNhIGxhdGVyIGJlY2FtZSBwcmVzaWRlbnQ/",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgTW9ucm9l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQm9laW5nIEItMjkgdGhhdCBkcm9wcGVkIHRoZSAnTGl0dGxlIEJveScgYXRvbWljIGJvbWIgb24gSGlyb3NoaW1hPw==",
            "answer": "RW5vbGEgR2F5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaXNlYXNlIGNyaXBwbGVkIFByZXNpZGVudCBGcmFua2xpbiBELiBSb29zZXZlbHQgYW5kIGxlZCBoaW0gdG8gaGVscCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uIGZpbmQgYSBjdXJlPyA=",
            "answer": "UG9saW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGlhbmlzdCBGcsOpZMOpcmljIENob3BpbiB3YXMgYSBjb21wb3NlciBvZiB3aGljaCBtdXNpY2FsIGVyYT8=",
            "answer": "Um9tYW50aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHdoYXQgd2FyIGRpZCB0aGUgIkN1YmFuIE1pc3NpbGUgQ3Jpc2lzIiBvY2N1cj8=",
            "answer": "Q29sZCBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIGZpZWxkIG1hcnNoYWwgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBgRGVzZXJ0IEZveGA/",
            "answer": "RXJ3aW4gUm9tbWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGRpc2NvdmVyZWQgUGVuaWNpbGxpbj8=",
            "answer": "QWxleGFuZGVyIEZsZW1taW5n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhcGl0YWwgb2YgU291dGggVmlldG5hbSBiZWZvcmUgdGhlIFZpZXRuYW0gV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "U2FpZ29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgV2FyIElJLCBIYXdrZXIgVHlwaG9vbnMgc2VydmVkIGluIHRoZSBQYWNpZmljIHRoZWF0ZXIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUHJpbWUgTWluaXN0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIGZvciBtb3N0IG9mIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "V2luc3RvbiBDaHVyY2hpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYWQgYW4gIk9yYW5nZSBSZXZvbHV0aW9uIiBiZXR3ZWVuIDIwMDQgYW5kIDIwMDU/",
            "answer": "VWtyYWluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhlcmVybyBnZW5vY2lkZSB3YXMgcGVycGV0cmF0ZWQgaW4gQWZyaWNhIGJ5IHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgY29sb25pYWwgbmF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "R2VybWFueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGlzdCB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIElyYW5pYyBlbXBpcmVzIGluIGNocm9ub2xvZ2ljYWwgb3JkZXI6",
            "answer": "TWVkaWFuLCBBY2hhZW1lbmlkLCBQYXJ0aGlhbiwgU2Fzc2FuaWQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciBkaWQgdGhlIEludmFzaW9uIG9mIEt1d2FpdCBieSBJcmFxIG9jY3VyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBSb21hbiBUcml1bXZpcmF0ZSBvZiA0MiBCQ0UsIHdoYXQgcmVnaW9uIG9mIHRoZSBSb21hbiBSZXB1YmxpYyB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gTGVwaWR1cz8=",
            "answer": "SGlzcGFuaWEg"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFNlY29uZCBCb2VyIFdhciBpbiAxODk5IHdhcyBmb3VnaHQgd2hlcmU/",
            "answer": "U291dGggQWZyaWNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHR1dG9yZWQgQWxleGFuZGVyIHRoZSBHcmVhdD8=",
            "answer": "QXJpc3RvdGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgTm9yd2F5IGdldCBpdHMgY29uc3RpdHV0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "MTgxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEh1bmRyZWQgWWVhcnMnIFdhciB3YXMgZm91Z2h0IGZvciBtb3JlIHRoYW4gYSBodW5kcmVkIHllYXJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcHJpbWUgbWluaXN0ZXIgb2YgQ2FuYWRhPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBNYWNkb25hbGQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3hmb3JkIFVuaXZlcnNpdHkgaXMgb2xkZXIgdGhhbiB0aGUgQXp0ZWMgRW1waXJlLiA=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgZGlkIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJSSBsYXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "NiB5ZWFycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdhcyB0cmllZCBhdCB0aGUgTnVyZW1iZXJnIHRyaWFscy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbGVhZGVyIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tdW5pc3QgUGFydHkgb2YgWXVnb3NsYXZpYSA/",
            "answer": "Sm9zaXAgQnJveiBUaXRv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVTUyBNaXNzb3VyaSAoQkItNjMpIGxhc3Qgc2VydmVkIGluIHRoZSBLb3JlYW4gV2FyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgQ29uc3RhbnRpbm9wbGUgY29ucXVlcmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBUdXJrcz8=",
            "answer": "MTQ1Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S3VibGFpIEtoYW4gaXMgdGhlIGdyYW5kY2hpbGQgb2YgR2VuZ2hpcyBLaGFuPw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFBlb3BsZSdzIFJlcHVibGljIG9mIENoaW5hIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAxLCAxOTQ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgeWVhcnMgZGlkIHRoZSBIdW5kcmVkIFllYXJzJyBXYXIgbGFzdD8=",
            "answer": "MTE2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgSm9zZWYgU3RhbGluIGJvcm4gaW4/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdyYW5kIFBhdHJpb3RpYyBXYXIgaW4gdGhlIFVTU1IgY29uY2x1ZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TWF5IDl0aCwgMTk0NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGFzc2Fzc2luYXRlZCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgSmFtZXMgQS4gR2FyZmllbGQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBHdWl0ZWF1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENyaXNpcyBvZiB0aGUgVGhpcmQgQ2VudHVyeSBiZWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "MjM1IEFE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTG91aXMgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgU3VuIEtpbmcgb2YgRnJhbmNlJz8=",
            "answer": "TG91aXMgWElW"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgR3JlYXQgTm9ydGhlcm4gV2FyLCBiZXR3ZWVuIFJ1c3NpYSBhbmQgU3dlZGVuLCBlbmQ/",
            "answer": "MTcyMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBSb21hbiBlbXBlcm9yIGluIHRoZSBZZWFyIG9mIEZvdXIgRW1wZXJvcnMgKDY5IEFEKT8=",
            "answer": "VmVzcGFzaWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIG9mIEFtZXJpY2EgY2VsZWJyYXRlIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgNHRoIG9mIEp1bHk/",
            "answer": "VGhlIHNpZ25pbmcgb2YgdGhlIERlY2xhcmF0aW9uIG9mIEluZGVwZW5kZW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVS5TLiBwcmVzaWRlbnQgd2FzIHNhaWQgdG8gaGF2ZSBiZWVuIHRvbyBob25lc3QgdG8gbGllIHRvIGhpcyBmYXRoZXIgYWJvdXQgY2hvcHBpbmcgZG93biBhIGNoZXJyeSB0cmVlPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9obiBNb3NlcyBCcm93bmluZywgdGhlIGRlc2lnbmVyIG9mIHRoZSBNMTkxOCBCQVIgKEJyb3duaW5nIEF1dG9tYXRpYyBSaWZsZSkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCByZWxpZ2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TW9ybW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHdhcyBub3QgYSBiZWFjaCBsYW5kaW5nIHNpdGUgaW4gdGhlIEludmFzaW9uIG9mIE5vcm1hbmR5Pw==",
            "answer": "U2lsdmVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2luZyBIZW5yeSBWSUlJIHdhcyB0aGUgc2Vjb25kIG1vbmFyY2ggb2Ygd2hpY2ggRXVyb3BlYW4gcm95YWwgaG91c2U/",
            "answer": "VHVkb3I="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW1lcmljYSdzIFN0cmF0ZWdpYyBEZWZlbnNlIFN5c3RlbSBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIENvbGQgV2FyIHdhcyBuaWNrbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgdGhpcyBmYW1vdXMgbW92aWUu",
            "answer": "U3RhciBXYXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHR3byBhdG9taWMgYm9tYnMgZHJvcHBlZCBvbiBKYXBhbiBieSB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBpbiBBdWd1c3QgMTk0NSB3ZXJlIG5hbWVkICdMaXR0bGUgTWFuJyBhbmQgJ0ZhdCBCb3knLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgZXhwbG9yZXIgdG8gc2FpbCB0byBOb3J0aCBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "TGVpZiBFcmlrc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWxsIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgYXJlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBTZXZlbiBXYXJyaW5nIFN0YXRlcyBFWENFUFQ6",
            "answer": "WmhhaSAo57+fKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYXR1cmFsIGNhc2Ugb2Ygc21hbGxwb3ggZG9jdW1lbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHNjaG9sYXJseSBlc3RpbWF0ZXMsIHdoYXQgcGVyY2VudGFnZSBvZiB0aGUgd29ybGQgcG9wdWxhdGlvbiBhdCB0aGUgdGltZSBkaWVkIGR1ZSB0byBUYW1lcmxhbmUncyBjb25xdWVzdHM/",
            "answer": "NSU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaW5mYW1vdXMgRXVyb3BlYW4gdHJhaXRvciB3YXMga25vd24gYXMgInRoZSBsYXN0IHBlcnNvbiB0byBlbnRlciBQYXJsaWFtZW50IHdpdGggaG9uZXN0IGludGVudGlvbnMiPw==",
            "answer": "R3V5IEZhd2tlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTWFuZnJlZCB2b24gUmljaHRob2ZlbidzIG5pY2tuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFJlZCBCYXJvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCB0aGUgYXR0ZW1wdGVkIGNvdXAgZCdldGF0IG9mIDE5OTEgaW4gdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbiBiZWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0IDE5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFdhciBvZiB0aGUgUGFjaWZpYyAoMTg3OSAtIDE4ODMpLCBCb2xpdmlhIGxvc3QgaXRzIGFjY2VzcyB0byB0aGUgUGFjaWZpYyBPY2VhbiBhZnRlciBiZWluZyBkZWZlYXRlZCBieSB3aGljaCBTb3V0aCBBbWVyaWNhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgQ2FuYWRhIGxlYXZlIHRoZSBjb25mZWRlcmF0aW9uIHRvIGJlY29tZSB0aGVpciBvd24gbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SnVseSAxc3QsIDE4Njc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBwcmlzb24gd2FzIEFkb2xmIEhpdGxlciBoZWxkIGluIDE5MjQ/",
            "answer": "TGFuZHNiZXJnIFByaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBXYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBSb3NlcyAoMTQ1NSAtIDE0ODcpIHdoaWNoIEVuZ2xpc2htYW4gd2FzIGR1YmJlZCAidGhlIEtpbmdtYWtlciI/",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBOZXZpbGxl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0IEpyLiB3YXMgdGhlIG9ubHkgR2VuZXJhbCBpbnZvbHZlZCBpbiB0aGUgaW5pdGlhbCBhc3NhdWx0IG9uIEQtRGF5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qm9oZGFuIEtobWVsbnl0c2t5IHdhcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZGVyIG9mIHRoZSBVa3JhaW5pYW4gQ29zc2Fja3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgcHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYW5kIHdoZW4gd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBjYXJkYm9hcmQgYm94IG1hZGUgZm9yIGluZHVzdHJpYWwgdXNlPw==",
            "answer": "RW5nbGFuZCwgMTgxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWdhaW5zdCB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5IGRpZCB0aGUgRHV0Y2ggUmVwdWJsaWMgZmlnaHQgdGhlIEVpZ2h0eSBZZWFycycgV2FyPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IHdhcyBTb2NyYXRlcyBleGVjdXRlZD8=",
            "answer": "UG9pc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgc2lnbmluZyBvZiB0aGUgR2Fkc2RlbiBQdXJjaGFzZT8=",
            "answer": "RnJhbmtsaW4gUGllcmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TWFydGluIEx1dGhlciBLaW5nIEpyLiBhbmQgQW5uZSBGcmFuayB3ZXJlIGJvcm4gdGhlIHNhbWUgeWVhci4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhbiBheGlzIHBvd2VyIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUk/",
            "answer": "IFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBXaW50ZXIgV2FyLCB0aGUgYW1vdW50IG9mIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbiBzb2xpZGVycyB0aGF0IGRpZWQgb3Igd2VudCBtaXNzaW5nIHdhcyBmaXZlIHRpbWVzIG1vcmUgdGhhbiBGaW5sYW5kJ3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgY29uc3RydWN0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBTdWV6IENhbmFsIGZpbmlzaD8=",
            "answer": "MTg2OQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNvdW50cnkgdG8gbGF1bmNoIGEgbWFuIGludG8gc3BhY2Uu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgQnJhemlsIHdhcyBhIGZvcm1lciBjb2xvbnkgdW5kZXI/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVnYWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHJvZGUgb24gaG9yc2ViYWNrIHRvIHdhcm4gdGhlIE1pbnV0ZW1lbiB0aGF0IHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIHdlcmUgY29taW5nIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgVS5TLiBSZXZvbHV0aW9uYXJ5IFdhcj8=",
            "answer": "UGF1bCBSZXZlcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQaHlzaWNpc3RzIGFpZGVkIE5hemkgR2VybWFueSBpbiB0aGVpciBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIG9mIGEgbnVjbGVhciB3ZWFwb24/",
            "answer": "V2VybmVyIEhlaXNlbmJlcmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbiBvZiB3aGljaCBwb3BlIHN1cHBvc2VkbHkgaGVsZCBhIGxlY2hlcm91cyBmw6p0ZSBpbnZvbHZpbmcgNTAgY291cnRlc2FucyBpbiB0aGUgcGFwYWwgcGFsYWNlPw==",
            "answer": "QWxleGFuZGVyIFZJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG9udG9sb2dpY2FsIGFyZ3VtZW50IGZvciB0aGUgcHJvb2Ygb2YgR29kJ3MgZXhpc3RlbmNlIGlzIGZpcnN0IGF0dHJpYnV0ZWQgdG8gd2hvbT8=",
            "answer": "QW5zZWxtIG9mIENhbnRlcmJ1cnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHllYXIgMTkwMCwgd2hhdCB3ZXJlIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyc3QgbmFtZXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gYm95IGFuZCBnaXJsIGJhYmllcyBib3JuIGluIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBhbmQgTWFyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIENvbGQgV2FyIGVuZGVkIHdpdGggSm9zZXBoIFN0YWxpbidzIGRlYXRoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHRhbmtzIHdhcyBkZXNpZ25lZCBhbmQgb3BlcmF0ZWQgYnkgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tPw==",
            "answer": "VG9nIElJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgU3BhbmlzaCBQZW5pbnN1bGFyIFdhciBzdGFydD8=",
            "answer": "MTgwOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmNpZW50IE5lYXIgRWFzdGVybiBwZW9wbGVzIHN0aWxsIGV4aXN0cyBhcyBhIG1vZGVybiBldGhuaWMgZ3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "QXNzeXJpYW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIHRoZSBkZWFkbGllc3QgcGFuZGVtaWNzLCB0aGUgIlNwYW5pc2ggRmx1Iiwga2lsbGVkIG9mZiB3aGF0IHBlcmNlbnRhZ2Ugb2YgdGhlIGh1bWFuIHdvcmxkIHBvcHVsYXRpb24gYXQgdGhlIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "MyB0byA2IHBlcmNlbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQWxiYW5pYW4gbmF0aW9uYWwgbGVhZGVyIFNrYW5kZXJiZWc/",
            "answer": "R2plcmdqIEthc3RyaW90aQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgZm91bmQgaW4gMTk0NiBieSB0d28geW91bmcgc2hlcGFyZHMgbmVhciBhIGNhdmU/",
            "answer": "RGVhZCBTZWEgU2Nyb2xscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTkzOSwgQnJpdGFpbiBhbmQgRnJhbmNlIGRlY2xhcmVkIHdhciBvbiBHZXJtYW55IGFmdGVyIGl0IGludmFkZWQgd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcnMgZGlkIHRoZSBCYXR0bGUgb2YgR2FsbGlwb2xpIHRha2UgcGxhY2U/",
            "answer": "MTkxNSAtIDE5MTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gV29ybGQgV2FyIEksIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBhbGxpYW5jZSBvZiBHZXJtYW55LCBBdXN0cmlhLUh1bmdhcnksIHRoZSBPdHRvbWFuIEVtcGlyZSwgYW5kIEJ1bGdhcmlhPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIENlbnRyYWwgUG93ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSB3YXMgYW4gYWxsaWVkIHBvd2VyIGluIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "U292aWV0IFVuaW9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlICJTaWVnZSBvZiBMZW5pbmdyYWQiIGxpZnRlZCBkdXJpbmcgV29ybGQgV2FyIElJPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSAxOTQ0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1pbmlndW4gd2FzIGRlc2lnbmVkIGluIDE5NjAgYnkgd2hpY2ggbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "R2VuZXJhbCBFbGVjdHJpYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggYWlyY3JhZnQgY2FycmllciBkaWQgdGhlIERvb2xpdHRlIFJhaWQgbGF1bmNoIGZyb20gb24gQXByaWwgMTgsIDE5NDIgZHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "VVNTIEhvcm5ldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW9kZXJuIGNvdW50cnkgaXMga25vd24gYXMgIlRoZSBHcmF2ZXlhcmQgb2YgRW1waXJlcyI/",
            "answer": "QWZnaGFuaXN0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RnJvbSAxOTQwIHRvIDE5NDIsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBjYXBpdGFsLWluLWV4aWxlIG9mIEZyZWUgRnJhbmNlID8=",
            "answer": "QnJhenphdmlsbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuY2llbnQgY2l0eSBvZiBDaGljaMOpbiBJdHrDoSB3YXMgYnVpbHQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2l2aWxpemF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TWF5YW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBUZXhhcyBzZWNlZGUgZnJvbSBNZXhpY28/",
            "answer": "MTgzNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZmFjaWxpdGllcyB3YXMgbm90IHByZXNlbnQgb24gdGhlIFRpdGFuaWM/",
            "answer": "RmFpbnRpbmcgcm9vbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF6aSBHZW5lcmFsIHdhcyBrbm93biBhcyB0aGUgIkRlc2VydCBGb3giPw==",
            "answer": "RXJ3aW4gUm9tbWVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBzb2Z0IGRyaW5rLCBEci4gUGVwcGVyPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBBbGRlcnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNlZWQgZHJpbGwgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIEJyaXRpc2ggaW52ZW50b3I/",
            "answer": "SmV0aHJvIFR1bGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFNwaXRmaXJlIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIHJhY2luZyBwbGFuZS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkkgZGlzYXBwcm92ZSBvZiB3aGF0IHlvdSBzYXksIGJ1dCBJIHdpbGwgZGVmZW5kIHRvIHRoZSBkZWF0aCB5b3VyIHJpZ2h0IHRvIHNheSBpdCIgaXMgYSBxdW90ZSBmcm9tIEZyZW5jaCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlciBWb2x0YWlyZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnJlemhuZXYgd2FzIHRoZSA1dGggbGVhZGVyIG9mIHRoZSBVU1NSLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhZ2Ugd2FzIEtpbmcgSGVucnkgViB3aGVuIGhlIGRpZWQ/",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgRGVwYXJ0bWVudCBvZiBIb21lbGFuZCBTZWN1cml0eSB3YXMgZm9ybWVkIGluIHJlc3BvbnNlIHRvIHRoZSBTZXB0ZW1iZXIgMTF0aCBhdHRhY2tzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIHdhcyBOT1QgYSBwYXJ0IG9mIHRoZSBTb3ZpZXQgVW5pb24/",
            "answer": "QWZnaGFuaXN0YW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIGFwcG9pbnRlZCBhcyBDaGFuY2VsbG9yIG9mIEdlcm1hbnk/",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSAzMCwgMTkzMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSBjb21wYW55IEVsZWN0cm9uaWMgQXJ0cyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnVpbGRpbmcgd2FzIHNldCBhZmxhbWUgb24gQXVndXN0IDI0dGgsIDE4MTI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFdoaXRlIEhvdXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgR2VuZ2hpcyBLaGFuJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGVtw7xqaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBIYXN0aW5ncyB3YXMgZm91Z2h0IGluIHdoaWNoIHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MTA2Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIGF0dHJpYnV0ZWQgY3JlZGl0IGZvciByZWNvcmRpbmcgdGhlIGVwaWMgcG9lbSBUaGUgT2R5c3NleT8=",
            "answer": "SG9tZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHVub2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBmb3IgR2VybWFueSBiZXR3ZWVuIDE5MTkgYW5kIDE5MzM/",
            "answer": "V2VpbWFyIFJlcHVibGlj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBdXN0cmFsaWEgYmVjb21lIGEgZmVkZXJhdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIG5hbWUgb2YgTmV3IFlvcmsgQ2l0eT8=",
            "answer": "TmV3IEFtc3RlcmRhbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBnaWZ0ZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5IHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIG9mIEFtZXJpY2E/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc2hpcCB3aGljaCB3YXMgb25seSBhIGZldyBtaWxlcyBhd2F5IGZyb20gdGhlIFJNUyBUaXRhbmljIHdoZW4gaXQgc3RydWNrIGFuIGljZWJlcmcgb24gQXByaWwgMTQsIDE5MTI/",
            "answer": "Q2FsaWZvcm5pYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gYWRkaXRpb24gdG8gaGlzIGNhcmVlciBhcyBhbiBhc3Ryb2xvZ2VyIGFuZCAicHJvcGhldCIsIE5vc3RyYWRhbXVzIHB1Ymxpc2hlZCBhIDE1NTUgdHJlYXRpc2UgdGhhdCBpbmNsdWRlZCBhIHNlY3Rpb24gb24gd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "TWFraW5nIGphbXMgYW5kIGplbGxpZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTQ1Mywgd2hpY2ggaW1wb3J0YW50IGNpdHkgZmVsbD8=",
            "answer": "Q29uc3RhbnRpbm9wbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEtvcmVhbiBXYXIgZW5kZWQgaW4gMTk1MyB3aXRob3V0IGFueSBjZWFzZWZpcmUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgMTkwMHMgdGFua3Mgd2VyZSBkZXNpZ25lZCBhbmQgYnVpbHQgQkVGT1JFIHRoZSBvdGhlcnM/",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBGVA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhbnRoZW9uIGluIFJvbWUgd2FzIHVzZWQgdG8gd29yc2hpcCB3aGF0IGdvZD8=",
            "answer": "QW55IGdvZCB0aGV5IHdhbnRlZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBldmVudCBtYXJrZWQgdGhlIHN0YXJ0IG9mIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "SW52YXNpb24gb2YgUG9sYW5kICgxOTM5KQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBoaXN0b3JpY2FsIGV2ZW50IHdhcyBUY2hhaWtvdnNreSdzIDE4MTIgT3ZlcnR1cmUgcmVmZXJlbmNpbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5hcG9sZW9uaWMgV2Fycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGlkZWEgb2YgU29jaWFsaXNtIHdhcyBhcnRpY3VsYXRlZCBhbmQgYWR2YW5jZWQgYnkgd2hvbT8=",
            "answer": "S2FybCBNYXJ4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIFdXSUksIGluIDE5NDUsIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIGRyb3BwZWQgYXRvbWljIGJvbWJzIG9uIHRoZSB0d28gSmFwYW5lc2UgY2l0aWVzIG9mIEhpcm9zaGltYSBhbmQgd2hhdCBvdGhlciBjaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "TmFnYXNha2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIE00MSBXYWxrZXIgQnVsbGRvZyByZW1haW5zIGluIHNlcnZpY2UgaW4gc29tZSBjb3VudHJpZXMgdG8gdGhpcyBkYXku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIHJlbWFpbmVkIG5ldXRyYWwgZHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "U3dpdHplcmxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbGxhcHNlIG9mIHRoZSBTb3ZpZXQgVW5pb24gdG9vayBwbGFjZSBpbiB3aGljaCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5MQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHRyYW5zZmVyIG9mIGRpc2Vhc2UsIGNyb3BzLCBhbmQgcGVvcGxlIGFjcm9zcyB0aGUgQXRsYW50aWMgc2hvcnRseSBhZnRlciB0aGUgZGlzY292ZXJ5IG9mIHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhcyBjYWxsZWQ/",
            "answer": "VGhlIENvbHVtYmlhbiBFeGNoYW5nZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gb2JqZWN0aXZlIG9mIHRoZSBHZXJtYW4gb3BlcmF0aW9uICJDYXNlIEJsdWUiIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUkgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgdG8gY2FwdHVyZSB3aGF0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2F1Y2FzdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB3YXMgbm90IG9uZSBvZiBKb3NlcGggU3RhbGluJ3MgdGVuIGJsb3dzIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUk/",
            "answer": "VmlzdHVsYS1PZGVyIE9mZmVuc2l2ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgQWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NTY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgY29sb255IHRoZSBVSyBjZWRlZCBtYXJraW5nIHRoZSBlbmQgb2YgdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggRW1waXJlPw==",
            "answer": "SG9uZyBLb25n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVS5TLiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgd2FzIGluIG9mZmljZSB3aGVuIHRoZSBHdWxmIFdhciBiZWdhbj8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIEguIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHBsYW5uZWQgaW52YXNpb24gb2YgSmFwYW4gdG93YXJkcyB0aGUgZW5kIG9mIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJST8=",
            "answer": "T3BlcmF0aW9uIERvd25mYWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgbWFuIHRvIHRyYXZlbCBpbnRvIG91dGVyIHNwYWNlIHR3aWNlPw==",
            "answer": "R3VzIEdyaXNzb20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGZpcnN0IHRlbGV2aXNlZCBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgZGViYXRlIHdhcyBiZXR3ZWVuIEppbW15IENhcnRlciBhbmQgR2VyYWxkIEZvcmQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmFtb3VzIDQ1IGZvb3QgdGFsbCBIb2xseXdvb2Qgc2lnbiBmaXJzdCBlcmVjdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkyMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgaGlzIHNpeCB3aXZlcyB3YXMgSGVucnkgVklJSSBtYXJyaWVkIHRvIHRoZSBsb25nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIG9mIEFyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgTmF0aW9uYWwgU2VjdXJpdHkgQWdlbmN5IGVzdGFibGlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Tm92ZW1iZXIgNCwgMTk1Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTHluZG9uIEIuIEpvaG5zb24gd2hlbiBoZSBhc3N1bWVkIHRoZSByb2xlIG9mIFByZXNpZGVudCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "NTU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXBvbGxvIG1pc3Npb24gd2FzIHRoZSBsYXN0IG9uZSBpbiBOQVNBJ3MgQXBvbGxvIHByb2dyYW0/",
            "answer": "QXBvbGxvIDE3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgc29uYXRhcyBkaWQgTHVkd2lnIHZhbiBCZWV0aG92ZW4gd3JpdGU/",
            "answer": "MzI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQm94aW5nIERheSBlYXJ0aHF1YWtlICYgdHN1bmFtaSBvY2N1ciBpbiB0aGUgSW5kaWFuIE9jZWFuPw==",
            "answer": "MjAwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgc3VsdGFuIFNhbGFkaW4/",
            "answer": "S3VyZGlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBTcGFuaXNoIENpdmlsIFdhciAoMTkzNiksIEZyYW5jaXNjbyBGcmFuY28gZm91Z2h0IGZvciB3aGljaCBwb2xpdGljYWwgZmFjdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TmF0aW9uYWxpc3QgU3BhaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGNpdHkgb2YgUm9tZSwgSXRhbHkgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "NzUzIEJDRQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2Ygb25lIG9mIHRoZSBzdXJ2aXZpbmcgcGFsYWNlcyBvZiBIZW5yeSBWSUlJIGxvY2F0ZWQgbmVhciBSaWNobW9uZCwgTG9uZG9uPw==",
            "answer": "SGFtcHRvbiBDb3VydA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSSBiZWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "MTkxNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaGlzdG9yaWNhbCBuYW1lIG9mIFNyaSBMYW5rYT8=",
            "answer": "Q2V5bG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtvcmVhbiBXYXIgc3RhcnRlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MTk1MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgY29tbW9ubHkgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIGFuY2llbnQgdHJhZGUgcm91dGVzIHRoYXQgY29ubmVjdGVkIHRoZSBFYXN0IGFuZCBXZXN0IG9mIEV1cmFzaWE/",
            "answer": "U2lsayBSb2Fk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNoZW1pY2FsIHRoYXQgd2FzIGRyb3BwZWQgb24gVmlldG5hbSBkdXJpbmcgdGhlIFZpZXRuYW0gd2FyPw==",
            "answer": "QWdlbnQgT3Jhbmdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBkaWQgdGhlIEV1cmVrYSBSZWJlbGxpb24sIGFuIDE4NTYgYmF0dGxlIGFnYWluc3QgY29sb25pYWwgcnVsZSwgdGFrZSBwbGFjZSBpbj8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJhbGlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY291bnRyaWVzIHdhcyBzZWEgY2hhcnRlZCBpbiAxNTAwIGJ5IHRoZSBQb3J0dWd1ZXNlIG1hcml0aW1lIGV4cGxvcmF0aW9ucz8=",
            "answer": "QnJhemls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFRzYXIgQm9tYmEsIHRoZSBtb3N0IHBvd2VyZnVsIG51Y2xlYXIgYm9tYiBldmVyIHRlc3RlZCwgaGFkIGEgeWllbGQgb2YgNTAgbWVnYXRvbnMgYnV0IHRoZW9yZXRpY2FsbHkgaGFkIGEgbWF4aW11bSB5aWVsZCBvZiBob3cgbXVjaD8=",
            "answer": "MTAwIE1lZ2F0b25z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBc3N5cmlhbiBraW5ncyBkaWQgTk9UIHJ1bGUgZHVyaW5nIHRoZSBOZW8tQXNzeXJpYW4gRW1waXJlPw==",
            "answer": "U2hhbXNoaS1BZGFkIElJSQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCBjb25zdHJ1Y3Rpb24gc3RhcnQgb24gIlRoZSBQZW50YWdvbiIsIHRoZSBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcnMgZm9yIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIERlcGFydG1lbnQgb2YgRGVmZW5zZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDExLCAxOTQx"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgeW91IGdyYWIgdGhlIGJsYWRlZCBlbmQgb2YgYSBsb25nc3dvcmQgaW4gYSBzcGVjaWZpYyB3YXksIHlvdSB3aWxsIG5vdCBjdXQgeW91cnNlbGYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgTGl0aHVhbmlhIGRlY2xhcmUgaW5kZXBlbmRlbmNlIGZyb20gdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TWFyY2ggMTF0aCwgMTk5MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGlzIGNvbnNpZGVyZWQgdG8gYmUgdGhlIHllYXIgdGhhdCB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBFbXBpcmUgZW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEZyZW5jaCBLaW5nZG9tIGhlbHBlZCB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBnYWluIHRoZWlyIGluZGVwZW5kZW5jZSBvdmVyIEdyZWF0IEJyaXRhaW4gZHVyaW5nIHRoZSBSZXZvbHV0aW9uYXJ5IFdhci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhvbWFzIENyYXBwZXIgd2FzIGEgcGx1bWJlciB3aG8gaW52ZW50ZWQgdGhlIGZsdXNoaW5nIHRvaWxldC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTg0NSwgYSBzZXJpZXMgb2Ygd2FycyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB3aGljaCBpbmRpZ2Vub3VzIHBlb3BsZSBiZWdhbiBpbiBOZXcgWmVhbGFuZD8=",
            "answer": "TcSBb3Jp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTTE5MTEgcGlzdG9sIGRlc2lnbmVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBoYXBwZW5lZCBvbiBKdW5lIDYsIDE5NDQ/",
            "answer": "RC1EYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVS5TLiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgd2FzIGZhbW91c2x5ICdhdHRhY2tlZCcgYnkgYSBzd2ltbWluZyByYWJiaXQ/",
            "answer": "SmltbXkgQ2FydGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWJvbGl0aW9uaXN0IEpvaG4gQnJvd24gcmFpZGVkIHRoZSBhcnNlbmFsIGluIHdoaWNoIFZpcmdpbmlhIFRvd24/",
            "answer": "SGFycGVyJ3MgRmVycnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFBhbmFtYSBDYW5hbCB3YXMgZmluaXNoZWQgdW5kZXIgdGhlIGFkbWluaXN0cmF0aW9uIG9mIHdoaWNoIFUuUy4gcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "V29vZHJvdyBXaWxzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2FyZ29uIElJLCBhIGtpbmcgb2YgdGhlIE5lby1Bc3N5cmlhbiBFbXBpcmUsIHdhcyBhIGRpcmVjdCBkZXNjZW5kYW50IG9mIFNhcmdvbiBvZiBBa2thZC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgdGhlIEVuaWdtYSBDeXBoZXIgYW5kIE1hY2hpbmUgd2FzIG9mIHdoYXQgbmF0aW9uYWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "R2VybWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdhcyBhIGdlcm1hbiBzb2xkaWVyIGluIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb2xkZXN0IFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "RGVsYXdhcmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHRvdGFsIGxlbmd0aCBvZiB0aGUgVGl0YW5pYz8=",
            "answer": "ODgyIGZ0IHwgMjY4LjggbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTGFzIFZlZ2FzIGNhc2lubyB3YXMgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBjb25zdHJ1Y3RlZCBhbmQgb3BlcmF0ZWQgYnkgbW9ic3RlciBCdWdzeSBTaWVnZWw/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEZsYW1pbmdv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2gga2luZyB3YXMga2lsbGVkIGF0IHRoZSBCYXR0bGUgb2YgQm9zd29ydGggRmllbGQgaW4gMTQ4NT8g",
            "answer": "UmljaGFyZCBJSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFNwaXRmaXJlIEwuRi4gTWsgSVggaGFkIHdoYXQgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "TWVybGluIDY2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEtpbmdkb20gb2YgUHJ1c3NpYSBicmllZmx5IGhlbGQgbGFuZCBpbiBFc3RvbmlhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmxvb2RpZXN0IGV2ZW50IGluIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgaGlzdG9yeSwgaW4gdGVybXMgb2YgY2FzdWFsdGllcz8=",
            "answer": "QmF0dGxlIG9mIEFudGlldGFt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBUcmFmYWxnYXIgdG9vayBwbGFjZSBvbiBPY3RvYmVyIDIzcmQsIDE4MDU=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNvZGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlIEdlcm1hbiBpbnZhc2lvbiBvZiB0aGUgU292aWV0IFVuaW9uIGluIFdXMj8=",
            "answer": "T3BlcmF0aW9uIEJhcmJhcm9zc2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgdGhlIDE1MTYgQmF0dGxlIG9mIE1hcmogRGFiaXEsIHRoZSBPdHRvbWFuIEVtcGlyZSB0b29rIGNvbnRyb2wgb2YgSmVydXNhbGVtIGZyb20gd2hpY2ggc3VsdGFuYXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TWFtbHVr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgd2FzIGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBMZWFndWUgb2YgTmF0aW9ucy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50cyBKb2huIEFkYW1zIGFuZCBUaG9tYXMgSmVmZmVyc29uIGRpZWQgd2l0aGluIGhvdXJzIG9mIGVhY2ggb3RoZXIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgR29vZ2xlIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDQsIDE5OTg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBDaHJpc3RvcGhlciBDb2x1bWJ1cyBzYWlsZWQgdG8gQW1lcmljYSwgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHJlZ2lvbiBoZSBhcnJpdmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJhaGFtYXMgQXJjaGlwZWxhZ28="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgd29tZW4gam9pbmVkIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIEFybWVkIFNlcnZpY2VzIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUk/",
            "answer": "MzUwLDAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBhbW9uZyB0aG9zZSBraWxsZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTAgU21vbGVuc2ssIFJ1c3NpYSBwbGFuZSBjcmFzaCB0cmFnZWR5Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBvbGlzaCBQcmVzaWRlbnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggaGFuZC1vdmVyIHNvdmVyZWlnbnR5IG9mIEhvbmcgS29uZyBiYWNrIHRvIENoaW5hPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEdlcm1hbiBvZmZlbnNpdmUgb3BlcmF0aW9uIGluIE9jdG9iZXIgMTk0MSB0byB0YWtlIE1vc2NvdyBiZWZvcmUgd2ludGVyPw==",
            "answer": "T3BlcmF0aW9uIFR5cGhvb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Sm9zZXBoIFN0YWxpbidzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgSW9zZWIgQmVzc2FyaW9uaXMgZHplIER6dWdhc2h2aWxpLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiB0aGUgQnVsZ2UgZW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSAyNSwgMTk0NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSSBiZWdpbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVseSAyOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyb3duZWQgQ2hhcmxlbWFnbmUgYXMgSG9seSBSb21hbiBFbXBlcm9yIG9uIENocmlzdG1hcyBEYXkgaW4gODAwPw==",
            "answer": "UG9wZSBMZW8gSUlJ"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcG9zaXRpb25zIGRpZCB0aGUgYXN0cm9ub21lciBhbmQgcGh5c2ljaXN0IElzYWFjIE5ld3RvbiBub3QgaG9sZD8=",
            "answer": "U3VydmV5b3IgdG8gdGhlIENpdHkgb2YgTG9uZG9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSBNb25nb2xpYW4gaW52YXNpb25zIG9mIEphcGFuLCB3aGF0IHdlcmUgdGhlIE1vbmdvbCBib2F0cyBtb3N0bHkgc3RvcHBlZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "VHlwaG9vbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHJ1bGVycyBkaWQgbm90IGJlbG9uZyB0byB0aGUgSGFic2J1cmcgZHluYXN0eT8=",
            "answer": "UGhpbGlwIFY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U2lyIElzc2FjIE5ld3RvbiBzZXJ2ZWQgYXMgYSBNZW1iZXIgb2YgUGFybGlhbWVudCwgYnV0IHRoZSBvbmx5IHJlY29yZGVkIHRpbWUgaGUgc3Bva2Ugd2FzIHRvIGNvbXBsYWluIGFib3V0IGEgZHJhZnQgaW4gdGhlIGNoYW1iZXJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEJvaGVtaWFuIFJldm9sdCAoMTYxOC0xNjIwKSBzdGFydGVkIGFmdGVyIFByb3Rlc3RhbnRzIGluIFByYWd1ZSBkaWQgd2hhdCB0byB0aGVpciBDYXRob2xpYyBMb3JkcyBSZWdlbnRzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhyZXcgdGhlbSBvdXQgb2YgYSB3aW5kb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbWFubmVkIG1vb24gbGFuZGluZ3MgaGF2ZSB0aGVyZSBiZWVuPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgV2FsbCBTdHJlZXQgQ3Jhc2ggdGFrZSBwbGFjZT8=",
            "answer": "MTkyOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmNpZW50IHBlb3BsZXMgd2FzIE5PVCBjbGFzc2lmaWVkIGFzIEhlbGxlbmljIChHcmVlayk/",
            "answer": "SWxseXJpYW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVS5TLiBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG9vayBwYXJ0IGluIHRoZSBQb3RzZGFtIENvbmZlcmVuY2UsIHdoZXJlIHRoZSBBbGxpZXMgcmVhY2hlZCBhIHBlYWNlIHNldHRsZW1lbnQgd2l0aCBHZXJtYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "SGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdGhlb3JldGljYWwgcGh5Y2lzaXN0cyBmaXJzdCBwcmVkaWN0ZWQgdGhlIGV4aXN0ZW5jZSBvZiBhbnRpbWF0dGVyPw==",
            "answer": "UGF1bCBEaXJhYw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCBBUlBBTkVUIHN1ZmZlciBhIDQgaG91ciBsb25nIG5ldHdvcmsgY3Jhc2g/",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNywgMTk4MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHZlbmRpbmcgbWFjaGluZXMgaW4gdGhlIGVhcmx5IDE4ODAncyBkaXNwZW5zZT8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdCBjYXJkcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQcmVzaWRlbnRzIG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHdhcyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0ZWQ/",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBNY0tpbmxleQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBraW5nIHdhcyBtYXJyaWVkIHRvIEVsZWFub3Igb2YgQXF1aXRhaW5lPw==",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgSUk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgaW4gdGhlIEluZG8tRXVyb3BlYW4gbGFuZ3VhZ2UgZmFtaWx5Pw==",
            "answer": "RmlubmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYSBkZWNsYXJlZCB0aGVpciBpbmRlcGVuZGVuY2UgZnJvbSB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBFbXBpcmUgb24gSnVseSA0dGgsIDE3NzYu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9zZXBoIFNtaXRoIHdhcyB0aGUgZm91bmRlciBvZiB3aGF0IHJlbGlnaW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TW9ybW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gcmVsYXRpb24gdG8gdGhlIEJyaXRpc2ggT2NjdXBhdGlvbiBpbiBJcmVsYW5kLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgdGhlIElSQSBzdGFuZCBmb3Iu",
            "answer": "SXJpc2ggUmVwdWJsaWNhbiBBcm15"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBhIFNlbWV0aWMgbGFuZ3VhZ2U/",
            "answer": "U3VtZXJpYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyaWVzIHBhcnRpY2lwYXRlZCBpbiB0aGUgTG9ic3RlciBXYXI/",
            "answer": "RnJhbmNlIGFuZCBCcmF6aWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdhcyBib3JuIG9uIHdoaWNoIGRhdGU/",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjAsIDE4ODk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIGFiYnJldmlhdGlvbiAiUk1TIiBzdGFuZCBmb3IgaW4gdGhlIFJNUyBUaXRhbmljIGluIDE5MTI/",
            "answer": "Um95YWwgTWFpbCBTaGlw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEhhZ2lhIFNvcGhpYSB3YXMgY29tbWlzc2lvbmVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGVtcGVyb3Igb2YgdGhlIEJ5emFudGluZSBFbXBpcmU/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluaWFuIEk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHNwb3J0IHRvIGhhdmUgYmVlbiBwbGF5ZWQgb24gdGhlIG1vb24/",
            "answer": "R29sZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbW9kZXJuIGRheSBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSByZWdpb24gdGhhdCB3YXMga25vd24gYXMgUGhyeWdpYSBpbiBhbmNpZW50IHRpbWVzPw==",
            "answer": "VHVya2V5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGxvbmcgZGlkIHRoZSBXYXJzYXcgVXByaXNpbmcgZHVyaW5nIFdvcmxkIFdhciBJSSBsYXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "NjMgRGF5cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFNTIG9yIFNjaHV0enN0YWZmZWwgZXN0YWJsaXNoZWQ/",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgNHRoLCAxOTI1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFRpYW5hbm1lbiBTcXVhcmUgcHJvdGVzdHMgb2YgMTk4OSB3ZXJlIGhlbGQgaW4gSG9uZyBLb25nLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgVVMgTmF2eSBzcHkgc2hpcCB3aGljaCB3YXMgYXR0YWNrZWQgYW5kIGNhcHR1cmVkIGJ5IE5vcnRoIEtvcmVhbiBmb3JjZXMgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "VVNTIFB1ZWJsbw=="
        }
    ],
    "UG9saXRpY3M=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBhdCB0aGUgb3V0YnJlYWsgb2YgdGhlIFNlY29uZCBXb3JsZCBXYXI/",
            "answer": "TmV2aWxsZSBDaGFtYmVybGFpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIHZvdGVkIHRvIHN0YXkgaW4gdGhlIEVVLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBSYWlkIDI6IEJlcmFuZGFsIiB3YXMgbWFpbmx5IGZpbG1lZCBpbiB3aGljaCBBc2lhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgVS5TLiBIb3VzZSBvZiBSZXByZXNlbnRhdGl2ZXM/",
            "answer": "NDM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UnVzc2lhIHBhc3NlZCBhIGxhdyBpbiAyMDEzIHdoaWNoIG91dGxhd3MgdGVsbGluZyBjaGlsZHJlbiB0aGF0IGhvbW9zZXh1YWxzIGV4aXN0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTYsIGluIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIHllYXIgZGlkIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlcnNvbmFsIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSA0MHRoIEdvdmVybm9yIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBTdGF0ZSBMb3Vpc2lhbmEsIEh1ZXkgTG9uZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtpbmdmaXNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIHByZXNpZGVudCBUaGVvZG9yZSBSb29zZXZlbHQgKDE5MDAtMTkwOCkgIHJhbiBmb3IgYW5vdGhlciB0ZXJtIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBQcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSBQYXJ0eSBpbiAxOTEyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmViIEJ1c2ggd2FzIGVsZWN0ZWQgYXMgR292ZXJub3Igb2YgRmxvcmlkYSBpbiAyMDAyLCBzdGFydGluZyBoaXMgcG9saXRpY2FsIGNhcmVlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgd2FzIGEgc2F0aXJpY2FsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBuYW1lZCAiRGVleiBOdXRzIiBydW5uaW5nIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudGlhbCBlbGVjdGlvbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIHZvdGVkIHRvIHN0YXkgaW4gdGhlIEVVLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgVS5TLiBIb3VzZSBvZiBSZXByZXNlbnRhdGl2ZXM/",
            "answer": "NDM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVzcGl0ZSBiZWluZyBzZXBlcmF0ZWQgaW50byBtdWx0aXBsZSBjb3VudHJpZXMsIFRoZSBTY2FuZGluYXZpYW4gY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB1bmlmaWVkIGJ5IGFsbCBoYXZpbmcgdGhlIHNhbWUgbW9uYXJjaC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UnVzc2lhIHBhc3NlZCBhIGxhdyBpbiAyMDEzIHdoaWNoIG91dGxhd3MgdGVsbGluZyBjaGlsZHJlbiB0aGF0IGhvbW9zZXh1YWxzIGV4aXN0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2ggbG9zdCB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDA0IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTYsIGluIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIHllYXIgZGlkIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGVsZW4gQ2xhcmsgd2FzIHRoZSAzN3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVyIG9mIEF1c3RyYWxpYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIHByZXNpZGVudCBUaGVvZG9yZSBSb29zZXZlbHQgKDE5MDAtMTkwOCkgIHJhbiBmb3IgYW5vdGhlciB0ZXJtIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBQcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSBQYXJ0eSBpbiAxOTEyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmViIEJ1c2ggd2FzIGVsZWN0ZWQgYXMgR292ZXJub3Igb2YgRmxvcmlkYSBpbiAyMDAyLCBzdGFydGluZyBoaXMgcG9saXRpY2FsIGNhcmVlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBhdCB0aGUgb3V0YnJlYWsgb2YgdGhlIFNlY29uZCBXb3JsZCBXYXI/",
            "answer": "TmV2aWxsZSBDaGFtYmVybGFpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgd2FzIGEgc2F0aXJpY2FsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBuYW1lZCAiRGVleiBOdXRzIiBydW5uaW5nIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudGlhbCBlbGVjdGlvbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UnVzc2lhIHBhc3NlZCBhIGxhdyBpbiAyMDEzIHdoaWNoIG91dGxhd3MgdGVsbGluZyBjaGlsZHJlbiB0aGF0IGhvbW9zZXh1YWxzIGV4aXN0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2ggbG9zdCB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDA0IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBKb3NlcGggU3RhbGluIGFzIEdlbmVyYWwgU2VjcmV0YXJ5IG9mIHRoZSBDb21tdW5pc3QgUGFydHkgb2YgdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TmlraXRhIEtocnVzaGNoZXY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlcnNvbmFsIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSA0MHRoIEdvdmVybm9yIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBTdGF0ZSBMb3Vpc2lhbmEsIEh1ZXkgTG9uZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtpbmdmaXNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBhdCB0aGUgb3V0YnJlYWsgb2YgdGhlIFNlY29uZCBXb3JsZCBXYXI/",
            "answer": "TmV2aWxsZSBDaGFtYmVybGFpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgd2FzIGEgc2F0aXJpY2FsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBuYW1lZCAiRGVleiBOdXRzIiBydW5uaW5nIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudGlhbCBlbGVjdGlvbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIHZvdGVkIHRvIHN0YXkgaW4gdGhlIEVVLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBSYWlkIDI6IEJlcmFuZGFsIiB3YXMgbWFpbmx5IGZpbG1lZCBpbiB3aGljaCBBc2lhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgVS5TLiBIb3VzZSBvZiBSZXByZXNlbnRhdGl2ZXM/",
            "answer": "NDM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVzcGl0ZSBiZWluZyBzZXBlcmF0ZWQgaW50byBtdWx0aXBsZSBjb3VudHJpZXMsIFRoZSBTY2FuZGluYXZpYW4gY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB1bmlmaWVkIGJ5IGFsbCBoYXZpbmcgdGhlIHNhbWUgbW9uYXJjaC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTYsIGluIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIHllYXIgZGlkIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGVsZW4gQ2xhcmsgd2FzIHRoZSAzN3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVyIG9mIEF1c3RyYWxpYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBKb3NlcGggU3RhbGluIGFzIEdlbmVyYWwgU2VjcmV0YXJ5IG9mIHRoZSBDb21tdW5pc3QgUGFydHkgb2YgdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TmlraXRhIEtocnVzaGNoZXY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIHByZXNpZGVudCBUaGVvZG9yZSBSb29zZXZlbHQgKDE5MDAtMTkwOCkgIHJhbiBmb3IgYW5vdGhlciB0ZXJtIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBQcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSBQYXJ0eSBpbiAxOTEyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmViIEJ1c2ggd2FzIGVsZWN0ZWQgYXMgR292ZXJub3Igb2YgRmxvcmlkYSBpbiAyMDAyLCBzdGFydGluZyBoaXMgcG9saXRpY2FsIGNhcmVlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBSYWlkIDI6IEJlcmFuZGFsIiB3YXMgbWFpbmx5IGZpbG1lZCBpbiB3aGljaCBBc2lhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVzcGl0ZSBiZWluZyBzZXBlcmF0ZWQgaW50byBtdWx0aXBsZSBjb3VudHJpZXMsIFRoZSBTY2FuZGluYXZpYW4gY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB1bmlmaWVkIGJ5IGFsbCBoYXZpbmcgdGhlIHNhbWUgbW9uYXJjaC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UnVzc2lhIHBhc3NlZCBhIGxhdyBpbiAyMDEzIHdoaWNoIG91dGxhd3MgdGVsbGluZyBjaGlsZHJlbiB0aGF0IGhvbW9zZXh1YWxzIGV4aXN0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTYsIGluIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIHllYXIgZGlkIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBKb3NlcGggU3RhbGluIGFzIEdlbmVyYWwgU2VjcmV0YXJ5IG9mIHRoZSBDb21tdW5pc3QgUGFydHkgb2YgdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TmlraXRhIEtocnVzaGNoZXY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlcnNvbmFsIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSA0MHRoIEdvdmVybm9yIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBTdGF0ZSBMb3Vpc2lhbmEsIEh1ZXkgTG9uZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtpbmdmaXNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIHByZXNpZGVudCBUaGVvZG9yZSBSb29zZXZlbHQgKDE5MDAtMTkwOCkgIHJhbiBmb3IgYW5vdGhlciB0ZXJtIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBQcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSBQYXJ0eSBpbiAxOTEyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmViIEJ1c2ggd2FzIGVsZWN0ZWQgYXMgR292ZXJub3Igb2YgRmxvcmlkYSBpbiAyMDAyLCBzdGFydGluZyBoaXMgcG9saXRpY2FsIGNhcmVlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgb25seSBwcmVzaWRlbnQgdG8gbm90IGJlIGluIG9mZmljZSBpbiBXYXNoaW5ndG9uIEQuQz8=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFdhc2hpbmd0b24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgd2FzIGEgc2F0aXJpY2FsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBuYW1lZCAiRGVleiBOdXRzIiBydW5uaW5nIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudGlhbCBlbGVjdGlvbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBQYWNpZmljIElzbGFuZGVyIGNvdW50cmllcyBpcyBydWxlZCBieSBhIGNvbnN0aXR1dGlvbmFsIG1vbmFyY2h5Pw==",
            "answer": "VG9uZ2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIHZvdGVkIHRvIHN0YXkgaW4gdGhlIEVVLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBSYWlkIDI6IEJlcmFuZGFsIiB3YXMgbWFpbmx5IGZpbG1lZCBpbiB3aGljaCBBc2lhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgVS5TLiBIb3VzZSBvZiBSZXByZXNlbnRhdGl2ZXM/",
            "answer": "NDM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVzcGl0ZSBiZWluZyBzZXBlcmF0ZWQgaW50byBtdWx0aXBsZSBjb3VudHJpZXMsIFRoZSBTY2FuZGluYXZpYW4gY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB1bmlmaWVkIGJ5IGFsbCBoYXZpbmcgdGhlIHNhbWUgbW9uYXJjaC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTYgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRpbWUgSGlsbGFyeSBDbGludG9uIGhhcyBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UnVzc2lhIHBhc3NlZCBhIGxhdyBpbiAyMDEzIHdoaWNoIG91dGxhd3MgdGVsbGluZyBjaGlsZHJlbiB0aGF0IGhvbW9zZXh1YWxzIGV4aXN0Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T25lIG9mIEJhcmFjayBPYmFtYSdzIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGNhbXBhaWduIHNsb2dhbidzIHdhcyAiWWVzIFdlIENhbiIu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHNlbmF0b3JzIGlzIGtub3duIGZvciBwZXJmb3JtaW5nIGEgMjQtaG91ciBsb25nIGZpbGlidXN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "U3Ryb20gVGh1cm1vbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBmb3JtZXIgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uJ3MgZnVsbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBKZWZmZXJzb24gQ2xpbnRvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGVsZW4gQ2xhcmsgd2FzIHRoZSAzN3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVyIG9mIEF1c3RyYWxpYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdC1zZXJ2aW5nIHNlbmF0b3IgaW4gVVMgaGlzdG9yeSwgc2VydmluZyBmcm9tIDE5NTkgdG8gMjAxMD8=",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEJ5cmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIFdhdGVyZ2F0ZSBTY2FuZGFsIG9jY3VyZWQgaW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyPw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQnJpdGlzaCBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBhdCB0aGUgb3V0YnJlYWsgb2YgdGhlIFNlY29uZCBXb3JsZCBXYXI/",
            "answer": "TmV2aWxsZSBDaGFtYmVybGFpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDB0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVTQT8=",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTEsICJUcnVlIENhcGl0YWxpc3QgUmFkaW8iIHdhcyBrbm93biBieSBhIGRpZmZlcmVudCBuYW1lLiBXaGF0IHdhcyB0aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZSBDb25zZXJ2YXRpdmUgUmFkaW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFMgaW4gSGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFuIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgIlNhbXVlbCIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlcmUgd2FzIGEgc2F0aXJpY2FsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBuYW1lZCAiRGVleiBOdXRzIiBydW5uaW5nIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudGlhbCBlbGVjdGlvbnMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==",
            "answer": "WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGxhcmdlc3QgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0IGluIDIwMTUgd2FzLi4u",
            "answer": "VGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgb2YgQW1lcmljYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBLaW5nZG9tIHZvdGVkIHRvIHN0YXkgaW4gdGhlIEVVLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIDIwMTQgbW92aWUgIlRoZSBSYWlkIDI6IEJlcmFuZGFsIiB3YXMgbWFpbmx5IGZpbG1lZCBpbiB3aGljaCBBc2lhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "SW5kb25lc2lh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGVvcGxlIGFyZSBpbiB0aGUgVS5TLiBIb3VzZSBvZiBSZXByZXNlbnRhdGl2ZXM/",
            "answer": "NDM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVubWFyayBoYXMgYSBtb25hcmNoLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVzcGl0ZSBiZWluZyBzZXBlcmF0ZWQgaW50byBtdWx0aXBsZSBjb3VudHJpZXMsIFRoZSBTY2FuZGluYXZpYW4gY291bnRyaWVzIGFyZSB1bmlmaWVkIGJ5IGFsbCBoYXZpbmcgdGhlIHNhbWUgbW9uYXJjaC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggbGV0dGVyIGRvIHlvdSBuZWVkIHRvIGhhdmUgb24gYSBFdXJvcGVhbiBkcml2ZXIgbGljZW5zZSBpbiBvcmRlciB0byByaWRlIGFueSBtb3RvcmJpa2VzPw==",
            "answer": "QQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RHVyaW5nIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLCB0aGUgU3RhdGUgb2YgQ2FsaWZvcm5pYSBwb3NzZXNzZWQgdGhlIG1vc3QgZWxlY3RvcmFsIHZvdGVzLCBoYXZpbmcgNTUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Sm9rbyBXaWRvZG8gaGFzIGFwcGVhcmVkIGluIHRoZSBjb3ZlciBvZiBhIFRJTUUgbWFnYXppbmUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2ggbG9zdCB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDA0IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIENvbnN0aXR1dGlvbiwgaG93IG9sZCBtdXN0IGEgcGVyc29uIGJlIHRvIGJlIGVsZWN0ZWQgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IlllcywgQW1lcmljYSBDYW4hIiB3YXMgdGhpcyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIHBvbGl0aWNpYW4ncyBkZSBmYWN0byBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gaW4gMjAwNC4=",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIFcuIEJ1c2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIFByZXNpZGVudHMgc2VydmVkIHRoZSBzaG9ydGVzdCB0ZXJtIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGlhbSBIZW5yeSBIYXJyaXNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgNDV0aCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgb2YgdGhlIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXM/",
            "answer": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXRlIG9mIFF1ZWVuc2xhbmQsIEF1c3RyYWxpYSB2b3RlZCBOTyB0byBhIHJlZmVyZW5kdW0gZm9yIGRheWxpZ2h0IHNhdmluZ3MgaW4gMTk5Mi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIFRydW1wIHdvbiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciB2b3RlIGluIHRoZSAyMDE2IFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsIGVsZWN0aW9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TmF6aSBHZXJtYW55IHN1cnJlbmRlcmVkIG9uIEhhcnJ5IFRydW1hbidzIGJpcnRoZGF5IHdoaWxlIGhlIHdhcyBwcmVzaWRlbnQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaWNjb2zDsiBNYWNoaWF2ZWxsaSdzIHdvcmsgdGhhdCBhcmd1ZWQgZWZmZWN0aXZlIGxlYWRlcnMgbmVlZGVkIHRvIGNydXNoIHRoZWlyIG9wcG9uZW50cyBhdCBhbGwgY29zdHM/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFByaW5jZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBjZW50cmFsaXNtPw==",
            "answer": "IENvbmNlbnRyYXRpb24gb2YgcG93ZXIgYW5kIGF1dGhvcml0eSBpbiBhIGNlbnRyYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uLg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJlY2FtZSBQcmltZSBNaW5pc3RlciBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20gaW4gSnVseSAyMDE2Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlcmVzYSBNYXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGxlYWRlciBvZiB0aGUgVUsgTGFib3VyIFBhcnR5IGluIFNlcHRlbWJlciAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IENvcmJ5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "R2VvcmdlIENsaW50b24sIFZpY2UgUHJlc2lkZW50IG9mIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzICgxODA1LTE4MTIpLCBpcyBhbiBhbmNlc3RvciBvZiBQcmVzaWRlbnQgQmlsbCBDbGludG9uLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIDIwMTYsIGluIHdoaWNoIG90aGVyIHllYXIgZGlkIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCBydW4gZm9yIFByZXNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIG9uZSBvZiBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVsaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyBoaXN0b3J5LCBob3cgbWFueSB2aWNlIHByZXNpZGVudHMgZGlkIEZyYW5rbGluIEQuIFJvb3NldmVsdCBoYXZlIGR1cmluZyBoaXMgdGltZSBpbiBvZmZpY2UgYXMgcHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SGVsZW4gQ2xhcmsgd2FzIHRoZSAzN3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVyIG9mIEF1c3RyYWxpYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=",
            "answer": "U2F4b3Bob25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd2FzIGFuIG9mZmljaWFsIGNhbmRpZGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgMjAxNyBCcml0aXNoIEdlbmVyYWwgRWxlY3Rpb24/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBCdWNrZXRoZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHN1Y2NlZWRlZCBKb3NlcGggU3RhbGluIGFzIEdlbmVyYWwgU2VjcmV0YXJ5IG9mIHRoZSBDb21tdW5pc3QgUGFydHkgb2YgdGhlIFNvdmlldCBVbmlvbj8=",
            "answer": "TmlraXRhIEtocnVzaGNoZXY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHBlcnNvbmFsIG5pY2tuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSA0MHRoIEdvdmVybm9yIG9mIHRoZSBVUyBTdGF0ZSBMb3Vpc2lhbmEsIEh1ZXkgTG9uZz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEtpbmdmaXNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gSnVuZSAyMDE3LCBTYXVkaSBBcmFiaWEgYW5kIEVneXB0IGJyb2tlIG9mZiB0aWVzIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBvdmVyIGl0cyBzdXBwb3NlZCBzdXBwb3J0IGZvciB0ZXJyb3Jpc20/",
            "answer": "UWF0YXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Rm9ybWVyIHByZXNpZGVudCBUaGVvZG9yZSBSb29zZXZlbHQgKDE5MDAtMTkwOCkgIHJhbiBmb3IgYW5vdGhlciB0ZXJtIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBQcm9ncmVzc2l2ZSBQYXJ0eSBpbiAxOTEyLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB1c2VkICJMZXQncyBNYWtlIEFtZXJpY2EgR3JlYXQgQWdhaW4iIGFzIGhpcyBjYW1wYWlnbiBzbG9nYW4gYmVmb3JlIERvbmFsZCBUcnVtcCdzIGNhbXBhaWduPw==",
            "answer": "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9ybWVyIFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB3YXMgbmlja25hbWVkICJUZWRkeSIgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgcmVmdXNlZCB0byBzaG9vdCBhIGRlZmVuc2VsZXNzIGJsYWNrIGJlYXI/",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgUm9vc2V2ZWx0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SmViIEJ1c2ggd2FzIGVsZWN0ZWQgYXMgR292ZXJub3Igb2YgRmxvcmlkYSBpbiAyMDAyLCBzdGFydGluZyBoaXMgcG9saXRpY2FsIGNhcmVlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBHZXJhbGQgRm9yZCBCZWNvbWUgUHJlc2lkZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZWZmb3J0IHRvIGRlcGxveSB0aGUgQ29tbW9uIENvcmUgU3RhdGUgU3RhbmRhcmRzIChDQ1NTKSBpbiB0aGUgVVMgYmVnaW4/",
            "answer": "MjAwOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBmYXRoZXIgYW5kIHNvbiBwYWlyIHRoYXQgd2VyZSBib3RoIFByaW1lIE1pbmlzdGVycyBvZiBDYW5hZGE/",
            "answer": "SnVzdGluIGFuZCBQaWVycmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0d2VlbiAxOTczIHRvIDE5OTAsIHdoYXQgY291bnRyeSB3YXMgcnVsZWQgYnkgZGljdGF0b3IgQXVndXN0byBQaW5vY2hldD8=",
            "answer": "Q2hpbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBBcmdlbnRpbmlhbiBwcmVzaWRlbnRzIHdhcyBlbGVjdGVkIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "answer": "TWF1cmljaW8gTWFjcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IFVTIHByZXNpZGVudCB0byBzZXJ2ZSB0d28gbm9uLWNvbnNlY3V0aXZlIHRlcm1zIGluIG9mZmljZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JvdmVyIENsZXZlbGFuZA=="
        }
    ],
    "QXJ0": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=",
            "answer": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGFpbnRlciBQaWV0IE1vbmRyaWFuICgxODcyIC0gMTk0NCkgd2FzIGEgcGFydCBvZiB3aGF0IG1vdmVtZW50Pw==",
            "answer": "TmVvcGxhc3RpY2lzbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGltZSBzaWduYXR1cmUgaXMgY29tbW9ubHkga25vd24gYXMg4oCcQ3V0IFRpbWU/4oCd",
            "answer": "Mi8y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIFNpc3RpbmUgQ2hhcGVsPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBGcmVuY2ggc2N1bHB0b3IgZGVzaWduZWQgdGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5PyA=",
            "answer": "RnLDqWTDqXJpYyBBdWd1c3RlIEJhcnRob2xkaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kncyBNb25hIExpc2EgZG9lcyBub3QgaGF2ZSBleWVicm93cy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN04oCZcyBzdHVkaW8gd2FzIGtub3duIGFzICdUaGUgRmFjdG9yeSc/",
            "answer": "QW5keSBXYXJob2w="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYXRpb25hbGl0eSB3YXMgdGhlIHN1cnJlYWxpc3QgcGFpbnRlciBTYWx2YWRvciBEYWxpPw==",
            "answer": "U3BhbmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QWxicmVjaHQgRMO8cmVyJ3MgYmlydGhwbGFjZSBhbmQgcGxhY2Ugb2YgZGVhdGggd2VyZSBpbi4uLg==",
            "answer": "TsO8cm5iZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naCBjdXQgb2ZmIG9uZSBvZiBoaXMgZWFycy4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBBbGJyZWNodCBEw7xyZXIgY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBwYWludGluZyAiVGhlIFlvdW5nIEhhcmUiPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhIGZpbmlzaGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTUwNA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgIlN3YW5zIFJlZmxlY3RpbmcgRWxlcGhhbnRzIiwgIlNsZWVwIiwgYW5kICJUaGUgUGVyc2lzdGVuY2Ugb2YgTWVtb3J5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGZvdW5kaW5nIGZhdGhlcnMgb2YgIkN1YmlzbS4i",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHBhaW50aW5ncyBpcyBub3QgYnkgQ2FzcGFyIERhdmlkIEZyaWVkcmljaD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIFNlYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgZmFtb3VzIG1hcmtlciBicmFuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29waWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0J3Mgc3R5bGUgd2FzIHRvIHVzZSBzbWFsbCBkaWZmZXJlbnQgY29sb3JlZCBkb3RzIHRvIGNyZWF0ZSBhIHBpY3R1cmU/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlcyBTZXVyYXQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGFuIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgdmFyaWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBjb2xvciBwdXJwbGU/",
            "answer": "S29iaWNoYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2kgd2FzIG5vdCB0aGUgY3JlYXRvciBvZiB0aGUgTW9uYSBMaXNhLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgcGFpbnQgYW5kIHBhc3RlbCB2ZXJzaW9ucyBvZiAiVGhlIFNjcmVhbSIgaXMgTm9yd2VnaWFuIHBhaW50ZXIgRWR2YXJkIE11bmNoIGJlbGlldmVkIHRvIGhhdmUgcHJvZHVjZWQ/",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
            "answer": "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgVGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFuIEdvZ2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgZGVwaWN0cyB0aGUgdmlldyBmcm9tIGhpcyBhc3lsdW0gaW4gU2FpbnQtUsOpbXktZGUtUHJvdmVuY2UgaW4gc291dGhlcm4gRnJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN0YXJyeSBOaWdodA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VmVudXMgb2YgV2lsbGVuZG9yZiBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIGVhcmxpZXN0IHdvcmtzIG9mIGFydCwgZGVwaWN0aW5nIHRoZSBwbGFuZXRzIE1hcnMgYW5kIFZlbnVzIGVtYnJhY2UgaW4gdGhlIGhlYXZlbnMgYXQgbmlnaHQu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFpbnRpbmcgd2FzIG5vdCBtYWRlIGJ5IFZpbmNlbnQgVmFuIEdvZ2g/",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5pbnRoIFdhdmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFN0YXR1ZSBvZiBMaWJlcnR5J3Mgb2ZmaWNpYWwgbmFtZSBpcyDigJxMaWJlcnR5IEVubGlnaHRlbmluZyB0aGUgV29ybGTigJ0u",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHBhaW50aW5nICJUaGUgU3RhcnJ5IE5pZ2h0IiBieSBWaW5jZW50IHZhbiBHb2doIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIHdoaWNoIGFydCBtb3ZlbWVudD8=",
            "answer": "UG9zdC1JbXByZXNzaW9uaXNt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGVwaWMgbXVyYWwgR3Vlcm5pY2E/",
            "answer": "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIGJpYmxpY2FsIGZyZXNjbyBUaGUgQ3JlYXRpb24gb2YgQWRhbT8=",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        }
    ],
    "Q2VsZWJyaXRpZXM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIGRlYXRoIGZvciBGcmVkZGllIE1lcmN1cnk/",
            "answer": "UG5ldW1vbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIGRlYXRoIGZvciBGcmVkZGllIE1lcmN1cnk/",
            "answer": "UG5ldW1vbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIGRlYXRoIGZvciBGcmVkZGllIE1lcmN1cnk/",
            "answer": "UG5ldW1vbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIGRlYXRoIGZvciBGcmVkZGllIE1lcmN1cnk/",
            "answer": "UG5ldW1vbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2VsZWJyaXRpZXMgd2FzIG5vdCBhIG1lbWJlciBvZiB0aGUgSmFja3NvbiA1Pw==",
            "answer": "Qm8gSmFja3Nvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgSmFrZSBMbG95ZCB3aG8gcGxheWVkIEFuYWtpbiBTa3l3YWxrZXIgaW4gVGhlIFBoYW50b20gTWVuYWNlIHRvIHF1aXQgYWN0aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "QnVsbHlpbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=",
            "answer": "U3VuZGFuY2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcydzIHJlYWwgbmFtZSB3YXMgRnJhbmNlcyBFdGhlbCBHdW1tPw==",
            "answer": "SnVkeSBHYXJsYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljaGFlbCBKYWNrc29uIGhhZCBhIHBldCBweXRob24gbmFtZWQg4oCYQ3J1c2hlcuKAmS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mICJtb290IiwgZm91bmRlciBvZiB0aGUgaW1hZ2Vib2FyZCA0Y2hhbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXN0b3BoZXIgUG9vbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEb3VnIFdhbGtlcidzIFlvdVR1YmUgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIE5vc3RhbGdpYSBDcml0aWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "UGF1bCBNY0NhcnRuZXkgaGFzIGFsd2F5cyB1c2VkIGhpcyBtaWRkbGUgbmFtZS4gV2hhdCBpcyBoaXMgcmVhbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lPyA=",
            "answer": "SmFtZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIENhcmxvcyBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93bj8g",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==",
            "answer": "Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIEouIFRydW1wJ3MgTWlkZGxlIE5hbWUgaXMuLi4=",
            "answer": "Sm9obg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCByYWRpbyBpY29uIEhvd2FyZCBTdGVybiBzdGFydCBhIGpvYiBhdCByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIFdOQkM/",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcGVvcGxlIGlzIE5PVCBhIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIEludGVybmV0IGNvbWVkeSBncm91cCBNZWdhNjQ/",
            "answer": "Sm9uIEphZmFyaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIGRlYXRoIGZvciBGcmVkZGllIE1lcmN1cnk/",
            "answer": "UG5ldW1vbmlh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBib3JuPw==",
            "answer": "SmFudWFyeSA4LCAxOTM1"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlbGlnaW9uIG9mIGZhbW91cyBzaW5nZXIgIkZyZWRkaWUgTWVyY3VyeSI/",
            "answer": "Wm9yb2FzdHJpYW5pc20="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIGZpbG0gbWFrZXIgRGFuIEJlbGwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGZvY3VzIGhpcyBmaWxtcyBvbj8=",
            "answer": "QWJhbmRvbmVkIEJ1aWxkaW5ncyBhbmQgRGVhZCBNYWxscw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGNhdXNlIG9mIE1hcmlseW4gTW9ucm9lcyBzdWljaWRlPw==",
            "answer": "RHJ1ZyBPdmVyZG9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IHRhbGwgaXMgVG9tIENydWlzZT8=",
            "answer": "NeKAsiA34oCz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R3d5bmV0aCBQYWx0cm93IGhhcyBhIGRhdWdodGVyIG5hbWVkLi4uPw==",
            "answer": "QXBwbGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBnZW5lcmFsbHkgY29uc2lkZXJlZCB0byBiZSBXaWxsaWFtIFNoYWtlc3BlYXJlJ3MgYmlydGggZGF0ZT8=",
            "answer": "QXByaWwgMjNyZCwgMTU2NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SWYgaGUgd2FzIHN0aWxsIGFsaXZlLCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXIgd291bGQgRWx2aXMgUHJlc2xleSBjZWxlYnJhdGUgaGlzIDEwMHRoIGJpcnRoZGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAzNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmVmb3JlIHZvaWNpbmcgUGVhcmwgaW4gU3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNlLCBEZWVkZWUgTWFnbm8gSGFsbCB3YXMgcGFydCBvZiB3aGljaCBBbWVyaWNhbiBiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBhcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2VsZWJyaXR5IGFubm91bmNlZCBoaXMgcHJlc2lkZW5jeSBpbiAyMDE1Pw==",
            "answer": "S2FueWUgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXVicmV5IEdyYWhhbSBpcyBiZXR0ZXIga25vd24gYXM=",
            "answer": "RHJha2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgd2FzIEthbnllIFdlc3QgYm9ybj8=",
            "answer": "QXRsYW50YSwgR2VvcmdpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIE5ldyBZb3JrIFlhbmtlZXMgb3V0ZmllbGRlciBkaWQgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UgbWFycnk/",
            "answer": "Sm9lIERpTWFnZ2lv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgTWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2UncyBmaXJzdCBodXNiYW5kPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgRG91Z2hlcnR5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWFyaWx5biBNb25yb2Ugd2FzIGJvcm4gb24gSnVseSAxLCAxOTI2Lg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcmFkaW8gcGVyc29uYWxpdHkgY2FsbHMgaGltc2VsZiAiVGhlIEtpbmcgb2YgQWxsIE1lZGlhIj8=",
            "answer": "SG93YXJkIFN0ZXJu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggd2VpZ2h0IGRpZCBDaHJpcyBQcmF0dCBsb3NlIGZvciBoaXMgcm9sZSBhcyBTdGFyLUxvcmQgaW4gIkd1YXJkaWFucyBvZiB0aGUgR2FsYXh5Ij8=",
            "answer": "NjAgbGJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlra2kgRGlhbW9uZCBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggR2xhZGlhdG9yIGluIHRoZSAxOTkyIFRWIHNob3cgIkdsYWRpYXRvcnMiPw==",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIG91dCBvZiB0aGVzZSBhY3RyZXNzZXMgaXMgdGhlIHlvdW5nZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "S2llcm5hbiBTaGlwa2E="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TGFkeSBHYWdhJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lIGlzIFN0ZWZhbmkgSm9hbm5lIEFuZ2VsaW5hIEdlcm1hbm90dGEu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQm9iIFJvc3MiIGRpZT8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VHVwYWMgU2hha3VyIGRpZWQgZHVlIHRvIGNvbXBsaWNhdGlvbnMgZnJvbSBiZWluZyBzdGFiYmVkIGluIDE5OTYu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgVFYgc2hvd3MgZGlkIHRoZSBjaGVmIEdvcmRvbiBSYW1zYXkgbm90IGFwcGVhcj8=",
            "answer": "QXVjdGlvbiBIdW50ZXJz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2Nob29sIGluIFN1cnJleSwgRW5nbGFuZCBkaWQgU3RldmUgQmFja3NoYWxsIGF0dGVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Q29sbGluZ3dvb2QgQ29sbGVnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmVpbCBIYW1idXJnZXIgaXMgcGxheWVkIGJ5IHdoaWNoIGNvbWVkaWFuPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZ2cgVHVya2luZ3Rvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGVjY2VudHJpYyBuYXR1cmFsIHBoaWxvc29waGVyIFR5Y2hvIEJyYWhlIGtlcHQgd2hhdCBhcyBhIHBldD8=",
            "answer": "TW9vc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzICJKYW1lcyBSb2xmZSIgYmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEFuZ3J5IFZpZGVvIEdhbWUgTmVyZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gY2VsZWJyaXR5IGRpZWQgaW4gMTk3NyBwbGF5aW5nIGdvbGYgaW4gTGEgTW9yYWxlamEsIE1hZHJpZD8=",
            "answer": "QmluZyBDcm9zYnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "TWFydGluIFNoZWVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBEb25hbGQgVHJ1bXAncyBmaXJzdCB3aWZlPw==",
            "answer": "SXZhbmEgWmVsbsOtxI1rb3bDoQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R2FiZSBOZXdlbGwgd2FzIGJvcm4gaW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhcj8=",
            "answer": "MTk2MiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbHkgSGVycmluZ3RvbiBpcyBmcm9tIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFlvcms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVFYgY2hlZiB3cm90ZSBhbiBhdXRvYmlvZ3JhcGh5IHRpdGxlZCAiSHVtYmxlIFBpZSI/",
            "answer": "R29yZG9uIFJhbXNheQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBPLkouIFNpbXBzb24gYXF1aXR0ZWQgb2YgaGlzIG11cmRlciBjaGFyZ2VzPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgdGhpcyBuZXcgdG9wIDEwMCByYXBwZXIgd2hvIGZlYXR1cmVkIGluICJDb21wdXRlcnMiIGFuZCAiQm9keSBEYW5jZSIgd2FzIGFycmVzdGVkIGluIGEgTllQRCBzdGluZyBmb3IgbXVyZGVyLg==",
            "answer": "Qm9iYnkgU2htdXJkYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgTXVoYW1tYWQgQWxpIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=",
            "answer": "NzQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdGVsZXZpc2lvbiBzaG93IGhhcyBEYW4gR2hlZXNsaW5nIGJlZW4gb24/",
            "answer": "QmlnIEJyb3RoZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgSmFtZXMgQ29idXJuJ3MgbGFzdCBmaWxtIHJvbGUgYmVmb3JlIGhpcyBkZWF0aD8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gR3Vu"
        }
    ],
    "QW5pbWFscw==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEV0aGlvcGlhbiBXb2xmIGJlZm9yZSB0aGV5IGtuZXcgaXQgd2FzIHJlbGF0ZWQgdG8gd29sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltaWVuIEphY2tlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCAgbGFuZCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "Q2hlZXRhaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENlcmF0b3NhdXJ1cywgYSBkaW5vc2F1ciBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIGEgaG9ybiBvbiB0aGUgdG9wIG9mIGl0cyBub3NlLCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIHRvIGJlIGEgZGVjZW5kZW50IG9mIHRoZSBUeXJhbm5vc2F1cnVzIFJleC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IGh1bWFucz8=",
            "answer": "SG9tbyBTYXBpZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEvEgWvEgXDFjSBpcyBhIGxhcmdlLCBmbGlnaHRsZXNzLCBub2N0dXJuYWwgcGFycm90IG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvci9jb2xvdXIgaXMgYSBwb2xhciBiZWFyJ3Mgc2tpbj8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXMgaXMgdGhlIExhdGluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIG1hcmluZSBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VhaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2FuZ2Fyb29zIGtlZXAgZm9vZCBpbiB0aGVpciBwb3VjaGVzIG5leHQgdG8gdGhlaXIgY2hpbGRyZW4u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN1Ym9yZGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIGZhbWlseSBIeWFlbmlkYWUgYmVsb25nIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "RmVsaWZvcm1pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9yIHdoYXQgcmVhc29uIHdvdWxkIGEgc3BvdHRlZCBoeWVuYSAibGF1Z2giPw==",
            "answer": "TmVydm91c25lc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgY2FsbCBhIGJhYnkgYmF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIFJ1c3NpYW4gZG9tZXN0aWNhdGlvbiBleHBlcmltZW50IGluIDE5NTk/",
            "answer": "Rm94ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIElVQ04gcmVjbGFzc2lmaWVkIHRoZSBzdGF0dXMgb2YgR2lhbnQgUGFuZGFzIGZyb20gZW5kYW5nZXJlZCB0byB2dWxuZXJhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdyBleHRpbmN0IHNwZWNpZXMgIlRoeWxhY2luZSIgd2FzIG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFzbWFuaWEsIEF1c3RyYWxpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBmbG9jayBvZiBjcm93cyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBhIGhvbWljaWRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBpcyBOT1QgYSBsaXphcmQ/",
            "answer": "VHVhdGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5saWtlIG9uIG1vc3Qgc2FsYW1hbmRlcnMsIHRoaXMgcGFydCBvZiBhIG5ld3QgaXMgZmxhdD8=",
            "answer": "VGFpbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2cgYnJlYWQgaXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBvbGRlc3QgYnJlZWRzIG9mIGRvZyBhbmQgaGFzIGZsb3VyaXNoZWQgc2luY2UgYmVmb3JlIDQwMCBCQ0Uu",
            "answer": "UHVncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "UGVyZWdyaW5lIEZhbGNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpc2ggRnVndSwgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIHdoYXQgZmFtaWx5IG9mIGZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UHVmZmVyZmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBjb2xvbnkgb2YgcG9seXBzIGFuZCBub3QgYSBqZWxseWZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZSBNYW4tb2YtV2Fy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBjYW4gc2VlIHdoYXQncyBiZWhpbmQgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyB3aXRob3V0IHR1cm5pbmcgdGhlaXIgaGVhZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvdXIgaXMgdGhlIGZlbWFsZSBibGFja2JpcmQ/",
            "answer": "QnJvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgYSBtYWxlIGJlZSB0aGF0IGNvbWVzIGZyb20gYW4gdW5mZXJ0aWxpemVkIGVnZz8=",
            "answer": "RHJvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBiZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "U2xvdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciByYXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWlzY2hpZWY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGJyb3dzZXIgRmlyZWZveCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgUmVkIFBhbmRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRlY2Fwb2RzIiBhcmUgYW4gb3JkZXIgb2YgdGVuLWZvb3RlZCBjcnVzdGFjZWFucy4gIFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFyZSBOT1QgZGVjYXBvZHM/",
            "answer": "S3JpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gd2hpY2ggYmlvbG9naWNhbCBwaHlsdW0gZG8gYWxsIG1hbW1hbHMsIGJpcmRzIGFuZCByZXB0aWxlcyBiZWxvbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2hvcmRhdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBsb25nZXN0IHZlbm9tb3VzIHNuYWtlPw==",
            "answer": "S2luZyBDb2JyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZyZXNod2F0ZXIgYW1waGliaWFuLCB0aGUgQXhvbG90bCwgY2FuIHJlZ3JvdyBpdCdzIGxpbWJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEV0aGlvcGlhbiBXb2xmIGJlZm9yZSB0aGV5IGtuZXcgaXQgd2FzIHJlbGF0ZWQgdG8gd29sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltaWVuIEphY2tlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCBpcyBhIG5hdHRlcmphY2s/",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCAgbGFuZCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "Q2hlZXRhaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENlcmF0b3NhdXJ1cywgYSBkaW5vc2F1ciBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIGEgaG9ybiBvbiB0aGUgdG9wIG9mIGl0cyBub3NlLCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIHRvIGJlIGEgZGVjZW5kZW50IG9mIHRoZSBUeXJhbm5vc2F1cnVzIFJleC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEvEgWvEgXDFjSBpcyBhIGxhcmdlLCBmbGlnaHRsZXNzLCBub2N0dXJuYWwgcGFycm90IG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvci9jb2xvdXIgaXMgYSBwb2xhciBiZWFyJ3Mgc2tpbj8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgcmhpbm8ncyBob3JuIG1hZGUgb2Y/",
            "answer": "S2VyYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN1Ym9yZGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIGZhbWlseSBIeWFlbmlkYWUgYmVsb25nIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "RmVsaWZvcm1pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9yIHdoYXQgcmVhc29uIHdvdWxkIGEgc3BvdHRlZCBoeWVuYSAibGF1Z2giPw==",
            "answer": "TmVydm91c25lc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdyBleHRpbmN0IHNwZWNpZXMgIlRoeWxhY2luZSIgd2FzIG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFzbWFuaWEsIEF1c3RyYWxpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2UgbGlmZXNwYW4gb2YgYSB3aWxkY2F0IGlzIG9ubHkgYXJvdW5kIDUtNiB5ZWFycy4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgcm9kZW50cy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBmbG9jayBvZiBjcm93cyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBhIGhvbWljaWRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBpcyBOT1QgYSBsaXphcmQ/",
            "answer": "VHVhdGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNyZWF0dXJlIGlzIGEgQm9ub2JvPw==",
            "answer": "QXBl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2xhc3Mgb2YgYW5pbWFscyBhcmUgbmV3dHMgbWVtYmVycyBvZj8=",
            "answer": "QW1waGliaWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmFtaWx5IHRoYXQgdGhlIGRvbWVzdGljIGNhdCBpcyBhIG1lbWJlciBvZj8=",
            "answer": "RmVsaWRhZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2F0cyBoYXZlIHdoaXNrZXJzIHVuZGVyIHRoZWlyIGxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29wcGVyLXJpY2ggcHJvdGVpbiB0aGF0IGNyZWF0ZXMgdGhlIGJsdWUgYmxvb2QgaW4gdGhlIEFudGFyY3RpYyBvY3RvcHVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVtb2N5YW5pbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "UGVyZWdyaW5lIEZhbGNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpc2ggRnVndSwgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIHdoYXQgZmFtaWx5IG9mIGZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UHVmZmVyZmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmlubmlzaCBMYXBwaHVuZCBkb2dzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgaGVyZGluZyByZWluZGVlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tb24gQ2hpbXBhbnplZT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuIHRyb2dsb2R5dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnkgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiwgd2hlcmUgZG9lcyBhbiBhYnlzc29wZWxhZ2ljIGFuaW1hbCBsaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXQgdGhlIGJvdHRvbSBvZiB0aGUgb2NlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBjb2xvbnkgb2YgcG9seXBzIGFuZCBub3QgYSBqZWxseWZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZSBNYW4tb2YtV2Fy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBiZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "U2xvdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciByYXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWlzY2hpZWY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciB2dWx0dXJlcz8=",
            "answer": "V2FrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGJyb3dzZXIgRmlyZWZveCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgUmVkIFBhbmRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRlY2Fwb2RzIiBhcmUgYW4gb3JkZXIgb2YgdGVuLWZvb3RlZCBjcnVzdGFjZWFucy4gIFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFyZSBOT1QgZGVjYXBvZHM/",
            "answer": "S3JpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gd2hpY2ggYmlvbG9naWNhbCBwaHlsdW0gZG8gYWxsIG1hbW1hbHMsIGJpcmRzIGFuZCByZXB0aWxlcyBiZWxvbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2hvcmRhdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEF4b2xvdGwgaXMgYW4gYW1waGliaWFuIHRoYXQgY2FuIHNwZW5kIGl0cyB3aG9sZSBsaWZlIGluIGEgbGFydmFsIHN0YXRlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEV0aGlvcGlhbiBXb2xmIGJlZm9yZSB0aGV5IGtuZXcgaXQgd2FzIHJlbGF0ZWQgdG8gd29sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltaWVuIEphY2tlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCBpcyBhIG5hdHRlcmphY2s/",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb2N0b3B1cyBjYW4gZml0IHRocm91Z2ggYW55IGhvbGUgbGFyZ2VyIHRoYW4gaXRzIGJlYWsu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEvEgWvEgXDFjSBpcyBhIGxhcmdlLCBmbGlnaHRsZXNzLCBub2N0dXJuYWwgcGFycm90IG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvci9jb2xvdXIgaXMgYSBwb2xhciBiZWFyJ3Mgc2tpbj8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBkbyBidXR0ZXJmbGllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9yIHdoYXQgcmVhc29uIHdvdWxkIGEgc3BvdHRlZCBoeWVuYSAibGF1Z2giPw==",
            "answer": "TmVydm91c25lc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgY2FsbCBhIGJhYnkgYmF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2UgbGlmZXNwYW4gb2YgYSB3aWxkY2F0IGlzIG9ubHkgYXJvdW5kIDUtNiB5ZWFycy4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBpcyBOT1QgYSBsaXphcmQ/",
            "answer": "VHVhdGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFBsYXR5cHVzIGlzIGEgbWFtbWFsLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNyZWF0dXJlIGlzIGEgQm9ub2JvPw==",
            "answer": "QXBl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2xhc3Mgb2YgYW5pbWFscyBhcmUgbmV3dHMgbWVtYmVycyBvZj8=",
            "answer": "QW1waGliaWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5saWtlIG9uIG1vc3Qgc2FsYW1hbmRlcnMsIHRoaXMgcGFydCBvZiBhIG5ld3QgaXMgZmxhdD8=",
            "answer": "VGFpbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2cgYnJlYWQgaXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBvbGRlc3QgYnJlZWRzIG9mIGRvZyBhbmQgaGFzIGZsb3VyaXNoZWQgc2luY2UgYmVmb3JlIDQwMCBCQ0Uu",
            "answer": "UHVncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29wcGVyLXJpY2ggcHJvdGVpbiB0aGF0IGNyZWF0ZXMgdGhlIGJsdWUgYmxvb2QgaW4gdGhlIEFudGFyY3RpYyBvY3RvcHVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVtb2N5YW5pbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtpbGxlciBXaGFsZSBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBkb2xwaGluLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpc2ggRnVndSwgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIHdoYXQgZmFtaWx5IG9mIGZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UHVmZmVyZmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhbm90aGVyIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSAiUG9lY2lsb3RoZXJpYSBNZXRhbGxpY2EgVGFyYW50dWxhIj8=",
            "answer": "R29vdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tb24gQ2hpbXBhbnplZT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuIHRyb2dsb2R5dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnkgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiwgd2hlcmUgZG9lcyBhbiBhYnlzc29wZWxhZ2ljIGFuaW1hbCBsaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXQgdGhlIGJvdHRvbSBvZiB0aGUgb2NlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBjb2xvbnkgb2YgcG9seXBzIGFuZCBub3QgYSBqZWxseWZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZSBNYW4tb2YtV2Fy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBjYW4gc2VlIHdoYXQncyBiZWhpbmQgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyB3aXRob3V0IHR1cm5pbmcgdGhlaXIgaGVhZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29tbW9uIHRlcm0gZm9yIGJvdmluZSBzcG9uZ2lmb3JtIGVuY2VwaGFsb3BhdGh5IChCU0UpPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkIENvdyBkaXNlYXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciByYXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWlzY2hpZWY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciB2dWx0dXJlcz8=",
            "answer": "V2FrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGJyb3dzZXIgRmlyZWZveCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgUmVkIFBhbmRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gd2hpY2ggYmlvbG9naWNhbCBwaHlsdW0gZG8gYWxsIG1hbW1hbHMsIGJpcmRzIGFuZCByZXB0aWxlcyBiZWxvbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2hvcmRhdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZyZXNod2F0ZXIgYW1waGliaWFuLCB0aGUgQXhvbG90bCwgY2FuIHJlZ3JvdyBpdCdzIGxpbWJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEF4b2xvdGwgaXMgYW4gYW1waGliaWFuIHRoYXQgY2FuIHNwZW5kIGl0cyB3aG9sZSBsaWZlIGluIGEgbGFydmFsIHN0YXRlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCBpcyBhIG5hdHRlcmphY2s/",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb2N0b3B1cyBjYW4gZml0IHRocm91Z2ggYW55IGhvbGUgbGFyZ2VyIHRoYW4gaXRzIGJlYWsu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXMgaXMgdGhlIExhdGluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIG1hcmluZSBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VhaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S2FuZ2Fyb29zIGtlZXAgZm9vZCBpbiB0aGVpciBwb3VjaGVzIG5leHQgdG8gdGhlaXIgY2hpbGRyZW4u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgcmhpbm8ncyBob3JuIG1hZGUgb2Y/",
            "answer": "S2VyYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBkbyBidXR0ZXJmbGllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIFJ1c3NpYW4gZG9tZXN0aWNhdGlvbiBleHBlcmltZW50IGluIDE5NTk/",
            "answer": "Rm94ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIElVQ04gcmVjbGFzc2lmaWVkIHRoZSBzdGF0dXMgb2YgR2lhbnQgUGFuZGFzIGZyb20gZW5kYW5nZXJlZCB0byB2dWxuZXJhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdyBleHRpbmN0IHNwZWNpZXMgIlRoeWxhY2luZSIgd2FzIG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFzbWFuaWEsIEF1c3RyYWxpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgcm9kZW50cy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBmbG9jayBvZiBjcm93cyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBhIGhvbWljaWRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBpcyBOT1QgYSBsaXphcmQ/",
            "answer": "VHVhdGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmFtaWx5IHRoYXQgdGhlIGRvbWVzdGljIGNhdCBpcyBhIG1lbWJlciBvZj8=",
            "answer": "RmVsaWRhZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtpbGxlciBXaGFsZSBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBkb2xwaGluLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "UGVyZWdyaW5lIEZhbGNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpc2ggRnVndSwgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIHdoYXQgZmFtaWx5IG9mIGZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UHVmZmVyZmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmlubmlzaCBMYXBwaHVuZCBkb2dzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgaGVyZGluZyByZWluZGVlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBhIGdyb3VwIG9mIGNyb3dzPw==",
            "answer": "TXVyZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhbm90aGVyIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSAiUG9lY2lsb3RoZXJpYSBNZXRhbGxpY2EgVGFyYW50dWxhIj8=",
            "answer": "R29vdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tb24gQ2hpbXBhbnplZT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuIHRyb2dsb2R5dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvdXIgaXMgdGhlIGZlbWFsZSBibGFja2JpcmQ/",
            "answer": "QnJvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29tbW9uIHRlcm0gZm9yIGJvdmluZSBzcG9uZ2lmb3JtIGVuY2VwaGFsb3BhdGh5IChCU0UpPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkIENvdyBkaXNlYXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciByYXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWlzY2hpZWY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciB2dWx0dXJlcz8=",
            "answer": "V2FrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGJyb3dzZXIgRmlyZWZveCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgUmVkIFBhbmRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRlY2Fwb2RzIiBhcmUgYW4gb3JkZXIgb2YgdGVuLWZvb3RlZCBjcnVzdGFjZWFucy4gIFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFyZSBOT1QgZGVjYXBvZHM/",
            "answer": "S3JpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gd2hpY2ggYmlvbG9naWNhbCBwaHlsdW0gZG8gYWxsIG1hbW1hbHMsIGJpcmRzIGFuZCByZXB0aWxlcyBiZWxvbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2hvcmRhdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBsb25nZXN0IHZlbm9tb3VzIHNuYWtlPw==",
            "answer": "S2luZyBDb2JyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZyZXNod2F0ZXIgYW1waGliaWFuLCB0aGUgQXhvbG90bCwgY2FuIHJlZ3JvdyBpdCdzIGxpbWJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEF4b2xvdGwgaXMgYW4gYW1waGliaWFuIHRoYXQgY2FuIHNwZW5kIGl0cyB3aG9sZSBsaWZlIGluIGEgbGFydmFsIHN0YXRlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEV0aGlvcGlhbiBXb2xmIGJlZm9yZSB0aGV5IGtuZXcgaXQgd2FzIHJlbGF0ZWQgdG8gd29sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltaWVuIEphY2tlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCBpcyBhIG5hdHRlcmphY2s/",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCAgbGFuZCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "Q2hlZXRhaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENlcmF0b3NhdXJ1cywgYSBkaW5vc2F1ciBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIGEgaG9ybiBvbiB0aGUgdG9wIG9mIGl0cyBub3NlLCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIHRvIGJlIGEgZGVjZW5kZW50IG9mIHRoZSBUeXJhbm5vc2F1cnVzIFJleC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb2N0b3B1cyBjYW4gZml0IHRocm91Z2ggYW55IGhvbGUgbGFyZ2VyIHRoYW4gaXRzIGJlYWsu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IGh1bWFucz8=",
            "answer": "SG9tbyBTYXBpZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEvEgWvEgXDFjSBpcyBhIGxhcmdlLCBmbGlnaHRsZXNzLCBub2N0dXJuYWwgcGFycm90IG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGljaCBjb3VudHJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "TmV3IFplYWxhbmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXMgaXMgdGhlIExhdGluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIG1hcmluZSBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VhaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgcmhpbm8ncyBob3JuIG1hZGUgb2Y/",
            "answer": "S2VyYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBkbyBidXR0ZXJmbGllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN1Ym9yZGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIGZhbWlseSBIeWFlbmlkYWUgYmVsb25nIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "RmVsaWZvcm1pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgY2FsbCBhIGJhYnkgYmF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIHdhcyBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIFJ1c3NpYW4gZG9tZXN0aWNhdGlvbiBleHBlcmltZW50IGluIDE5NTk/",
            "answer": "Rm94ZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIElVQ04gcmVjbGFzc2lmaWVkIHRoZSBzdGF0dXMgb2YgR2lhbnQgUGFuZGFzIGZyb20gZW5kYW5nZXJlZCB0byB2dWxuZXJhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2UgbGlmZXNwYW4gb2YgYSB3aWxkY2F0IGlzIG9ubHkgYXJvdW5kIDUtNiB5ZWFycy4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBmbG9jayBvZiBjcm93cyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBhIGhvbWljaWRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWFscyBpcyBOT1QgYSBsaXphcmQ/",
            "answer": "VHVhdGFyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VW5saWtlIG9uIG1vc3Qgc2FsYW1hbmRlcnMsIHRoaXMgcGFydCBvZiBhIG5ld3QgaXMgZmxhdD8=",
            "answer": "VGFpbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2F0cyBoYXZlIHdoaXNrZXJzIHVuZGVyIHRoZWlyIGxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2cgYnJlYWQgaXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBvbGRlc3QgYnJlZWRzIG9mIGRvZyBhbmQgaGFzIGZsb3VyaXNoZWQgc2luY2UgYmVmb3JlIDQwMCBCQ0Uu",
            "answer": "UHVncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtpbGxlciBXaGFsZSBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBkb2xwaGluLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "UGVyZWdyaW5lIEZhbGNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBhbm90aGVyIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSAiUG9lY2lsb3RoZXJpYSBNZXRhbGxpY2EgVGFyYW50dWxhIj8=",
            "answer": "R29vdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tb24gQ2hpbXBhbnplZT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuIHRyb2dsb2R5dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnkgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiwgd2hlcmUgZG9lcyBhbiBhYnlzc29wZWxhZ2ljIGFuaW1hbCBsaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXQgdGhlIGJvdHRvbSBvZiB0aGUgb2NlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBjb2xvbnkgb2YgcG9seXBzIGFuZCBub3QgYSBqZWxseWZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZSBNYW4tb2YtV2Fy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBjYW4gc2VlIHdoYXQncyBiZWhpbmQgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyB3aXRob3V0IHR1cm5pbmcgdGhlaXIgaGVhZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29tbW9uIHRlcm0gZm9yIGJvdmluZSBzcG9uZ2lmb3JtIGVuY2VwaGFsb3BhdGh5IChCU0UpPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkIENvdyBkaXNlYXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRlY2Fwb2RzIiBhcmUgYW4gb3JkZXIgb2YgdGVuLWZvb3RlZCBjcnVzdGFjZWFucy4gIFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFyZSBOT1QgZGVjYXBvZHM/",
            "answer": "S3JpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEF4b2xvdGwgaXMgYW4gYW1waGliaWFuIHRoYXQgY2FuIHNwZW5kIGl0cyB3aG9sZSBsaWZlIGluIGEgbGFydmFsIHN0YXRlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzICJoaXBwb3BvdGFtdXMiIG1lYW4gYW5kIGluIHdoYXQgbGFuZ2F1Z2U/",
            "answer": "Uml2ZXIgSG9yc2UgKEdyZWVrKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCBpcyBhIG5hdHRlcmphY2s/",
            "answer": "VG9hZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENlcmF0b3NhdXJ1cywgYSBkaW5vc2F1ciBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIGEgaG9ybiBvbiB0aGUgdG9wIG9mIGl0cyBub3NlLCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIHRvIGJlIGEgZGVjZW5kZW50IG9mIHRoZSBUeXJhbm5vc2F1cnVzIFJleC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW4gb2N0b3B1cyBjYW4gZml0IHRocm91Z2ggYW55IGhvbGUgbGFyZ2VyIHRoYW4gaXRzIGJlYWsu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IGh1bWFucz8=",
            "answer": "SG9tbyBTYXBpZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvci9jb2xvdXIgaXMgYSBwb2xhciBiZWFyJ3Mgc2tpbj8=",
            "answer": "QmxhY2s="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXMgaXMgdGhlIExhdGluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIG1hcmluZSBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VhaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IkthbWVhLCIgdGhlIEdpbGJlcnRlc2UgSXNsYW5kZXIgd29yZCBmb3IgZG9nLCBpcyBkZXJpdmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIEVuZ2xpc2ggcGhyYXNlICJDb21lIGhlcmUhIg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgcmhpbm8ncyBob3JuIG1hZGUgb2Y/",
            "answer": "S2VyYXRpbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBkbyBidXR0ZXJmbGllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN1Ym9yZGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIGZhbWlseSBIeWFlbmlkYWUgYmVsb25nIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "RmVsaWZvcm1pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIElVQ04gcmVjbGFzc2lmaWVkIHRoZSBzdGF0dXMgb2YgR2lhbnQgUGFuZGFzIGZyb20gZW5kYW5nZXJlZCB0byB2dWxuZXJhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGF2ZXJhZ2UgbGlmZXNwYW4gb2YgYSB3aWxkY2F0IGlzIG9ubHkgYXJvdW5kIDUtNiB5ZWFycy4g",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgcm9kZW50cy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBmbG9jayBvZiBjcm93cyBpcyBrbm93biBhcyBhIGhvbWljaWRlLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFBsYXR5cHVzIGlzIGEgbWFtbWFsLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNyZWF0dXJlIGlzIGEgQm9ub2JvPw==",
            "answer": "QXBl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2F0cyBoYXZlIHdoaXNrZXJzIHVuZGVyIHRoZWlyIGxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29wcGVyLXJpY2ggcHJvdGVpbiB0aGF0IGNyZWF0ZXMgdGhlIGJsdWUgYmxvb2QgaW4gdGhlIEFudGFyY3RpYyBvY3RvcHVzPw==",
            "answer": "SGVtb2N5YW5pbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEtpbGxlciBXaGFsZSBpcyBjb25zaWRlcmVkIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBkb2xwaGluLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCBhbmltYWw/",
            "answer": "UGVyZWdyaW5lIEZhbGNvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpc2ggRnVndSwgaXMgbWFkZSBmcm9tIHdoYXQgZmFtaWx5IG9mIGZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UHVmZmVyZmlzaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmlubmlzaCBMYXBwaHVuZCBkb2dzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgaGVyZGluZyByZWluZGVlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBhIGdyb3VwIG9mIGNyb3dzPw==",
            "answer": "TXVyZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBDb21tb24gQ2hpbXBhbnplZT8=",
            "answer": "UGFuIHRyb2dsb2R5dGVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnkgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiwgd2hlcmUgZG9lcyBhbiBhYnlzc29wZWxhZ2ljIGFuaW1hbCBsaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXQgdGhlIGJvdHRvbSBvZiB0aGUgb2NlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBjYW4gc2VlIHdoYXQncyBiZWhpbmQgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyB3aXRob3V0IHR1cm5pbmcgdGhlaXIgaGVhZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29tbW9uIHRlcm0gZm9yIGJvdmluZSBzcG9uZ2lmb3JtIGVuY2VwaGFsb3BhdGh5IChCU0UpPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkIENvdyBkaXNlYXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgYSBtYWxlIGJlZSB0aGF0IGNvbWVzIGZyb20gYW4gdW5mZXJ0aWxpemVkIGVnZz8=",
            "answer": "RHJvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBiZWFycz8=",
            "answer": "U2xvdGg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgY2Fybml2b3Jlcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "IkRlY2Fwb2RzIiBhcmUgYW4gb3JkZXIgb2YgdGVuLWZvb3RlZCBjcnVzdGFjZWFucy4gIFdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGFyZSBOT1QgZGVjYXBvZHM/",
            "answer": "S3JpbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZyZXNod2F0ZXIgYW1waGliaWFuLCB0aGUgQXhvbG90bCwgY2FuIHJlZ3JvdyBpdCdzIGxpbWJzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEV0aGlvcGlhbiBXb2xmIGJlZm9yZSB0aGV5IGtuZXcgaXQgd2FzIHJlbGF0ZWQgdG8gd29sdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2ltaWVuIEphY2tlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzICJoaXBwb3BvdGFtdXMiIG1lYW4gYW5kIGluIHdoYXQgbGFuZ2F1Z2U/",
            "answer": "Uml2ZXIgSG9yc2UgKEdyZWVrKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QSBjYXJuaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0cyBmbGVzaCwgd2hhdCBkb2VzIGEgbnVjaXZvcm91cyBhbmltYWwgZWF0Pw==",
            "answer": "TnV0cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENlcmF0b3NhdXJ1cywgYSBkaW5vc2F1ciBrbm93biBmb3IgaGF2aW5nIGEgaG9ybiBvbiB0aGUgdG9wIG9mIGl0cyBub3NlLCBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIHRvIGJlIGEgZGVjZW5kZW50IG9mIHRoZSBUeXJhbm5vc2F1cnVzIFJleC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBzbHVn4oCZcyBibG9vZCBpcyBncmVlbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciBtb2Rlcm4gZGF5IGh1bWFucz8=",
            "answer": "SG9tbyBTYXBpZW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBvZiBCcm93biBCZWFyIGlzIG5vdCBleHRpbmN0Pw==",
            "answer": "U3lyaWFuIEJyb3duIEJlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SGlwcG9jYW1wdXMgaXMgdGhlIExhdGluIG5hbWUgZm9yIHdoaWNoIG1hcmluZSBjcmVhdHVyZT8=",
            "answer": "U2VhaG9yc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2FzaG1lcmUgaXMgdGhlIHdvb2wgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBraW5kIG9mIGFuaW1hbD8=",
            "answer": "R29hdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgIlBvbGFyIEJlYXIiPw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdXMgTWFyaXRpbXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBiZWFyIGRvZXMgTk9UIGRlZmVjYXRlIGR1cmluZyBoaWJlcm5hdGlvbi4g",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgbGVncyBkbyBidXR0ZXJmbGllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIHN1Ym9yZGVyIGRvZXMgdGhlIGZhbWlseSBIeWFlbmlkYWUgYmVsb25nIHRvPw==",
            "answer": "RmVsaWZvcm1pYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkga25vd24gbGl2aW5nIHNwZWNpZXMgb2YgaHllbmFzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "NA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzY2llbnRpZmljIGZhbWlseSBkb2VzIHRoZSBBYXJkd29sZiBiZWxvbmcgdG8/",
            "answer": "SHlhZW5pZGFl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm9yIHdoYXQgcmVhc29uIHdvdWxkIGEgc3BvdHRlZCBoeWVuYSAibGF1Z2giPw==",
            "answer": "TmVydm91c25lc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgY2FsbCBhIGJhYnkgYmF0Pw==",
            "answer": "UHVw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGVldGFoPw==",
            "answer": "QWNpbm9ueXgganViYXR1cw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNiwgdGhlIElVQ04gcmVjbGFzc2lmaWVkIHRoZSBzdGF0dXMgb2YgR2lhbnQgUGFuZGFzIGZyb20gZW5kYW5nZXJlZCB0byB2dWxuZXJhYmxlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5vdyBleHRpbmN0IHNwZWNpZXMgIlRoeWxhY2luZSIgd2FzIG5hdGl2ZSB0byB3aGVyZT8=",
            "answer": "VGFzbWFuaWEsIEF1c3RyYWxpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR3JheSBXb2xmJ3Mgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FuaXMgTHVwdXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBhcmUgcm9kZW50cy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFBsYXR5cHVzIGlzIGEgbWFtbWFsLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGNyZWF0dXJlIGlzIGEgQm9ub2JvPw==",
            "answer": "QXBl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc3BlY2llcyBpcyBub3QgZXh0aW5jdD8=",
            "answer": "S29tb2RvIGRyYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2xhc3Mgb2YgYW5pbWFscyBhcmUgbmV3dHMgbWVtYmVycyBvZj8=",
            "answer": "QW1waGliaWFu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QSBjYXRlcnBpbGxhciBoYXMgbW9yZSBtdXNjbGVzIHRoYW4gaHVtYW5zIGRvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Q2F0cyBoYXZlIHdoaXNrZXJzIHVuZGVyIHRoZWlyIGxlZ3Mu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2cgYnJlYWQgaXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBvbGRlc3QgYnJlZWRzIG9mIGRvZyBhbmQgaGFzIGZsb3VyaXNoZWQgc2luY2UgYmVmb3JlIDQwMCBCQ0Uu",
            "answer": "UHVncw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3BlY2llcyBpcyBhICJtb3VudGFpbiBjaGlja2VuIj8=",
            "answer": "RnJvZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmlubmlzaCBMYXBwaHVuZCBkb2dzIHdlcmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgaGVyZGluZyByZWluZGVlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciBhIGdyb3VwIG9mIGNyb3dzPw==",
            "answer": "TXVyZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QnkgZGVmaW5pdGlvbiwgd2hlcmUgZG9lcyBhbiBhYnlzc29wZWxhZ2ljIGFuaW1hbCBsaXZlPw==",
            "answer": "QXQgdGhlIGJvdHRvbSBvZiB0aGUgb2NlYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgYSBjb2xvbnkgb2YgcG9seXBzIGFuZCBub3QgYSBqZWxseWZpc2g/",
            "answer": "UG9ydHVndWVzZSBNYW4tb2YtV2Fy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGlnZXJzIGhhdmUgb25lIGNvbG91ciBvZiBza2luIGRlc3BpdGUgdGhlIHN0cmlwZXkgZnVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "UmFiYml0cyBjYW4gc2VlIHdoYXQncyBiZWhpbmQgdGhlbXNlbHZlcyB3aXRob3V0IHR1cm5pbmcgdGhlaXIgaGVhZHMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvdXIgaXMgdGhlIGZlbWFsZSBibGFja2JpcmQ/",
            "answer": "QnJvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "WW91IGNhbiB0ZWxsIHRoZSBhZ2Ugb2YgYSBsYWR5YmlyZCBieSBjb3VudGluZyB0aGUgc3BvdHMgb24gaGlzIGJhY2su",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29tbW9uIHRlcm0gZm9yIGJvdmluZSBzcG9uZ2lmb3JtIGVuY2VwaGFsb3BhdGh5IChCU0UpPw==",
            "answer": "TWFkIENvdyBkaXNlYXNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgdGVldGggZG9lcyBhbiBhZHVsdCByYWJiaXQgaGF2ZT8=",
            "answer": "Mjg="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBmb3IgYSBtYWxlIGJlZSB0aGF0IGNvbWVzIGZyb20gYW4gdW5mZXJ0aWxpemVkIGVnZz8=",
            "answer": "RHJvbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBhIHJhYmJpdCdzIGFib2RlPw==",
            "answer": "QnVycm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciByYXRzPw==",
            "answer": "TWlzY2hpZWY="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29sbGVjdGl2ZSBub3VuIGZvciB2dWx0dXJlcz8=",
            "answer": "V2FrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGJyb3dzZXIgRmlyZWZveCBpcyBuYW1lZCBhZnRlciB0aGUgUmVkIFBhbmRhLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBiaXJkIGlzIGJvcm4gd2l0aCBjbGF3cyBvbiBpdHMgd2luZyBkaWdpdHM/",
            "answer": "SG9hdHppbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VG8gd2hpY2ggYmlvbG9naWNhbCBwaHlsdW0gZG8gYWxsIG1hbW1hbHMsIGJpcmRzIGFuZCByZXB0aWxlcyBiZWxvbmc/",
            "answer": "Q2hvcmRhdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBsb25nZXN0IHZlbm9tb3VzIHNuYWtlPw==",
            "answer": "S2luZyBDb2JyYQ=="
        }
    ],
    "VmVoaWNsZXM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTk5MyBTd2VkaXNoIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgU2FhYiBleHBlcmltZW50ZWQgd2l0aCByZXBsYWNpbmcgdGhlIHN0ZWVyaW5nIHdoZWVsIHdpdGggYSBqb3lzdGljayBpbiBhIFNhYWIgOTAwMC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZyb250LXdoZWVsLWRyaXZlIGNhciBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSBEYXRzdW4gKG5vdyBOaXNzYW4pPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgZW5naW5lIHVzZXMgbG9iZXMgdG8gb3BlbiBhbmQgY2xvc2UgaW50YWtlIGFuZCBleGhhdXN0IHZhbHZlcywgYW5kIGFsbG93cyBhbiBhaXIvZnVlbCBtaXh0dXJlIGludG8gdGhlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftc2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSBIdXNzYXJ5YSBzdXBlcmNhciwgbWFkZSBieSB0aGUgY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciAiQXJyaW5lcmEiLCBhc3NlbWJsZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVycyBoYWQgYSB3YXIgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaXQ/",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwYXNzZW5nZXIgamV0cyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9laW5nIDc0Ny04"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW56byBGZXJyYXJpIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGFuIGF1dG8gcmFjZXIgZm9yIHdoYXQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGJlZm9yZSBmb3VuZGluZyBoaXMgb3duIGNhciBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "QWxmYSBSb21lbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29tcGxldGUgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmFsb2d5OiBBdWRpIGlzIHRvIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gYXMgSW5maW5pdGkgaXMgdG8gPw==",
            "answer": "Tmlzc2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENoZXZyb2xldCBDb3J2ZXR0ZSBoYXMgYWx3YXlzIGJlZW4gbWFkZSBleGNsdXNpdmVseSB3aXRoIFY4IGVuZ2luZXMgb25seS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIG1vdG9yY3ljbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGJyYW5kIGRvZXMgTk9UIGJlbG9uZyB0byBHZW5lcmFsIE1vdG9ycz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FyIG1vZGVscyBhcmUgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgTGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk/",
            "answer": "QXZlbnRhZG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFyaWFibGUgVmFsdmUgVGltaW5nIHRlY2hub2xvZ3kgaXMgdXNlZCBieSBCTVc/",
            "answer": "VkFOT1M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgNCBSaW5ncyBpbiBBdWRpJ3MgTG9nbyByZXByZXNlbnQ/",
            "answer": "UHJldmlvdXNseSBpbmRlcGVuZGVudCBhdXRvbW9iaWxlIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaW4gdGhlIExleHVzIFNDNDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MVVaLUZF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJyaXZhIGlzIG93bmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBEZXV0c2NoZSBCYWhuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEdlbmVyYWwgTW90b3JzIEVWMSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHN0cmVldC1sZWdhbCBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGVsZWN0cmljIHZlaGljbGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgb3ZlciA2IG1pbGxpb24gR2VuZXJhbCBNb3RvcnMgdmVoaWNsZXMgd2VyZSByZWNhbGxlZCBkdWUgdG8gd2hhdCBjcml0aWNhbCBmbGF3Pw==",
            "answer": "RmF1bHR5IGlnbml0aW9uIHN3aXRjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJFYWdsZSIgYnJhbmQgb2YgdGlyZXMsIGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgdGlyZSBzdXBwbGllciBvZiBOQVNDQVI/",
            "answer": "R29vZHllYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb2RlbCB3YXMgdGhlIHNwb3J0cyBjYXIgZ2lmdGVkIHRvIFl1cmkgR2FnYXJpbiBieSB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIGdvdmVybm1lbnQgaW4gMTk2NT8=",
            "answer": "TWF0cmEgRGpldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgbm90IG1hZGUgYnkgRm9yZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTNyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NDI3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaXNzYW4ncyBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXVkaSBkb2VzIG5vdCB1c2UgSGFsZGV4IGJhc2VkIGFsbCB3aGVlbCBkcml2ZSBzeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "QXVkaSBBOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIHRyYWluIHdhcyBTdGVwbmV5LCBhIHRyYWluIG9uIHRoZSBCbHVlYmVsbCBSYWlsd2F5IG5vdGFibGUgZm9yIGhpcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIGluICJUaGUgUmFpbHdheSBTZXJpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TEImU0NSIEExWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIFN1YmFydSB2ZWhpY2xlcyBhcmUgbWFkZSBpbiBDaGluYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNub3dtb2JpbGUgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IENhbmFkaWFuIEpvc2VwaC1Bcm1hbmQgQm9tYmFyZGllciBpbiAxOTM3Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgVHJhYmFudCA2MDEgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "RWFzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FycyBpcyBOT1QgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIDUgTW9kZXJuIFN1cGVyY2FycyBieSBGZXJyYXJpPw==",
            "answer": "VGVzdGFyb3NzYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTk5MyBTd2VkaXNoIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgU2FhYiBleHBlcmltZW50ZWQgd2l0aCByZXBsYWNpbmcgdGhlIHN0ZWVyaW5nIHdoZWVsIHdpdGggYSBqb3lzdGljayBpbiBhIFNhYWIgOTAwMC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSBIdXNzYXJ5YSBzdXBlcmNhciwgbWFkZSBieSB0aGUgY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciAiQXJyaW5lcmEiLCBhc3NlbWJsZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBSdXNzaWFuIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXI/",
            "answer": "QllE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpZmZlcmVuY2UgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgbGVuZ3RocyBvZiBhIEJvZWluZyA3NzctMzAwRVIgYW5kIGFuIEFpcmJ1cyBBMzUwLTEwMDAgaXMgY2xvc2VzdCB0bzo=",
            "answer": "MC4xbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW56byBGZXJyYXJpIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGFuIGF1dG8gcmFjZXIgZm9yIHdoYXQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGJlZm9yZSBmb3VuZGluZyBoaXMgb3duIGNhciBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "QWxmYSBSb21lbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29tcGxldGUgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmFsb2d5OiBBdWRpIGlzIHRvIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gYXMgSW5maW5pdGkgaXMgdG8gPw==",
            "answer": "Tmlzc2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2ZWhpY2xlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIGZ1bGwgZ2xhc3Mgcm9vZiBhdCBiYXNlIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBBdmFudGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENoZXZyb2xldCBDb3J2ZXR0ZSBoYXMgYWx3YXlzIGJlZW4gbWFkZSBleGNsdXNpdmVseSB3aXRoIFY4IGVuZ2luZXMgb25seS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIG1vdG9yY3ljbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3VwZXJjYXIgY29tcGFueSBpcyBmcm9tIFN3ZWRlbj8=",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGJyYW5kIGRvZXMgTk9UIGJlbG9uZyB0byBHZW5lcmFsIE1vdG9ycz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FyIG1vZGVscyBhcmUgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgTGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk/",
            "answer": "QXZlbnRhZG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFyaWFibGUgVmFsdmUgVGltaW5nIHRlY2hub2xvZ3kgaXMgdXNlZCBieSBCTVc/",
            "answer": "VkFOT1M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgNCBSaW5ncyBpbiBBdWRpJ3MgTG9nbyByZXByZXNlbnQ/",
            "answer": "UHJldmlvdXNseSBpbmRlcGVuZGVudCBhdXRvbW9iaWxlIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaW4gdGhlIExleHVzIFNDNDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MVVaLUZF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmVycmFyaSBoYXMgbmV2ZXIgbWFkZSBhIFYxMCBlbmdpbmUgZm9yIGFueSBvZiBpdHMgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJFYWdsZSIgYnJhbmQgb2YgdGlyZXMsIGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgdGlyZSBzdXBwbGllciBvZiBOQVNDQVI/",
            "answer": "R29vZHllYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJQIFplcm8iIGxpbmU/",
            "answer": "UGlyZWxsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb2RlbCB3YXMgdGhlIHNwb3J0cyBjYXIgZ2lmdGVkIHRvIFl1cmkgR2FnYXJpbiBieSB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIGdvdmVybm1lbnQgaW4gMTk2NT8=",
            "answer": "TWF0cmEgRGpldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgbm90IG1hZGUgYnkgRm9yZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTNyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NDI3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXVkaSBkb2VzIG5vdCB1c2UgSGFsZGV4IGJhc2VkIGFsbCB3aGVlbCBkcml2ZSBzeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "QXVkaSBBOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIHRyYWluIHdhcyBTdGVwbmV5LCBhIHRyYWluIG9uIHRoZSBCbHVlYmVsbCBSYWlsd2F5IG5vdGFibGUgZm9yIGhpcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIGluICJUaGUgUmFpbHdheSBTZXJpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TEImU0NSIEExWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qk1XIE0gR21iSCBpcyBhIHN1YnNpZGlhcnkgb2YgQk1XIEFHIHRoYXQgZm9jdXNlcyBvbiBjYXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIkdUTyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgYnkgRmVycmFyaT8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNub3dtb2JpbGUgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IENhbmFkaWFuIEpvc2VwaC1Bcm1hbmQgQm9tYmFyZGllciBpbiAxOTM3Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgVHJhYmFudCA2MDEgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "RWFzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FycyBpcyBOT1QgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIDUgTW9kZXJuIFN1cGVyY2FycyBieSBGZXJyYXJpPw==",
            "answer": "VGVzdGFyb3NzYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZyb250LXdoZWVsLWRyaXZlIGNhciBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSBEYXRzdW4gKG5vdyBOaXNzYW4pPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIGZlYXR1cmVzIG9uIHRoZSBsb2dvIGZvciBBYmFydGgsIHRoZSBtb3RvcnNwb3J0IGRpdmlzaW9uIG9mIEZpYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgZW5naW5lIHVzZXMgbG9iZXMgdG8gb3BlbiBhbmQgY2xvc2UgaW50YWtlIGFuZCBleGhhdXN0IHZhbHZlcywgYW5kIGFsbG93cyBhbiBhaXIvZnVlbCBtaXh0dXJlIGludG8gdGhlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftc2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSmFwYW5lc2UgY29tcGFueSBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBsYXJnZXN0IG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBvZiBtb3RvcmN5Y2xlcz8=",
            "answer": "SG9uZGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVycyBoYWQgYSB3YXIgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaXQ/",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaGFzIG9mZmljaWFsbHkgYmFubmVkIHRoZSBjaXZpbGlhbiB1c2Ugb2YgZGFzaCBjYW1zIGluIGNhcnM/",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwYXNzZW5nZXIgamV0cyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9laW5nIDc0Ny04"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpZmZlcmVuY2UgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgbGVuZ3RocyBvZiBhIEJvZWluZyA3NzctMzAwRVIgYW5kIGFuIEFpcmJ1cyBBMzUwLTEwMDAgaXMgY2xvc2VzdCB0bzo=",
            "answer": "MC4xbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2ZWhpY2xlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIGZ1bGwgZ2xhc3Mgcm9vZiBhdCBiYXNlIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBBdmFudGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbW9kZWxzIGhhcyBiZWVuIGJhZGdlLWVuZ2luZWVyZWQgKHJlYmFkZ2VkKSB0aGUgbW9zdD8=",
            "answer": "SXN1enUgVHJvb3Blcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2FyIG1vZGVsIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IE1hbGF5c2lhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIFByb3Rvbj8=",
            "answer": "S2VsaXNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIG1vdG9yY3ljbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZ1bGwgRW5nbGlzaCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIEJNVyBpcyBCYXZhcmlhbiBNb3RvciBXb3Jrcw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3VwZXJjYXIgY29tcGFueSBpcyBmcm9tIFN3ZWRlbj8=",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXV0b21vYmlsZXMgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgVGVsc2EgTW90b3JzIG9wZXJhdGUgb24gd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBlbmVyZ3k/",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWNpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFyaWFibGUgVmFsdmUgVGltaW5nIHRlY2hub2xvZ3kgaXMgdXNlZCBieSBCTVc/",
            "answer": "VkFOT1M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJyaXZhIGlzIG93bmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBEZXV0c2NoZSBCYWhuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmVycmFyaSBoYXMgbmV2ZXIgbWFkZSBhIFYxMCBlbmdpbmUgZm9yIGFueSBvZiBpdHMgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJFYWdsZSIgYnJhbmQgb2YgdGlyZXMsIGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgdGlyZSBzdXBwbGllciBvZiBOQVNDQVI/",
            "answer": "R29vZHllYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJQIFplcm8iIGxpbmU/",
            "answer": "UGlyZWxsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb2RlbCB3YXMgdGhlIHNwb3J0cyBjYXIgZ2lmdGVkIHRvIFl1cmkgR2FnYXJpbiBieSB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIGdvdmVybm1lbnQgaW4gMTk2NT8=",
            "answer": "TWF0cmEgRGpldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaXNzYW4ncyBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIHRyYWluIHdhcyBTdGVwbmV5LCBhIHRyYWluIG9uIHRoZSBCbHVlYmVsbCBSYWlsd2F5IG5vdGFibGUgZm9yIGhpcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIGluICJUaGUgUmFpbHdheSBTZXJpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TEImU0NSIEExWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIFN1YmFydSB2ZWhpY2xlcyBhcmUgbWFkZSBpbiBDaGluYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qk1XIE0gR21iSCBpcyBhIHN1YnNpZGlhcnkgb2YgQk1XIEFHIHRoYXQgZm9jdXNlcyBvbiBjYXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNub3dtb2JpbGUgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IENhbmFkaWFuIEpvc2VwaC1Bcm1hbmQgQm9tYmFyZGllciBpbiAxOTM3Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FycyBpcyBOT1QgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIDUgTW9kZXJuIFN1cGVyY2FycyBieSBGZXJyYXJpPw==",
            "answer": "VGVzdGFyb3NzYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIGZlYXR1cmVzIG9uIHRoZSBsb2dvIGZvciBBYmFydGgsIHRoZSBtb3RvcnNwb3J0IGRpdmlzaW9uIG9mIEZpYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgZW5naW5lIHVzZXMgbG9iZXMgdG8gb3BlbiBhbmQgY2xvc2UgaW50YWtlIGFuZCBleGhhdXN0IHZhbHZlcywgYW5kIGFsbG93cyBhbiBhaXIvZnVlbCBtaXh0dXJlIGludG8gdGhlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftc2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSmFwYW5lc2UgY29tcGFueSBpcyB0aGUgd29ybGQncyBsYXJnZXN0IG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBvZiBtb3RvcmN5Y2xlcz8=",
            "answer": "SG9uZGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSBIdXNzYXJ5YSBzdXBlcmNhciwgbWFkZSBieSB0aGUgY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciAiQXJyaW5lcmEiLCBhc3NlbWJsZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBSdXNzaWFuIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXI/",
            "answer": "QllE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVycyBoYWQgYSB3YXIgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaXQ/",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaGFzIG9mZmljaWFsbHkgYmFubmVkIHRoZSBjaXZpbGlhbiB1c2Ugb2YgZGFzaCBjYW1zIGluIGNhcnM/",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwYXNzZW5nZXIgamV0cyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9laW5nIDc0Ny04"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpZmZlcmVuY2UgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgbGVuZ3RocyBvZiBhIEJvZWluZyA3NzctMzAwRVIgYW5kIGFuIEFpcmJ1cyBBMzUwLTEwMDAgaXMgY2xvc2VzdCB0bzo=",
            "answer": "MC4xbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW56byBGZXJyYXJpIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGFuIGF1dG8gcmFjZXIgZm9yIHdoYXQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGJlZm9yZSBmb3VuZGluZyBoaXMgb3duIGNhciBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "QWxmYSBSb21lbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29tcGxldGUgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmFsb2d5OiBBdWRpIGlzIHRvIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gYXMgSW5maW5pdGkgaXMgdG8gPw==",
            "answer": "Tmlzc2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbW9kZWxzIGhhcyBiZWVuIGJhZGdlLWVuZ2luZWVyZWQgKHJlYmFkZ2VkKSB0aGUgbW9zdD8=",
            "answer": "SXN1enUgVHJvb3Blcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENoZXZyb2xldCBDb3J2ZXR0ZSBoYXMgYWx3YXlzIGJlZW4gbWFkZSBleGNsdXNpdmVseSB3aXRoIFY4IGVuZ2luZXMgb25seS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIG1vdG9yY3ljbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZ1bGwgRW5nbGlzaCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIEJNVyBpcyBCYXZhcmlhbiBNb3RvciBXb3Jrcw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3VwZXJjYXIgY29tcGFueSBpcyBmcm9tIFN3ZWRlbj8=",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGJyYW5kIGRvZXMgTk9UIGJlbG9uZyB0byBHZW5lcmFsIE1vdG9ycz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FyIG1vZGVscyBhcmUgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgTGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk/",
            "answer": "QXZlbnRhZG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCTVcgd2FzIGVzdGFibGlzaGVkIGluIDE5MTYsIGl0IHdhcyBwcm9kdWNpbmcgYXV0b21vYmlsZXMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaW4gdGhlIExleHVzIFNDNDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MVVaLUZF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJyaXZhIGlzIG93bmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBEZXV0c2NoZSBCYWhuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmVycmFyaSBoYXMgbmV2ZXIgbWFkZSBhIFYxMCBlbmdpbmUgZm9yIGFueSBvZiBpdHMgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgb3ZlciA2IG1pbGxpb24gR2VuZXJhbCBNb3RvcnMgdmVoaWNsZXMgd2VyZSByZWNhbGxlZCBkdWUgdG8gd2hhdCBjcml0aWNhbCBmbGF3Pw==",
            "answer": "RmF1bHR5IGlnbml0aW9uIHN3aXRjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJFYWdsZSIgYnJhbmQgb2YgdGlyZXMsIGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgdGlyZSBzdXBwbGllciBvZiBOQVNDQVI/",
            "answer": "R29vZHllYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJQIFplcm8iIGxpbmU/",
            "answer": "UGlyZWxsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb2RlbCB3YXMgdGhlIHNwb3J0cyBjYXIgZ2lmdGVkIHRvIFl1cmkgR2FnYXJpbiBieSB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIGdvdmVybm1lbnQgaW4gMTk2NT8=",
            "answer": "TWF0cmEgRGpldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgbm90IG1hZGUgYnkgRm9yZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTNyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NDI3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIHRyYWluIHdhcyBTdGVwbmV5LCBhIHRyYWluIG9uIHRoZSBCbHVlYmVsbCBSYWlsd2F5IG5vdGFibGUgZm9yIGhpcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIGluICJUaGUgUmFpbHdheSBTZXJpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TEImU0NSIEExWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qk1XIE0gR21iSCBpcyBhIHN1YnNpZGlhcnkgb2YgQk1XIEFHIHRoYXQgZm9jdXNlcyBvbiBjYXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIkdUTyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgYnkgRmVycmFyaT8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgVHJhYmFudCA2MDEgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "RWFzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZyb250LXdoZWVsLWRyaXZlIGNhciBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSBEYXRzdW4gKG5vdyBOaXNzYW4pPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIGZlYXR1cmVzIG9uIHRoZSBsb2dvIGZvciBBYmFydGgsIHRoZSBtb3RvcnNwb3J0IGRpdmlzaW9uIG9mIEZpYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgZW5naW5lIHVzZXMgbG9iZXMgdG8gb3BlbiBhbmQgY2xvc2UgaW50YWtlIGFuZCBleGhhdXN0IHZhbHZlcywgYW5kIGFsbG93cyBhbiBhaXIvZnVlbCBtaXh0dXJlIGludG8gdGhlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftc2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSXRhbGlhbiBjaXR5IGlzIGhvbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgJ0ZpYXQnPw==",
            "answer": "VHVyaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVycyBoYWQgYSB3YXIgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaXQ/",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaGFzIG9mZmljaWFsbHkgYmFubmVkIHRoZSBjaXZpbGlhbiB1c2Ugb2YgZGFzaCBjYW1zIGluIGNhcnM/",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwYXNzZW5nZXIgamV0cyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9laW5nIDc0Ny04"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2ZWhpY2xlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIGZ1bGwgZ2xhc3Mgcm9vZiBhdCBiYXNlIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBBdmFudGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENoZXZyb2xldCBDb3J2ZXR0ZSBoYXMgYWx3YXlzIGJlZW4gbWFkZSBleGNsdXNpdmVseSB3aXRoIFY4IGVuZ2luZXMgb25seS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2FyIG1vZGVsIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IE1hbGF5c2lhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIFByb3Rvbj8=",
            "answer": "S2VsaXNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZ1bGwgRW5nbGlzaCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIEJNVyBpcyBCYXZhcmlhbiBNb3RvciBXb3Jrcw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3VwZXJjYXIgY29tcGFueSBpcyBmcm9tIFN3ZWRlbj8=",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXV0b21vYmlsZXMgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgVGVsc2EgTW90b3JzIG9wZXJhdGUgb24gd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBlbmVyZ3k/",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWNpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBkbyB0aGUgNCBSaW5ncyBpbiBBdWRpJ3MgTG9nbyByZXByZXNlbnQ/",
            "answer": "UHJldmlvdXNseSBpbmRlcGVuZGVudCBhdXRvbW9iaWxlIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaW4gdGhlIExleHVzIFNDNDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MVVaLUZF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmVycmFyaSBoYXMgbmV2ZXIgbWFkZSBhIFYxMCBlbmdpbmUgZm9yIGFueSBvZiBpdHMgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEdlbmVyYWwgTW90b3JzIEVWMSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHN0cmVldC1sZWdhbCBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGVsZWN0cmljIHZlaGljbGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgb3ZlciA2IG1pbGxpb24gR2VuZXJhbCBNb3RvcnMgdmVoaWNsZXMgd2VyZSByZWNhbGxlZCBkdWUgdG8gd2hhdCBjcml0aWNhbCBmbGF3Pw==",
            "answer": "RmF1bHR5IGlnbml0aW9uIHN3aXRjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJFYWdsZSIgYnJhbmQgb2YgdGlyZXMsIGFuZCBpcyB0aGUgb2ZmaWNpYWwgdGlyZSBzdXBwbGllciBvZiBOQVNDQVI/",
            "answer": "R29vZHllYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJQIFplcm8iIGxpbmU/",
            "answer": "UGlyZWxsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgbm90IG1hZGUgYnkgRm9yZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTNyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "NDI3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaXNzYW4ncyBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBjcmVhdGVkIHRoZSAiQXZlbnRhZG9yIj8=",
            "answer": "TGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXVkaSBkb2VzIG5vdCB1c2UgSGFsZGV4IGJhc2VkIGFsbCB3aGVlbCBkcml2ZSBzeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "QXVkaSBBOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIFN1YmFydSB2ZWhpY2xlcyBhcmUgbWFkZSBpbiBDaGluYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIkdUTyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgYnkgRmVycmFyaT8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNub3dtb2JpbGUgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IENhbmFkaWFuIEpvc2VwaC1Bcm1hbmQgQm9tYmFyZGllciBpbiAxOTM3Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgVHJhYmFudCA2MDEgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "RWFzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMTk5MyBTd2VkaXNoIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgU2FhYiBleHBlcmltZW50ZWQgd2l0aCByZXBsYWNpbmcgdGhlIHN0ZWVyaW5nIHdoZWVsIHdpdGggYSBqb3lzdGljayBpbiBhIFNhYWIgOTAwMC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZyb250LXdoZWVsLWRyaXZlIGNhciBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSBEYXRzdW4gKG5vdyBOaXNzYW4pPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIGZlYXR1cmVzIG9uIHRoZSBsb2dvIGZvciBBYmFydGgsIHRoZSBtb3RvcnNwb3J0IGRpdmlzaW9uIG9mIEZpYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBwYXJ0IG9mIGFuIGF1dG9tb2JpbGUgZW5naW5lIHVzZXMgbG9iZXMgdG8gb3BlbiBhbmQgY2xvc2UgaW50YWtlIGFuZCBleGhhdXN0IHZhbHZlcywgYW5kIGFsbG93cyBhbiBhaXIvZnVlbCBtaXh0dXJlIGludG8gdGhlIGVuZ2luZT8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftc2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IGlzIHRoZSBIdXNzYXJ5YSBzdXBlcmNhciwgbWFkZSBieSB0aGUgY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciAiQXJyaW5lcmEiLCBhc3NlbWJsZWQgaW4/",
            "answer": "UG9sYW5k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgaGFzIG9mZmljaWFsbHkgYmFubmVkIHRoZSBjaXZpbGlhbiB1c2Ugb2YgZGFzaCBjYW1zIGluIGNhcnM/",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBwYXNzZW5nZXIgamV0cyBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9laW5nIDc0Ny04"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpZmZlcmVuY2UgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgbGVuZ3RocyBvZiBhIEJvZWluZyA3NzctMzAwRVIgYW5kIGFuIEFpcmJ1cyBBMzUwLTEwMDAgaXMgY2xvc2VzdCB0bzo=",
            "answer": "MC4xbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2ZWhpY2xlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIGZ1bGwgZ2xhc3Mgcm9vZiBhdCBiYXNlIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBBdmFudGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbW9kZWxzIGhhcyBiZWVuIGJhZGdlLWVuZ2luZWVyZWQgKHJlYmFkZ2VkKSB0aGUgbW9zdD8=",
            "answer": "SXN1enUgVHJvb3Blcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2FyIG1vZGVsIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IE1hbGF5c2lhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIFByb3Rvbj8=",
            "answer": "S2VsaXNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGRvZXMgTk9UIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlIG1vdG9yY3ljbGVzPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZ1bGwgRW5nbGlzaCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIEJNVyBpcyBCYXZhcmlhbiBNb3RvciBXb3Jrcw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGJyYW5kIGRvZXMgTk9UIGJlbG9uZyB0byBHZW5lcmFsIE1vdG9ycz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXV0b21vYmlsZXMgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgVGVsc2EgTW90b3JzIG9wZXJhdGUgb24gd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBlbmVyZ3k/",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWNpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBtYXNzLXByb2R1Y2VkIGh5YnJpZCB2ZWhpY2xlPw==",
            "answer": "VG95b3RhIFByaXVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FyIG1vZGVscyBhcmUgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgTGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk/",
            "answer": "QXZlbnRhZG9y"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJyaXZhIGlzIG93bmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBEZXV0c2NoZSBCYWhuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgc3ViLWNvbXBhbnkgb2YgdGhlIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gR3JvdXA/",
            "answer": "T3BlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEdlbmVyYWwgTW90b3JzIEVWMSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHN0cmVldC1sZWdhbCBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGVsZWN0cmljIHZlaGljbGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgb3ZlciA2IG1pbGxpb24gR2VuZXJhbCBNb3RvcnMgdmVoaWNsZXMgd2VyZSByZWNhbGxlZCBkdWUgdG8gd2hhdCBjcml0aWNhbCBmbGF3Pw==",
            "answer": "RmF1bHR5IGlnbml0aW9uIHN3aXRjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBtb2RlbCB3YXMgdGhlIHNwb3J0cyBjYXIgZ2lmdGVkIHRvIFl1cmkgR2FnYXJpbiBieSB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIGdvdmVybm1lbnQgaW4gMTk2NT8=",
            "answer": "TWF0cmEgRGpldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgbm90IG1hZGUgYnkgRm9yZD8=",
            "answer": "Q2Ftcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaXNzYW4ncyBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBjcmVhdGVkIHRoZSAiQXZlbnRhZG9yIj8=",
            "answer": "TGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQXVkaSBkb2VzIG5vdCB1c2UgSGFsZGV4IGJhc2VkIGFsbCB3aGVlbCBkcml2ZSBzeXN0ZW0/",
            "answer": "QXVkaSBBOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBraW5kIG9mIHRyYWluIHdhcyBTdGVwbmV5LCBhIHRyYWluIG9uIHRoZSBCbHVlYmVsbCBSYWlsd2F5IG5vdGFibGUgZm9yIGhpcyBhcHBlYXJhbmNlIGluICJUaGUgUmFpbHdheSBTZXJpZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TEImU0NSIEExWA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qk1XIE0gR21iSCBpcyBhIHN1YnNpZGlhcnkgb2YgQk1XIEFHIHRoYXQgZm9jdXNlcyBvbiBjYXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIkdUTyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgYnkgRmVycmFyaT8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb3VudHJ5IHdhcyB0aGUgVHJhYmFudCA2MDEgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "RWFzdCBHZXJtYW55"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FycyBpcyBOT1QgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIDUgTW9kZXJuIFN1cGVyY2FycyBieSBGZXJyYXJpPw==",
            "answer": "VGVzdGFyb3NzYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlcmUgYXJlIHRoZSBjYXJzIG9mIHRoZSBicmFuZCAiRmVycmFyaSIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkPw==",
            "answer": "SXRhbHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGZyb250LXdoZWVsLWRyaXZlIGNhciBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSBEYXRzdW4gKG5vdyBOaXNzYW4pPw==",
            "answer": "Q2hlcnJ5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWFsIGZlYXR1cmVzIG9uIHRoZSBsb2dvIGZvciBBYmFydGgsIHRoZSBtb3RvcnNwb3J0IGRpdmlzaW9uIG9mIEZpYXQ/",
            "answer": "U2NvcnBpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28/",
            "answer": "QnVsbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSXRhbGlhbiBjaXR5IGlzIGhvbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgJ0ZpYXQnPw==",
            "answer": "VHVyaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY291bnRyeSBoYXMgdGhlIGludGVybmF0aW9uYWwgdmVoaWNsZSByZWdpc3RyYXRpb24gbGV0dGVyICdBJz8=",
            "answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVycyBoYWQgYSB3YXIgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgaXQ/",
            "answer": "VG95b3Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEphcGFuZXNlIFNoaW5rYW5zZW4gYmVhdCB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIFRHVidzIHNwZWVkIHJlY29yZCBmb3IgZmFzdGVzdCBlbGVjdHJpYyByYWlsIHRyYWluLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGRpZmZlcmVuY2UgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgbGVuZ3RocyBvZiBhIEJvZWluZyA3NzctMzAwRVIgYW5kIGFuIEFpcmJ1cyBBMzUwLTEwMDAgaXMgY2xvc2VzdCB0bzo=",
            "answer": "MC4xbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RW56byBGZXJyYXJpIHdhcyBvcmlnaW5hbGx5IGFuIGF1dG8gcmFjZXIgZm9yIHdoYXQgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGJlZm9yZSBmb3VuZGluZyBoaXMgb3duIGNhciBjb21wYW55Pw==",
            "answer": "QWxmYSBSb21lbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q29tcGxldGUgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmFsb2d5OiBBdWRpIGlzIHRvIFZvbGtzd2FnZW4gYXMgSW5maW5pdGkgaXMgdG8gPw==",
            "answer": "Tmlzc2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SmFndWFyIENhcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbmZhY3R1cmVyPw==",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyB2ZWhpY2xlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhIGZ1bGwgZ2xhc3Mgcm9vZiBhdCBiYXNlIG1vZGVsPw==",
            "answer": "UmVuYXVsdCBBdmFudGltZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIENoZXZyb2xldCBDb3J2ZXR0ZSBoYXMgYWx3YXlzIGJlZW4gbWFkZSBleGNsdXNpdmVseSB3aXRoIFY4IGVuZ2luZXMgb25seS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgVGVzbGEgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBVSyBUcmFpbiBkb2VzIE5PVCBnbyBvdmVyIDEyNU1QSD8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "VENBUw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2FyIG1vZGVsIHByb2R1Y2VkIGJ5IE1hbGF5c2lhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIFByb3Rvbj8=",
            "answer": "S2VsaXNh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGZ1bGwgRW5nbGlzaCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIEJNVyBpcyBCYXZhcmlhbiBNb3RvciBXb3Jrcw==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXNzaXMgY29kZXMgYXJlIHVzZWQgYnkgQk1XIDMtc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "RTQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3VwZXJjYXIgY29tcGFueSBpcyBmcm9tIFN3ZWRlbj8=",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIGJyYW5kIGRvZXMgTk9UIGJlbG9uZyB0byBHZW5lcmFsIE1vdG9ycz8=",
            "answer": "Rm9yZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QXV0b21vYmlsZXMgcHJvZHVjZWQgYnkgVGVsc2EgTW90b3JzIG9wZXJhdGUgb24gd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBlbmVyZ3k/",
            "answer": "RWxlY3RyaWNpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVmFyaWFibGUgVmFsdmUgVGltaW5nIHRlY2hub2xvZ3kgaXMgdXNlZCBieSBCTVc/",
            "answer": "VkFOT1M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIGlzIE5PVCB0aGUgZnVuY3Rpb24gb2YgZW5naW5lIG9pbCBpbiBjYXIgZW5naW5lcz8=",
            "answer": "Q29tYnVzdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SG93IG11Y2ggaG9yc2Vwb3dlciBpcyBwcm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgU0Q0MC0yIExvY29tb3RpdmU/",
            "answer": "MywwMDA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaW4gdGhlIExleHVzIFNDNDAwPw==",
            "answer": "MVVaLUZF"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Vm9sa3N3YWdlbidzIGxlZ2VuZGFyeSBWUjYgZW5naW5lIGhhcyBjeWxpbmRlcnMgcG9zaXRpb25lZCBhdCB3aGF0IGRlZ3JlZSBhbmdsZT8=",
            "answer": "MTUgRGVncmVl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QXJyaXZhIGlzIG93bmVkIGJ5IHRoZSBEZXV0c2NoZSBCYWhuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RmVycmFyaSBoYXMgbmV2ZXIgbWFkZSBhIFYxMCBlbmdpbmUgZm9yIGFueSBvZiBpdHMgY2Fycy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIEdlbmVyYWwgTW90b3JzIEVWMSB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHN0cmVldC1sZWdhbCBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIGVsZWN0cmljIHZlaGljbGUu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnVnYXR0aSB3YXMgYW4gSXRhbGlhbiBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxNCwgb3ZlciA2IG1pbGxpb24gR2VuZXJhbCBNb3RvcnMgdmVoaWNsZXMgd2VyZSByZWNhbGxlZCBkdWUgdG8gd2hhdCBjcml0aWNhbCBmbGF3Pw==",
            "answer": "RmF1bHR5IGlnbml0aW9uIHN3aXRjaA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIHRpcmUgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGlzIGZhbW91cyBmb3IgaXRzICJQIFplcm8iIGxpbmU/",
            "answer": "UGlyZWxsaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgQ2FkaWxsYWMgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTkwMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGN5bGluZGVyLWxpa2UgcGFydHMgdGhhdCBwdW1wIHVwIGFuZCBkb3duIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgZW5naW5lPw==",
            "answer": "UGlzdG9ucw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuaWNrbmFtZSB3YXMgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQWlyIENhbmFkYSBGbGlnaHQgMTQzIGFmdGVyIGl0IHJhbiBvdXQgb2YgZnVlbCBhbmQgZ2xpZGVkIHRvIHNhZmV0eSBpbiAxOTgzPw==",
            "answer": "R2ltbGkgR2xpZGVy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMSBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzQ2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMiBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "MzY0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIExTMyBlbmdpbmUgaXMgaG93IG1hbnkgY3ViaWMgaW5jaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "Mzc2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBOaXNzYW4ncyBtb3N0IHBvcHVsYXIgZWxlY3RyaWMgY2FyPw==",
            "answer": "TGVhZg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2FyIG1hbnVmYWN0dXJlciBjcmVhdGVkIHRoZSAiQXZlbnRhZG9yIj8=",
            "answer": "TGFtYm9yZ2hpbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgQ2hldnJvbGV0IExVViBtaW5pIHRydWNrIG1ha2UgaXRzIGRlYnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk3Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1ham9yaXR5IG9mIFN1YmFydSB2ZWhpY2xlcyBhcmUgbWFkZSBpbiBDaGluYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Qk1XIE0gR21iSCBpcyBhIHN1YnNpZGlhcnkgb2YgQk1XIEFHIHRoYXQgZm9jdXNlcyBvbiBjYXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Uu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXIgbWFudWZhY3R1cmVyIGdhdmUgYXdheSB0aGVpciBwYXRlbnQgZm9yIHRoZSBzZWF0LWJlbHQgaW4gdGhlIGludGVyZXN0IG9mIHNhdmluZyBsaXZlcz8=",
            "answer": "Vm9sdm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gIkdUTyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgYnkgRmVycmFyaT8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNub3dtb2JpbGUgd2FzIGludmVudGVkIGJ5IENhbmFkaWFuIEpvc2VwaC1Bcm1hbmQgQm9tYmFyZGllciBpbiAxOTM3Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2FycyBpcyBOT1QgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIDUgTW9kZXJuIFN1cGVyY2FycyBieSBGZXJyYXJpPw==",
            "answer": "VGVzdGFyb3NzYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZmFzdGVzdCByb2FkIGxlZ2FsIGNhciBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/",
            "answer": "S29lbmlnc2VnZyBBZ2VyYSBSUw=="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ29taWNz": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIEJhdG1hbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJ1Y2UgV2F5bmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFydmVsIENvbWljcywgVGF1cnVzIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIGFuZCBsZWFkZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggY3JpbWluYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Wm9kaWFj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiBjb21pY3MsIGJ5IHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgbmFtZSBpcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBEci4gSm9uYXRoYW4gQ3JhbmUga25vd24/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmVjcm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljIGJvb2sgIkFyY2hpZSIsIEJldHR5IGlzIGZyaWVuZHMgd2l0aCBWZXJvbmljYSBiZWNhdXNlIHNoZSBpcyByaWNoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29taWMgYWJvdXQgYSB5b3VuZyBib3ksIGFuZCBhIHRpZ2VyIHdobyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSBhIHN0dWZmZWQgYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVhZHBvb2wncyBpZGVudGl0eSBpcyBTbGFkZSBXaWxzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUHJlLVN1cGVyIEdlbmVzaXMgdW5pdmVyc2Ugb2YgIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mICBTYWxseSBBY29ybidzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWxpYXMgQWNvcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgUm9ib3RpY2l6ZXI/IA==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIENoYXJsZXMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiIGNvbWljIGNvbWUgb3V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljcywgd2hpY2ggU29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvb2sgY29tbWFuZCBvZiB0aGUgRGFyayBMZWdpb24gYWZ0ZXIgTHVnZXIncyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TGllbi1EYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBcmNoaWUiIGNvbWljcywgd2hvIHdhcyBKdWdoZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9hbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkdyZWVuIEFycm93IiBzaWRla2ljayBjb21tb25seSB3ZWFycyBhIGJhc2ViYWxsIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "Um95IEhhcnBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmF0bWFuIHNpZGVraWNrIGlzIHRoZSBzb24gb2YgVGFsaWEgYWwgR2h1bD8=",
            "answer": "RGFtaWFuIFdheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gc2l4IHllYXIgb2xkIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzIGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIHdoYXQgdGhlb2xvZ2lhbj8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBDYWx2aW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0dWZmZWQgdGlnZXIgaW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMgaXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgd2hhdCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEhvYmJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgaW5zcGlyYXRpb24gZm9yIEN1dGhiZXJ0IENhbGN1bHVzIGluIHRoZSBUaW50aW4gc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0ZSBQaWNhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByaW5ncyBmcm9tIHRoZSBEQyBDb21pY3MnICJMYW50ZXJuIENvcnBzIiBhcmUgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBQYXJhc2l0aWM/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWdvIChDb21wYXNzaW9uKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgdGhlICJLaW5nZG9tIG9mIERhcmtuZXNzIiBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "RGVyc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmlvbmljbGUsIHdobyB3YXMgZm9ybWVybHkgYSBBdi1NYXRvcmFuIGFuZCBpcyBub3cgdGhlIFRvYSBvZiBMaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGFrdWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWFydmVsIENvbWljcyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdobyBmb3VuZGVkIHRoZSBCUFJEPw==",
            "answer": "VHJldm9yIEJydXR0ZW5ob2xt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFiZSBTYXBpZW4ncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFuZ2RvbiBFdmVyZXR0IENhdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSByYWNlIG9mIEludmluY2libGUncyBmYXRoZXI/",
            "answer": "VmlsdHJ1bWl0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHN1cGVyaGVybyB0ZWFtcyBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHRoZSBJbnZpbmNpYmxlIGNvbWljcz8=",
            "answer": "R3VhcmRpYW5zIG9mIHRoZSBHbG9iZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBjb21pYyBzZXJpZXMgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEtpcmttYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFJvYmluIGluIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWNzPw==",
            "answer": "RGljayBHcmF5c29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVhZHBvb2wncyBpZGVudGl0eSBpcyBTbGFkZSBXaWxzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUHJlLVN1cGVyIEdlbmVzaXMgdW5pdmVyc2Ugb2YgIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mICBTYWxseSBBY29ybidzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWxpYXMgQWNvcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgUm9ib3RpY2l6ZXI/IA==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIENoYXJsZXMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU2FuIERpZWdvIENvbWljLUNvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBoYWlyIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbnN0cmVhbSBjb21pYyBib29rIHZlcnNpb24gKEVhcnRoLTYxNikgb2YgRGFyZWRldmlsPw==",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiIGNvbWljIGNvbWUgb3V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljcywgd2hpY2ggU29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvb2sgY29tbWFuZCBvZiB0aGUgRGFyayBMZWdpb24gYWZ0ZXIgTHVnZXIncyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TGllbi1EYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBcmNoaWUiIGNvbWljcywgd2hvIHdhcyBKdWdoZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9hbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljICJBdmEncyBEZW1vbiIsIHdoYXQgc2luIGlzICJOZXZ5IE5lcnZpbmUiIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBvZj8g",
            "answer": "RW52eSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gc2l4IHllYXIgb2xkIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzIGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIHdoYXQgdGhlb2xvZ2lhbj8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBDYWx2aW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0dWZmZWQgdGlnZXIgaW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMgaXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgd2hhdCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEhvYmJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU3VzaWUncyBzdHVmZmVkIHJhYmJpdD8=",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk3OCwgU3VwZXJtYW4gdGVhbWVkIHVwIHdpdGggd2hhdCBjZWxlYnJpdHksIHRvIGRlZmVhdCBhbiBhbGllbiBpbnZhc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVoYW1tYWQgQWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgaW5zcGlyYXRpb24gZm9yIEN1dGhiZXJ0IENhbGN1bHVzIGluIHRoZSBUaW50aW4gc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0ZSBQaWNhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSAiTWFzdGVyIE9mIE1hZ25ldGlzbSIgTWFnbmV0bz8=",
            "answer": "TWF4IEVpc2VuaGFyZHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmlvbmljbGUsIHdobyB3YXMgZm9ybWVybHkgYSBBdi1NYXRvcmFuIGFuZCBpcyBub3cgdGhlIFRvYSBvZiBMaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGFrdWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWFydmVsIENvbWljcyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIb21lc3R1Y2sgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdhbXplZSdzIGxhc3QgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdobyBmb3VuZGVkIHRoZSBCUFJEPw==",
            "answer": "VHJldm9yIEJydXR0ZW5ob2xt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZWxsYm95J3MgdHJ1ZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QW51bmcgVW4gUmFtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHN1cGVyaGVybyB0ZWFtcyBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHRoZSBJbnZpbmNpYmxlIGNvbWljcz8=",
            "answer": "R3VhcmRpYW5zIG9mIHRoZSBHbG9iZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIEJhdG1hbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJ1Y2UgV2F5bmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiBjb21pY3MsIGJ5IHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgbmFtZSBpcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBEci4gSm9uYXRoYW4gQ3JhbmUga25vd24/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmVjcm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBjb21pYyBzZXJpZXMgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEtpcmttYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljIGJvb2sgIkFyY2hpZSIsIEJldHR5IGlzIGZyaWVuZHMgd2l0aCBWZXJvbmljYSBiZWNhdXNlIHNoZSBpcyByaWNoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29taWMgYWJvdXQgYSB5b3VuZyBib3ksIGFuZCBhIHRpZ2VyIHdobyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSBhIHN0dWZmZWQgYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUHJlLVN1cGVyIEdlbmVzaXMgdW5pdmVyc2Ugb2YgIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mICBTYWxseSBBY29ybidzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWxpYXMgQWNvcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWMgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgS2lsbGluZyBKb2tlIj8=",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBNb29yZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU2FuIERpZWdvIENvbWljLUNvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBoYWlyIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbnN0cmVhbSBjb21pYyBib29rIHZlcnNpb24gKEVhcnRoLTYxNikgb2YgRGFyZWRldmlsPw==",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiIGNvbWljIGNvbWUgb3V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljcywgd2hpY2ggU29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvb2sgY29tbWFuZCBvZiB0aGUgRGFyayBMZWdpb24gYWZ0ZXIgTHVnZXIncyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TGllbi1EYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBcmNoaWUiIGNvbWljcywgd2hvIHdhcyBKdWdoZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9hbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljICJBdmEncyBEZW1vbiIsIHdoYXQgc2luIGlzICJOZXZ5IE5lcnZpbmUiIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBvZj8g",
            "answer": "RW52eSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkdyZWVuIEFycm93IiBzaWRla2ljayBjb21tb25seSB3ZWFycyBhIGJhc2ViYWxsIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "Um95IEhhcnBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmF0bWFuIHNpZGVraWNrIGlzIHRoZSBzb24gb2YgVGFsaWEgYWwgR2h1bD8=",
            "answer": "RGFtaWFuIFdheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0dWZmZWQgdGlnZXIgaW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMgaXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgd2hhdCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEhvYmJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU3VzaWUncyBzdHVmZmVkIHJhYmJpdD8=",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk3OCwgU3VwZXJtYW4gdGVhbWVkIHVwIHdpdGggd2hhdCBjZWxlYnJpdHksIHRvIGRlZmVhdCBhbiBhbGllbiBpbnZhc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVoYW1tYWQgQWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmlvbmljbGUsIHdobyB3YXMgZm9ybWVybHkgYSBBdi1NYXRvcmFuIGFuZCBpcyBub3cgdGhlIFRvYSBvZiBMaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGFrdWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIb21lc3R1Y2sgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdhbXplZSdzIGxhc3QgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdobyBmb3VuZGVkIHRoZSBCUFJEPw==",
            "answer": "VHJldm9yIEJydXR0ZW5ob2xt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHN1cGVyaGVybyB0ZWFtcyBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHRoZSBJbnZpbmNpYmxlIGNvbWljcz8=",
            "answer": "R3VhcmRpYW5zIG9mIHRoZSBHbG9iZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIEJhdG1hbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJ1Y2UgV2F5bmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFydmVsIENvbWljcywgVGF1cnVzIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIGFuZCBsZWFkZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggY3JpbWluYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Wm9kaWFj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiBjb21pY3MsIGJ5IHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgbmFtZSBpcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBEci4gSm9uYXRoYW4gQ3JhbmUga25vd24/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmVjcm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljIGJvb2sgIkFyY2hpZSIsIEJldHR5IGlzIGZyaWVuZHMgd2l0aCBWZXJvbmljYSBiZWNhdXNlIHNoZSBpcyByaWNoLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFJvYmluIGluIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWNzPw==",
            "answer": "RGljayBHcmF5c29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWMgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgS2lsbGluZyBKb2tlIj8=",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBNb29yZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU2FuIERpZWdvIENvbWljLUNvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBcmNoaWUiIGNvbWljcywgd2hvIHdhcyBKdWdoZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9hbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmF0bWFuIHNpZGVraWNrIGlzIHRoZSBzb24gb2YgVGFsaWEgYWwgR2h1bD8=",
            "answer": "RGFtaWFuIFdheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0dWZmZWQgdGlnZXIgaW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMgaXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgd2hhdCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEhvYmJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk3OCwgU3VwZXJtYW4gdGVhbWVkIHVwIHdpdGggd2hhdCBjZWxlYnJpdHksIHRvIGRlZmVhdCBhbiBhbGllbiBpbnZhc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVoYW1tYWQgQWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgaW5zcGlyYXRpb24gZm9yIEN1dGhiZXJ0IENhbGN1bHVzIGluIHRoZSBUaW50aW4gc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0ZSBQaWNhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByaW5ncyBmcm9tIHRoZSBEQyBDb21pY3MnICJMYW50ZXJuIENvcnBzIiBhcmUgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBQYXJhc2l0aWM/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWdvIChDb21wYXNzaW9uKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSAiTWFzdGVyIE9mIE1hZ25ldGlzbSIgTWFnbmV0bz8=",
            "answer": "TWF4IEVpc2VuaGFyZHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmlvbmljbGUsIHdobyB3YXMgZm9ybWVybHkgYSBBdi1NYXRvcmFuIGFuZCBpcyBub3cgdGhlIFRvYSBvZiBMaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGFrdWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWFydmVsIENvbWljcyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIb21lc3R1Y2sgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdhbXplZSdzIGxhc3QgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFiZSBTYXBpZW4ncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFuZ2RvbiBFdmVyZXR0IENhdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSByYWNlIG9mIEludmluY2libGUncyBmYXRoZXI/",
            "answer": "VmlsdHJ1bWl0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHN1cGVyaGVybyB0ZWFtcyBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHRoZSBJbnZpbmNpYmxlIGNvbWljcz8=",
            "answer": "R3VhcmRpYW5zIG9mIHRoZSBHbG9iZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiBjb21pY3MsIGJ5IHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgbmFtZSBpcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBEci4gSm9uYXRoYW4gQ3JhbmUga25vd24/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmVjcm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBjb21pYyBzZXJpZXMgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEtpcmttYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFJvYmluIGluIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWNzPw==",
            "answer": "RGljayBHcmF5c29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29taWMgYWJvdXQgYSB5b3VuZyBib3ksIGFuZCBhIHRpZ2VyIHdobyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSBhIHN0dWZmZWQgYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUHJlLVN1cGVyIEdlbmVzaXMgdW5pdmVyc2Ugb2YgIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mICBTYWxseSBBY29ybidzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWxpYXMgQWNvcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgUm9ib3RpY2l6ZXI/IA==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIENoYXJsZXMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU2FuIERpZWdvIENvbWljLUNvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBoYWlyIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbnN0cmVhbSBjb21pYyBib29rIHZlcnNpb24gKEVhcnRoLTYxNikgb2YgRGFyZWRldmlsPw==",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljcywgd2hpY2ggU29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvb2sgY29tbWFuZCBvZiB0aGUgRGFyayBMZWdpb24gYWZ0ZXIgTHVnZXIncyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TGllbi1EYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljICJBdmEncyBEZW1vbiIsIHdoYXQgc2luIGlzICJOZXZ5IE5lcnZpbmUiIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBvZj8g",
            "answer": "RW52eSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkdyZWVuIEFycm93IiBzaWRla2ljayBjb21tb25seSB3ZWFycyBhIGJhc2ViYWxsIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "Um95IEhhcnBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmF0bWFuIHNpZGVraWNrIGlzIHRoZSBzb24gb2YgVGFsaWEgYWwgR2h1bD8=",
            "answer": "RGFtaWFuIFdheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gc2l4IHllYXIgb2xkIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzIGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIHdoYXQgdGhlb2xvZ2lhbj8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBDYWx2aW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0dWZmZWQgdGlnZXIgaW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMgaXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgd2hhdCBwaGlsb3NvcGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzIEhvYmJlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU3VzaWUncyBzdHVmZmVkIHJhYmJpdD8=",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgaW5zcGlyYXRpb24gZm9yIEN1dGhiZXJ0IENhbGN1bHVzIGluIHRoZSBUaW50aW4gc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0ZSBQaWNhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByaW5ncyBmcm9tIHRoZSBEQyBDb21pY3MnICJMYW50ZXJuIENvcnBzIiBhcmUgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBQYXJhc2l0aWM/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWdvIChDb21wYXNzaW9uKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSAiTWFzdGVyIE9mIE1hZ25ldGlzbSIgTWFnbmV0bz8=",
            "answer": "TWF4IEVpc2VuaGFyZHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgdGhlICJLaW5nZG9tIG9mIERhcmtuZXNzIiBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "RGVyc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWFydmVsIENvbWljcyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdobyBmb3VuZGVkIHRoZSBCUFJEPw==",
            "answer": "VHJldm9yIEJydXR0ZW5ob2xt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZWxsYm95J3MgdHJ1ZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QW51bmcgVW4gUmFtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFiZSBTYXBpZW4ncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFuZ2RvbiBFdmVyZXR0IENhdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSByYWNlIG9mIEludmluY2libGUncyBmYXRoZXI/",
            "answer": "VmlsdHJ1bWl0ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHN1cGVyaGVybyB0ZWFtcyBhcHBlYXJzIGluIHRoZSBJbnZpbmNpYmxlIGNvbWljcz8=",
            "answer": "R3VhcmRpYW5zIG9mIHRoZSBHbG9iZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiBjb21pY3MsIGJ5IHdoYXQgb3RoZXIgbmFtZSBpcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBEci4gSm9uYXRoYW4gQ3JhbmUga25vd24/",
            "answer": "U2NhcmVjcm93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFJvYmluIGluIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWNzPw==",
            "answer": "RGljayBHcmF5c29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29taWMgYWJvdXQgYSB5b3VuZyBib3ksIGFuZCBhIHRpZ2VyIHdobyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSBhIHN0dWZmZWQgYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVhZHBvb2wncyBpZGVudGl0eSBpcyBTbGFkZSBXaWxzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzdXBlcmhlcm9zIGRpZCBXb25kZXIgV29tYW4gTk9UIGhhdmUgYSBsb3ZlIGludGVyZXN0IGluPw==",
            "answer": "R3JlZW4gQXJyb3c="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhpcyBNYXJ2ZWwgc3VwZXJoZXJvIGlzIG9mdGVuIGNhbGxlZCAiVGhlIG1hbiB3aXRob3V0IGZlYXIiLg==",
            "answer": "RGFyZWRldmls"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUHJlLVN1cGVyIEdlbmVzaXMgdW5pdmVyc2Ugb2YgIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mICBTYWxseSBBY29ybidzIGJyb3RoZXI/",
            "answer": "RWxpYXMgQWNvcm4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgUm9ib3RpY2l6ZXI/IA==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIENoYXJsZXMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWMgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgS2lsbGluZyBKb2tlIj8=",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBNb29yZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBoYWlyIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbnN0cmVhbSBjb21pYyBib29rIHZlcnNpb24gKEVhcnRoLTYxNikgb2YgRGFyZWRldmlsPw==",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGNvbWljcywgd2hpY2ggU29uaWMgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvb2sgY29tbWFuZCBvZiB0aGUgRGFyayBMZWdpb24gYWZ0ZXIgTHVnZXIncyBhc3Nhc3NpbmF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "TGllbi1EYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJBcmNoaWUiIGNvbWljcywgd2hvIHdhcyBKdWdoZWFkJ3MgZmlyc3QgZ2lybGZyaWVuZD8=",
            "answer": "Sm9hbmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljICJBdmEncyBEZW1vbiIsIHdoYXQgc2luIGlzICJOZXZ5IE5lcnZpbmUiIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBvZj8g",
            "answer": "RW52eSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkdyZWVuIEFycm93IiBzaWRla2ljayBjb21tb25seSB3ZWFycyBhIGJhc2ViYWxsIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "Um95IEhhcnBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggQmF0bWFuIHNpZGVraWNrIGlzIHRoZSBzb24gb2YgVGFsaWEgYWwgR2h1bD8=",
            "answer": "RGFtaWFuIFdheW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU3VzaWUncyBzdHVmZmVkIHJhYmJpdD8=",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk3OCwgU3VwZXJtYW4gdGVhbWVkIHVwIHdpdGggd2hhdCBjZWxlYnJpdHksIHRvIGRlZmVhdCBhbiBhbGllbiBpbnZhc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVoYW1tYWQgQWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgaW5zcGlyYXRpb24gZm9yIEN1dGhiZXJ0IENhbGN1bHVzIGluIHRoZSBUaW50aW4gc2VyaWVzPw==",
            "answer": "QXVndXN0ZSBQaWNhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByaW5ncyBmcm9tIHRoZSBEQyBDb21pY3MnICJMYW50ZXJuIENvcnBzIiBhcmUgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBQYXJhc2l0aWM/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWdvIChDb21wYXNzaW9uKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSAiTWFzdGVyIE9mIE1hZ25ldGlzbSIgTWFnbmV0bz8=",
            "answer": "TWF4IEVpc2VuaGFyZHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdobyBmb3VuZGVkIHRoZSBCUFJEPw==",
            "answer": "VHJldm9yIEJydXR0ZW5ob2xt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZWxsYm95J3MgdHJ1ZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QW51bmcgVW4gUmFtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFiZSBTYXBpZW4ncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFuZ2RvbiBFdmVyZXR0IENhdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGNpdHkgZGlkIHRoZSBoZXJvZXMgc2F2ZSBmcm9tIHRoZSBBbnRpLUdvZD8=",
            "answer": "U3BpcmFsIENpdHk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmxhY2sgSGFtbWVyLCB3aGF0IGRpbWVuc2lvbiBkb2VzIENvbG9uZWwgV2VpcmQgdHJhdmVsIHRocm91Z2g/",
            "answer": "UGFyYS1ab25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIEJhdG1hbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJ1Y2UgV2F5bmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gTWFydmVsIENvbWljcywgVGF1cnVzIGlzIHRoZSBmb3VuZGVyIGFuZCBsZWFkZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggY3JpbWluYWwgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "Wm9kaWFj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzIHBhcmVudHM/",
            "answer": "VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBjb21pYyBzZXJpZXMgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiPw==",
            "answer": "Um9iZXJ0IEtpcmttYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFJvYmluIGluIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWNzPw==",
            "answer": "RGljayBHcmF5c29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29taWMgYWJvdXQgYSB5b3VuZyBib3ksIGFuZCBhIHRpZ2VyIHdobyBpcyBhY3R1YWxseSBhIHN0dWZmZWQgYW5pbWFsPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEd1bm5lcmtyaWdnIENvdXJ0IGJ5IFRvbSBTaWRkZWxsPw==",
            "answer": "QW50aW1vbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "RGVhZHBvb2wncyBpZGVudGl0eSBpcyBTbGFkZSBXaWxzb24u",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCBIb21lc3R1Y2sgVXBkYXRlIHdhcyBbU10gR2FtZSBPdmVyIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNXRoLCAyMDE0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhvbWVzdHVjayBTZXJpZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGFsdGVybmF0ZSBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgS2luZ2RvbSBvZiBMaWdodHM/",
            "answer": "UHJvc3BpdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljIEhvbWVzdHVjaywgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGlzIERhdmUgU3RyaWRlci4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJQZXBlIiBtZW1lIG9yaWdpbmF0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIGNvbWljIGRyYXduIGJ5IE1hdHQgRnVyaWUgY2FsbGVkICJCb3kncyBDbHViIj8=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXNzdWUgb2YgdGhlICJTb25pYyB0aGUgSGVkZ2Vob2ciIGNvbWljIGRpZCBTY291cmdlIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyBtYWtlIGhpcyBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nICMxMQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgY29taWMsIHdobyB3YXMgdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgUm9ib3RpY2l6ZXI/IA==",
            "answer": "UHJvZmVzc29yIENoYXJsZXMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggdW5pdmVyc2UgY3Jvc3NvdmVyIHdhcyBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGluIHRoZSAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIiBjb21pYyBpc3N1ZSAjMjQ3Pw==",
            "answer": "TWVnYSBNYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBCYXRtYW4gY29taWMgc2VyaWVzICJUaGUgS2lsbGluZyBKb2tlIj8=",
            "answer": "QWxhbiBNb29yZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgU2FuIERpZWdvIENvbWljLUNvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk3MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIEdhcmZpZWxkIGNvbWljIGZpcnN0IHB1Ymxpc2hlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk3OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGF1dGhvcmVkIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIFRpbnRpbj8=",
            "answer": "SGVyZ8Op"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVzaWduYXRpb24gZ2l2ZW4gdG8gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDaW5lbWF0aWMgVW5pdmVyc2U/",
            "answer": "RWFydGgtMTk5OTk5"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgVWx0cm9uIG9mIEVhcnRoLTYxNj8=",
            "answer": "SGVucnkgUHlt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVhbCBoYWlyIGNvbG91ciBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbnN0cmVhbSBjb21pYyBib29rIHZlcnNpb24gKEVhcnRoLTYxNikgb2YgRGFyZWRldmlsPw==",
            "answer": "QmxvbmRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZmlyc3QgIlRoZSBXYWxraW5nIERlYWQiIGNvbWljIGNvbWUgb3V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MjAwMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWx0ZXItZWdvIG9mIHRoZSBEQyBjb21pY3MgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJTdXBlcm1hbiI/",
            "answer": "Q2xhcmsgS2VudA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYmNvbWljICJBdmEncyBEZW1vbiIsIHdoYXQgc2luIGlzICJOZXZ5IE5lcnZpbmUiIGJhc2VkIG9mZiBvZj8g",
            "answer": "RW52eSA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIkdyZWVuIEFycm93IiBzaWRla2ljayBjb21tb25seSB3ZWFycyBhIGJhc2ViYWxsIGNhcD8=",
            "answer": "Um95IEhhcnBlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIERDIENvbWljcyAyMDE2IHJlYm9vdCwgUmViaXJ0aCwgd2hpY2ggc3BlZWRzdGVyIGVzY2FwZWQgZnJvbSB0aGUgU3BlZWQgRm9yY2UgYWZ0ZXIgaGUgaGFkIGJlZW4gZXJhc2VkIGZyb20gZXhpc3RhbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "V2FsbHkgV2VzdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZnVsbCBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBiYWJ5c2l0dGVyIGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zYWx5bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGJhYnlzaXR0ZXIncyBib3lmcmllbmQ/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gc2l4IHllYXIgb2xkIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluIENhbHZpbiBhbmQgSG9iYmVzIGlzIG5hbWVkIGFmdGVyIHdoYXQgdGhlb2xvZ2lhbj8=",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBDYWx2aW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU3VzaWUncyBzdHVmZmVkIHJhYmJpdD8=",
            "answer": "TXIuIEJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2FsdmluIGFuZCBIb2JiZXMsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBhdCBDYWx2aW4ncyBzY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFNwaXR0bGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBCYXRtYW4gdHJvbGxzIHRoZSBvbmxpbmUgY2hhdCByb29tcywgd2hhdCBhbGlhcyBkb2VzIGhlIHVzZT8=",
            "answer": "Sm9uRG9lMjk3"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gMTk3OCwgU3VwZXJtYW4gdGVhbWVkIHVwIHdpdGggd2hhdCBjZWxlYnJpdHksIHRvIGRlZmVhdCBhbiBhbGllbiBpbnZhc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "TXVoYW1tYWQgQWxp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyByaW5ncyBmcm9tIHRoZSBEQyBDb21pY3MnICJMYW50ZXJuIENvcnBzIiBhcmUgY2xhc3NpZmllZCBhcyBQYXJhc2l0aWM/",
            "answer": "SW5kaWdvIChDb21wYXNzaW9uKQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIG5hbWVzIG9mIHRoZSB0d28gIkNhbm9uIGZhbiB0cm9sbHMiIGluICJIb21lc3R1Y2siPw==",
            "answer": "TWllcmZhIER1cmdhcyBhbmQgTmVrdGFuIFdoZWxhbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgd2hhdCBpcyBEYXZlIFN0cmlkZXIncyBndWFyZGlhbj8=",
            "answer": "QnJv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkhvbWVzdHVjayIgdGhlICJLaW5nZG9tIG9mIERhcmtuZXNzIiBpcyBhbHNvIGtub3duIGFzPw==",
            "answer": "RGVyc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQmlvbmljbGUsIHdobyB3YXMgZm9ybWVybHkgYSBBdi1NYXRvcmFuIGFuZCBpcyBub3cgdGhlIFRvYSBvZiBMaWdodD8=",
            "answer": "VGFrdWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Rm91bmQgaW4gdGhlIE1hcnZlbCBDb21pY3MgZmljdGlvbmFsIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBuZWFybHkgaW5kZXN0cnVjdGlibGUgbWV0YWwgdGhhdCBjb2F0cyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBib25lcyBhbmQgY2xhd3M/",
            "answer": "QWRhbWFudGl1bQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgcGVyc29uIHRvIHRha2UgdXAgdGhlIG1hbnRsZSBvZiBOaWdodCBPd2wgaW4gdGhlIFdhdGNobWVuIGdyYXBoaWMgbm92ZWw/",
            "answer": "RGFuaWVsIERyZWliZXJn"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgTWFydmVsIENvbWljcyBmb3VuZGVkPw==",
            "answer": "MTkzOQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIb21lc3R1Y2sgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEdhbXplZSdzIGxhc3QgbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrYXJh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmV0dGVyIGtub3duIGJ5IGhpcyBuaWNrbmFtZSBMb2dhbiwgd2hhdCBpcyBXb2x2ZXJpbmUncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgSG93bGV0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIFRocmVlIFZpcnR1ZXMgb2YgQmlvbmljbGU/",
            "answer": "VW5pdHksIER1dHksIERlc3Rpbnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBIZWxsYm95J3MgdHJ1ZSBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QW51bmcgVW4gUmFtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEhlbGxib3kgdW5pdmVyc2UsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEFiZSBTYXBpZW4ncyBiaXJ0aCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "TGFuZ2RvbiBFdmVyZXR0IENhdWw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHVscCBoZXJvIG1hZGUgYXBwZWFyYW5jZXMgaW4gSGVsbGJveSBhbmQgQlBSRCBjb21pY3MgYmVmb3JlIGdldHRpbmcgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZj8=",
            "answer": "TG9ic3RlciBKb2huc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "U2tpbm5lciBTd2VldA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCdzIHRoZSB3ZWFrbmVzcyBvZiBhbWVyaWNhbiB2YW1waXJlcyAoU2NvdHQgU255ZGVyJ3MgQW1lcmljYW4gVmFtcGlyZSk/",
            "answer": "R29sZA=="
        }
    ],
    "U2NpZW5jZTogR2FkZ2V0cw==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGJhc2Ugc3RhdGlvbiB0cmFja2VycyB1c2VkIGZvciB0aGUgSFRDIFZpdmUgY2FsbGVkPw==",
            "answer": "TGlnaHRob3VzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHRlcm0gImJhdHRlcnkiIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIGFuIGVsZWN0cmljYWwgc3RvcmFnZSBkZXZpY2Ugd2FzIGNvaW5lZCBieT8=",
            "answer": "QmVuamFtaW4gRnJhbmtsaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbW11bmljYXRpb24gcHJvdG9jb2wgTkZDIHN0YW5kcyBmb3IgTmVhci1GaWVsZCBDb250cm9sLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXNpZ25lZCB0aGUgIkJldGFtYXgiIHZpZGVvIGNhc3NldHRlIGZvcm1hdD8=",
            "answer": "U29ueQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIFdlc3Rlcm4gRWxlY3RyaWMgTW9kZWwgNTAwIHRlbGVwaG9uZSB1c2VzIHRvbmUgZGlhbGluZyB0byBkaWFsIHBob25lIG51bWJlcnMu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYnV6endvcmQgZGlkIEFwcGxlIEluYy4gdXNlIHRvIGRlc2NyaWJlIHRoZWlyIHJlbW92YWwgb2YgdGhlIGhlYWRwaG9uZSBqYWNrPw==",
            "answer": "Q291cmFnZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgVEhYIHN1Yndvb2ZlciBjcm9zc292ZXIgZnJlcXVlbmN5Pw==",
            "answer": "ODAgSHo="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWljcm9waG9uZXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgbm90IG9ubHkgdG8gcGljayB1cCBzb3VuZCwgYnV0IGFsc28gdG8gcHJvamVjdCBzb3VuZCBzaW1pbGFyIHRvIGEgc3BlYWtlci4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIHBhdGVudGVkIGEgc3RlYW0gZW5naW5lIHRoYXQgcHJvZHVjZWQgY29udGludW91cyByb3RhcnkgbW90aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "SmFtZXMgV2F0dA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIFRhbWFnb3RjaGkgZGlnaXRhbCBwZXQgcmVsZWFzZWQ/",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgT2N1bHVzIFJpZnQgcmV2ZWFsZWQgdG8gdGhlIHB1YmxpYyB0aHJvdWdoIGEgS2lja3N0YXJ0ZXIgY2FtcGFpZ24/",
            "answer": "MjAxMg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIENEIGJlZ2luIHRvIGFwcGVhciBvbiB0aGUgY29uc3VtZXIgbWFya2V0Pw==",
            "answer": "MTk4Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGlQaG9uZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hvIGJ1aWx0IHRoZSBmaXJzdCBsYXNlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlb2RvcmUgSGFyb2xkIE1haW1hbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkZXZlbG9wZWQgdGhlIEhvbG9sZW5zPw==",
            "answer": "TWljcm9zb2Z0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjZWxsdWxhciBkZXZpY2UgY29tcGFuaWVzIGlzIE5PVCBoZWFkcXVhcnRlcmVkIGluIEFzaWE/",
            "answer": "Tm9raWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TW9iaWxlIGhhcmR3YXJlIGFuZCBzb2Z0d2FyZSBjb21wYW55ICJCbGFja2JlcnJ5IExpbWl0ZWQiIHdhcyBmb3VuZGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIGNvdW50cnk/",
            "answer": "Q2FuYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCByb3VuZCBpcyBhIGNsYXNzaWMgQUstNDcgY2hhbWJlcmVkIGluPw==",
            "answer": "Ny42MngzOW1t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcm91bmQgZG9lcyBhIFdXMiBNMSBHYXJhbmQgZmlyZT8=",
            "answer": "LjMwLTA2"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgIk1pdHN1YmlzaGkgV2FrYW1hcnUiPw==",
            "answer": "QSByb2JvdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "T3V0IG9mIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgTkFTQSBTcGFjZSBTaHV0dGxlcywgd2hpY2ggMiBoYXZlIGJlZW4gZGVzdHJveWVkIGluIGRpc2FzdGVycz8=",
            "answer": "Q2hhbGxlbmdlciBhbmQgQ29sdW1iaWE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIG1lYXN1cmUgYmxvb2QgcHJlc3N1cmU/",
            "answer": "U3BoeWdtb21hbm9tZXRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBzaWduaWZpY2FudCBzaWRlIHZlbnR1cmUgdGhlIHBvcHVsYXIgZmlyZWFybXMgY29tcGFueSwgUmVtaW5ndG9uLCBoYXMgcHVyc3VlZD8=",
            "answer": "VHlwZXdyaXRlcnM="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWUgaGVhdmlseSBmZWF0dXJlcyBtdXNpYyBmcm9tIHRoZSBnZW5yZSAiRXVyb2JlYXQiPw==",
            "answer": "SW5pdGlhbCBE"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIEluaXRpYWwgRCwgaG93IGRvZXMgVGFrdW1pIEZ1aml3YXJhIGRlc2NyaWJlIGEgZHJpZnQ/",
            "answer": "Jy4gLiAuIHRoZSBmcm9udCB0aXJlcyBzbGlkZSBzbyB0aGUgY2FyIHdvbid0IGZhY2UgdGhlIGluc2lkZSc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIHNlcmllcyAiRnVsbCBNZXRhbCBBbGNoZW1pc3QiLCB3aGF0IGRvIEFsY2hlbWlzdHMgY29uc2lkZXIgdGhlIGdyZWF0ZXN0IHRhYm9vPw==",
            "answer": "SHVtYW4gVHJhbnNtdXRhdGlvbiA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuaW1hdGVkIGZpbG0gIlNwaXJpdGVkIEF3YXkiIHdvbiB0aGUgQWNhZGVteSBBd2FyZCBmb3IgQmVzdCBBbmltYXRlZCBGZWF0dXJlIGF0IHRoZSA3NXRoIEFjYWRlbXkgQXdhcmRzIGluIDIwMDMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc3R1ZmZlZCBsaW9uIGluIEJsZWFjaD8=",
            "answer": "S29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lLCBGdWxsIE1ldGFsIFBhbmljISwgd2hvIGlzIEthbmFtZSdzIGJlc3QgZnJpZW5kPw==",
            "answer": "S3lva28gVG9raXdh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB0cnVlIG1vb24gcHJpbmNlc3MgaW4gU2FpbG9yIE1vb24/",
            "answer": "U2FpbG9yIE1vb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lLCAiU3VwZXIgU29uaWNvIiwgd2hhdCBpcyBTdXBlciBTb25pY28ncyBmYXZvcml0ZSBmb29kPw==",
            "answer": "TWFjcm9vbnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb3VudHJpZXMgZG9lcyAiSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlOiBTdGFyZHVzdCBDcnVzYWRlcnMiIG5vdCB0YWtlIHBsYWNlIGluPw==",
            "answer": "UGhpbGlwcGluZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIE5vcmFnYW1pIHdobyBpcyBvbmUgb2YgdGhlIG1haW4gcHJvdGFnb25pc3RzPw==",
            "answer": "WXVraW5l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24sIEFzaCdzIFBpa2FjaHUgcmVmdXNlcyB0byBnbyBpbnRvIGEgcG9rZWJhbGwu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBNZWxhbmNob2x5IG9mIEhhcnVoaSBTdXp1bWl5YSIgc2VyaWVzLCB0aGUgU09TIEJyaWdhZGUgY2x1YiBsZWFkZXIgaXMgdW5rbm93aW5nbHkgdHJlYXRlZCBhcyBhKG4pIF9fIGJ5IGhlciBwZWVycy4=",
            "answer": "R29k"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUb2FydSBLYWdha3Ugbm8gUmFpbGd1biIgYW5pbWUsICBlc3BlcnMgY2FuIG9ubHkgcmVhY2ggYSBtYXhpbXVtIG9mIGxldmVsIDYgaW4gdGhlaXIgYWJpbGl0aWVzLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUb2FydSBNYWp1dHN1IG5vIEluZGV4IiBhbmltZSwgVG91bWEgS2FtaWpvdSBpcyBhIGxldmVsIDAgZXNwZXIgdGhhdCBoYXMgdGhlIGFiaWxpdHkgdG8gZG8gd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "RGlzcGVsbCBhbnkgZXNwZXIgb3IgbWFnaWNhbCBwb3dlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjYXVzZWQgdGhlIHRpdHVsYXIgbWFzY290IG9mIFlvLUthaSBXYXRjaCwgSmliYW55YW4sIHRvIGJlY29tZSBhIHlva2FpPw==",
            "answer": "QmVpbmcgcnVuIG92ZXIgYnkgYSB0cnVjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "T24gd2hhdCBtZWRpdW0gd2FzICJDbGFubmFkIiBmaXJzdCBjcmVhdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "VmlzdWFsIG5vdmVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRGlnaW1vbiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgSmFwYW5lc2UgbmFtZSBmb3IgdGhlIGZpbmFsIGV2b2x1dGlvbmFyeSBzdGFnZT8=",
            "answer": "VWx0aW1hdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWUgZGlkIFNlaWppIEtpc2hpIE5PVCBkaXJlY3Q/",
            "answer": "QW5vdGhlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZGV2aWNlIHRoYXQgYWxsb3dzIGZvciBpbmZpbml0ZSBlbmVyZ3kgaW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lICJEaW1lbnNpb24gVyI/",
            "answer": "Q29pbHM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGhlcm9pbmUgb2YgIkh1bWFuaXR5IEhhcyBEZWNsaW5lZCIgaXMgYSBtZWRpYXRvciBiZXR3ZWVuIGh1bWFucyBhbmQgd2hhdD8=",
            "answer": "RmFpcmllcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "TWVkYWthIEt1cm9rYW1pIGZyb20gIk1lZGFrYSBCb3giIGhhcyB3aGF0IGFibm9ybWFsaXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEVuZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWthdHN1a2kncyBzdWJjbGFzcyBpbiAiTG9nIEhvcml6b24iIGlzIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "IFRyYWNrZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk9uZSBQaWVjZSIsIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgZ2lybCB3aG8gb3ZlcmNhbWUgaGVyIGVuc2xhdmVkIHBhc3QgYW5kIGJlY2FtZSBhbiBhZ2VudCBvZiBhbiBhcm15IHRvIGZpZ2h0IHRoZSBjb3JydXB0IGdvdmVybm1lbnQ/",
            "answer": "S29hbGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkpvSm8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSIsIEZhdGhlciBFbnJpY28gUHVjY2hpIHVzZXMgYSB0b3RhbCBvZiAzIHN0YW5kcyBpbiBQYXJ0IDY6IFN0b25lIE9jZWFuLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkEgQ2VydGFpbiBNYWdpY2FsIEluZGV4LCIgd2hhdCBpcyBBY2NlbGVyYXRvciBhYmxlIHRvIGNvbnRyb2w/",
            "answer": "VmVjdG9ycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkh1bnRlciB4IEh1bnRlciIsIHdoYXQgYXJlIG1lbWJlcnMgaW4gS2lsbHVhJ3MgZmFtaWx5IGtub3duIGZvciBiZWluZz8=",
            "answer": "QXNzYXNzaW5z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQXR0YWNrIG9uIFRpdGFuIiBmaXJzdCBhaXI/",
            "answer": "MjAxMw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQmlzaG91am8gU2Vuc2hpIFNhaWxvciBNb29uIiBhaXIgaW4gSmFwYW4/",
            "answer": "MTk5Mg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "IlNpbGhvdWV0dGUiLCBhIHNvbmcgcGVyZm9ybWVkIGJ5IHRoZSBncm91cCAnS0FOQS1CT09OJyBpcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBhcyB0aGUgc2l4dGVlbnRoIG9wZW5pbmcgb2Ygd2hpY2ggYW5pbWU/",
            "answer": "TmFydXRvOiBTaGlwcMWrZGVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUbyBMb3ZlLVJ1IiBzZXJpZXMsIFBla2UgaXMgY29uc2lkZXJlZCBhIGZlbWFsZSByb2JvdC4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gMjAxMywgdmlydHVhbCBwb3Atc3RhciBIYXRzdW5lIE1pa3UgaGFkIGEgc3BvbnNvcnNoaXAgd2l0aCB3aGljaCBwaXp6YSBjaGFpbj8=",
            "answer": "RG9taW5vJ3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTEgVFYgYW5pbWUgc2VyaWVzLCAiVEhFIGlET0xNQFNURVIiLCB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBJb3JpJ3Mgc3R1ZmZlZCB0b3kgYnVubnk/",
            "answer": "Q2hhcmxlcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgIkpvSm9zIiB0aGF0IGFyZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdHMgYXJlIHRoZXJlIGluIHRoZSBzZXJpZXMgIkpvam8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSI/",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBhbmltYXRlZCAiVG8gTG92ZS1SdSI/",
            "answer": "WGViZWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBhbmltYXRlZCAiUHN5Y2hvIFBhc3MiPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZHVjdGlvbiBJLkc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3R1ZGlvIGFuaW1hdGVkIFNvdWwgRWF0ZXI/",
            "answer": "Qm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzdHVkaW8gYW5pbWF0ZWQgRnVsbG1ldGFsIEFsY2hlbWlzdD8=",
            "answer": "Qm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzdHVkaW8gYW5pbWF0ZWQgT3VyYW4gSGlnaCBTY2hvb2wgSG9zdCBDbHViPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJLYWdlcm91IERhemUiIHNlcmllcywgU2hpbnRhcm8gS2lzYXJhZ2kgaXMgcHJvbWluZW50bHkgc2hvd24gd2l0aCB0aGUgY29sb3IgcmVkLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSmFwYW5lc2UgbXVzaWMgZ3JvdXAgd2FzIGZvcm1lZCB0byBwcm9kdWNlIHRoZW1lIG11c2ljIGZvciB0aGUgYW5pbWUgIkd1aWx0eSBDcm93biI/",
            "answer": "RWdvaXN0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdGhlbWUgc29uZyBvZiAiTmVvbiBHZW5lc2lzIEV2YW5nZWxpb24iPw==",
            "answer": "QSBDcnVlbCBBbmdlbCdzIFRoZXNpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBQbHVtIGZyb20gIk5vIEdhbWUgTm8gTGlmZSIgaXMgYSBnaXJsLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkxvdmUgTGl2ZTogU2Nob29sIElkb2wgUHJvamVjdCIgd2hhdCBwc2V1ZG9ueW0gZG9lcyBLb3RvcmkgTWluYW1pIHVzZSBpbiBoZXIgam9iIGFzIGEgbWFpZD8=",
            "answer": "TWluYWxpbnNreQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSBtYW5nYSBVenVtYWtpPw==",
            "answer": "SnVuamkgSXRv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBjb2xvdXIgaGFpciBkb2VzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiB0aGUgWXUtR2ktT2ghIG9yaWdpbmFsIGFuaW1lIHNlcmllcyBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "UmVkLCBibGFjayBhbmQgeWVsbG93"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgdGhlIDIwMTcgYW5pbWUgIkxhbmQgb2YgdGhlIEx1c3Ryb3VzIj8=",
            "answer": "UGhvc3Bob3BoeWxsaXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGVwaXNvZGUgb2YgWXUtR2ktT2g6IER1ZWwgTW9uc3RlcnMsIHdoYXQgYm9vayBpcyBTZXRvIEthaWJhIHNlZW4gcmVhZGluZyBhdCBEb21pbm8gSGlnaCBTY2hvb2w/",
            "answer": "VGh1cyBTcG9rZSBaYXJhdGh1c3RyYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlLCB3aG8gc2F5cyAiWWFyZSB5YXJlIGRhemUiPw==",
            "answer": "Sm90YXJvIEt1am8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE5hcnV0byBtYW5nYSwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYW1lIG9mIFRzdW5hZGU/",
            "answer": "U2VuanU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lICJNeSBIZXJvIEFjYWRlbWlhIiwgd2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIHNob3duIHdpdGggdGhlIGFiaWxpdHkgdG8gbWFuaXB1bGF0ZSBncmF2aXR5Pw==",
            "answer": "VXJhcmFrYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlIGFuZCBkaXJlY3RlZCB0aGUgYW5pbWF0ZWQgbW92aWUgIlNwaXJpdGVkIEF3YXkiICgyMDAxKT8=",
            "answer": "SGF5YW8gTWl5YXpha2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gRHJhZ29uIEJhbGwgWiwgd2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgZmlyc3QgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHRvIGdvIFN1cGVyIFNhaXlhbiAyPw==",
            "answer": "R29oYW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGVwaXNvZGUgb2YgU291bCBFYXRlciByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MjAwOA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gS2lsbCBMYSBLaWxsLCB0aGUgd2VhcG9uIG9mIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGlzIGEga2F0YW5hLiA=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkludXlhc2hhIiwgd2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGhlcm9zIGFyZSBsb29raW5nIHRvIGNvbGxlY3Q/",
            "answer": "SmV3ZWwgU2hhcmRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29yZ2kgaW4gQ293Ym95IEJlYm9wPw==",
            "answer": "RWluc3RlaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYWdlIG9mIEFzaCBLZXRjaHVtIGluIFBva2Vtb24gd2hlbiBoZSBzdGFydHMgaGlzIGpvdXJuZXk/",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1hbmdhIEpvSm8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSBpcyBzcGxpdCBpbnRvIGhvdyBtYW55IHBhcnRzPw==",
            "answer": "OA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tm8gR2FtZSBObyBMaWZlIGZpcnN0IGFpcmVkIGluIDIwMTQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBsaW5lIG11dHRlcmVkIGluIHRoZSBhbmltZSBmaWxtICJUaGUgRW5kIG9mIEV2YW5nZWxpb24iPw==",
            "answer": "IkhvdyBkaXNndXN0aW5nLiI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuaW1lIEF0dGFjayBvbiBUaXRhbiB3YXMgZGlyZWN0ZWQgYnkgVGV0c3VyxY0gQXJha2ksIHRoZSBzYW1lIHBlcnNvbiB3aG8gZGlyZWN0ZWQgdGhlIGFuaW1lIEhpZ2hzY2hvb2wgb2YgdGhlIERlYWQu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZ1dHVyZSBEaWFyeSIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgWXVubyBHYXNhaSdzIFBob25lIERpYXJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "WXVraXRlcnUgRGlhcnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc29uZyB3YXMgdGhlIGNhbGxzaWduIGZvciBTdGVmYW4gVmVyZGVtYW5uJ3MgS1dGTSByYWRpbyBzdGF0aW9uIGluIFVyYXNhd2EgTmFva2kncyAiTW9uc3RlciI/",
            "answer": "T3ZlciB0aGUgUmFpbmJvdw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBtYW5nYSBoYXZlIHRoZSBtb3N0IHRhbmtvdWJhbiB2b2x1bWVzPw==",
            "answer": "R29sZ28gMTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzcG9ydCBpcyBiZWluZyBwbGF5ZWQgaW4gdGhlIEFuaW1lIEV5ZXNoaWVsZCAyMT8=",
            "answer": "QW1lcmljYW4gRm9vdGJhbGw="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCAiQXR0YWNrIG9uIFRpdGFuIiBTZWFzb24gMiBiZWdpbiBhaXJpbmc/",
            "answer": "MjAxNw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgb2YgIkxvZyBIb3Jpem9uIiBhcmUgdHJhcHBlZCBpbiB3aGF0IGdhbWU/",
            "answer": "RWxkZXIgVGFsZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SWtraSBLdXJvZ2FuZSBpcyBrbm93biBieSB3aGF0IG5pY2tuYW1lIGF0IHRoZSBiZWdpbm5pbmcgb2YgIkNoaXZhbHJ5IG9mIGEgRmFpbGVkIEtuaWdodCI/",
            "answer": "V29yc3QgT25l"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "S3J1c3R5IGlzIHRoZSBndWlsZCBtYXN0ZXIgb2Ygd2hpY2ggZ3VpbGQgaW4gIkxvZyBIb3Jpem9uIj8=",
            "answer": "RC4gRC4gRA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgbWFuZ2EgIlBpbmcgUG9uZyIgYmVnaW4gc2VyaWFsaXphdGlvbj8=",
            "answer": "MTk5Ng=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJEcmFnb24gQmFsbCIgZnJhbmNoaXNlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEdva3UncyBicm90aGVyPw==",
            "answer": "UmFkaXR6"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvcmlrbyIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgZm9vZHMgaXMga25vd2luZ2x5IGNvbXBhdGlibGUgd2l0aCBUb3Jpa28/",
            "answer": "UG9pc29uIFBvdGF0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRvZXMgUGFydCA3IG9mICJKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUiIHRha2UgcGxhY2UgaW4/",
            "answer": "MTg5MA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyICJSZWlnZW4iICBpbiB0aGUgRW5nbGlzaCBkdWIgb2YgIk1vYiBQc3ljaG8gMTAwIj8=",
            "answer": "Q2hyaXMgTmlvc2k="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvIExvdmUtUnUiLCBSZW4gYW5kIFJ1biBhcmUgZnJvbSB3aGF0IHBsYW5ldD8=",
            "answer": "TWVtb3J6ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlICJUbyBMb3ZlLVJ1IiBNYW5nYSB3YXMgc3RhcnRlZCBpbiB3aGF0IHllYXI/",
            "answer": "MjAwNg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkxpdHRsZSBXaXRjaCBBY2FkZW1pYSIsIHdoYXQgaXMgU2hpbnkgQ2hhcmlvdCdzIGFsaWFzIGF0IEx1bmEgTm92YSBBY2FkZW15Pw==",
            "answer": "VXJzdWxhIENhbGxpc3Rpcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSGFpa3l1dSEhLCB3aG8gaXMgbm90IGEgbWVtYmVyIG9mIEthcmFzdW5vIFZCQz8=",
            "answer": "U2hpZ2VydSBZYWhhYmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkJsYWNrIExhZ29vbiIsIHdoYXQgY29sb3VyIGlzIFJvY2sncyB0aWU/",
            "answer": "VGVhbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gQ2hvYml0cywgSGlkZWtpIGZvdW5kIENoaWkgaW4gaGlzIGFwYXJ0bWVudC4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3R1ZGlvIGFuaW1hdGVkIEFmcm8gU2FtdXJhaT8=",
            "answer": "R29uem8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgd29ybGQgaW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lICJCdWRkeWZpZ2h0Ij8=",
            "answer": "QW5jaWVudCBEcmFnb24gV29ybGQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGhlcm9pbmUgb2YgdGhlIGFuaW1lLCBGdWxsIE1ldGFsIFBhbmljIQ==",
            "answer": "S2FuYW1lIENoaWRvcmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBuYW1lIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBDaGloaXJvIGdpdmVuIGluIHRoZSAyMDAxIG1vdmllICJTcGlyaXRlZCBBd2F5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2VuIChUaG91c2FuZCk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBwb3NzZXNzZXMgdGhlIFN0YW5kIG5hbWVkIFNpbHZlciBDaGFyaW90Pw==",
            "answer": "SmVhbiBQaWVycmUgUG9sbmFyZWZm"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluICJIdW1hbml0eSBIYXMgRGVjbGluZWQiIGhhcyBubyBkaXNjZXJuYWJsZSBuYW1lIGFuZCBpcyBzaW1wbHkgcmVmZXJyZWQgdG8gYXMgJ0knIGZvciBtb3N0IG9mIHRoZSBzZXJpZXMu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc3R1ZGlvIG1hZGUgQ293Ym95IEJlYm9wPw==",
            "answer": "U3VucmlzZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U3R1ZGlvIEdoaWJsaSBpcyBhIEphcGFuZXNlIGFuaW1hdGlvbiBzdHVkaW8gcmVzcG9uc2libGUgZm9yIHRoZSBmaWxtcyAiV29sZiBDaGlsZHJlbiIgYW5kICJUaGUgQm95IGFuZCB0aGUgQmVhc3QiLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkZhaXJ5IFRhaWwiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuaWNrbmFtZSBvZiBOYXRzdSBEcmFnbmVlbD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNhbGFtYW5kZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDl0aCBQb2tlbW9uIG1vdmllLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIFByaW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgU2VhPw==",
            "answer": "TWFuYXBoeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhpZ2hzY2hvb2wgb2YgdGhlIERlYWQiLCB3aGVyZSBkaWQgS29tdXJvIGFuZCBTYWVrbyBlc3RhYmxpc2ggdG8gbWVldCBhZnRlciB0aGUgYnVzIGV4cGxvc2lvbj8=",
            "answer": "RWFzdGVybiBQb2xpY2UgU3RhdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYmFuZCBuYW1lIGlzbid0IGEgU3RhbmQgaW4gIkpvSm8ncyBCaXp6YXJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSI/",
            "answer": "QUMvREM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGZvdXJ0aCBwYXJ0IG9mIEpvSm8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSBpcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "Sm9zdWtlIEhpZ2FzaGlrYXRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciB3aXRoIHllbGxvdyBoYWlyIGluIHRoZSBhbmltZSBOYXJ1dG8/",
            "answer": "TmFydXRv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "R29zaG8gQW95YW1hIE1hZGUgVGhpcyBTZXJpZXM6IChEZXRlY3RpdmUgQ29uYW4gLyBDYXNlIENsb3NlZCEp",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJNZWxhbmNob2x5IG9mIEhhcnVoaSBTdXp1bWl5YSIgc2VyaWVzLCB0aGUgbmFycmF0b3IgZ29lcyBieSB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgS3lvbi4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBzb25nIHBsYXlzIGluIHRoZSBlbmRpbmcgY3JlZGl0cyBvZiB0aGUgYW5pbWUgIkVyZ28gUHJveHkiPw==",
            "answer": "UGFyYW5vaWQgQW5kcm9pZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIEFzc2Fzc2luYXRpb24gQ2xhc3Nyb29tIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIGNsYXNzIHRoYXQgS29yb3NlbnNlaSB0ZWFjaGVzPw==",
            "answer": "Q2xhc3MgMy1F"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhyb3VnaG91dCB0aGUgZW50aXJldHkgb2YgIkRyYWdvbiBCYWxsIFoiLCBHb2t1IG9ubHkga2lsbHMgdHdvIGNoYXJhY3RlcnM6IGEgbWluaWJvc3MgbmFtZWQgWWFrb24gYW5kIEtpZCBCdXUu",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkEgQ2VydGFpbiBTY2llbnRpZmljIFJhaWxndW4iLCBob3cgbWFueSAic2lzdGVycyIgZGlkIEFjY2VsZXJhdG9yIGhhdmUgdG8ga2lsbCB0byBhY2hpZXZlIHRoZSBydW1vcmVkIGxldmVsIDY/",
            "answer": "MjAsMDAw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGF0dGFjayAiS2FtZWhhbWVoYSIgaW4gRHJhZ29uIEJhbGwgWiB3YXMgbmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBmYW1vdXMga2luZyBvZiBIYXdhaWku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBhbmltZSBvZiB0aGUgbWVjaGEgZ2VucmUgYmVnYW4gYWlyaW5nIGluIDE5ODI/",
            "answer": "VGhlIFN1cGVyIERpbWVuc2lvbiBGb3J0cmVzcyBNYWNyb3Nz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIEFEViAoRW5nbGlzaCkgRHViIG9mIHRoZSBhbmltZSAiR2hvc3QgU3RvcmllcyIsIHdoaWNoIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpcyBwb3J0cmF5ZWQgYXMgYSBQZW50YWNvc3RhbCBDaHJpc3RpYW4/",
            "answer": "TW9tb2tvIEtvaWdha3Vibw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDIwMTIgYW5pbWF0ZWQgZmlsbSAiV29sZiBDaGlsZHJlbiIsIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgd29sZiBjaGlsZHJlbj8=",
            "answer": "QW1lICYgWXVraQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk9uZSBQaWVjZSIsIHdobyBjb25maXJtcyB0aGUgZXhpc3RlbmNlIG9mIHRoZSBsZWdlbmRhcnkgdHJlYXN1cmUsIE9uZSBQaWVjZT8=",
            "answer": "RWR3YXJkICJXaGl0ZWJlYXJkIiBOZXdnYXRl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTYWlsb3IgTW9vbiIgc2VyaWVzLCB3aGF0IGlzIFNhaWxvciBKdXBpdGVyJ3MgY2l2aWxpYW4gbmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFrb3RvIEtpbm8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkpvSm8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgU3RhbmRzIGRvZXMgTk9UIGhhdmUgYSB0aW1lLWJhc2VkIGFiaWxpdHk/",
            "answer": "MjB0aCBDZW50dXJ5IEJveQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyAiU2hvdSBTdXp1a2kiIGluIHRoZSBFbmdsaXNoIGR1YiBvZiAiTW9iIFBzeWNobyAxMDAiPw==",
            "answer": "Q2FzZXkgTW9uZ2lsbG8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvIExvdmUtUnU6IERhcmtuZXNzIiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGdpcmxzIGF0dGVtcHQgbWFraW5nIGEgaGFyZW0gZm9yIFJpdG8gWXV1a2k/",
            "answer": "TW9tbyBEZXZpbHVrZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gUG9rw6ltb24gQ2hyb25pY2xlcywgd2h5IHdhcyBNaXN0eSBhZnJhaWQgb2YgR3lhcmFkb3M/",
            "answer": "U2hlIGNyYXdsZWQgaW50byBpdCdzIG1vdXRoIGFzIGEgYmFieS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvIExvdmUtUnUiLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHRvIGhlYXIgb2YgWWFtaSdzIHBhc3QgZnJvbSBoZXI/",
            "answer": "Uml0bw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhpZ2hzY2hvb2wgRHhEIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgaXRlbSBzb21lIGh1bWFucyBhcmUgYm9ybiB3aXRoPw==",
            "answer": "U2FjcmVkIEdlYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkpld2VscGV0IFN1bnNoaW5lIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc29uZyB0aGF0IHBsYXlzIHdoZW4gS2Fub24gYW5kIGhlciBmcmllbmRzIGJ1c3Qgb3V0IG9mIHByaXNvbj8=",
            "answer": "SSBEb24ndCBXYW50IHRvIE1pc3MgYSBUaGluZw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgc2Nob29sIGluIHRoZSBhbmltZSBhbmQgbWFuZ2EgIkdvc2ljayI/",
            "answer": "U3QuIE1hcmd1ZXJpdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlB1ZWxsYSBNYWdpIE1hZG9rYSBNYWdpY2EiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIE1hZG9rYSdzIHlvdW5nZXIgYnJvdGhlcj8=",
            "answer": "VGF0c3V5YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBhbmltYXRlZCAiSGlkYW1hcmkgU2tldGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "U2hhZnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBwcm9kdWNlZCAiTG9nIEhvcml6b24iPw==",
            "answer": "U2F0ZWxpdGU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgbWFpbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGFuaW1lICJPbmUtUHVuY2ggTWFuIj8=",
            "answer": "U2FpdGFtYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lICJNci4gT3NvbWF0c3UiLCBob3cgbWFueSBicm90aGVycyBkb2VzIE9zb21hdHN1LXNhbiBoYXZlPw==",
            "answer": "NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYW5pbWUgaGF2ZSBvdmVyIDcsNTAwIGVwaXNvZGVzPw==",
            "answer": "U2F6YWUtc2Fu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIEJsYWNrIEJ1dGxlciwgd2hvIGlzIGJldHJvdGhlZCB0byBiZSBtYXJyaWVkIHRvIENpZWwgUGhhbnRvbWhpdmU/",
            "answer": "RWxpemFiZXRoIE1pZGZvcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBQbHVtIGZyb20gIk5vIEdhbWUgTm8gTGlmZSIgaXMgb2Ygd2hhdCByYWNlPw==",
            "answer": "RGhhbXBpcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QW9pIE1peWFtb3JpIGlzIHRoZSBwcm9kdWN0aW9uIG1hbmFnZXIgb2Ygd2hhdCBhbmltZSBpbiAiU2hpcm9iYWtvIj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFRoaXJkIEFlcmlhbCBHaXJscyBTcXVhZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RHJ1aWQgaXMgYSBtYWdlIGNsYXNzIGluICJMb2cgSG9yaXpvbiIu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk9uZSBQaWVjZSIsIHdoYXQgZG9lcyAidGhlIFBpcmF0ZSBLaW5nIiBtZWFuIHRvIHRoZSBjYXB0YWluIG9mIHRoZSBTdHJhdyBIYXQgUGlyYXRlcz8=",
            "answer": "RnJlZWRvbQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaXMgZnJvbSAiTGVnZW5keiA6IFRhbGUgb2YgdGhlIERyYWdvbiBLaW5ncyI/",
            "answer": "U2hpcm9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIHN0YW5kcyBmcm9tICJKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUiIG1pbWljcyB0aGUgbGlrZW5lc3Mgb2YgYSB0b21hdG8/",
            "answer": "UGVhcmwgSmFt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvcmlrbyIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgSGVhdmVubHkgS2luZ3MgaGFzIGFuIGVuaGFuY2VkIHNlbnNlIG9mIEhlYXJpbmc/",
            "answer": "WmVicmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhcm1vcmVkIHRpdGFuIGluICJBdHRhY2sgT24gVGl0YW4iPw==",
            "answer": "UmVpbmVyIEJyYXVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkhpZ2hzY2hvb2wgRHhEIiwgS29uZWtvIFRvdWpvdSBpcyBmcm9tIHdoYXQgcmFjZT8=",
            "answer": "TmVrb21hdGE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIlRvIExvdmUtUnU6IERhcmtuZXNzIiwgWWFtaSByZXZlYWxzIGhlciByZWFsIG5hbWUgaXMgRXZlLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gTXMuIEtvYmF5YXNoaSdzIERyYWdvbiBNYWlkLCB3aG8gaXMgS29iYXlhc2hpJ3MgbWFpZD8=",
            "answer": "VG9ocnU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIE92ZXJsb3JkIEFuaW1lIHdobyB3YXMgQ29jeXR1cyBtYWRlIGJ5Pw==",
            "answer": "V2FycmlvciBUYWtlbWlrYXp1Y2hp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBGdW5ueSBWYWxlbnRpbmUncyBzdGFuZCBpbiBKb2pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUgUGFydCA3LCBTdGVlbCBCYWxsIFJ1bj8=",
            "answer": "RGlydHkgRGVlZHMgRG9uZSBEaXJ0IENoZWFw"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBPbmUgUGllY2U/",
            "answer": "THVmZnk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGFydCBmcm9tIHRoZSBKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUgbWFuZ2EgaXMgYWJvdXQgYSBob3JzZSByYWNlIGFjcm9zcyBBbWVyaWNhPw==",
            "answer": "UGFydCA3OiBTdGVlbCBCYWxsIFJ1bg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgQXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSBtYW5nYSBNb25zdGVyIEh1bnRlciBPcmFnZT8=",
            "answer": "CUhpcm8gTWFzaGltYQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNlcmllcyBKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUsIHdoaWNoIG1haW4gY2hhcmFjdGVyIG1ha2VzIHRoZSBncmVhdGVzdCBudW1iZXIgb2YgcmVjdXJyaW5nIGFwcGVhcmFuY2VzPw==",
            "answer": "Sm90YXJvIEt1am8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyBnaXZlbiB0aGUgdGl0bGUgIkZ1bGwgTWV0YWwiIGluIHRoZSBhbmltZSBzZXJpZXMgIkZ1bGwgTWV0YWwgQWxjaGVtaXN0Ij8=",
            "answer": "RWR3YXJkIEVscmlj"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNoYWt1Z2FuIG5vIFNoYW5hIiB3aGF0IHdhcyB0aGUgU2hhbmEgdXN1YWxseSByZWZlcnJlZCBhcz8=",
            "answer": "RmxhbWUtSGFpcmVkIEJ1cm5pbmctRXllZCBIdW50ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gYW50YWdvbmlzdCBvZiB0aGUgc2Vjb25kIHBhcnQgb2YgSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlIGlzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmc/",
            "answer": "S2Fycw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgdGhlIGZpZnRoIHBhcnQgb2YgSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlIGlzIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmc/",
            "answer": "R2lvcm5vIEdpb3Zhbm5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2luY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbmFtZXMgYXJlIG5vdCBhIGNoYXJhY3RlciBvZiBKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmU/",
            "answer": "Sm9KbyBLaWthc3U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgYW5pbWUgIkhpbW91dG8hIFVtYXJ1LWNoYW4iIGFpcj8=",
            "answer": "MjAxNQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "S2l6bmFpdmVyIGlzIGFuIGFkYXB0YXRpb24gb2YgYSBtYW5nYS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "U2F0ZWxsYSBpbiAiUmU6WmVybyIgaXMgdGhlIHdpdGNoIG9mIHdoYXQ/",
            "answer": "RW52eQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkh1bnRlciB4IEh1bnRlciIsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgaXMgTk9UIGEgdHlwZSBvZiBOZW4gYXVyYT8=",
            "answer": "UmVzdG9yYXRpb24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUbyBMb3ZlLVJ1IiBzZXJpZXMsIEdvbGRlbiBEYXJrbmVzcyBpcyBzZW50IHRvIGtpbGwgTGFsYSBEZXZpbHVrZS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlYXNvbiBmb3IgdGhlIGJhbm5pbmcgb2YgZXBpc29kZSAzNSBvZiB0aGUgIlBva8OpbW9uIE9yaWdpbmFsIFNlcmllcyIgQW5pbWU/",
            "answer": "R3VuIFVzYWdl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5ODggZmlsbSAiQWtpcmEiLCBUZXRzdW8gZW5kcyB1cCBkZXN0cm95aW5nIFRva3lvLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYW1lIG9mIEVkd2FyZCBhbmQgQWxwaG9uc2UgaW4gdGhlIEZ1bGxtZXRhbCBBbGNoZW1pc3Qgc2VyaWVzLg==",
            "answer": "RWxyaWM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBhdXRob3Igb2YgdGhlIG1hbmdhIHNlcmllcyAiQXN0cm8gQm95Ij8=",
            "answer": "T3NhbXUgVGV6dWth"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBvcmlnaW5hdGVkIGFzIGEgbWFuZ2E/",
            "answer": "QWtpcmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcGVyc29uIGZyb20gIkpvSm8ncyBCaXphcnJlIEFkdmVudHVyZSIgZG9lcyBOT1QgaG91c2UgYSByZWZlcmVuY2UgdG8gYSBiYW5kLCBhcnRpc3QsIG9yIHNvbmcgZWFybGllciB0aGFuIDE5ODA/",
            "answer": "R2lvcm5vIEdpb3Zhbm5h"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBwcm9kdWNlZCB0aGUgYW5pbWUgYWRhcHRhdGlvbiBvZiAieHh4SG9saWMiPw==",
            "answer": "UHJvZHVjdGlvbiBJLkc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBwcm9kdWNlZCAiU3dvcmQgQXJ0IE9ubGluZSI/",
            "answer": "QS0xIFBpY3R1cmVz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggUG9rw6ltb24gYW5kIGl0J3MgZXZvbHV0aW9ucyB3ZXJlIGJhbm5lZCBmcm9tIGFwcGVhcmluZyBpbiBhIG1haW4gcm9sZSBhZnRlciB0aGUgRXBpc29kZSAzOCBJbmNpZGVudD8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFBvcnlnb24gTGluZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gRnVsbCBNZXRhbCBQYW5pYyEsIFdoaXNwZXJlZCBhcmUgdGhvc2Ugd2hvIGFyZSBjYXBhYmxlIG9mIGNyZWF0aW5nIEJsYWNrIFRlY2hub2xvZ3ku",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmaWxtcyB3YXMgTk9UIGRpcmVjdGVkIGJ5IEhheWFvIE1peWF6YWtpPw==",
            "answer": "V29sZiBDaGlsZHJlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgRGlyZWN0b3Igb2YgdGhlIDE5ODggQW5pbWUgZmlsbSAiR3JhdmUgb2YgdGhlIEZpcmVmbGllcyI/",
            "answer": "SXNhbyBUYWthaGF0YQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgQXNoIEtldGNodW0ncyBzZWNvbmQgUG9rZW1vbj8=",
            "answer": "Q2F0ZXJwaWU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgSnVua28gRW5vc2hpbWEncyBpbXBvc3RlciBhdCB0aGUgYmVnaW5uaW5nIG9mIERhbmdhbnJvbnBhOiBUcmlnZ2VyIEhhcHB5IEhhdm9jIGlzPw==",
            "answer": "TXVrdXJvIElrdXNhYmE="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZmluYWwgdmlsbGFpbiBpbiB0aGUgbWFuZ2Egc2VyaWVzICJCbGVhY2giPw==",
            "answer": "WWh3YWNo"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHR3byBtYWluIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgb2YgIk5vIEdhbWUgTm8gTGlmZSIsIFNvcmEgYW5kIFNoaXJvLCB0b2dldGhlciBnbyBieSB3aGF0IG5hbWU/",
            "answer": "Qmxhbms="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggbWFuZ2EgZGlkIHRoZSAiNDA0IEdpcmwiIGZyb20gNGNoYW4gb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "WW90c3ViYSYh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IGRvZXMgdGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBEcmFnb3dpemFyZCwgUWludXMgQXhpYSdzIGZyb20gdGhlIGFuaW1lICJCdWRkeWZpZ2h0IiBkaWZmZXIgYmV0d2VlbiB0aGUgSmFwYW5lc2UgYW5kIEVuZ2xpc2ggZHVicz8=",
            "answer": "RGlmZmVyZW50IEdlbmRlcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBob3Jyb3IgbWFuZ2EgYXJ0aXN0IHdobyBtYWRlIFV6dW1ha2k/",
            "answer": "SnVuamkgSXRv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "VGhlIGFuaW1lICJMdWNreSBTdGFyIiBmb2xsb3dzIHRoZSBzdG9yeSBvZiBvbmUgZ2lybCB3aG8gaXMgdW5hd2FyZSBzaGUgaXMgR29kLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIGNoYXJhY3RlciBNb21vbmdhIGZyb20gdGhlICJPdmVybG9yZCIgc2VyaWVzIG9yZGVycyBoaXMgc2VydmFudHMgdG8gY2FsbCBoaW0gYnkgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "QWlueiBPb2FsIEdvd24="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjcmVhdG9yIG9mIHRoZSBtYW5nYSBzZXJpZXMgIk9uZSBQaWVjZSI/",
            "answer": "RWlpY2hpcm8gT2Rh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkpvSm8ncyBCaXp6YXJlIEFkdmVudHVyZTogU3RhcmR1c3QgQ3J1c2FkZXJzIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbGFzdCBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBwcm90YWdvbmlzdCBKb3Rhcm8/",
            "answer": "S3Vqbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIE1hbmdhIHRpdGxlcyB3YXMgbm90IGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgVXJhc2F3YSBOYW9raT8=",
            "answer": "TXkgRmF0aGVyJ3MgSm91cm5hbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlLCB3aW5jaCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMgYWJsZSB0byBhY2NlbGVyYXRlIHRpbWU/",
            "answer": "RW5yaWNvIFB1Y2Np"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1lIFNldmVuIERlYWRseSBTaW5zIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2Ygb25lIG9mIHRoZSBzaW5zPw==",
            "answer": "RGlhbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgc3R1ZGlvIFRyaWdnZXIncyBmaXJzdCBvcmlnaW5hbCBsb25nLWZvcm0gYW5pbWF0ZWQgc2VyaWVzIGZvciB0ZWxldmlzaW9uPw==",
            "answer": "S2lsbCBsYSBLaWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJUbyBMb3ZlLVJ1IiBzZXJpZXMsIGhvdyBtYW55IFRyYW5zLXdlYXBvbnMgd2VyZSBjcmVhdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "Mw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJSZTpaZXJvIiBtYW5nYSBzZXJpZXMsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZSBmb2xsb3dpbmcgU2luIEFyY2hiaXNob3BzIGVhdHMgUmVtJ3MgZXhpc3RlbmNlPw==",
            "answer": "TGV5IEJhdGVua2FpdG9z"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBKb0pvJ3MgQml6YXJyZSBBZHZlbnR1cmUgUGFydCA1Pw==",
            "answer": "VmVudG8gQXVyZW8="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Q2xlZmFpcnkgd2FzIGludGVuZGVkIHRvIGJlIEFzaCdzIHN0YXJ0aW5nIFBva8OpbW9uIGluIHRoZSBwaWxvdCBlcGlzb2RlIG9mIHRoZSBjYXJ0b29uLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYXRpb24gc3R1ZGlvIHByb2R1Y2VkICJHdXJyZW4gTGFnYW5uIj8=",
            "answer": "R2FpbmF4"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5pbWF0aW9uIHN0dWRpbyBhbmltYXRlZCB0aGUgMjAxNiBhbmltZSAiTW9iIFBzeWNobyAxMDAiPw==",
            "answer": "Qm9uZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyAiSm9KbydzIEJpemFycmUgQWR2ZW50dXJlOiBQaGFudG9tIEJsb29kIiBmaXJzdCByZWxlYXNlZD8=",
            "answer": "MTk4Nw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjb2xvc3NhbCB0aXRhbiBpbiAiQXR0YWNrIE9uIFRpdGFuIj8=",
            "answer": "QmVydG9sdCBIb292ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk9uZSBQaWVjZSIsIHdoaWNoIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIGlzIE5PVCBhbiBBbmNpZW50IFdlYXBvbj8=",
            "answer": "SnVwaXRlcg=="
        }
    ],
    "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=": [
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgdmlsbGFpbiBvZiAnJ1RoZSBMaW9uIEtpbmcnJz8=",
            "answer": "U2Nhcg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBkaWQgbm90IGZlYXR1cmUgaW4gdGhlIGNhcnRvb24gJ1dhY2t5IFJhY2VzJz8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIERyYWdvbiBXYWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBTY29vYnktRG9vJ3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==",
            "answer": "U2Nvb2JlcnQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gU291dGggUGFyaywgd2hhdCBpcyBTdGFuJ3Mgc3VybmFtZT8=",
            "answer": "TWFyc2g="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHBsYXllZCBTdGFuJ3MgZG9nIGluIHRoZSBTb3V0aCBQYXJrIGVwaXNvZGUgIkJpZyBHYXkgQWwncyBCaWcgR2F5IEJvYXQgUmlkZSI/",
            "answer": "R2VvcmdlIENsb29uZXk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggJ0ZhbWlseSBHdXknIGNoYXJhY3RlciBnb3QgaGlzIG93biBzcGluLW9mZiBzaG93IGluIDIwMDk/",
            "answer": "Q2xldmVsYW5kIEJyb3du"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHNvbmcgJ0xpdHRsZSBBcHJpbCBTaG93ZXInIGZlYXR1cmVzIGluIHdoaWNoIERpc25leSBjYXJ0b29uIGZpbG0/",
            "answer": "QmFtYmk="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggIlRveSBTdG9yeSIgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdhcyB2b2ljZWQgYnkgRG9uIFJpY2tsZXM/",
            "answer": "TXIuIFBvdGF0byBIZWFk"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QnV0dGVycyBTdG90Y2gsIFBpcCBQaXJydXAsIGFuZCBXZW5keSBUZXN0YWJ1cmdlciBhcmUgYWxsIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaW4gd2hpY2ggbG9uZyBydW5uaW5nIGFuaW1hdGVkIFRWIHNlcmllcz8=",
            "answer": "U291dGggUGFyaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgRGlzbmV5IGNhcnRvb24gY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "RGFmZnkgRHVjaw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcmVsYXRpb25zaGlwIGJldHdlZW4gUmljayBhbmQgTW9ydHkgaW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5Ij8=",
            "answer": "R3JhbmRmYXRoZXIgYW5kIEdyYW5kc29u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgRGlzbmV5IGZpbG0gIkEgR29vZnkgTW92aWUiIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==",
            "answer": "MTk5NQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhbmRhcmQgZnJhbWUgcmF0ZSBmb3IgYW5pbWF0aW9uPw==",
            "answer": "MjQgRlBT"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBTaWQncyBkb2cgaW4gIlRveSBTdG9yeSI/",
            "answer": "U2N1ZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY2l0eSBkaWQgQW5nZXIgYmVyYXRlIGZvciBydWluaW5nIHBpenphIGluICJJbnNpZGUgT3V0Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2FuIEZyYW5jaXNjbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFBpeGFyIGZpbG0sICJUb3kgU3RvcnkiIHdoYXQgd2FzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBjaGlsZCB3aG8gb3duZWQgdGhlIHRveXM/",
            "answer": "QW5keQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkF2YXRhcjogVGhlIExhc3QgQWlyYmVuZGVyIiwgd2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudCBkb2VzIEFhbmcgYmVnaW4gdG8gbGVhcm4gYWZ0ZXIgYmVpbmcgZGVmcm9zdGVkPw==",
            "answer": "V2F0ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgcmVhbCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaW4gdGhlIGNhcnRvb24gc2VyaWVzIE15IExpdHRsZSBQb255OiBGcmllbmRzaGlwIGlzIE1hZ2ljPw==",
            "answer": "Um9zZSBNYXJlbmU="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "QmlsbCBDaXBoZXIgaW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIkdyYXZpdHkgRmFsbHMiIGlzIHRoZSBnb29kIGd1eS4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlIGFjdGVkIHRoZSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgSGljY3VwIGluIHRoZSBtb3ZpZSAiSG93IHRvIFRyYWluIFlvdXIgRHJhZ29uIj8=",
            "answer": "SmF5IEJhcnVjaGVs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5OTMgRGlzbmV5IGFuaW1hdGVkIHNlcmllcyAiQm9ua2VycyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgQm9ua2VyJ3Mgc2Vjb25kIHBhcnRuZXI/",
            "answer": "TWlyYW5kYSBXcmlnaHQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZXBpc29kZSBmcm9tIFRoZSBBbWF6aW5nIFdvcmxkIE9mIEd1bWJhbGwgd29uIHRoZSBDaGlsZHJlbnMgQ2hvaWNlIEF3YXJkIGF0IHRoZSBCcml0aXNoIEFuaW1hdGlvbiBBd2FyZHMgaW4gMjAxNj8=",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNoZWxs"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIGFuaW1hdGVkIHNlcmllcyBSV0JZLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSB3ZWFwb24gdXNlZCBieSBXZWlzcyBTY2huZWU/",
            "answer": "TXlydGVuYXN0ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBub3QgYSBGbGludHN0b25lcyBjaGFyYWN0ZXI/",
            "answer": "TG9yZCBSb2NraW5naGFtIElY"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBBbWF6aW5nIFdvcmxkIG9mIEd1bWJhbGwiLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIHByaW5jaXBhbCBvZiBFbG1vcmUgSnVuaW9yIEhpZ2g/",
            "answer": "UHJpbmNpcGFsIEJyb3du"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIlN0ZXZlbiBVbml2ZXJzZSIsIHdobyBhcmUgdGhlIG1haW4gdHdvIGVtcGxveWVlcyBvZiBUaGUgQmlnIERvbnV0Pw==",
            "answer": "U2FkaWUgYW5kIExhcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIGNhcnRvb24gY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyBOT1Qgdm9pY2VkIGJ5IFJvYiBQYXVsc2VuPw==",
            "answer": "TWF4IFRlbm55c29uIChCZW4gMTAp"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIENhcnRvb24gTmV0d29yayBzZXJpZXMgIlJlZ3VsYXIgU2hvdyI/",
            "answer": "Si4gRy4gUXVpbnRlbA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgIlJXQlkiPw==",
            "answer": "TW9udHkgT3Vt"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBFdmVyZXN0J3MgZmF2b3JpdGUgZm9vZCBpbiB0aGUgTmlja2Vsb2Rlb24vTmljayBKci4gc2VyaWVzICJQQVcgUGF0cm9sIj8=",
            "answer": "TGl2ZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlNwb25nZUJvYiBTcXVhcmVQYW50cyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgU2FuZHkgQ2hlZWsncyBwbGFjZSBvZiByZXNpZGVuY2U/",
            "answer": "U2FuZHkncyBUcmVlZG9tZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tICJTcG9uZ2VCb2IgU3F1YXJlUGFudHMiIGlzIG5vdCBhIHNxdWlkPw==",
            "answer": "R2FyeQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyIsIHdoZXJlIGRpZCBIb21lciBhbmQgTWFyZ2UgZmlyc3QgbWVldD8=",
            "answer": "QXQgU3VtbWVyIENhbXA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5IiwgZnJvbSB3aGljaCBkaW1lbnNpb24gZG8gUmljayBhbmQgTW9ydHkgb3JpZ2luYXRlIGZyb20/",
            "answer": "Qy0xMzc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIk15IExpdHRsZSBQb255OiBGcmllbmRzaGlwIGlzIE1hZ2ljIiwgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcG9uaWVzIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIHF1YWxpdHkgb2YgaG9uZXN0eT8=",
            "answer": "QXBwbGVqYWNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkdyYXZpdHkgRmFsbHMiLCB3aGF0IGRvZXMgUXVlbnRpbiBUcmVtYmxleSBkbyB3aGVuIGhlIGlzIGRyaXZlbiBvdXQgZnJvbSB0aGUgV2hpdGUgSG91c2U/",
            "answer": "RWF0IGEgc2FsYW1hbmRlciBhbmQganVtcCBvdXQgdGhlIHdpbmRvdy4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBEaXBwZXIncyByZWFsIG5hbWUgZnJvbSAiR3Jhdml0eSBGYWxscyI/",
            "answer": "TWFzb24gUGluZXM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkdyYXZpdHkgRmFsbHMiLCBob3cgbXVjaCBkb2VzIFdhZGRsZXMgd2VpZ2ggd2hlbiBNYWJsZSB3aW5zIGhpbSBpbiAiVGhlIFRpbWUgVHJhdmVsZXIncyBQaWciPw==",
            "answer": "MTUgcG91bmRz"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgZXBpc29kZXMgd2VyZSBpbiBzZWFzb24gZml2ZSBvZiBTYW11cmFpIEphY2s/",
            "answer": "MTA="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQWxsaWdhdG9yIHRoYXQgVGhlIFNpbXBzb25zICJraWxsZWQiIGluIHRoZSBlcGlzb2RlICJLaWxsIFRoZSBBbGxpZ2F0b3IgYW5kIFJ1biI/",
            "answer": "Q2FwdGFpbiBKYWNr"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NjggQ2FydG9vbiBTaG93ICJXYWNreSBSYWNlcyIgd2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgY2F2ZW1lbiBkdW8gd2hvIHJvZGUgaW4gVGhlIEJvdWxkZXIgTW9iaWxlPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIFNsYWcgQnJvdGhlcnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QmVubnksIEJyYWluLCBGYW5jeS1GYW5jeSwgU3Bvb2sgYW5kIENob28tQ2hvbyB3ZXJlIGtub3duIGFzc29jaWF0ZXMgb2Ygd2hhdCBIYW5uYSBCYXJiZXJhIGNhcnRvb24gY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==",
            "answer": "VG9wIENhdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgSm9ubnkncyBwZXQgZG9nIGluIFRoZSBBZHZlbnR1cmVzIG9mIEpvbm55IFF1ZXN0Pw==",
            "answer": "QmFuZGl0"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "RG9uYWxkIER1Y2sgcGxheWVkIHRoZSByb2xlIG9mIEJvYiBDcmF0Y2hpdCBpbiBEaXNuZXkncyAxOTgzIGFkYXB0YXRpb24gb2YgQSBDaHJpc3RtYXMgQ2Fyb2wu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Qmx1ZSBEYW51YmUgd2FzIG9uZSBvZiB0aGUgbXVzaWNhbCBwaWVjZXMgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gRGlzbmV5J3MgMTk0MCdzIGZpbG0gRmFudGFzaWEu",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlZCBGaW5uIGluIEFkdmVudHVyZSBUaW1lPw==",
            "answer": "SmVyZW15IFNoYWRh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "Tmlja2Vsb2Rlb24gaXMgb3duZWQgYnkgd2hhdCBwYXJlbnQgY29tcGFueT8=",
            "answer": "VmlhY29t"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIkZhdCBBbGJlcnQgYW5kIHRoZSBDb3NieSBLaWRzIiwgd2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVycycgZmljdGlvbmFsIGdhbmc/",
            "answer": "VGhlIEp1bmt5YXJkIEdhbmc="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gIkF2YXRhcjogVGhlIExhc3QgQWlyYmVuZGVyIiBhbmQgIlRoZSBMZWdlbmQgb2YgS29ycmEiLCBMYXZhYmVuZGluZyBpcyBhIHNwZWNpYWxpemVkIGJlbmRpbmcgdGVjaG5pcXVlIG9mIEZpcmViZW5kaW5nLg==",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggc2luZ2VyIHByb3ZpZGVkIHRoZSB2b2ljZSBvZiBNZXRyb2lkJ3MgTW90aGVyIEJyYWluIGluIHRoZSBhbmltYXRlZCBzZXJpZXMgIkNhcHRhaW4gTjogVGhlIEdhbWUgTWFzdGVyIj8=",
            "answer": "TGV2aSBTdHViYnM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTaHJlayIgZmlsbSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIERvbmtleSBpcyBwbGF5ZWQgYnkgRWRkaWUgTXVycGh5Lg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5IiwgUmljayB1c2VzIHRoZSBjYXRjaHBocmFzZSAiV3ViYmEgTHViYmEgRHViIER1YiIsIHdoaWNoIG1lYW5zIHdoYXQgaW4gQmlyZHBlcnNvbj8=",
            "answer": "SSBhbSBpbiBncmVhdCBwYWluLCBwbGVhc2UgaGVscCBtZS4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB0b3duIHdhcyAiU3ByaW5nZmllbGQiIGZyb20gIlRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyIgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBuYW1lZCBhZnRlcj8=",
            "answer": "U3ByaW5nZmllbGQsIE9yZWdvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBvbmx5IHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIHRvIGhhdmUgYSBzcGVha2luZyBwYXJ0IGluIGFsbCBvZiB0aGUgRGlzbmV5IFBpeGFyIGZlYXR1cmUgZmlsbXM/IA==",
            "answer": "Sm9obiBSYXR6ZW5iZXJnZXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIGxhc3QgZXBpc29kZSBvZiAiRnV0dXJhbWEiIGFpcj8=",
            "answer": "U2VwdGVtYmVyIDQsIDIwMTM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBmaWxtcyB3YXMgRG9uIEJsdXRoIGJvdGggdGhlIHdyaXRlciwgZGlyZWN0b3IsIGFuZCBwcm9kdWNlciBmb3I/",
            "answer": "QWxsIERvZ3MgR28gVG8gSGVhdmVu"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBDYXJ0b29uIE5ldHdvcmsgc2hvdyBhaXJlZCBpdHMgZmlyc3QgZXBpc29kZSBvbiBOb3ZlbWJlciA0dGgsIDIwMTM/",
            "answer": "U3RldmVuIFVuaXZlcnNl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHdlYi1jb21pYyBIb21lc3R1Y2ssIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgdGhlIDQga2lkcyBwbGF5Pw==",
            "answer": "U2J1cmI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGlzIHRoZSAiZHVtYiBibG9uZGUiIGNoYXJhY3RlciBpbiBOaWNrZWxvZGVvbidzICJUaGUgTG91ZCBIb3VzZSI/",
            "answer": "TGVuaQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "QWRhbSBXZXN0IHdhcyB0aGUgbWF5b3Igb2Ygd2hpY2ggY2FydG9vbiB0b3duPw==",
            "answer": "UXVhaG9n"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggSGFubmEtQmFyYmVyYSBjYXJ0b29uIGNoYXJhY3RlciB0cmF2ZWxsZWQgd2l0aCBhIGNhbmluZSBjb21wYW5pb24gbmFtZWQgQmVlZ2xlIEJlYWdsZT8=",
            "answer": "R3JhcGUgQXBl"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG51bWJlciBvbiBHZXJhbGQncyBzaGlydCBpbiAiSGV5IEFybm9sZCEiPw==",
            "answer": "MzM="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TmlnaHQgb24gQmFsZCBNb3VudGFpbiB3YXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIHBpZWNlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBEaXNuZXkncyAxOTQwJ3MgZmlsbSBGYW50YXNpYS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "U25hZ2dsZXB1c3Mgd2FzIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIFlvZ2kgWWFob29pZXMgaW4gdGhlIDE5Nzcgc2hvdyBTY29vYnkncyBBbGwtU3RhciBMYWZmLWEtTHltcGljcy4=",
            "answer": "RmFsc2U="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VG93bnNlbmQgQ29sZW1hbiBwcm92aWRlZCB0aGUgdm9pY2UgZm9yIHdoaWNoIHR1cnRsZSBpbiB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgMTk4NyBzZXJpZXMgb2YgIlRlZW5hZ2UgTXV0YW50IE5pbmphIFR1cnRsZXMiPw==",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhYmlsaXR5IGRvZXMgUHJpbmNlc3MgU29maWEgdGhlIEZpcnN0IGhhdmUgZnJvbSBoZXIgYW11bGV0IHRoYXQgYWxsb3dzIGhlciB0byBicmVhdGhlIHVuZGVyd2F0ZXI/",
            "answer": "TWVybWFpZCBUcmFuc2Zvcm1hdGlvbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gVGhlIFNpbXBzb25zLCB3aGljaCB3YXIgZGlkIFNleW1vdXIgU2tpbm5lciBzZXJ2ZSBpbiB0aGUgVVNBIEFybXkgYXMgYSBHcmVlbiBCZXJldD8=",
            "answer": "VmlldG5hbSBXYXI="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgTWFnZ2llIFNpbXBzb24ncyBmaXJzdCBjYW5vbmljYWwgd29yZCwgbm90IGluY2x1ZGluZyB0aGUgVHJhY2V5IFVsbG1hbiBzaG9ydHM/",
            "answer": "RGFkZHku"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBhbmltYXRlZCBpbnRlcm5ldCBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaXMga25vd24gdG8gYW5zd2VyIGVtYWlscyB3aXRoIGhpcyBib3hpbmcgZ2xvdmVzPw==",
            "answer": "U3Ryb25nIEJhZA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2VuZHkgTy4gS29vcGEgYXBwZWFyZWQgaW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIERJQyBDYXJ0b29ucywgYnV0IHdoYXQgd2FzIHNoZSBrbm93biBhcz8=",
            "answer": "S29vdGllIFBpZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2F0Y2hwaHJhc2UgdXNlZCBieSBSaWNrIFNhbmNoZXogaW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5Ij8=",
            "answer": "U2xhbSBkdW5rLCBub3RoaW5nIGJ1dCBuZXQh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIHZvaWNlcyBmb3IgUnVieSBpbiB0aGUgYW5pbWF0ZWQgc2VyaWVzIFJXQlk/",
            "answer": "TGluZHNheSBKb25lcw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IERpc25leSBtb3ZpZSB0byB1c2UgQ0dJPw==",
            "answer": "VGhlIEJsYWNrIENhdWxkcm9u"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FydG9vbiBjaGFyYWN0ZXIsIEFuZHkgQ2FwcCwga25vd24gYXMgaW4gR2VybWFueT8=",
            "answer": "V2lsbGkgV2Fra2Vy"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyBsb3N0IGluIEhhd2FpaWFuIGFuZCBpcyBhbHNvIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIGEgbGl0dGxlIGdpcmwgaW4gYSAyMDAyIGZpbG0gd2hpY2ggZmVhdHVyZXMgYSBhbGllbiBuYW1lZCAiU3RpdGNoIj8=",
            "answer": "TGlsbw=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggVGVlbmFnZSBNdXRhbnQgTmluamEgVHVydGxlIHRyYWRpdGlvbmFsbHkgd2VhcnMgYW4gb3JhbmdlIGJhbmRhbmE/",
            "answer": "TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBsaXZlIGluIGEgcGluZWFwcGxlIHVuZGVyIHRoZSBzZWEgaW4gdGhlIGNhcnRvb24gIlNwb25nZUJvYiBTcXVhcmVQYW50cyIu",
            "answer": "U3BvbmdlQm9iIFNxdWFyZVBhbnRzIA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlICJTdGFyIFdhcnMiIHVuaXZlcnNlLCB3aGF0IHNwZWNpZXMgaXMgR3JhbmQgQWRtaXJhbCBUaHJhd24/",
            "answer": "Q2hpc3M="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIDE5NjkgQ2FydG9vbiBzaG93ICJEYXN0YXJkbHkgYW5kIE11dHRsZXkgaW4gVGhlaXIgRmx5aW5nIE1hY2hpbmVzIiwgd2hpY2ggd2VyZSBOT1Qgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBseXJpY3MgaW4gdGhlIG9wZW5pbmcgdGhlbWU/",
            "answer": "U3RhYiBoaW0="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "TnV0Y3JhY2tlciBTdWl0ZSB3YXMgb25lIG9mIHRoZSBtdXNpY2FsIHBpZWNlcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiBEaXNuZXkncyAxOTQwJ3MgZmlsbSBGYW50YXNpYS4=",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBSdWJ5IFJvc2UncyB3ZWFwb24gZnJvbSBSV0JZPw==",
            "answer": "Q3Jlc2NlbnQgUm9zZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIHNlYSB3aXRjaCBpbiB0aGUgMTk4OSBEaXNuZXkgZmlsbSAiVGhlIExpdHRsZSBNZXJtYWlkIj8=",
            "answer": "VXJzdWxh"
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "VGhlIHN0b3AgbW90aW9uIGNvbWVkeSBzaG93ICJSb2JvdCBDaGlja2VuIiB3YXMgY3JlYXRlZCBieSB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==",
            "answer": "U2V0aCBHcmVlbg=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "Tmlja2Vsb2Rlb24gcmVqZWN0ZWQgdGhlIHBpbG90IHRvIEFkdmVudHVyZSBUaW1lLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": true,
            "question": "V2F5bG9uIFNtaXRoZXJzIGZyb20gIlRoZSBTaW1wc29ucyIgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgYmxhY2sgd2hlbiBoZSBmaXJzdCBhcHBlYXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgc2VyaWVzLg==",
            "answer": "VHJ1ZQ=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hpY2ggU2FucmlvIGNoYXJhY3RlciB3YXMgaW50cm9kdWNlZCBpbiAxOTk2Pw==",
            "answer": "UG9tcG9tcHVyaW4="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIENhcnRvb24gTmV0d29yayBzZXJpZXMgIkFkdmVudHVyZSBUaW1lIj8=",
            "answer": "UGVuZGxldG9uIFdhcmQ="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNob3cgIkZvc3RlcidzIEhvbWUgRm9yIEltYWdpbmFyeSBGcmllbmRzIiwgd2hpY2ggY2hhcmFjdGVyIGhhZCBhbiBvYnNlc3Npb24gd2l0aCBiYXNrZXRiYWxsPw==",
            "answer": "V2lsdA=="
        },
        {
            "multiple_choice": false,
            "question": "SW4gIkdyYXZpdHkgRmFsbHMiLCB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIEJpbGwgQ2lwaGVyIHJlbWFya3MgdGhhdCAidGhlIHVuaXZlcnNlIGlzIHdoYXQ/Ig==",
            "answer": "QSBob2xvZ3JhbSA="
        }
    ]
}